<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/136753/post/26057847/comment/327942243</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>A 150-pound hollow sphere of blackened titanium is all that remains of a motor casing from a Delta II rocket that fell to Earth in 2001, landing in the Saudi Arabian desert west of Riyadh. A 600-pound stainless-steel fuel tank, also from a Delta II rocket, sits nearby, dented, gashed and rusty &amp;#8212; scarred by its descent from space to a farm near Georgetown, Texas, in 1997. An artist once asked whether he could use the mangled metal in a sculpture. (It was Air Force property, so the answer was no.) Ailor said he has occasionally worried about thieves dragging the tanks  to sell as scrap. But he and the dozen or so researchers he works with at Aerospace Corp.\'s Center for Orbital and Reentry Debris Studies, or CORDS, where he is the principal scientist, usually don\'t concern themselves with space trash\'s artistic or monetary value. They\'re interested in the science of it &amp;#8212; and in safety. \"We worry about orbital debris,\" Ailor said. Aerospace Corp. is a nonprofit research and development organization that provides technical advice to the military, NASA and other government and commercial customers. The job of Ailor\'s group is to see how space debris affects satellites and what hazards it poses when it reenters the atmosphere. CORDS also publishes predictions of when larger items might crash to Earth so that some debris might be recovered and returned for analysis. It is the only group in the world that systematically brings fallen space junk back to the laboratory for testing,Louis Vuitton Portafogli, Ailor said. Over 37 years, the researchers have collected about 10 or so samples of the detritus, including the Delta rocket components, in an effort to better understand how scraps in space behave when they reenter Earth\'s atmosphere. The team analyzes the size and shape of the debris and uses sophisticated computer programs to reconstruct its fall to the ground. It examines melted holes and compositional properties of the found metal to estimate how much Heating the space junk underwent during reentry &amp;#8212; which tells scientists the maximum temperatures Reached and helps explain why these types of objects survive. The hope is to keep satellites, and people, from harm. There are more than 22,000 pieces of space debris larger than 4 inches orbiting the Earth, and millions of smaller items in orbit that are too small to be tracked with precision, according to a 2011 report commissioned by NASA. Even tiny bits of debris, such as paint chips, can damage satellites and manned spacecraft when they\'re traveling in low-Earth orbit at about 21,600 mph. An aluminum sphere half an inch in diameter has the potential to do as much damage upon collision as a 400-pound safe traveling at 60 mph. Larger items such as defunct satellites can pulverize the objects they hit in space, generating ever more pieces of dangerous floating trash. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:136753:26057847</id><idPostId>26057847</idPostId><idBlogId>136753</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:136753</id><idBlogId>136753</idBlogId><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com</link><displayName>HOCKEYCENTRIC</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-canucks-are-more-than-one-line-and-luongo/</link><displayName>The Canucks Are More Than One Line And Luongo</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:14:26.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:136753:26057847:327942243</id><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-canucks-are-more-than-one-line-and-luongo/#IDComment327942243</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:14:26.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The Canucks Are More Than One Line And Luongo by desg143m2</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://nikefrchaussures.com/</link><idEmailMd5>0d80b107fdc8f16c4f8bbfb7f6991cff</idEmailMd5><displayName>desg143m2</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://nikefrchaussures.com/"&gt;desg143m2&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-canucks-are-more-than-one-line-and-luongo/"&gt;The Canucks Are More Than One Line And Luongo&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>