<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3j4kz/update/2012-03-29T18:34:03/85940a24ae15c0a3d0d8ca58f07d0c17a65236622b819a6c2d1cbc0bceb88897</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I worked in QA for around 18 months as a bit of a "foot in the door" exercise, y'know bringing in some cash while working on a portfolio to apply for artist positions.  I started at Realtime Worlds, moved my life to the other end of the continent and to be fair it was pretty good.  Realtime knew how to treat their employees, even the QA contract employees (not to such a high degree but still pretty good).  Overtime was time and a half and as crunch time got more intense it was double pay and meals on the company. Product meetings and update meetings every few weeks saw snacks, beers and fizzy drinks around for everyone.  The devs were pretty good at sorting the bugs, but overall APB was awful and so the company died.  I was quite impressed with the treatment of the QA staff at Realtime.  But it wasn't so good at Codemasters when I started working there.  Devs didn't want to touch the bugs, they'd dismiss any critique etc.  QA were separated  into a completely different building on the opposite side of the car park. Overtime was paid in the form of time Off and so was of no benefit to anyone.  OT would often run into the silly hours of the morning and we'd be expected to drive home (40 miles away for me), and get in again the next day to do it all again. No incentives, no bonuses, no actual overtime pay. It was the perfect example of how not to treat staff.

So when the contracts were up and 90% of the team got the sack, a couple of mates I'd made there and I set up our own indie company and are making our own damned games and getting paid for it. So, for anyone who has talent and would only be using QA as a stop gap for a career - don't bother. Find some like minded people with the skills needed to make games (coder, artist, sound designer) and get making your own stuff - it sure as hell beats working for a faceless and Cold corporation and you don't even need to get dressed in the morning!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zt292</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7d9s</id></website><link>http://games.ign.com/articles/122/1221612p1.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:03:15+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:34:03+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3j4kz</id><link>http://games.ign.com/articles/122/1221612p1.html#comment-479974730</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzqq7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>