<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jnxe/post/2012-04-02T03:52:49</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>- Total control is great and I liked the idea of Elite but there needs to be something to avoid unrealistic moves with some players who aren't able to use them. I believe that players, besides having ratings and DNA, should have Abilities like 2K12's My Player mode (http://www.operationsports.com/features ... my-player/) This would highlight each players go to move and abilities more, making it more real and make people avoid trying to pull out moves with any player (something that could be done on the Elite 12 demo) in order to avoid the generic feel Elite 11 had. Besides this could be used to have different animations for each ability, an aniation when the player can't make the move, an animation when the player can do it with difficulty, an animation when the player can do it fluently (in this category there could be signature animations for the elite players that can do it well). This could also be used on Dynasty and Become Lengendary modes, spend the Off season trying to develop some go to moves with a specific player (in Become Legendary your player).

-After playing the Elite 11 demo again today I though (as many do) that rebound can't be on the right stick, it feels so unnatural and awkward. Instead, right stick up should be to contest a shot and it could make us choose between contesting with the right hand or with the left hand. It would help to make use of fundamentals (left hand to contest right handed shooter and viceversa), it would affect shots and it avoids relying so much on the block button (which should be effective with the best shot blockers, not every player unless it's an easy block).

-I believe there boxout should be manual so you cover better the rim while trying to get the rebound (there has been several times while I was playing Live 10 that an oponent came out of nowhere and got the offensive rebound while I was in a better position, those things could be avoided with a boxout button).

-I was thinking that with Elite's shooting controlls (if they keep the idea) there needs to help us (or at least me) how to shoot bank shots. I tried doing than on the Elite demo but there wasn't any good explanation about how to do it well and it feels unintuitive. Maybe if they added a light or a nonsaturated green next to the green (than represents a good shot) which means a good bank shot it would be more helpful and would encourage more players to do those shots when it's needed.
Here are some examples I did to show how was I thinking (the angles of your player should alter the bank shot sweet Spot):
http://i41.tinypic.com/sc3ty9.jpg
http://i41.tinypic.com/2v9ynv8.jpg</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6vi3dl</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/bjrz</id></website><link>http://stickskills.com/2012/04/01/nba-live-13-wishlist-what-do-you-want/</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T01:45:34+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T07:52:49+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jnxe</id><link>http://stickskills.com/2012/04/01/nba-live-13-wishlist-what-do-you-want/#comment-483336186</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zvwn6</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>