<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/c63v5a/update/2011-05-08T12:29:09/3468dafe8fcac96b65e422b0b69f26762bc742637156e46d48da2d069a498410</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Marriage is certainly NOT bad for everyone!  

And the result of the good, strong marriage is that the children produced very often do not turn out of the liberals like Ms. Diaz, with 'round heels'.  Ms. Diaz's problem may be that she just wants to maybe 'try that one over there' out...just one more casual relationship and then 'I'll settle down'.  But she exists in a profession that is based on transient relationships.  And too much money....too much everything.  And of course that alone is enough to foster the insane 'Bleeding heart out of guilt liberal lunacy' we are all now being affected by because of the nuts holding sway over us politically.

As will all liberals, if they are a failure at life or living, or in this case marriage, then they take it upon themselves to condemn it across the board.  It must be bad for everyone.  That mentality is probably what brought the Roman Empire down. 

You know Ms. Diaz, the more candy you eat, the more you want.  You know?  You are confusing being a basically insatiable pleasure seeker for choosing parting over stability, long term love, affection and a cohesive family unit.  The subtext of your liberal opinions are easy to read.  You are a hot mess.This silly Hollywood 'party girl' and aging bed hopper should study human psychology and  s e x u a l i t y   as it applies to her own genus and phylum.  Or study the mammal's around her in La La Land that she would more than likely favor granting  'legal rights' to.  Mammals (we are one) who give birth to and have children that require a long period of development are geared, indeed genetically imprinted to stay together in order to successfully rear their young.  What we see now is generations of lazy, hedonistic loser's like Ms. Diaz who espouse this horrible ideology to our youth.  

But, I don't know...is there any hope when you have to space out the word ' s e x u a l i t y ? '</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/5s3o1x</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yjmx</id></website><link>http://www.foxnews.com/opinion/2011/05/06/dr-keith-ablow-cameron-diaz-right-4-reasons-marriage-dying-institution/</link><postedTime>2011-05-06T19:35:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-05-08T16:29:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/c63v5a</id><link>http://www.foxnews.com/opinion/2011/05/06/dr-keith-ablow-cameron-diaz-right-4-reasons-marriage-dying-institution/#comment-199755217</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8nldh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-05-06</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>