<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/eansx5/update/2011-11-16T21:16:59/d20e570ac77a3fe4e922709e9da16365a84b9067703e09afe89c975bf891d2f5</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/eazbgt</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g1x8d</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>@Caesar0330

I'm not telling you anything the scientist aren't. If you where to read any of the reports about global warming/climate change/greenhouse gasses (most are on online, not Always in their entirety) they all come up inconclusive. Its all the politicians/activists/hippies that bitch about global warming demanding that we stop..... I don't know exactly. The simple fact is no one can tell you what's going on with the weather because what are we going to compare the weather to? Different weather? There's no such thing as control weather, we don't know what would be the optimal climate for the earth because there a lot about the Earth, and the surrounding cosmic bodies that effect the Earth, that we don't know. In fact there's so much that isn't known a high school graduate can poke obvious holes into this global warming swindle.

If its all the pollution that all those factories pump into the air thats making everything hotter why did the climate get Colder between the decades of 1940-1980? And; The green movement got a significant boost around the mid-nineties, not long after the collapse of the USSR, so there was a group of people that hate the giant capitalist oil companies, and today there are a group of people that hate the giant capitalist oil companies, is there something up with that? What makes more sense; that as the CO2 (that had to exist as different properties earlier) levels rise it get trapped in the atmosphere creating a hotter climate or that as the sun gets hotter (because the sun at its most basic level that is understood is a big ball of energy, the energy often expresses itself as heat and light which is good for us, but we have no control over it so it does get hotter than usual, which effects us, I wanted to make that clear) heating the Earth more than usual and in turn heating the oceans more the usual, meaning more water form the ocean gets evaporated which would mean there's more CO2 in the atmosphere? Because the oceans in the world are huge wouldn't that mean it could take hundreds of years for external temperatures effect an oceanic mass? If its all the factories pollution of CO2 thats causing global warming than how come separately the ocean, decomposing leaves and other tree products, and livestock cause more CO2 omissions than all those factories? If the Earth can't handle temperatures as hot as they are know then how come it was hotter during the middle ages?

Rebuttal?      
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/mivd8i</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7d9s</id></website><link>http://tv.ign.com/articles/121/1212671p1.html</link><postedTime>2011-11-16T23:05:35+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-11-17T02:16:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/eansx5</id><link>http://tv.ign.com/articles/121/1212671p1.html#comment-365452024</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zduyx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-11-16</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>