<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msmfrb/update/2012-03-27T08:39:48/cf66530ac4759259bce308bf48aa9357bc8a30ddecb6ae0698217b12adfffb2b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>

The ‘Mystery’ of Screenwriting – 10 Stages to Success


By JJ Abrams


 


As the first season of Alcatraz draws to a close, I felt it
was finally time for me to share my  with a new generation of
screen-writers. 


I knew from an early age that I would make it in the TV
business. From my humble beginnings I really never thought that I would be able
to master the craft and follow in the footsteps of those literary giants who
had come before me. That was until I realised that I didn’t have to. You see
what I had was an unnatural amount of energy. I watched talented peers of mine
wasting time developing their skills and deepening into the mystery of life,
while I was churning out an average of 16 new show ideas every hour. My
efficiency was legendary. It enabled me to spend the majority of my time
hanging out with likeminded TV executives who were absolutely unencumbered by a
desire to create something that would actually be loved by an audience. We
shared a passion for the science behind what keeps those ratings up. Even at
that early stage, I was dreaming of putting together a professional and
talented team which had all the veneer of quality but absolutely no direction
or purpose. 


Presently, I see so many budding screen-writers out there
who remind me of myself but are still really struggling to  industry
adulation. If, like me, your energy levels far outweigh your talent, do not be
despondent. You are capable of great things (well mediocre things that a lot of
people think are great). Don’t make things too complicated for yourself. These
tips are dedicated to kindred spirits:


 


JJ Abrams  Formula – The 10 stages to Success


 


1.       Efficiency is the key. Your aim should  be maximum
control, minimum effort. Creators who stay involved with the process after the
first two episodes are losers, wasting their life. Remember to move on.


 


2.       Don’t spend too much time on creation either. Remember, if
you follow these tips, people will keep watching your show irrespective of how
well drawn the situation is. The first step in creation is to pick a scenario
or location that people think is pretty cool. Next, scour the internet for
conspiracy and  knowledge websites. Don’t waste time understanding any of
them, just pick up enough so you could convince someone with no knowledge of
the subject that you kind of know what you are talking about. 


 


3.       Print out a list of Myers Briggs personalities. Copy and
paste them into character bios, the production team can deal with details like
names etc. If you want to add a bit of polish, just pick a couple of names of
famous philosophers or scientists. The most important stage is to get a great
casting director. Remember, all we are trying to achieve is the veneer of quality. With our meagre
abilities, we know that before long things are going to get pretty
incomprehensible. Good actors/good-looking actors can help paper over the
cracks and buy us some time.


 


4.       Now for the most important step. Those of you who have seen
my TED talk will know that I am obsessed with mysteries and believe that a
mystery brings more pleasure than knowledge. Those of you with true
understanding of the art of literary creation also understand that I have
completely confused the means with the end and am mired in some kind of
narcissistic, self-satisfied sludge. THE CENTRAL MYSTERY is crucial to the
success of your show. It must be a mystery that without understanding of, none
of the actions of your characters can make complete sense. They must all do
weird stuff which necessitates the viewer to keep watching to work out what is
going on. In my experience, the viewer will put up with almost anything in
pursuit of making sense of a character. All subsequent stages represent clever
ways of confusing, distracting and deceiving the viewer into continuing
watching despite their strong (and valid) reservations about the series. 


 


5.       Get the geeks on your side. This is the ultimate inoculation
against valid criticism and really very easy to achieve. First, lure the
geeks. Pepper the series with mystical, literary and pop culture
references. They don’t actually have to mean anything but your viewers will
certainly try to read into them. They will come up with theories that far
surpass your own creative abilities and add depth to the dross that you have
served up. You can even cherry-pick a couple of these for future plot
development or even future shows.  be thinking about the next show!
Second, appease the geeks. Do the convention circuits, do endless
interviews, release merchandising, multiple editions of DVDs, epic extra
features etc.


 


6.       By episode 7 or 8 of the first season, viewers will be
starting to suspect you don’t actually have a plan (although your loyal and
growing geek fan army will be vigorously defending you on the net). You on the
other hand want to squeeze every drop out of this dry fruit before the furore
 epic proportions. You should have already moved on to your next project
by now, leaving production in the hands of a feckless but enthusiastic writing
team. If you haven’t, jump ship NOW! This retains your mystique and your
departure can  be correlated with when the show started to ‘go downhill’.



 


7.       Instruct your writing team to use the following strategies


a.      
 answer a question with a
question even if it doesn’t make sense for the characters, the current storyline,
the flow of the series or most importantly the sanity of the viewers.


b.     
Surgically excise normal curiosity
from all characters so they don’t keep demanding answers that any believable
character would.


c.   
Create “Trojan horse reveals” that
look like genuine explanations but on reflection actually embody more mystery.
Great ways to do this include using mysterious glowing light, doors behind
doors, keyholes behind keyholes, weird looking contraptions, additions of new
characters.


d.     
Wry looks and maniacal laughter are
great substitutes for plot development


e.      Fight fire with fire. Refuse to explain a mystery and
simultaneously create five more. As you go along crush the viewer under the
sheer weight of unexplained nonsense. All but the most committed will have long
given up in trying to understand and tie everything
together.  If you have done it right
you will have manifested a kind of televisual Stockholm Syndrome where viewers
cannot reconcile the number of hours they have sunk into your show and will see
their only option as to start to ‘love their captors’. 


 


8.       Remember at all times, show utter contempt for your viewing
public. They love it.


 


9.       When the show does finally end (hopefully it will be
cancelled abruptly after many seasons so I (my writing team) don’t have to try
and wrap up a story that I never had any intention of doing in the first place.
Alternatively, ramp up the questions to be answered and sacrifice all the hard
work in characterisation that the real members of the production team have put
in to cover up your own inadequacy. Write an ending that really makes no sense
so that it can be claimed it is open to interpretation. Have fun being
extremely patronising to any viewer that actually has taste in fiction and
understands that they have been manipulated into  many hours of viewing of an empty husk of a
tv show, by asserting that they are obsessed with getting ‘answers’ and can’t
just ‘enjoy a story for its own sake’.


 


10.   The
tenth and final step is the most important. In fact it’s the most central.
Without this step none of the others make sense. At the center of all
screen-writing theory there has been a cover-up, one which only a select few of
writers is privy to. These writers have been holding this  for many years
and passing it down from generation to generation for reasons that might well
be explained below. These writers may be people that you know or maybe
completely new people, I’m not quite sure yet but it might well become clear if
you keep reading. One of them lives in California, and was, until now searching
for a key that was stolen from her by two hooded men with …lets say… dragon
tattoos on their forearms. This key opens a trapdoor within her grandfather’s
apartment, the grandfather who in a flashback we might discover initiated her
into this  screen-writing tradition. She found the key yesterday and, my
sources tell me that she went to the trapdoor opened it and some kind of
mysterious glowing light shot out of it to reveal a green trapdoor with
phoenixes on it with three keyholes and a scrap of parchment with some kind of
… wait a sec, wikipedia’s so slow today… ok… Talmudic code on it. As soon as
the first trapdoor opened there was a knock at the door and an orthodox Jew
called Herodotus, drenched in rain from a storm looking all dramatic marches
in, spies the parchment and says “The Bible code can be viewed as a part of
Talmudic scholarship, albeit one of the more controversial parts. Throughout
history, many Jewish, and later Christian, scholars have attempted to find
hidden or coded messages within the Bible's text, notably including Isaac Newton” He shoots this mysterious lady in
her mysterious chest, she’ s Bleeding right now, I’ll tell you later what
happens to her. So you see the pieces start to fall together, the  of
screen-writing have something to do with the most famous book ever, the bible.
Is there some kind of code to screen writing? Well let me explain it all to
you, I want you to understand and  access to this mystery. This trapdoor is
not isolated. There are lets say 20, no hold on we have a bit more space here
80 …er… ok 90 trapdoors all over the world and when all of them have been
opened I will definitely, I promise, reveal the Secrets to screen-writing that
I hold. I absolutely promise you that if you keep reading my blog posts,
watching my shows, that eventually, if you can stay the course, I will, as I
get more news, reveal the contents of the trapdoors and unravel the mystery of
the bible code, the mysterious Jew, the mysterious chiming sound heard around
owl sanctuaries (did I mention that one yet?) and how it all relates to the
central mystery of screen-writing of all. The mystery that even I am not privy
to. The mystery behind why I keep getting commissioned to do TV series. The
mystery that, believe me, no one really understands. 







 
 

</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lvpkl</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/vh3p</id></website><link>http://tvrecaps.ew.com/recap/alcatraz-season-1finale/</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T08:32:46+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-27T12:39:48+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msmfrb</id><link>http://tvrecaps.ew.com/recap/alcatraz-season-1finale/#comment-477370354</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zlarm</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>