<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qte9/update/2012-03-29T11:54:37/664741378c658a8e9103121694b894691b29ef3aae8464e807e249f555bc77cd</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>   Sorry, but I agree with Naknek_Bob and Chad Fenton.  This was just a little thrill-seeking moment for a person that had 'touching a moose' on her list of crazy, wild stuff to do.  A lot of people on this comment board are getting pretty worked up over something that is actually pretty tame/lame as an issue.  There's probably thousands of people that have done this EXACT same thing in Alaska over the years.  I'll bet a few people try to pet a hibernating bear every winter.  What about class IV white water rafters?  Climbing (and dying) on Denali?  Kayaking up next to killer whales?  Susan Butcher's (R.I.P.) team getting stomped out of the race on a trail that was inadvertently made for easier 'moose travel'.  The Extreme Snowboard/Skiing competitions that are held on near vertical mountain faces.    

   And, all people that are considered animal lovers out there on these  boards, wouldn't you rather have a few people that try a wacky personal thrill stunt like this, touching an animal with their fingers, than Reaching out and touching a moose with a .300 Winchester Magnum, which usually puts far more stress on the moose.  Usually.

   I can't wait to see a YouTube of someone getting chased through the woods by a grizzly up by Byers Creek or down around Crescent Lake with a Salmon or 3 lbs of bacon strapped to his/her daypack.



Also, the person in the house that filmed it all had the responsibility to keep her kid safe, inside, period.  It was Mrs. Hernandez' fault all on her own to accept the risk and repercussions for what she was doing.  It was probably a long winter for her, too.  This might have been a way to blow out a little cabin Fever! </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z2km8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dneq</id></website><link>http://community.adn.com/?q=adn/node/160533</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T03:26:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:54:37+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qte9</id><link>http://community.adn.com/?q=adn/node/160533#comment-479599298</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/d71r4</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>