<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwophv/post/2012-03-31T06:18:16</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>What I don't understand is why, when you  the right age, nobody teaches you about this stuff. In hindsight, I'd feel more comfortable knowing that breastfeeding isn't  going to be easy, that it mightn't last as long as you expect, or that you physically (&amp; through NO fault of your own), may not be able to breastfeed. We seem to discover all of this after the fact &amp; when we're hardly in a state to think logically and rationally about it. We've just had babies!! I think that if we're better educated from the beginning than perhaps a lot of emotional/ mental health issues might be avoided. We might feel more comfortable with making our feeding decisions because we're not living up to some idealised notion of how it should all happen. Many of us seem to drive ourselves crazy trying to find solutions to feeding 'problems' when it'd be so much easier to move on &amp; enjoy our babies with our families instead of pumping EBM for little or no  &amp; feeling terrible every time you Reach for the formula to make up a bottle. Before my LO was born, I didn't even consider that I'd have even the smallest issue with feeding for 6 months plus. Well it didn't happen &amp; now I see that its quite common to have some Hiccups along the way. I am grateful for this forum and the opportunity to read the stories of other courageous women. It is helping me to exorcise my own demons. So thankyou, and well done to all of us.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67u8pq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/4e5f</id></website><link>http://www.fearlessformulafeeder.com/2012/03/fff-friday-if-i-dont-try-everything-i.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T05:58:06+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T10:18:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwophv</id><link>http://www.fearlessformulafeeder.com/2012/03/fff-friday-if-i-dont-try-everything-i.html#comment-481714612</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>