<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mg6woi/update/2012-02-07T14:10:30/714b97d805f6d89941d188cc963dfed0d4b02d7d9d322269bd7b2efe454a299f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Lucy I used to buy gas and electricity for the NHS:  £500 million pounds at one one point. So I know what I'm talking about.
And you are SO wrong!  So naive!  You sound as if you've been drinking John Major invented Kool Aid.
That delusion, because that is exactly what it is, is that energy markets are competitive. They aren't. They are driven by wholesale markets and have prices accordingly.

If you think that competition drives down energy costs, you should get out more often.  You don't have to go far.  Take a drive.  Pass by each petrol station. See any bargain petrol station? See any appreciable difference in price? Unless you drive around all day looking, which rather defeats the purpose. Or buy overpriced groceries at a supermarket and other bait and switch tactics.

Similarly, UK electricity and gas prices come from wholesale movements in natural gas markets.
There are plenty of issues in the UK domestic market about transparency, but you sound as if you and Which are just re hashing the same old crap.  We hear it all the time from 1997:  If only feckless energy consumers would switch supplier they would have lower prices.

What is needed, and should be your efforts instead of setting up a supply company is to ask for the end of confusing pricing.  There should be one default tariff that is 100% transparent based on wholesale price movements and published distribution costs and a transparent margin.  That is how large industrials buy gas and power and it saves them millions.

This month it's Cold.  Guess what?  The wholesale costs have gone up.  But the only option domestic users have is to buy on forward prices:  That is your price moves only once a year or so.  
The absolutely laughable conceit that crooks like the Big Six tell Ofgem, (and even worse that they believe it !) is that they buy gas and power on wholesale markets up to a year or two in advance, and THEY CAN'T CHANGE that price.  This is laughable to anyone who knows anything about commodity markets.  Their excuse is that in order to  supplies they have to fix the price, which is a ridiculous lie.  They have contracts, sometimes lasting for many years,  with big  shore producers or LNG terminals etc, which are based on volumes.  That means the gas will  show up absent force majeure.  What is unclear is what price it is.  That price is set by the wholesale markets and changes every day. The price is FOB : Free on Board exactly the same as in oil markets. 

A transparent price is likely to be up in the Cold and down the rest of the year.  I saved the NHS millions most years. And on some years it cost them a little bit more.  But whatever it was, it was 100% transparent.  Hospitals that fell for the energy prices are  going up spiel got killed, and some of the patients too, simply because they confused risk mitigation with risk total avoidance.

Two final points: In the USA, there are even more companies offering domestic power, and it is insanely easy to switch, next day in most cases.
However, because the default option is that the local supplier has 100% transparent pricing linked to widely available published wholesale rates that change monthly based on actual meter reads unless you are incredibly risk averse, or gullible, most people stick to the existing supplier. Their only other option is to buy on a fixed price and people aren't that anal.
In New York State for example, 85% of customers stay with their existing supplier, in Illinois,over 98% in Chicago for example.

Interestingly, the second largest supplier in the United States is Direct Energy, owned by Centrica (British Gas).  They have a potential market in the US and Canada of over 250 million in the various states and provinces.  If they had the market share  that Centrica has in the UK that would be well over 120 million households. But they have only two million.  Because people quite rightly feel that they have no influence over wholesale markets and it's stupid to try and second guess them.  But, most importantly,  the default tariff is the best deal. 

But in the UK, people often are because they have been sold either Peak Oil or the fairy tale of competition.  

Any doubts as to what I say?  A very easy test.  Go to the websites of the various stitching up with sites all given at least £40 a customer commission by the Big Six, all hidden from customers of course.

And all those sites?  Active ONLY in the UK.  Minimal, if any, operations in the US or Europe or anywhere else.  

Go for a default price structure.  But good luck getting one from the Big Six, and their stitch up site enablers at Ofgem.

Happy to help further.  It's a noble cause I'd love to support but hate to see you going about it  the wrong way.  

Finally, let me point out that if 38 Degrees got the government to Act so EVERYONE was on default (with a choice not to of course),  then far more people would save much more money than a narrow range of 38 Degrees followers.  Want to prevent unnecessary deaths among the elderly?  Do it that way so everyone benefits.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yh4raa</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/egca</id></website><link>http://blog.38degrees.org.uk/2012/02/07/the-big-switch-q-a/</link><postedTime>2012-02-06T23:25:51+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-07T19:10:30+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mg6woi</id><link>http://blog.38degrees.org.uk/2012/02/07/the-big-switch-q-a/#comment-432172974</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h453a</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-06</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>