<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwjatn/update/2012-03-31T03:48:45/3162d4a287496cc54c268307941124ec71af0f4e2b94a1234d032f2c62f2fd80</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw9hrg</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h47qm</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I agree. Having only entered KPop in late 2007, I missed out on Shinhwa before they left for the army. The months leading up to this comeback were full of hype, and I was getting really excited (against my better judgement, having been Burned before) for this legendary boygroup. 

Did they meet my expectations from all the hype &lt;i&gt;everyone&lt;/i&gt; was throwing around? Not really. 

I had expected a group that would be able to dance ridiculously complex dances -- they're known as one of the best dance groups around, after all. I had expected a group that would be able to sing flawlessly live, both dancing and sitting down; their comeback stage last night left me very underwhelmed, with the weak vocals in the Venus performance. Maybe I've gotten used to the higher quality of groups I follow (DBSK, B1A4, SHINee, etc.), but Shinhwa's vocal performance left me feeling as if I were watching some rookie group who couldn't be bothered learning how to sing and dance at the same time.

Their album was good, I agree, but it really isn't as good as everyone is saying. The first few songs are the better ones, but the second half of the album runs together.

I commend Shinhwa for coming back, but they need to step up their game if they want to win some new fans who weren't around during their heyday and not just cater to their old fans.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67by6x</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/nou3</id></website><link>http://seoulbeats.com/2012/03/shinhwas-venus-when-legend-comes-to-life/</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T05:00:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T07:48:45+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwjatn</id><link>http://seoulbeats.com/2012/03/shinhwas-venus-when-legend-comes-to-life/#comment-481631816</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rgtpf</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>