<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk19m9/update/2012-03-26T11:48:46/8315ea209c4b45746da7c178865889a0007b83bf2c674f616909fccef423adee</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The race card, the racial thing – whatever it’s gonna be called, it is the number one asset this administration believes it has to win in 2012

Their own polling data has shown that to be true over and over again.  But how far are they willing to push that?  Race.  The charges of racism?  I believe all the way if they have to.  And they are gonna get people stirred up.  And if Barack Obama doesn’t win re-election, watch them stand back while the riots break out, and watch them mouth the words “Burn baby Burn.”  I don’t think they are willing to go that far, I know it.  If they can’t have America, nobody will.  That’s how big – that’s how important this election coming up is.  Even the people who pay attention to this stuff…they don’t realize how big this is.  How important to the country. We are truly at a fork in the road here

You know, Republicans used to be the party that would unite behind the nominee when they were chosen – it frustrated the hell out of us Democrats who were Always bitching over this or that right up until the election.  That’s not the case anymore, and your Republicans are much weaker because of it.  I’ll say this, if Republicans don’t get their s h it together and vote for whoever is the nominee – and I mean WHOEVER is the nominee, then it will be another four years of Barack Obama

 If we are too stupid as a country to fix this mess…then so be it.  It’s over.  The America we know, the America we knew – it’s over.  Done.  And we will only have ourselves to blame.

(excerpts)

http://theulstermanreport.com/2012/03/24/insider-warned-us-obamas-racial-division-plan-now-underway/</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rpi96</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t33k</id></website><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/thought-about-the-healthcare-law-arguments-before-us-supreme-court-that-start-today/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T11:08:01+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T15:48:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk19m9</id><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/thought-about-the-healthcare-law-arguments-before-us-supreme-court-that-start-today/#comment-476485046</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cojum</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>