<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwm97j/post/2012-03-30T09:20:49</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Thank you. Good. Carry on.
I respect the Prime Minister for the decisions that he has heeded over, ones that appear to be deeply unpopular with those shouty folk.
Things like the inappropriately tagged "Granny Tax". This removes a huge breach in fairness between the young and old, a breach that there is no logical reasoning for (*because* it exists isn't an argument). Changes to public service pensions also. These are the things which greatly harm him but are very good for the country.

I propose another decision that will create bad press.
Not only has foreign aid not improved the situation of developing countries, there is significant evidence that it actual harms a country and is holding them back. 
As a very simple example, where a country is given aid, they have no need to seek finance externally. Therefore, they do not pursue a credit rating. Where a country does not have a credit rating, nor can any business within that country so a profitable business cannot Reach it's potential. Equally, these countries do not, in general, collect taxes from their people. Therefore individuals in the country have no tangible vested interest in the actions of their government.These are small points and by no means the full picture but these countries are capable of standing on their own two feet and we need to be active and encourage them to do so. Not by carrot, but by stick. By withdrawing, over a short period of time (say, 5 years), all aid awarded to them.
Now, opponents will say that we can't do this because people will die. Interestingly, typically, developing countries who do not receive aid have better mortality and morbidity rates. So there ;),
We can't do it all ourselves but we can lead the way. We could be the generation that sets Africa free rather than keeping it trapped in the sticky web of aid.
And all of this is not to mention the money that will be left available for building our infrastructure, our economy, fixing the messes in our country. If your house is Burning and your neighbour is trying to build one across the road, you don't cross the road to help him. You put out your fire and then, if he still needs help, you go.

Go on, Mr Cameron, I dare you to be so bold.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hjpv7</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/politics/david-cameron/9171481/Brick-by-brick-were-tearing-down-the-big-state.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T19:17:41+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:20:49+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwm97j</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/politics/david-cameron/9171481/Brick-by-brick-were-tearing-down-the-big-state.html#comment-480731031</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c8yiw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>