<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw3jyt/post/2012-03-31T11:59:42</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>A modest proposal: the Congress should legislate and mandate that Americans purchase an electric car. This is not beyond the Scope of the commerce clause because people who do not purchase an electric car affect commerce by forcing the rest to purchase oil, thus increasing the price of gasoline and Heating oil and increasing pollution which will affect health care costs across state lines. Higher oil prices ruin the economy by making all products from food to medicines more expensive.

But isn't a mandate to buy a car creating commerce? No, the car market is unique in the fact that everyone will ride in a vehicle with an internal combustion engine at some point in their lives. Therefore this is not creating commerce but instead regulating the means of funding the very basic right of freedom of transportation which is at the very heart of liberty. But what if you do not need an electric car -- you are healthy enough to walk or ride a bicycle wherever you have business? That does not matter -- eventually you will get older and will have to enter the car market by either buying, calling a cab or riding a bus. It is inevitable for everybody.

Ridiculous you say? Well you have not been paying attention to the government's argument for the mandate to purchase health insurance.

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67urre</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yv37</id></website><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/2012/03/m-fiskers_bad_karma.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T06:16:23+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T15:59:42+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw3jyt</id><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/2012/03/m-fiskers_bad_karma.html#comment-481945157</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mdeau</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>