<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/206085/post/127795742/comment/328147438</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I wasn&amp;#039;t very surprised when i saw the outcome of the &amp;quot;what would you do&amp;quot; video shown in class. The white guy who tried to steal the bike first received the benefit of the doubt so much from the people who were passing by the scene. They didn&amp;#039;t really give him a hard time either. Some people claimed they contemplated calling the police, but they did not. When the black kid was stealing the bike however, almost everyone gave him a hard time about it. He was being confronted so much. Cops were called immediately that the kid said it wasn&amp;rsquo;t his bike. There was just so much hostility towards the black kid that was not there when the white actor was the one stealing the bike. Even though people won&amp;rsquo;t want to admit it, there were underlying racist intentions behind it. I feel like white America is just a whole lot less sympathetic to the youth that are not of their skin color. I don&amp;rsquo;t blame them either, because this is true for any ethnicity. It&amp;rsquo;s easier to identify and feel bad for someone that looks more like you than someone who is completely different from you. It might not necessarily be racist, but race definitely plays a part when a person starts to formulate assumptions. That&amp;rsquo;s what stereotypes are, assumptions. You assume an asian kid is smart and good at math because he is asian. You assume a black kid is bad and a criminal because he&amp;rsquo;s black. That&amp;rsquo;s how this works. It can&amp;rsquo;t be helped in America where black is seen as evil, and white is seen as good. As we saw from the video about the experiments with the black and white dolls, even children share this belief that white is right. It&amp;rsquo;s gonna be hard to get this feeling out of our self-conscious. We don&amp;rsquo;t really do it deliberately, it just happens. Evil is associated with darkness, so that makes sense. Honestly I don&amp;rsquo;t think we&amp;rsquo;ll be able to surpass this type of feeling until some point in the future where everyone will be so mixed that we&amp;rsquo;ll all be the same skin tone. That will be when racism ends. Perhaps. But even then there will  be the issue of social hierarchy. There will Always be that divide of rich and poor. There is no way of getting rid of this type of disparity. It&amp;rsquo;s part of life. People&amp;rsquo;s ambition and their Thirst for power leads them to want to accomplish more than others and step on those below them along the way. It&amp;rsquo;s human nature. They say man is inherently good, and maybe this is true. But we also have the potential for evil, and that we cannot change. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:206085:127795742</id><idPostId>127795742</idPostId><idBlogId>206085</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:206085</id><idBlogId>206085</idBlogId><link>http://www.worldinconversation.org</link><displayName>World In Conversation</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.worldinconversation.org/2012/03/29/voices-from-the-classroom-138/</link><displayName>Voices From The Classroom</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T00:17:16.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:206085:127795742:328147438</id><link>http://www.worldinconversation.org/2012/03/29/voices-from-the-classroom-138/#IDComment328147438</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T00:17:16.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Voices From The Classroom by JenuineX</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://intensedebate.com/people/JenuineX</link><idEmailMd5>da3e5f3dec33d46f2db126fdf67dd5b3</idEmailMd5><displayName>JenuineX</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://intensedebate.com/people/JenuineX"&gt;JenuineX&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.worldinconversation.org/2012/03/29/voices-from-the-classroom-138/"&gt;Voices From The Classroom&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>