<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/312236/post/127937081/comment/328558250</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Tortilla Appetizers

1 package super size flour tortillas, recipe uses 6 tortillas (package usually has 12)
2 - 8 ounce packages Philadelphia cream cheese - softened
1/3 cup Kraft mayonnaise
2 tablespoons green onions, chopped
1/4 cup black olives, chopped
3 - 2 1/2  ounce packages Buddig  pressed cooked beef (or corned beef or ham)

(Amount of green onions and black olives can be increased according to taste.)

Combine cream cheese and mayonnaise until smooth.  Fold in onions and olives.  Divide cream cheese mixture onto 6 tortillas.  Spread a thin layer of cream cheese mixture on tortilla.  Arrange 5  of beef over cream cheese mixture.  Tightly roll up tortilla.  Wrap in plastic wrap.  Place in refrigerator at least 3 hours or over night.  To serve, cut in 3/4" .  Makes 64.

***

Bacon and Green Chile Roll-ups

8  bacon
1 (9-oz.) container Fritos Bean Dip
4 oz. cream cheese, softened
3 to 4 super-large flour tortillas
1/4 cup finely chopped red bell pepper
1 (4.5-oz.) can Old El Paso Chopped Green Chiles

Cook bacon until crisp.  Drain on paper towels.  Crumble bacon; set aside.

In medium bowl, combine bean dip and cream cheese; mix well.  Spread each tortilla with bean dip mixture.  Sprinkle each with bell pepper, green chiles and bacon.  Roll up each tortilla.  Wrap each in plastic wrap.  Refrigerate over night.

To serve, cut rolls into 3/4 inch pieces.

***

Bacon Wrapped Smokies

2 packages Hillshire Farm smoked sausages
bacon
light brown sugar
toothpicks

Wrap a 1/2 strip of bacon around each smokie sausage.  Secure bacon by putting a toothpick through the bacon and sausage.  Place on a foil lined cookie sheet.  Sprinkle light brown sugar over sausages.  Cover with foil and refrigerate overnight.  Bake in a 350° oven for 35 minutes or until Heated through.

AND FOR SOMETHING SWEET
Cream Cheese Dip

1/2 cup sugar
1/2 teaspoon vanilla
8 oz cream cheese
1 stick of butter
1/2 bag Nestle semi-chocolate "mini" chips
1 box of graham cracker sticks

Soften in the microwave and combine the butter and cream cheese. Add in the vanilla. Slowly stir in the sugar, making sure it is  mixed together. Finally, add in the chocolate chips. 

This recipe does not make very much, so if your planning for a larger crowd you may want to double the recipe. Enjoy!!!!!!!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:312236:127937081</id><idPostId>127937081</idPostId><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:312236</id><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><link>http://www.denpdf.com</link><displayName>denpdf.com</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.denpdf.com/easy-appetizers-easy-appetizers/</link><displayName>easy appetizers- Easy appetizers?</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T18:31:30.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:312236:127937081:328558250</id><link>http://www.denpdf.com/easy-appetizers-easy-appetizers/#IDComment328558250</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T18:31:30.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on easy appetizers- Easy appetizers? by j-s-lovestocook</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>da3e9105d3f0a4cad272bd8c52bea9f8</idEmailMd5><displayName>j-s-lovestocook</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>j-s-lovestocook commented on &lt;a href="http://www.denpdf.com/easy-appetizers-easy-appetizers/"&gt;easy appetizers- Easy appetizers?&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>