<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkzf4e/update/2012-03-25T16:42:34/9768d8ba6688752dea5166715effadb76cab98c0feb2b52e421b6afb98934238</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>It's! that! and a Hell! of a lot more Mr Plouffe. Our Nation(s), Families, are under ASSAULT/ATTACK from within and without. War has been declared on this President ( A symbol of the Times) from within and without for the last four years (These PEOPLE have decided they are better-, SET! in their ways/mindset and Better-than everybody ,else, is their argument) War by,of, for, THEMSELVES on AMERICANS! unemployed, welfare recipients, unborn,Minorities, Muslims, Hispanics, Latino's, labor, The Vote, Children, Immigrants,Women, American-FAMILIES,Middle-class, 99%, OWS and the USA Government.The Lines have been crossed. If The President doesn't "MAKE A STAND" who will? That's what a true Leader does (Homeland security begins at Home, literally! and so does Nation-building). The greatest threat to Americans currently are it's Extremist partisan/influences refusing to do anything about any REAL issues, especially, LEADING, and UNEMPLOYMENT ( Wrecking The Nation,Economy, Recovery,Presidency,Minorities,Civil-rights and Middle-class,Families is their hunger,Thirst and FORTE!)  These are the two GREATEST threats facing Americans, at this moment, not, the PRESIDENT or becoming president. My question is, How much is one American ($$$$Life) worth to us Americans, Republican, Independent, or Democrat? What value do You place on your own Life? What is that CURRENCY? because NOTHING else matters ultimately in this civilization,Humanity. We only go round Once.

For what it's WORTH...The wealthy,GOP, Tea-party doesn't hold a monopoly on all Our  "VOICES"  majority-faculties,YET! ("NO" limited-government). They can throw their weight/wealth/dollars around THINKING they're Obstructing,holding-down,holding- back! America. Like -HELL!!- they- are! Dirty is dirty even-so money... Let Me DECLARE! Make clear to All. Democracy isn't CHEAP! (there is "NO" magic wand of Politics, Private-sector or economics much-less Social NONSENSE) or for PROFIT! neither is Liberty, Social-Equality,Civil-Rights,Freedom, BLOOD, JUSTICE, Sweat,Tears,struggles and Sacrifices of Americans. They cannot be bought,sold or counterfeited for a CHEAP surrogate/counterfeit."NO" matter what garb they masquerade themselves in, INCLUDING not Limited -to ,COUNTER-terrorism,/Terrorism, Fearmongering, Counter-Citizenship, Fearmongering, Anti-Counter Immigrant, fearmongering, Anti-Counter-Barrack Obama nonsense, Fear mongering, Anti- Counter- women fearmongering, Anti-counter Muslims, Fearmongering Counter! Counter! Counter! Humanity! Life! Reality! Where the HELL!! does it all COUNTER-ENDS/Begins? The Government will either do it's Job and "DEFEND ALL AMERICANS" in GOOD and BAD Times or allow same,old,scenarios to be continually-perpetually played out politically, economically, and socially...The WRECKERS/CORRUPTERS/COUNTERFEITS/CRIMINALS/FAKES will Always BLAME the Government NOT! THEMSELVES! for the ills,and deficiencies, while Americans LANQUISHES. Some say, "know your POWER" I say," know who you ARE, know Your WORTH." Know where the HELL! You STAND.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rhk3r</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ewhe</id></website><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/trayvon-martin/david-plouffe-obama-reacted-as-parent-to-trayvon-martin-shooting.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-25T16:40:53+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-25T20:42:34+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkzf4e</id><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/trayvon-martin/david-plouffe-obama-reacted-as-parent-to-trayvon-martin-shooting.php#comment-476017566</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/apzzq</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>