<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3p11y/update/2012-03-29T20:37:58/d9700b0f4e4b91ce7f70244f33acf231d869a6865f1d9df1acdd12629c71a02e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3pcy5</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hslh2</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> I keep thinking about the repeated headlines I've seen since 2008 indicating that gun sales have gone through the roof since Obama's election (supposedly due to fears of gun Bans), even to the point where gun sellers have had to put customers on waiting lists. Someone stated this week on the news that there are now more guns in this country than there are people.

There is another lesson in all this that should be ingrained in our youth (and any other people prone to quick tempers and violence): You can't just physically assault someone these days and be guaranteed to walk away from it. I've met many women in recent years who are packing legal Heat too, so I think the idea of an "easy target" is much less probable today.

I've never been involved in a physical confrontation with a stranger in all my years, because I don't meet aggression with more aggression, but with reason and compassion (our generation was taught to "bless them that curse you, and pray for them who despitefully use you" Luke 6:28). I doubt anyone believes Martin would have been slain had he simply told Zimmerman he was visiting a relative, and for how long. 

I, for one, am mindful of that fact that there are many, many folks walking around with legal weapons these days, and I'm not about to give them a reason to use them. Let's teach this to our children.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z40t9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ju4p</id></website><link>http://www.breitbart.com/Big-Journalism/2012/03/29/The-Trayvon-Timeline-How-a-Local-Crime-Story-Became-a-National-Racial-Outrage</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:31:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:37:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3p11y</id><link>http://www.breitbart.com/Big-Journalism/2012/03/29/The-Trayvon-Timeline-How-a-Local-Crime-Story-Became-a-National-Racial-Outrage#comment-480075561</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h40lt</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>