<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nunl/post/2012-03-29T13:02:52</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The height and weight of both Zimmerman and Martin is totally irrelevant. Why are people debating this? "Chasing" versus "Following"? Pure semantics and an excuse for this criminal.
What now do you have to say to the Police video of Zimmerman that does not show ANY signs of injury to Zimmerman?  No broken nose. No wound in the back of the head from being slammed on the pavement. Zimmerman is a liar and should be in jail right next to individuals at the judicial level who decided that this young man's life was not worth following the investigative protocol that would be afforded to all others. The State of Florida, Texas and many others have been increasingly bold in their determination to exercise their bigoted, racist views through manipulation of the law and common human decency. 

The nation for the most part has mirrored this rise in their despicable mindset. From the very moment Barack Obama took office, the gutter snipes have lifted their ugly heads and turned up the Heat of racism in this nation to new heights. Barack Obama is our President. Barack Obama is Black. Barack Obama will be our president again. (There is no way he will lose to any of the morons the GOP has trotted out to represent the Republicans) Get over it.

In the mean time those of you who are not WASP, I urge you to exercise your constitutional right right to bare arms and defend yourself from the Zimmerman's and Deryl Dedmon's of the world. Challenge authority at every turn when they refuse to Act in a manner that is fair and just for ALL PEOPLE.They work for you. If you are a taxpayer then you pay their salaries. Demand from them what is right and refuse to be bullied or ignored. 

As for me I refuse to be a victim at the hands of any criminal be they White, Black, Hispanic, Asian, civilian or crooked law enforcement official. I am locked, cocked and ready to rock.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6loe2e</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/27/justice/florida-teen-shooting-witnesses/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T18:02:34+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:02:52+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nunl</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/27/justice/florida-teen-shooting-witnesses/index.html#comment-479654220</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/82ffo</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>