<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwilp5/post/2012-03-31T08:22:40</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This forum is just for views not for discussions on the topic.  Looks like some of the people even call them sikhs to show personal vendetta.  Hindus have seen power after a thousands of years of slavery and the power has gone to their head.  What they did to Sikhs in 1984, Burning them alive, butchering them was just a show  "'Who is in power".  They could not do it to muslims because hindus make lots and lots of money in muslim countries.  They could not do it to Christians, they will lose their bread in the west. So they showed their power on sikhs.  Bhindrawale issue could be Resolved in million less destructive ways. But no Hindus had to show their power.  Shame on them.  British rules has been replaced by Maharashtra and Gujrat.  All the money is reinvested there.  Punjabis are not good politicians.  They are being befooled by south indians.  they were divided by Nehru among Arya Samajis and Sikhs who are so close to each other.  India is a shame on democracy.  Foreign countries and philanthropists from the G7 countries have to be careful when helping india.  They are shown India the ways Hindus want to show them at different times.  I am a proud Canadian and will die for Canada.  By the way how many Hindus died in Afghanistan and Iraq.  They are too busy filling medical schools in usa and Canada by fair or foul means.  Shame on them.  Recruit some hindus in the army, and see them run back to india.
"</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67efwp</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/4r1e</id></website><link>http://fullcomment.nationalpost.com/2012/03/30/counterpoint-balwant-singh-rajoana-case-is-about-the-rule-of-law-in-india/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:18:55+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T12:22:40+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwilp5</id><link>http://fullcomment.nationalpost.com/2012/03/30/counterpoint-balwant-singh-rajoana-case-is-about-the-rule-of-law-in-india/#comment-481786456</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7m06</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>