<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwlkdg/update/2012-03-30T13:17:40/5a5039fa40ea32bfe3433ec1a3b960dba2d9c40ef65d6c91d01b97d183a67d9a</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>From Steve Novella at SBM, in February this year:-

why the journo who posted the article could not find this I can only speculate.


"Overall we have a very inconsistent  pattern. The vaccine does not appear to be a consistent or unique risk  factor for narcolepsy in these populations. The task force concludes  from this that there must be another factor or factors that is combining with the  vaccine to increase the risk. This is logically possible, but until this  factor X is identified it remains speculation.
Narcolepsy is a neurological disorder characterized by excessive daytime sleepiness (narcoleptics sleep all night and all day), cataplexy (a tendency to lose muscle tone and collapse in response to stress), hypnagogia (hallucinations associated with a fusion of the dream state and the waking state, so-called waking dreams), and sleep Paralysis (being paralyzed upon awaking from sleep). There is a strong genetic predisposition for narcolepsy. In fact it is only seen with a certain genetic type known as the (HLA) DQB1*0602 genotype.
All of the individuals who developed narcolepsy following the Pandemrix vaccine have the narcolepsy HLA type. Therefore there is the possibility that the vaccine only increases risk within  this genetic populations, perhaps combined with other gene variants. Perhaps something else is also  triggering the increase in Iceland, but not Finland and Sweden, to  explain the rise in narcolepsy there in the unvaccinated.
Another possibility is that there is one or more confounding factors  leading to the increase in narcolepsy, and the vaccines are a  correlating but not causative factor.
Such is the nature of epidemiology, or observational studies.  Variables are not controlled for and confounding factors are Always a  possibility. That does not mean that observational data is not useful or  cannot be definitive – but it requires careful, thoughtful, and  thorough collection and analysis of data from multiple different angles.  The data we have so far from Finland is very preliminary, and generates  more questions than answers. There is certainly sufficient cause for  caution and further analysis. But at this point I would not be surprised  by any particular outcome, since the data can be interpreted in many  ways.
Conclusion
While there is an intriguing correlation between the Pandemrix vaccine and narcolepsy, this correlation is inconsistent – it is isolated to a few countries and to one age group and there is a rise in narcolepsy in Iceland not correlated to the vaccine. Further the cases identified so far are restricted to those with a known genetic predisposition to narcolepsy. This could mean that this population is susceptible to some factor in the vaccine, but it could also mean that they are susceptible to some other trigger, or perhaps were destined to get narcolepsy and the apparent increase in entirely an artifact of observation and reporting."

enough said</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z5rz3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/mxvz</id></website><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/health-news/swine-flu-jab-linked-to-narcolepsy-7599682.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T07:02:07+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:17:40+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwlkdg</id><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/health-news/swine-flu-jab-linked-to-narcolepsy-7599682.html#comment-480970517</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/aklpx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>