<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31v9f/delete/2012-03-29T16:05:14</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>You must be a psychic as knw you know what  everyone is thinking. First he was walking behind the buildings not on the street or sidewalk. Yes, Zimmerman did get out of his vehicle to see where Martin was going. He lost him in the dark &amp; since the dispatcher told him he didn't have to follow him, he was walking back to his vehicle. Martin was walking toward him at that time not running away, as you say. Some words were exchanged &amp; Martin punched Zimmerman in the nose, breaking it (according to EMS who attended him after). The ounch knocked Zimmerman, as he probably didn't see it coming. Martin then jumped on him, punching &amp; banging Zimmerman's head on a sidewalk.  From there, lets review the fact that where Martin was originally walking was behind the buildings - no sidewalks. That means he had to change direction &amp; walk toward Zimmerman, who was walking to his vehicle on the sidewalk. After confronted by Martin, the punch, knockdown &amp; banging of Zimmerman's head began. Zimmerman tried to push Martin  &amp; in the process his gun slid out of his pocket or holster (report didn't say which) &amp; they grappled for it, while Zimmerman was yelling help from a person he saw witnessing the beating. The witness yelled stop, I'm calling 911 &amp; ran upstairs to cal. His next observation was Martin lying on the grass &amp; Zimmerman getting up,  just before police arrived. Zimmerman was being questioned while his head wounds were attended to by EMS personnel at the scene. Zimmerman declined going to the hospital, against EMS advice. Zimmerman was cuffed &amp; taken to the Police Station, questioned &amp; released. He went to the hospital the following morning to have the head wound stitched (advice of EMS), but it was already healing, so could not be stitched. These are facts that can be verified. 1 - Martin followed Zimmerman back to or toward his vehicle,  not continued to run or walk away, not  continuing to go where he was going. 2 - Zimmerman had stopped following Martin as advised.
3 -  Martin now became the aggressor &amp; escalated it by punching Zimmerman. 4 - Zimmerman at no time brandished the gun while following Martin or going back to his vehicle. It was concealed as the law requires.  Draw your conclusions from here. If it had been reversed &amp; Martin had been the Neighborhood Watchman &amp; Zimmerman was the attacked who was killed by Martin, would you still be outraged? Would Race Baiters, Sharpton &amp; JJ or the New Black Panther Party reps be protesting? I doubt it. Sharpton &amp; JJ do it for only one thing &amp; that is press coverage. Their relevancy expired a long time ago. I grieve for the parents, but if Zimmerman had not Acted, it may have been his parents that were grieving. I also didn't see Sharpton or JJ protesting the 16 yr old black youth Tyson, who shot &amp; killed two British guys in Cold blood. He was just given a life sentence &amp; his sister arrested for threatening a witness during the trial. I don't see anyone protesting or advocating for those victims.</body><verb>delete</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r8gyn</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f7e3</id></website><link>http://mobile.wnd.com/2012/03/witness-trayvon-martin-attacked-zimmerman/</link><postedTime>2012-03-25T00:17:57+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:05:14+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31v9f</id><link>http://mobile.wnd.com/2012/03/witness-trayvon-martin-attacked-zimmerman/#comment-479832001</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/55v8x</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>killed</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>