<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mim5h0/update/2012-03-22T17:40:52/5607286c870478891a06f87759a9c21aa616a3292b084dd276ab6c364f2839cf</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Greetings, fellow Cardassians.  And, hello to anyone else reading my words, whether you be human, Klingon, Romulan, Ferenghi, or even Bajoran.  I am Gul Dukat.  Now, the more astute of you may be saying, “But wait a minute… Didn’t the Federation say that Gul Dukat died in the Fire Caves of Bajor after a fight with Captain Benjamin Sisko?”  Well, yes and no.  I did sort of die, but the Pah-Wraiths took kindness on me and gave me new life in their spiritual world.  And, I am eternally grateful for their generosity… even if the place is a bit boring.  Nevertheless, I have managed to make contact with the outside world.  And, when I did, I just happened to learn about these chronicles of the history of Terok Nor after the Bajor Occupation and the Federation took over operations of the station.  Naturally, I felt compelled to tell my side of the story.  Now, not everything that went on after the Occupation involved me, so I will only be popping in whenever my presence was felt.
 
Of course, this would be one of those times.  Now, I was enjoying a nice snack in my office going over some reports when I received word that a Cardassian had been arrested on Terok Nor.  Obviously, he would have been tried and received an unfair trial from the Bajorans.  So, I wanted to be sure that he was okay by contacting the station, while secretly I was beginning to make plans with my good friend Damar about a  rescue of this Aamin Marritza.  Then, I heard that the prisoner on Terok Nor was not Marritza but rather Gul Darhe’el; and I was confused.  As you no doubt know, Darhe’el 8 years prior.  I was even at the funeral.  Funny side note:  I was quite proud of the little  job I did at the funeral, looking all somber and even shedding a tear.  However, I was not sad to see Darhe’el dead.  He was one of the main people who had me demoted from Legate to Gul after the Occupation.  Naturally, I pointed out the hypocrisy in this since he himself had lost Gallitep to the Bajorans.  But, I guess losing a mine is nothing compared to losing a whole planet.  Anyway, after I heard this, I knew immediately that the poor Cardassian who had been arrested was an innocent man and called Odo to tell him of this egregious mistake.  Then, I learned of this whole deal with Marritza and how he had had surgery to alter his face to look like Darhe’el so that he could ease his cowardice conscious and bring us “evil” Cardassians to justice because he couldn’t stand a little screaming.  Naturally, I was making plans with Damar to change our rescue mission into one of assassination.  However, some drunken Bajoran did the deed for us.  I was a little grateful for that, but also a little pissed that I was able to do the deed myself.  Nothing would have pleased me more than to have been able to strangle that pathetic little coward until his eyes went Cold.  Well, except licking Bajoran spring wine Off of the naked body of Tora Naprem.  But, that’s another story for another day.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ynh1j</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/duet,70951/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T15:00:28+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T21:40:52+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mim5h0</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/duet,70951/#comment-473983991</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h9iku</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>