<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjp0l/post/2012-03-26T14:52:19</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk9py6</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zrljz</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>It must have been accompanied by that horrid word fear...i had 4 kids, 2 i was sick almost the whole time, well up to 6 months, and for all 4 there was a migraine every  month for 6 months, like clockwork, then the rib pain, but after the first day the rib pain you get used to , then the last 2 preg siatic nerve in my back went out whole leg woudl jut  like it was not there, then there is the Heartburn..but u get used to it, and drink water lots of water. and God would  give me the evenings Off from Morning sickness with the 2 i had if with...aabsolutely no preg is perfect, or easy, nothing worth having is easy. I feel so bad that we dont have laws about informed concent, and the options, escpecially if sickness was one, as there is gravol. and there is a medication my daughter in law had to take and her kid came out perfect, My friend pucked till there was blood, she ahd to take that med for all 3 pregs. so there is a solutions, sadly, the oneness seems to be on us to find it, physiican heal thyslef, if abortion is a medical issue as stated by prochoice, why is it not councelled properly? Like any medical procedure etc. this is the options.: a b c etc. Shame the government does not do something about the laws, just cuz somethign is legal dont mean we should do it. But when you mentioned morning sickeness you noticed in the article the ecact thing i noticed. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6la883</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/1to1</id></website><link>http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/my-wife-she-had-an-abortion-here-last-friday</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:10:20+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:52:19+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjp0l</id><link>http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/my-wife-she-had-an-abortion-here-last-friday#comment-476629896</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lqnkg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>