<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34wc5/update/2012-03-29T11:24:36/45e0ca7198bb8b80c49e1a09b4ae52a0dee9a434c9187a7857902104dbf270ab</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>"If convicted, the three face between 15 years and life in jail"

No, no no... If the suspects are convicted they should be Burned alive tied to stakes with a dozen or more nude FEMEN women teasing them as they Burn slowly. Sure, the nude FEMEN women would have sent the message to others like the convicted animals "control yourself or Burn alive.” Of course I say nude FEMEN women because it appears the feminist group are not intimidated over going nude to highlight this very heinous crime. I don’t blame them one bit. Therefore I say let the women continue to bare their body for sake of drawing long lasting attention to this matter with the bottom line; “control yourselves guys or Burn alive like these losers.” 
 
Please do not accuse me of going medieval here because if I really wanted to go medieval I’d recommend that the men be tied completely nude to stakes with ropes smeared with poison ivy, then parade nude girls before them. Wait for their manhood to rise and then start   with dull blades… an inch every hour until there’s nothing left. Then cut  their fingers and toes (again with dull blades) and then wait another week before finishing them Off with concentrated acid bath. Also their “powerful” parents should be made to scrub public toilets everyday for one year… for aiding and abetting. This tells you how horrified I am of this crime. 
 
As for the fact the suspects were initially released on account of having powerful parents. Sounds like this happened in Nigeria!
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zrk3h</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6flb</id></website><link>http://www.vanguardngr.com/2012/03/girl-dies-after-horror-gang-rape/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:13:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:24:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34wc5</id><link>http://www.vanguardngr.com/2012/03/girl-dies-after-horror-gang-rape/#comment-479574544</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cdp3a</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>