<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nw3w/update/2012-03-29T13:21:15/a58fafc93f73a6899ca8c89de3887293a50007917574d4d2bcf25c8c268bdd42</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I live in chronic pain and really, could make a case for both sides of this issue. 

On one hand, I know MJ has medicinal benefits. No disputing that. 

There's the issue of taking narcotics to manage chronic pain. There can be issues with acetaminophen toxicity which is used in a lot of these narcotics. 

Don't like taking acetaminophen? There's oxycontin. No thank you! Bottom line is that MJ doesn't have the toxicity issues and oxycontin is a nightmarish experience for many. Its over prescribed and although you start to take the drug, it soon starts to take YOU. Bad news. You also must live with a cloud hanging over your head about withdrawal should you be unable to get your narcotics. You miss your dose and within 10 hours, you are starting to come undone. 

So, while you do become essentially addicted (you really do despite what others may say) to using MJ for your chronic pain, if you run out, you don't have the withdrawal issue but, your pain is not managed now. 

I've often thought about using MJ for may pain and another issue that it can treat very well. I hate taking pharmaceutical meds. So why don't I?

I used to use MJ for years. Daily. I mean, half a joint with my AM coffee. A joint around lunch. One in the afternoon. One before supper. 2 or more after supper.  I wasn't alone and surely others here can relate to this. Hey, it feels good to be high doesn't it?

Now, do I get "high" from the meds I take now? Not really. I feel them an hour or so after taking them. I mean, I know I am under the influence of them. I only take them when I feel the pain creeping up and have to nail it then rather than play catch up. 

So, I feel that although MJ would help me and it would be "organic" as opposed to what I am taking now, it would also result in me being stoned all the time. 

I have kids. I would rather keep it quiet if I did this and although I could have cookies, butter or other means with which to take MJ that otherwise would turn my office into virtual smoked filled orange VW bus in 1971, I'd still be "stoned" and I would look it too. 

I have nothing against people with a legit need for MJ. While I have some concerns about 22 yo old's getting it for "Anxiety" and "Back pain". I just can't help but feel a majority of people seeking MJ for "treatment" really just wan't to be "legal" about doing it and getting access to top grade buds at the local Bud Stop. 

I'm sure there are others in my situation. I know it'd help but, don't know if I really want to go there. 

Chronic pain is something some people just don't understand. It's really hard to get a doctor that understands this and while wanting to attend to your needs, doesn't just hand you a script for oxycontin either. You, the patient. have to do your homework before opening a potential Pandora's Box. It happens. Happened to me too until I took charge and did my own homework. 

Sorry to be so verbose here. I would just advise to be careful and honestly weigh the pros and cons to using MJ. Trust me, it really can be an addictive herb. Yes, if given a choice, I'd rather we Ban alcohol and legalize MJ. Alcohol has NO redeeming qualities and the financial and personal costs from it's abuse, and just recreational usage, is beyond mere numbers. 

</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6za74x</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rvdh</id></website><link>http://www.pressherald.com/news/marijuana-dispensary-has-quiet-opening_2012-03-29.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T04:01:16+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:21:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nw3w</id><link>http://www.pressherald.com/news/marijuana-dispensary-has-quiet-opening_2012-03-29.html#comment-479668966</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dh2df</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>