<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/191971/post/127904745/comment/328593721</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>&amp;quot;At this point the viewership numbers are surprising as they have been on a decline since Bound For Glory. I find it ironic that we have seen this decline in viewership around the same time that Vince Russo turned the Head of Creative Position over to Bruce Pritchard. Things have gotten dramatically worse since Russo left and TNA has been experiencing some of their lowest viewed episodes in a very long time.&amp;quot; 
 
YEP. 
 
&amp;quot;Bruce Pritchard has done exactly what the IWC Establishment wanted. He slowed down the product, focused on younger guys, had the championships as the central element and more. The problem is the IWC doesn&amp;#039;t give a crap about what works. They only care about their personal opinions and what they like. They don&amp;#039;t like Hogan despite still being over huge. They want to spend all this time on old school wrestling promos and matches instead of the over-the-top characters.&amp;quot; 
 
YEP. 
 
On a side note, BABYFACE Hogan doesn&amp;#039;t draw ratings as well as HEEL Hogan. 
 
&amp;quot;I became a wrestling fan during the Attitude . The Attitude  wasn&amp;#039;t popular because of old school wrestling angles or great matches. It was popular because of the moments. Moments such as Bedpan McMahon, Stone Cold&amp;#039;s Beer Bath, the Montreal Screwjob, the nWo taking over Nitro and things like that. Those moments are missing from the current IMPACT Wrestling product.&amp;quot; 
 
I agree those over the top moments are missing on Impact Wrestling and is partially why ratings are down. The other reasons I&amp;#039;ve covered in other posts so I won&amp;#039;t go there again here. 
 
Just on a side note I remember Wrestlemania 1 and watched wrestling until 1989 shortly after I got my drivers license and had other things to do as a teen, but then in mid 1996 I was flipping the channels and saw Hulk Hogan wearing black and white as a bad guy in a group called the NWO and started watching wrestling again on a regular basis to this day. 
 
&amp;quot;IMPACT Wrestling is a really good pro wrestling show. It has focus and talented wrestlers. There are some really good matches and really good promos. However, a huge portion of the audience doesn&amp;#039;t care about the pro wrestling aspect of it. They want characters, storylines and OMG moments that can only happen in pro wrestling and aren&amp;#039;t happening now.&amp;quot; 
 
YEP. I want the characters, storylines and OMG moments. 
 
&amp;quot;There will be many critics blaming people like Hogan or Russo (even though he is elsewhere) but you need to look at the fact that the current product is a toned down version of its former self.&amp;quot; 
 
YEP, Russo brought some of that OMG moments that I miss. 
 
&amp;quot;Another sad story for yours truly is the rumor that  Steiner is no longer part of the IMPACT Wrestling roster. I am a huge fan of Steiner&amp;#039;s and highly enjoy his promos and character.&amp;quot; 
 
I agree, Steiner was entertaining and he had some of those OMG moments. 
 
&amp;quot;The departure makes me hone in on the names that have been absent lately: The Pope, Shannon Moore, Winter, Mark Haskins, Douglas Williams and many others. How many of them will be shown the door? It will be interesting to see.&amp;quot; 
 
If they show them the door I hope it&amp;#039;s the right ones. On that list, Pope is the only one I hope sticks around, but there are others that should be shown the door, I won&amp;#039;t name them here because most of my posts have covered that subject. 
 
&amp;quot;People say that ROH and TNA are so close&amp;quot; 
 
They are NOT. But tell that to Suzanne_A. 
 
&amp;quot;Sunday is Wrestlemania and despite being more of a TNA fan, I am excited for the show. The quality of the WWE has gone downhill over the years but one year that Always gets my blood pumping is Wrestlemania. Even if you don&amp;#039;t get the best wrestling, it is the showcase of what pro wrestling is. The production is top notch and the atmosphere is out of this world.&amp;quot; 
 
YEP same here and I agree. I&amp;#039;m a big Triple H and Rock fan and will enjoy their matches. I&amp;#039;m surprised no word on Stone Cold Steve Austin (which I&amp;#039;m a big fan of) at Wrestlemania. 
 
&amp;quot;Very few PPVs in history have that same buzz that Wrestlemania has. I can only name two shows that I have felt similar about: Starrcade 1997 with Sting vs Hulk Hogan and Bound For Glory 2006. BFG 2006 was the moment I knew that I was a TNA fan for life. The awe of sitting in my living room while Sting made his return and captured the World Title is something I will never forget.&amp;quot; 
 
I agree those were 2 good moments. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:191971:127904745</id><idPostId>127904745</idPostId><idBlogId>191971</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:191971</id><idBlogId>191971</idBlogId><link>http://www.tnasylum.com</link><displayName>http://www.tnasylum.com/</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.tnasylum.com/2012/03/talons-take.html</link><displayName>Talon\'s Take</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T15:47:30.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:191971:127904745:328593721</id><link>http://www.tnasylum.com/2012/03/talons-take.html#IDComment328593721</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T15:47:30.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Talon\'s Take by Mr. Eric Eric</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://intensedebate.com/people/MrEricEric</link><idEmailMd5>0881b76566ac0619f98114ef1b0a6929</idEmailMd5><displayName>Mr. Eric Eric</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://intensedebate.com/people/MrEricEric"&gt;Mr. Eric Eric&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.tnasylum.com/2012/03/talons-take.html"&gt;Talon\'s Take&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>