<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkpb61/update/2012-03-26T16:25:21/719cf5a759a785cd9e93acf43b87b38ddbbcf59887918d213d33f621c47d9696</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I've already gushed about the Hunger Games on recent threads,so I'll just chip in to second/third/fourth the Peeta-love and complain that they mishandled that bread-scene.Not only does the movie fail to acknowledge the extend of Katniss' desperation as well as the life-saving hope Peeta's gesture inspires in her,it also doesn't do justice to Peeta's character:In the book,he is a pre-teen child (not an adolescent like in the movie-would it have killed them to get child actors for that scene?) who,touched by the suffering of another person DELIBERATELY puts himself at risk by purposefully Burning those breads,knowing he would have to suffer physical and emotional abuse for this.In the movie,he might just as well have Burnt the breads out of clumsiness.Did not want!
Regarding Haymitch:Yes,he came across too likeable to me,but that may be down him being played by Woody Harrelson-that guy made even a scumbag like Larry Flynt downright likeable by playing him in a movie.
Also:OMG teh clothes and hair and shoez etc. in the Capitol!
Plus,again,the sneaky allusions to 20th century totalitarianism/barbarism via the Capitol's achitecture-come visit me in Germany,I'll show you 70-80 year-old buildings done in that style- and the little introductory propaganda flick played at the reaping,which cleverly rips Off Leni Riefenstahl,while the clothes and hairstyles worn by the youths alluded to the 1930s/40s.
I also loved the nature-shots in the forests,I had to look up the filming locations,turns out it was filmed in North Carolina.I initially wasn't sure whether it was filmed in the US at all,because I recognized some of the flora,especially the flowers for Rue's body,to be European in origin.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lc6kr</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ync</id></website><link>http://shakespearessister.blogspot.com/2012/03/hunger-games-thread.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:53:01+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T20:25:21+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkpb61</id><link>http://shakespearessister.blogspot.com/2012/03/hunger-games-thread.html#comment-476713248</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mfej</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>