<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi642s/post/2012-03-22T22:06:16</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I was a witness to this accident.  I was right behind the two vehicles heading towards downtown, on Scenic.  The facts to this report are not completely accurate.  The firemen did not pull the victim from the Nissan before it caught on fire...it was in fact two fast  gentle men, not firemen, from the neighboring apartments that ran full speed to an ALREADY Burning car, pull the guy out of the car and dragged him about 15 feet away from the car.  The victim was a rather large fellow, and it took both the guys to drag, his unconscious, Bleeding and lifeless body to safety, all before the fire department even showed up.  Not only that, but the same apartment complex had other members that showed up with a long hose and was spraying water from the side walk best they could, that is why in the pictures you see water on the ground.  It was the brave  of the bystanders who grabbed this guy out of a Burning car and put out the fire all before the fire department showed up.  Im not saying the fire department didn't do a great job, they responded so fast, less than 5 minutes. I just want to give credit where credit is due.  The two guys,  fast and bravely, running towards a Burning car with in seconds of the accident, not knowing if the car was going to explode or not (when the car was spinning in the middle of Scenic right after it was hit it did appear to have an explosion of sorts a fireball like flew from the hood).  

I barely escaped this accident myself by seconds...I drive this street every morning to work.  I did not react like the two men did...I sat in my car shocked and stunned.  I was shaking from adrenalin and couldn't move...I was really amazed that these guys did what they did.  I have a cell picture of the two guys with victim across the street, but it blurry and far away.  I am hoping everyone is okay...the accident was brutal and bay far the worst I have ever witnessed first hand.  I don't know why or how it happened...I do know that i was not paying as good as attention as I should have because I could not recall what happened until the earth shattering sound of metal on metal.  I feel lucky that I got away unharmed and pray that the people all recover and people pay more attention to the road.  Being late to work or dropping Off your kids to school is not worth what I saw today.        </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ybwlp</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnmf</id></website><link>http://www.modbee.com/2012/03/22/2124609/driver-seriously-hurt-in-scenic.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T17:00:00+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T02:06:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi642s</id><link>http://www.modbee.com/2012/03/22/2124609/driver-seriously-hurt-in-scenic.html#comment-474141632</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zdj01</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>