<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwvld6/update/2012-03-30T15:56:42/48e6757f9920c5584200af422cc4fa5d75e975ca647c4478321614676617053f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw5r10</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5uiik</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Thanks for all your comments.  Near us is a small cottage and outside it is a tiny wind turbine - diameter &lt;2m and about 20ft high.  I often walk past it and it's going like the clappers most of the time (windy place).  It can hardly be heard and doesn't intrude at all.

I asked the owner, out of curiosity, what it achieved.  The answer was 70% of the house's energy - the other 20% came from a wood-Burning stove, with 10% from solar panels.  The electricity was stored in lead-acid Batteries and the house was very efficient in its consumption.

Oh, and the house was disconnected from the grid.

That is  GOOD wind-turbine.  Houses which are lucky to have the space and the wind should perhaps put one up.

Plastering massive towers all over our wildest Spots (which also tend to be our windiest) is not good.  Planning to run a grid on a resource that needs back-up a lot of the time is not good.  Wasting a fortune on boutique and unreliable method of large-scale power generation when there are so many better options available is not good.

Hydro-electric power is generally good, when it is done without too much greed and sensitively.  We have a lot of rain (in some parts of the country) and the power has 24/7 reliability if the size of scheme is sensible.

Size and location is everything.  meanwhile, let's have some nuclear power stations so we can start exporting electricity to France when theirs run down.

'EDB power - has a nice ring to it, rather nicer than EDF.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6znp2a</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/earth/energy/windpower/9173642/Wind-farms-We-are-baffled-that-a-prince-of-the-realm-would-ruin-our-land.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:49:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:56:42+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwvld6</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/earth/energy/windpower/9173642/Wind-farms-We-are-baffled-that-a-prince-of-the-realm-would-ruin-our-land.html#comment-481132522</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/guz2t</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>