<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3u6jr/post/2012-03-29T15:12:38</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Slight correction. Don't _explicitly_ offer athletic scholarships.

I'm willing to bet that, at Union, athletes are "more than proportionally" represented both by number and by dollars in the scholarships that are awarded that include "leadership", "character", or any of a host of other unmeasurable traits (or possibly measurable). The reason I'm willing to bet this is that I've seen it at other D-III schools. 

I'm also not saying that it's wrong. One reason for this is that, especially at a school where they have to pay to play, they probably have more than their fair share of those attributes ("I can't define it, but I know it when I see it"). After all, a gifted athlete that is "given" an education based on his physical skills, not his social or intellectual or leadership skills, will naturally gravitate to the free education. So the athletes that are "just the same as everyone else" are siphoned Off to other schools, and only those who are actually concerned about developing their leadership potential, or those on the "borderline" athletically, who will have to develop their social and leadership skills, are left for the D-III schools. But there are, in fact, plenty of late bloomers who are just Itching for a chance to show up those who passed them over.

Additionally, those scholarships are awarded by committee. It is tremendously helpful to have a champion on the committee. An athlete has a champion on the committee (if not a coach, a faculty member who has an interest in the success of the team). It's not often that a dancer or a musician has such a champion.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hyxel</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dtzm</id></website><link>http://www.uscho.com/2012/03/28/frozen-four-no-small-achievement-for-non-scholarship-union/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T10:03:16+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:12:38+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3u6jr</id><link>http://www.uscho.com/2012/03/28/frozen-four-no-small-achievement-for-non-scholarship-union/#comment-479777591</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c3w2o</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>