<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp30v3/update/2012-03-22T09:04:20/43009298facb26b802dd426eb3899c8ae8be293ce2e9a4d208fb67c8bbb6ad22</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Up until recently the only Wonder Woman stories I had ever read were some of her appearances in Justice League and Batman comics. I've Always been interested in her as a character, but with only so much cash available each month, I usually stuck to the Bat family books since I've loved that group since i was a child.
So the rebooted Wonder Woman series seemed like the perfect time to jump on board with this character and I've really enjoyed it. There were a couple of "hmm?" moments, but for the most part it was an interesting story with beautiful artwork. I really loved that Diana's world was so different than what I've been used to with the Gotham books (gods and such). 
Now, I read this latest issue and find out that WW comes from a world that is more vicious and Cold-blooded than I ever imagined. Part of me was disappointed in this development, but then Diana appears to be just as shocked as us readers. I was interested to see how this was going to develop over the next couple of issues.
Then I started finding out more about her pre-reboot story. The only new child from an island of immortal warriors? A clay baby instead of an immortal-god offspring? I can't believe that the creative team had the option of tweaking those cool ideas, but went in the direction that they have gone.
I'm no expert on WW so I don't feel the same betrayal and outrage that a lot of you other fans are experiencing.  Though it is pretty crappy that they've made the Amazons into pseudo-black widows. I'm wondering if I should give this series one or two more issues to see how it plays out, or if I should just cancel it and start buying up her earlier books? </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y53yu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/m7rp</id></website><link>http://dcwomenkickingass.tumblr.com/post/19704793909</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T00:06:55+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T13:04:20+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp30v3</id><link>http://dcwomenkickingass.tumblr.com/post/19704793909#comment-473557713</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rnje9</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>