<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk4ex1/update/2012-03-25T22:41:43/7b5c2833d258e348390540caf3d3166cd97a4f8b4c35bf2ce5fdf449e15e1bf2</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Team Holler had a good episode.  I was a little pumped when they found that clue in the yellow-red metal box outdoors by just driving by all the people looking through the roadside plane junk--it's  a little fun when people scramble and thoroughly search for something that isn't hidden all that well, and Team Holler is the perfect team to see just bypassing all of that.

I was worried about Bopper's lungs in the water there, but he did fine--and it was great to see Mark dishing to the teacher-agent about Bopper's crush on her partner.  Was &lt;i&gt;he&lt;/i&gt; flirting?  Or was it just smalltalk?  Or "alliance-building", just in case...  My bet is it was just smalltalk, and a delight in betraying his shy buddy's romance to a woman who could pass the info on.

The Vomiting?  Well, he seems pretty good at using a barf bag and getting it all in there on time, I totally blew it once when I was a kid.  And without question, way ahead of anybody arriving at the finish mat, and pretty much neck and neck with the Taurus SHO winners, was the pure Joy on camera that we saw from Bopper the last time Mark was throwing up in the taxi.  He was dying laughing, squinting, snapping his finger in a laugh spasm, just great television...</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rb5rd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/this-is-wicked-strange-baku-azerbaijan,71222/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T02:10:37+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T02:41:43+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk4ex1</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/this-is-wicked-strange-baku-azerbaijan,71222/#comment-476179692</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dq0jt</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>