<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tc60/post/2012-03-29T09:28:48</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>You claim, in a nutshell, that mass-immigration is the result of conservatives losing an immigration argument, against 'post-war radical universalists', and that, because the latter made discussion of immigration a taboo, conservatives resorted to criticising Islam as a means of showing dissent against mass immigration; but Islam, despite being used by disenfranchised men to justify criminality, is not a problem really. The real issue, you claim, is the general social changes consistent with the movement of peoples around the world.

Conservatives never lost 'the argument'. They were drowned out by hysterical 'anti-Nazi' rhetoric and their careers were ruined when they did manage to be heard. Enoch Powell was right in both his (decent and legitimate) assessment and moral convictions pertaining to mass third-world immigration. Conservatives already won 'the argument' back in the sixties but they were destroyed by thugs wielding the sword of Hitler. Thus far there has been no defence against it because the thugs in question took control of Leviathan and the State became an enemy of the nation who created it.

Using criticism of Islam, as a means of showing dissent against mass third-world immigration, does not invalidate criticism of Islam. Islam &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; its representation in the real world. If that means it has some individuals who want to kill the 'infidels' then that's part of what it is too. Your implication that they are just bad eggs you would find anywhere, and who would find a substitute justification to perform Acts of mass murder, is ridiculous. Whilst Mohammed was indeed a paedophile, by our standards, I won't assert that he has anything to do with the gangs of anti-white paedophiles roaming our streets and preying on the school-girls of every major city though. I'm sure that the Islam connection is merely coincidental!

You are partly correct about working class resistance to social changes. No decent white person wants to live near thousands of threatening base black 'youths' or feel an alien in his own homeland as his town is covered in mosques. You conflated social-change with mass-immigration though. Not the same. What about all the English who left for Australia or Canada? Big social problems, were there? Didn't think so. The issue is social-change as a result of race and culture. Some mix and others don't. Hear many white people expressing dislike of the Chinese? Plenty of them here and they are as ethnocentric as any. Why not? Blacks have been Americans from the start. Enough said.

&lt;i&gt;"normal human feelings were redefined as forms of mental illness"&lt;/i&gt;

Absolutely Spot on. And herein lies the problem with utopian social-engineering - of molding the man to the plan. It will never win but it will cause massive misery in trying to. A couple of years ago I thought that we were seeing the beginning of the end. We were promised a "bonfire of the quangos" and a "great repeal bill". We were lied to. Betrayed by the same ilk who destroyed Enoch Powell.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hzyt0</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ms5i</id></website><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/edwest/100147680/how-islam-became-a-scapegoat-for-the-problems-of-immigration/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T14:00:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:28:48+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tc60</id><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/edwest/100147680/how-islam-became-a-scapegoat-for-the-problems-of-immigration/#comment-479487995</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z6h99</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>