<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mtl4l9/update/2012-02-29T10:36:30/b04859d2ad2b6c5a9db74d8e90bc5470b599118408c24ca736377300f3aea660</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mt69mx</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6gy99</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>He's a hyena. 

At some point - at Harvard in that combined law-MBA program, maybe earlier, probably later on after being at - Romney figured out one of the ways to exploit the condition of American corporations under the Reagan administration's defenestration of regulatory oversight, by adapting a few basic business concepts - using private capital instead of junk bonds, to avoid shareholders' derivative rights legal actions &amp; criminal investigations; how offering long puts to mature business owners would likely work on their increasing Anxiety about stagnant dividend returns by realizing capital  on selling their businesses ; &amp; how to systematize the bait-&amp;-switch sales technique to take advantage of the pressure on mid-level dealmakers in Wall Street investment banks to make deals. 

That was his niche, &amp; it comprised his total contribution to business. His supposed involvement with start-ups like Staples was limited to  as a go-between for the Mormon church investment arm's investment in the Bain &amp; Company new ventures group, &amp; being able to share in the profits of Bain &amp; Company as a general partner while his main work was in running the Bain Capital project. 

So, what does that approach to business tell us about his approach to elected office? It tells us he's coldly cynical, that he sees the role of business as entailing evading responsibility to public authority oversight, and that his business style is to play fast &amp; loose with the truth. He's living out those characteristics in this campaign for the nomination, essentially gambling with other people's money in making a 'long put' against the impression of American swing voters will have as to the state of the economy as of election day in November 2012. 

In order to play the long put on an American presidential election, you have to place the buy as a Republican, because the Republican voter base is notoriously reliable at about ~42.5% of likely voters, whereas the Democratic voter base is relatively unreliable, fluctuating from ~38 to ~47.5%, &amp; because Republican state governments Act to suppress voter turnout aiming at the Democratic voter base. What Republican politics aims at - the program the RNC Inc. sells to Big Business - is achieving a lower end Democratic voter base turnout (based on a combination of vote suppression &amp; lack of enthusiasm for voting at all in the moderate part of the Democratic base), plus being more successful in attracting a majority of independent voters (who tend to be white, generally better-educated &amp; middle-to-upper middle class income earners). If it works to produce a close election (note even necessarily a win, as Bush the younger showed in 2000), then state government based re-districting tends to operate as a sort of multiplier effect, yielding a higher ratio of the electoral college votes than a simple translation from the national popular vote split would predict.  

Due to this larger reality, national polling becomes largely a side show to attract &amp; fascinate the rubes, like any grifter knows. That 42.5% rock-bottom GOP voter base means that it's really not necessary to animate support for the RNC nominee; it's only necessary to find some way to animate the GOP voter base - meaning it can be achieved through manipulating animosity towards the Democratic party nominee. That's why the employment of the assertion by Republicans,  including their leaders, of "defeating President Obama" can afford to be so openly naked: it's not going to bother the GOP base, indeed the opposite, &amp; it's unlikely to have much if any effect on independents, who generally don't pay attention to political decisions until the last few weeks before election day &amp; are inclined to dismiss pretty much anything partisan politicians say before then as politics-as-usual that both sides engage in.  

This systematic approach to winning elections is why we end up with so many basic incompetents at public management as presidents, Reagan &amp; Bush the younger being outstanding examples of this type. What tends to work against this approach is the charismatic brilliance of the sort of innately gifted populist combined politico-manager that only the Democratic party has proven able to identify in the media-oriented context of the modern American electoral system over the last 80 years: FDR, JFK, Clinton &amp; now Obama. 

Note who's not on this list: Truman, LBJ &amp; Carter from the Dems, &amp; Reagan from the Republicans. The first 3 lacked that charismatic brilliance, despite having managerial skills. The last wasn't in the least brilliant, leave aside in any way a competent manager, but he did create an aura of charisma about himself through spending the better part of 4 decades honing The Speech &amp; melding it into a brand &amp; a persona so powerful it ended up even fooling him. But you can add the beneficiary of that illusion of charismatic brilliance to the list of those with actual charismatic brilliance, and what you end up with is what the RNC systematic approach has the most difficulty with - &amp; has yet to prove able to beat.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yph165</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tz1k</id></website><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/tom-brokaw-explains-mitt-romneys-personality-with-comparison-to-rapper-fiddy-cents/</link><postedTime>2012-02-29T13:25:16+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-29T15:36:30+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mtl4l9</id><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/tom-brokaw-explains-mitt-romneys-personality-with-comparison-to-rapper-fiddy-cents/#comment-452400362</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7zl7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>