<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6n4g/update/2012-03-30T11:33:55/dd15e4e548354abee6ea1be18878aa894edf6548e568bf830df50f0305262ac0</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw5km9</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6ibvk</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Agree in part. The US trained the Taliban in the proxy war against the Soviet Union. But unlike you, I see no contradiction between then and now. The world was a different place (Cold War), and the Taliban and the rest of the population were equally willing to benefit from their "alliance" with the US. 
Needs must. 
The fact that situation has since changed radically does not make the US's  - totally superfluous - military campaign against the Taliban hypocritical, but just reflects the transformation in the geo-strategic situation (realpolitik). 
At the time, their foreign policy was geared towards preventing the Communist influence from Gaining a foothold in that region, and women rights were low down on the agenda.
Whether you like it not, the USA, as was the former UdSSR, is an empire, whose geo-political (self-)interests extend across the globe. That what empires do!
On balance I still regard the States as a force for the good (I realise we may have to agree to disagree on that point) - even if it is a little too willing to sup with some fairly repugnant ogres to pursue its own self-serving agenda. 
But which state doesn't operate solely in its own interests?
P.S.: Can you really envisage a path to peace in Afghanistan which does not involve the Taliban?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h38cr</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/mxvm</id></website><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/moral-crimes-being-used-to-persecute-afghan-women-7594920.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T23:17:53+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:33:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6n4g</id><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/moral-crimes-being-used-to-persecute-afghan-women-7594920.html#comment-480863309</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8dzlm</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>