<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkuj0v/post/2012-03-26T10:44:48</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Why can’t a woman be more like a man…well it’s very simple because men and women are different. The late thinker Christopher Hitchens once commented on how women are generally not that funny particularly when compared to men. Interestingly, John Belushi once uttered something similar too. The almost instantaneous rebuttal from the PC “shame”-mill featured a number of remarks to the contrary by the current crop of contemporary female comedians. Central to their case was that woman comedians have become just as “offensive” and “smutty” as their male counterparts. Hitchens’s didn’t disagree in the least; in fact, he used that very fact to support his case. He said this demonstrated mimicry and not original thought. Anyone can be vulgar; it’s still debatable that vulgar comedy has much value since it’s rather easy to do. Real comedic talents such as Bill Cosby have been outspoken against this vulgar trend for years. Hitchens went on to say that for femininity and women to be funny it should require originality akin to the great comedians present and past. Moreover, he never said that femininity being funny is impossible rather it’s like this…think of a baby girl playing, there are many funny moments but the full expression evokes a number of other emotions. And, yes, it’s a hard wired response…so what? What should be of interest isn’t our “evolutionary” programming but the both predictable and venomous response of our culture to a very honest observation, but, alas this is the “new normal”. In my opinion this entire dialogue should be rejected as a complete waste of human effort and time…this goes for every other aspect of the human experience where sex differences matter. Can women be funny isn’t really the question, I wonder more about why they are choosing to be just like the very people they say they are not like and even claim to be better than, men. Let’s look at the end-state here - women can be just as foul-mouthed as a man? Pardon me, but what has exactly been  here…female liberation? These dots connect throughout society, pres barry, is an admitted feminist and we should only expect more of this regressive nonsense. Like comedy, men and women differ on many other things. The “lens” we look through to see these “differences” matters most and it is this aspect that is, sadly, most ignored. You can train anyone to be a Cold blooded killer. Sighting-in and pulling a trigger requires relatively little skill by way of modern technology. But how can we call ourselves “progressive” if we insist on some false notion of equality by making women killers like men? Never mind the obvious inefficiencies of females in the military, what has been accomplished if we’ve expanded the pool of trained killers in society? The idea that “equality” equals good is drilled-into the collective daily, but, what about the adverse aspects of equality particularly the dogmatic and absolute kind that ignores common sense and truth. That today we can all call it “progress” when females show us how “free” they’ve become by joking about disabled children and describing Flatulence and fecal matter? Look, men and women are different, when we have the courage to admit that as a society we’ll all be a whole lot better Off. Since I am a man, I will say this, being a man is very hard, unrewarding and not the romantic over-embellished fairly tale that is sold to boys…which feminist have targeted to mimic. We grind away like all other people. Certain things are best left for men and there really isn’t anything sinister about that. Coming home from combat with experiences that will forever haunt you, provided you’re lucky enough to not be dead, attached to a bed or melted is not FUN! It’s not liberating, it’s “duty”. Frankly, I see progress as trying to end war rather than bringing new people into it. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6reekh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yv37</id></website><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/2012/03/m-why_cant_a_women_be_more_like_a_man.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-25T06:20:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T14:44:48+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkuj0v</id><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/2012/03/m-why_cant_a_women_be_more_like_a_man.html#comment-476440684</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mdamu</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>