<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwz98p/update/2012-03-30T14:41:43/c06694d7684c5dbe0ebcec20041f7fff73cc0f95881cc2a8be997464352457a9</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrtee</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ak4n0</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Have to pretty much agree with this. The U.S. - Israel - Corporate Bankster union is a blight on the world populace. And the people of America have handed their citizenship of  what used to be a Republic away to that union, refusing to see it for what it is because they've been so brainwashed and made to hop from foot to foot believing in one "savior" after another that the natural result is apathy. Which of course  that the same people will  be at the top creating more chaos, and the only change will be to increase said chaos.

America, and by extension NATO, IMF, World Bank aka, the Western imperialistic Fascist regime, is basically only dealt with like a forest fire. Impossible to contain, one can only starve it of fuel, and then wait patiently until it suffocates, or let it Burn itself out. And it will. They Always do. The U.S. is very close to the end of its reign, and like every empire before it, that end will come as an implosion.

The rest of the world needs to basically see Americans and the new Western ideals for what they now are, and summarily reject them. Embrace their own cultures, and seek ways to embrace the cultures of other countries that are like minded. Find a way as many Middle Eastern countries and China have been trying to do, to reject and eliminate all need for American currency, and stop chasing what they see on American TV. By developing production, true and fair trade with other like minded nations, and increasing the prosperity of their own internal consumer bases, the rest of the world can make American consumerism irrelevant and unnecessary. And since all America can do for anyone is consume, it will collapse under its own unsupportable weight.

It is only after this happens that the world will truly be free.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/675ja9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6dsr</id></website><link>http://therealnews.com/t2/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=31&amp;Itemid=74&amp;jumival=8133</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:49:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:41:43+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwz98p</id><link>http://therealnews.com/t2/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=31&amp;Itemid=74&amp;jumival=8133#comment-481057157</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rhc7x</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>