<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk97sa/post/2012-03-26T13:32:09</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I used to be dependent on benzos. I didn't abuse them. I took a low, twice daily dose, as prescribed, for 11 years. I had the same crippling panic and Anxiety you describe, all day, every day. I thought I was dying, convinced my heart was going to explode at any moment. I hated having to take the pills every day. I hated feeling numb, but I needed them to function. I tried every antidepressant, benzodiazepine, and combination of the two that you can think of. I went to at least 10 different therapists, dozens of self-help and group programs, cognitive behavioral therapy, music therapy, meditation, yoga, hypnosis, all in an attempt to 'fix' whatever was wrong with me. One night I went to a concert with a friend. I was late getting  of work, and in the rush to get out the door I forgot to take my pill. I usually had an emergency dose in my wallet, but for whatever reason that night it wasn't there. About 10 minutes into the concert, I had a nuclear grade meltdown. The cops thought I was having a bad acid trip and I was nearly arrested. I ended up in the psych ward for three days. I did a lot of (drug assisted) soul searching in those three days, and it became clear that I couldn't live life on these drugs and I couldn't live life without them. I couldn't handle the fear, but being completely numb for the rest of my life was just as bad. That was a turning point for me. When I got out, I called a friend who had beat a serious painkiller addiction about three years prior and begged her to tell me how she did it. She offered to take me to an NA meeting. I figured what the hell, I've tried every psychopharmacological and theraputic remedy out there and I still feel like hell. What's it gonna hurt? It was there that I realized that I am an addict, and that my need for benzos was a SYMPTOM of my addiction. After about three months in NA, I began to wean myself, very, very slowly,  of my 'medicine'. It took me 7 months. My first year without benzos was hell. I had almost daily panic attacks. The physical symptoms of withdrawl lasted almost 5 months. I ended up in the emergency room 4 times, but stopped going when I realized that hitting the hospital for a panic attack and then refusing benzodiazepines looks, and is, crazy. I kept going to meetings and working my steps as though my life Depended on it (it did). In my second year, my panic attacks lessened in frequency and intensity. Around 1 year and 9 months clean, I realized I hadn't had an episode in almost a week. This realization caused me to have an extreme panic attack, which is really funny now but not so much then. However, I kept coming back, and over time my Anxiety lessened and lessened, and by my own reckoning, the last time I had a genuine panic attack was a month after my third 'birthday'. It's been a long, hard road, but I am now almost 5 1/2 years clean. Yes, I still have the occasional bout with generalized Anxiety. But I have tools to deal with this and it no longer controls me. I have incredible friends who supoort me, and who I am able to support. I realize this is a little long winded, but I understand the hell of long term panic and Anxiety, and the pharmacological hell that can accompany it. I went through over a decade of pain, and I didn't think it was possible for me to ever have a normal life. I thought I was permanently broken. My life is amazing today. Absolutely beautiful.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/y3dfc2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/74jr</id></website><link>http://www.thefix.com/node/2261</link><postedTime>2012-03-06T00:03:58+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:32:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk97sa</id><link>http://www.thefix.com/node/2261#comment-476564977</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-06</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>