<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7bui/update/2012-03-30T15:23:41/d7a8a79915aaabaf60945d2d63726cc4465fbd0b435f38cc428a668f45545a91</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m33ane</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c7opi</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Then consider this like I did: Steven Sandstrom is the only thing between you and Carl Wimmer being our next congressbarassment from the new 4th District.

Only, Sandstrom isn't an unemployed crook (Rick Koerber, Carl, really??) and bully. He's created and run a successful business and when he speaks, I hear an honest person saying what he honestly believes in. I really don't think he's just saying things for political hay. When it came time to take the Heat for his legislation, Sandstrom showed up at a podium at the Capital and faced his critics and generally ridiculous rabble trying to Shout him down with Sunday school slogans.

And unlike any Utah legislators who introduce controversial and prickly lawmaking, Sandstrom showed up and defended it, not behind closed doors or through the media, but alone and in person. You show me ONE other Utah legislator who will stand alone at a podium and defend his thinking against a crowd of rude, uninformed activists and children.

I don't agree with 90% of what Sandstrom states he believes in, but I will say that he has shown something that none of our elected officials have shown me: Guts, commitment and character. You may hate his politics, but Sandstrom displays some of the qualities I hear people yearning for in any party, any candidate.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zod03</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6rx1</id></website><link>http://m.sltrib.com/sltrib/mobile/53821090-78/sandstrom-district-seat-legislative.html.csp</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:32:20+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:23:41+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7bui</id><link>http://m.sltrib.com/sltrib/mobile/53821090-78/sandstrom-district-seat-legislative.html.csp#comment-481099386</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gw94t</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>