<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3jco0/post/2012-03-29T18:10:20</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Emma you are clearly enraged by this incident and are therefore completely biased in this incident. I have listened to the 911 call, heard the 911 calls from other citizens, and viewed the video of Zimmerman going into the police station. I shall tell you this I have had my nose fractured playing flag football and it Bled profusely, but I inched my nose, tilted it forward and in less than 10 minutes it stopped Bleeding. I then cleaned Off my face and because I was wearing dark clothing, no one could even tell I was Bleeding. Listening to the tape Zimmerman tells the 911 operator that Martin got away, and you can tell that Zimmerman wasn't running at that time, for if he was you would have heard the "wind" noise that you could hear when the operator said "we don't need you to do that". Since Zimmerman couldn't find him, the only way that Martin and Zimmerman could have come back into contact was if Martin instigated that contact. Eliminate the race issue and try to listen to the evidence without reading anything personal into it. The police video quality is terrible and therefore nothing can be taken from it. Don't allow some people to use you to further their own agenda.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zcxr4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T06:16:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:10:20+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3jco0</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html#comment-479955203</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gq3mr</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>