<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tsdo/post/2012-03-29T10:23:16</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3v6oi</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lg4e1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Well, everyone here seems to want to relive the Cold War.  You view a small percentage of the population of that time and try to condemn a whole generation and .  By the way, do you think current veterans are not suffering from PTSD?   willing to be tough guys, stand up to this one, stand up to that one, yet no one pays a price.  You want to stand up to Russia, fine.  You want to relive the Cold War, fine.  But do the necessary things thatgo along with it.  Initiate a draft. I know some here will say that today's weapons systems are so sophisticated we can't use draftees, blah,blah ,blah. There's still logistics.  Don't hire truck drivers from KBR for $100,000/year, use draftees.  They can cook, load docks, some may even see combat.  That would be good, focus the nation's attention.  Bring back that tax rates that existed to finance this new Cold War.

You see the world through your spectacles, I see it through mine.  You view that  as a disaster, and then Mike the expatriate (take you more seriously if you actually lived here) rhapsodizes about the eighties .  I am sure he picked the 80's because that was the  of Reagan.  You're right, there were no drug problems and no drug casulaties in the 80's, may be besides ectasy and crack.  And we surely didn't have to worry about PTSD because everytime there was an opportunity for confrontation, Ronnie was either a bully (Grenada and that quick little airstrike over Libya) or he ran (Lebanon).

Every Era has its up and downs, but at least through the sixties there was the offer of hope. Today, and probably starting in the 80's, just greed and self interest.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z244q</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/egg0</id></website><link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2012/03/29/romneys_russia_comments_reflect_long-held_distrust_113652-comments.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T03:04:41+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:23:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tsdo</id><link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2012/03/29/romneys_russia_comments_reflect_long-held_distrust_113652-comments.html#comment-479525500</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lg4e1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>