<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miyfho/update/2012-03-22T20:55:22/a3e465f20bd1206b99a290edca8f092ba4f7471836b9348529e62402afd91abe</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mimyji</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5w47h</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>When a person explodes from anger or frustration it's not likely their going to use nice words or keep their composure while expressing themselves. Certainly under normal circumstances she'd probably befriend the woman who at the time was frustrated.

Here's the problem, your response to her obvious breakdown has a hint of hatred in it. It actually show's what whites and those who adore whites have been doing to blacks for many years. Using our weaknesses or most vunerable moments against us. Now you're on this board encouraging other blacks to be selfrighteous and merciless towards their own. Is that of GOD? 

Proverbs 26:22-28 (NIV 84)

22 The words of a gossip are like choice morsels;they go down to a man's inmost parts.


23 Like a coating of glaze over earthenwareare fervent lips with an evil heart. 

24 A malicious man disguises himself with his lips,but in his heart he harbors deceit.

25 Though his speech is charming, do not believe him,for seven abominations fill his heart. 


26 His malice may be concealed by deception,but his wickedness will be exposed in the assembly. 
27 If a man digs a pit, he will fall into it;if a man rolls a stone, it will roll back on him.

28 A lying tongue hates those it hurts,and a flattering mouth works ruin. 




Proverbs 26:22-28 (Amplified)


 22.The words of a whisperer  or  slanderer                are like dainty morsels
 or  words of sport [to some, but to                others are like deadly wounds];
 and they go down into the innermost parts of the                body 
[or of the victim’s nature].

23  Burning lips [uttering insincere words of love] and a wicked                
heart are like an earthen vessel covered with the scum thrown Off 
from molten silver                [making it appear to be solid silver].

24  He who hates pretends with his lips, but stores up deceit                within
himself.25  When he speaks kindly, do not trust him, for seven
 abominations are in his heart.

26  Though his hatred covers itself with guile, his wickedness                shall
 be shown openly before the assembly.27  Whoever digs a pit
 [for another man’s feet] shall fall into                it himself, and he who rolls
 a stone [up a height to do mischief], it will return                upon him. 

28  A lying tongue hates those it wounds  and  crushes, and a flattering
 mouth works ruin.


</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y1ckz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t26w</id></website><link>http://newsone.com/nation/boycewatkins/students-violent-reaction-to-trayvon-martin-tells-us-something/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T17:57:30+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T00:55:22+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miyfho</id><link>http://newsone.com/nation/boycewatkins/students-violent-reaction-to-trayvon-martin-tells-us-something/#comment-474104512</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/50644</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>