<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3wnke/post/2012-03-30T02:03:39</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m334om</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lcflh</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Solid writing And1, but I'm unable to infer a sound central premise. Do fans romanticize and embellish performances by athletes playing through injury? Probably. Would fans have reacted differently had Melo played poorly? Of course. Neither of those arguments, however, support your conclusion (Melo shouldn't have played.) 

For one, if Carmelo was was at serious risk of re-injuring his groin to the extent he'd possibly miss significant time, it's up to the coaching and training staff to make sure he doesn't play. Secondly, if the risks of significant re-injury were minimal, and it was more a matter of being able to fight through the pain, then 1)why shouldn't Melo have played? and 2) why is it wrong for fans to glorify his performance after he plays great? For 2) In other words, why is it wrong for fans to make a distinction between a great performance while healthy and a great performance while injured, and why shouldn't the latter be  viewed as significantly more impressive? You seem to understand that distinction yourself with the Reed reference. which you glorify yourself ( to the extent that you won't allow Melo or anyone else to compare to him/it)

 As for 1) given how many injuries the Knicks had outside of Melo, even a 60-70% Melo was needed to improve the chances of beating Orlando in a critical game at home. Therefore, given the circumstances (other injuries +playoff odds), it was prudent to play Anthony. Right now, the Knicks have no other choice if they want to make the playoffs. There aren't enough games the Knicks can lose and still Ensure a playoff Spot to make up for resting a player for said games. Secondly, I don't understand why you have an issue with New York fans' "tough-guy" identity. Clearly there's a well-established history of Knicks having tough teams, and that toughness personifying characteristics that for some reason resonate with the fans (I'm assuming you can establish why this would make sense). 

To me, this was merely a contrarian attempt to subtly (it's in the subtext) defend MDA and deflect Melo's new-found approval. It's really interesting to me the people who can't seem to get over the resignation, and would rather bicker their very limited perceptions of the past instead of jumping back on the bandwagon </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z99np</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lilw</id></website><link>http://www.theknicksblog.com/2012/03/29/whole-lotta-catch-and-makes-from-post-doubles/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:00:09+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T06:03:39+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3wnke</id><link>http://www.theknicksblog.com/2012/03/29/whole-lotta-catch-and-makes-from-post-doubles/#comment-480303906</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hzra3</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>