<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mktxpb/update/2012-03-25T21:37:45/282b2e7acca0d80f6d91470fb958992cd4894438a79a2a6cdc7448f728e22262</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Purchased brand new 1999 1/2 VW TDI first new.  the car carrier loved the fuel efficient diesel powerful beautiful. Paid $3500 Canadian for ultimate warranty gold warranty...After 3 months rough idle 5 times to the dealer no luck... Dealer was  great! First EGR system I found on internet told mechanic... Removed egr pipe plugged. $400 bill on car with 5000 klms 3000 miles I said no pay no way... It has to be done every 5000 no thanks it was diesel in Canada the problem. Then in winter no Heat around town. They could not adjust module to work properly. If ten minutes on highway no problem lots of Heat. Then at 100 klms 65 mph the thin splash fiberglass pan cracked spun around front tire locked. Wheel put me in ditch no damage but scared the hell out of me and fmy family. Still loved the car and dealer was great... They even installed electric Heated seats for the no cab Heat problems....they felt sorry so it was  Free! Then car broke down was towed evwery 5000 klm 3000 miles. Twice plugged up. They willl do all diesels free but only for original owner. Car swas too low scraped all the time on driveway to parking lots stores gas stations . Head light got chewed up. By road when fell out of basket. The dealer said on the assemblty line the headlight was cracket duct taped to be.removed At quality control point but was missed one winter later 18000 miles the tape fell apart headlight assembly fell inside engine and dragged.below on highway ..... Made in USA assembled in Mexico sold to me in Canada Price $25986 plus $3500 gold warranry plus 15% tax $33908.00. I had enough.I lived in the dealership... 16 months 124 visits.... I had enough...  Private sale for $22,000 16 months old. Bought 10 year old Toyota Tacoma for $10,000 never back to dealer no problems klove the little truck never so happy! 

 My mom had VW golf some minor problems but had electric power  windows would never work properly to prevent kids or adults from chrushing fingers  the safety would keep stopping the window and would keep coming down when it hit the window track. She had to  put up twice and hold power switch to force closed past safety. She sold her VW andd will never buy again VW.

My dad who had Jetta TDI his whole life and still does.... Says VW  have "a couple of problems" whenever they change the .motor or car style over... He is LOYAL VW LIFETIME OWNER... Be said for three years they were no Heat interior then next three years the Heat would drive you out of the car. His car had door handles fall  and a fuel tank fall Off.a tire and rim once a mirror but once you get the first two year bugs out they would be great! The fuel mileage was 50 to 60 mpg. That's all he cared about but he traded every.3 1/2 years....  He knows all the VW staff by name and all repairs are covered by warranty. He had 14 TDI jetta's he Is now 81 years and has a 2011. 
The. Sydney dealer is the greatest but my experience has been one of grief and danger ..... I miss my sexy VW Jetta TDI but neveer again.
Sincerely, Stephen Sydney NS Canada</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/chv5na</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/c5o8</id></website><link>http://www.windingroad.com/forums/vw-talk/are-vws-really-unreliable/</link><postedTime>2011-01-06T14:29:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T01:37:45+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mktxpb</id><link>http://www.windingroad.com/forums/vw-talk/are-vws-really-unreliable/#comment-476152762</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-01-06</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>