<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mc4unr/update/2012-02-04T01:00:28/a97657d3b50d242686be1caa5a486c1a9d6c817c50bd72fdb3ed43ca8d0ae410</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>THIS IS A MESSAGE TO ANY MUSLIM READING THIS: I have killed many of yourpeople, I have raped your women and children and killed them as well, Ihave Burned Qurans and desecrated the bodies of dead Muslims. Me and myboys took a shit on the body of an Iraqi girl as her parents watched and sobbed, they were detained tortured and executed. I have watched Iraqis Burn to death as I smiled and laughed. I fired a Rocket Launcher at one child who was only around twenty five feet from where I was standing and who has surrendered his body flew for miles. I force fed a woman her daughters eye balls and let the child live parentless and blind with my name Burned into her forehead. We set up shop in an Iraqishouse and made him and his wife watch as we brutally raped his fifteen year old daughter repeatedly for week before eventually hacking all her limbs Off while she was alive and letting her Bleed out. A hail of gunfire sent the parents to hell. I have more repect for a cockroach than an arab or muslim. Burn in hell you cunts.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yr1epz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/u6cr</id></website><link>http://www.worldstaruncut.com/uncut/42848</link><postedTime>2012-02-04T05:05:46+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-04T06:00:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mc4unr</id><link>http://www.worldstaruncut.com/uncut/42848#comment-429172427</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h2jwp</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-04</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>