<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/85tf4k/update/2011-01-12T21:59:37/d430963ffabe0eff59bbc1ce0ac98914ae813e09a41fcab5296f66966a60b91e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>God bless and protect Sarah Palin whom many millions wish were our President, now more than ever. It seems the speech writers have been Burning the midnight oil and the 'poser' in Chief is on his way to Arizona to perform for the camera's. How we miss the days of a Ronald Reagan who was well known for writing his own heartfelt speeches and addresses to the people by his own hand, rather than 'scheduling his talking points appearances' after someone else has written the script. Strange, also, that this is the first time he's visited the state where he has stirred so much controversy. The state he is suing.

If this President does not condemn the wretched rhetoric of his own party at this 'photo op' appearance, outright, then nothing he has to say is of any importance to the people of the United States. I certainly have no intention of watching anymore of his speeches on any topic much less this one, but prefer instead to watch the analysis after the fact. We've all seen him lying via his ever present teleprompter quite enough. Will he even drag tat thing to Arizona with him? 

Besides the far left of Obama's outrageous base using this event for their own , and to afford some kind of 'sainthood' to Obama, the fact that this President is being depicted as some kind of national healer is repugnant. He has not ever been a 'healer' and never will be. He lied to attain office, veered  to the left once  office under false pretenses and now is lying and posing as a centrist to hold on to his 'power'. And the Presidency should not be about 'power' but about 'protection' of and for the people. We should not even be having the conversations we've had since this President took 'power' on the size and dreadful Scope of Obama's ever growing government. 

And by protecting the people, that includes protecting Sarah Palin Mr. unworthy President. Not your people demonizing her while you, as usual, stand on the sidelines and say nothing and make no effort to 'lead' and 'unify'. The only demon here is the progressive fringe of your uber liberal progressive Democratic party which is an outrage on America.

Again, God Bless Sarah. And condolences to the injured and dead that resulted from an event that had nothing...NOTHING to do with Sarah Palin

</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/c7scfa</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yjmx</id></website><link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2011/01/12/obama-visits-rep-giffords-ahead-memorial-service/</link><postedTime>2011-01-12T23:20:58+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-01-13T02:59:37+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/85tf4k</id><link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2011/01/12/obama-visits-rep-giffords-ahead-memorial-service/#comment-128477047</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8nldh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-01-12</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>