<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mbiujp/update/2012-03-10T15:15:38/febeaa1efa68f3315d82d09442ddfe023d68145be8b8312aba02170517d22ff9</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Private owners of Tractor-Trailers could use the tax credit to buy a new NAT Gas Tractor or modify their existing one and reduce their costs of hauling all the goods, foods, and materials we all need.  Additionally, if all Diesel Trucks and Buses across American used Nat Gas we'd reduce the amount of large vehicle pollution by 30-percent.  The vapor from Burning Liquid Natural Gas (LNG) or Compressed Natural Gas (CNG) is essentially water.  And, it smells a heck of a lot better than diesel fuel.  "Truck driver's wives and/or husbands would like the change in the way they smell changing from diesel to natural gas."  We're talking about the same Natural Gas that you use to cook and Heat your homes. The Nat Gas  would give FREE ENTERPRISE the chance to crawl out from under the heavy burden of high energy costs.   ADDITIONALLY!  It would without a doubt lower the price of gasoline because demand would be way down in the US.   Could you imagine also driving a Natural Gas Car or Truck?  You could have a "Natural Gas Pod" at your home and be your own filling station.  And, you could wash your own windshield (not that they do that anymore). The amount of jobs created by the Natural Gas  would be enormous, perhaps as many TWO -MILLION!  Manufacturing the parts for engines, pipelines, natural gas pods, new fueling stations, restaurants to feed all those workers, more housing for the people with new jobs, etc.  It wasn't Obama that came up with the Natural Gas , it's been around since 2007 and revised several times.     WE NEED The Natural Gas Act 2012 to pass.   
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/y0zveq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f047</id></website><link>http://thehill.com/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/215019-cantor-opposes-natural-gas-vehicles-bill-dimming-prospects</link><postedTime>2012-03-08T19:21:55+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-10T20:15:38+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mbiujp</id><link>http://thehill.com/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/215019-cantor-opposes-natural-gas-vehicles-bill-dimming-prospects#comment-461645273</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hdrcn</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-08</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>