<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nxlh/post/2012-03-29T12:59:14</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This made me so mad I had to come turn on my PC and respond.  If it had been atheists, would they have been arrested?  How about vegans, PETA, or any other group or person other than a preacher?  He was  50 feet away from the entrance; no one in line complained; he wasn't breaking a law.  Your commentator who said immidate means bother is  for a non-existent cause for the policeman's action.  The preacher didn't need a permit.  He wasn't demonstrating, protesting, or  anything other than reading straight passages from the Bible.  He wasn't in a location like people at the airport that you MUST walk past.  Even if the preacher had gone up to the line and offered people a Bible, as long as he kept moving and didn't harrass anyone who said no, I can't se how that's breaking a law either.  I want your commentator to prove that too me from the law.  Many people today think that we have freedom FROM religion guaranteed to us.  That's wrong.  What we do have is freedom OF religion.  Anyone's religious beliefs have the right to be expressed incluing those of every faith I, or any American, don't agree with.

So, even if the preacher did this to make a point and get on the news, I'm Glad he did.  It seems that everyone's free speech and assembly in public locations is fine unless it's someone with a Bible.  I'm sick of it.  If I have to listen to others, watch people Burn our flag, listen to groups filled with hate (1 in particular comes to mind in the Trayvon Martin case), because their rights are protected under free speech, I want my rights as a Christian to be protected too.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zh26v</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yjmx</id></website><link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2012/03/29/taking-liberties-arrested-for-reading-bible/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:06:50+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:59:14+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nxlh</id><link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2012/03/29/taking-liberties-arrested-for-reading-bible/#comment-479651341</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzy8y</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>