<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m4ey5p/update/2012-03-01T17:01:08/b48836146a26ca8d28474477ff718c40af584a467119bf1a5d275be03652c392</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m4e585</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hf3sl</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I do not recall stating that a perfect healthcare system does exist, nor do I recall stating that I wanted the US to copy any particular country's system. I have talked to plenty of people in the UK who are fed up with the NHS, particularly as it relates to mental health care; I know many in Canada who complain about wait times, though that is more an issue of too little physicians than a flaw in the system; and so forth. That said, I have friends in both Canada and France, those who do not make enough to go outside the system, who state how thankful they are to have that as, if they were in the US, they would not. I am not asking for a perfect system. I *am* asking for one that is less broken that ours.

Edit -- In Response To Your Own Edits:

"There are a lot of benefits in the US. We get fairly quick care. We get decent care. Doctors are much more free to make treatment decisions than they are in universal healthcare systems."

There absolutely are benefits to the US system, which I have not denied. As for that last sentence, however, I would suggest you speak with physicians about how much choice they feel they have. Though I in no way claim it to be necessarily better in another system, insurance companies deny claims quite a bit here, leaving physicians frustrated and without as much choice as they would want. And, to note, there are quite a few downsides.

"It's not just greed that has caused medical costs to increase. All of the wonderful advancements that we have access to cost money. They're expensive. Think of the MRI's, the PET scans, the in office devices that are used. They're expensive and increase costs. We want the best and latest care available, but complain about the costs."

When did I claim that greed was the sole reason medical costs have increased? I never did. Of course medical care is going to be more expensive now than 50 years ago -- we use more technology, rightfully so, then we did then. Greed and corruption have, however, played a role, such has been discussed throughout the comments. Other factors, such as defensive medicine practiced as a result of our country's flawed malpractice system, also do contribute, especially when you look at the overuse of tests such as MRIs.

"But if anyone honestly thinks that we can truly have universal access to cheaper, faster, better, more efficient care and continue to encourage development and have access to the most advanced technology and medications, they're being unrealistic."

Of course not -- that would be the impossible, ideal system, no? Every system has its drawbacks and trade-offs. But we need to find a better balance between those things. Though having to wait years to be treated for strep throat would not be acceptable (and, of course, this isn't quite the reality anywhere), it is of my opinion and stance that having to wait an extra week or two for an elective procedure is worth the trade-Off that someone has access to basic care.

Furthermore, I would like to point out that, once again, I have not advocated for any particular system. I have not, for example, said that we should attempt to make access purely equal, as I feel that is unrealistic as of this point in time and, perhaps, any point in time. I am, once again, merely advocating that we do more than we currently are and am open to ideas on how to accomplish this. It is others who have jumped to the assumption that I am advocating X System. 

"We don't have enough healthcare providers in this country. This isn't an issue of purposely withholding care from sick people to prevent crowding. If you give everyone free access to healthcare and you even get a slight increase in office visits for Colds or annual physicals for young healthy people, the system will become overloaded, people spill over into ER's and it's a never ending cycle."

First of all, as I stated, this is not an inherit flaw in the system; but a reflection of a physician shortage. And, for what it is worth, I have frequently advocated that the government do more to address this issue, instead of making it worse. For example, the government wants to cut Graduate Medical Education funding -- the funds used to train physicians -- when we most need it and, in fact, likely need an increase. 

I do also feel the need to, once again, point out that while more people insured does lead to longer wait times, it is also not as catastrophic as you make it out to be. I say this as someone who has lived, since starting college, in MA and who has many friends who have lived up in Canada. Are the wait times longer? Yes, they are; however, they are not so absurd that people are not getting care and, more importantly, they are actually getting care while in another system they may not. Those who would be uninsured or in a situation such as my mother's in a different system are thankful and supportive of the system. Those who could afford it in either system simply seek care outside of it. 

"Physicians won't be happy if the government places further restraints on their ability to make decisions for their patients."

I agree with you 100%. We are doing to physicians what we have already done to educators. It did not work there; it will not work here. 

"Medical advancements are going to continue to be expensive. Nobody's going to be happy with cheap universal access to primitive medicine. "

Of course medical advancements are going to be expensive and that is something that must be taken into account. That said, many of our current treatments for common chronic illness -- asthma, diabetes, mental health conditions, etc -- have not changed tremendously in the past years and, even though some new medications have come out, many studies now seem to show that, for many of them, there is not much difference between new and old. Covering basic care is something that we can manage to do.

"As it is right now, healthy people can see doctors quickly, sick people can see doctors quickly. That's a good thing. You can't say that in most countries."

As it is right now, a sick person who, to perhaps no fault of their own, cannot afford basic care, does not get it and dies. My mother and those like her worked hard to support themselves and it still was not enough to pay for a simple inhaler. I don't think the fact that this happens is something we, as a country, should use as an argument that our healthcare system is up-to-par. In fact, in comparison to other developed countries, we live shorter lives, have higher infant mortality and, overall, are a sicker country. The WHO ranks us under Costa Rica and just above Slovenia in terms of health care. [Lack of] access is a major reason for that.

"Pharmaceutical and medical technology companies will not continue to develop new ideas if the government places major restrictions on profits."

When did I argue for placing restrictions of profits? Once again, as a tip, I never did. I want our country to continue innovating. I certainly don't want to restrict that. What I do want restricted is pharmaceutical companies' current ability to sway government policy via financial incentive. I, essentially, want corruption restricted. If that is done, then people, if they rightfully earn it, can make as much as is possible.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yom1nn</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/qj7o</id></website><link>http://www.kevinmd.com/blog/2012/02/mother-fell-cracks-system-died.html</link><postedTime>2012-02-28T00:03:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-01T22:01:08+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m4ey5p</id><link>http://www.kevinmd.com/blog/2012/02/mother-fell-cracks-system-died.html#comment-453788093</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/533z9</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>