<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrxk6/post/2012-03-30T12:19:58</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>How would any TV journalist's analysis of a copied video image qualify as legitimate, professional forensics? It's preposterous. The Breitbart.com response attemting to disprove the preposterous from the same blurry image is as ridiculous as the ABC charge. Speaking from experience, a broken nose doesn't  Bleed. The extent of damage to Zimmerman's nose will be validated one way or the other by medical reports. As will the amount of grass in his hair and damage to his head, thus proving or disproving Zimmerman was the one lying on his back having his head bashed into the ground. Period.

To determine who was the aggressor, the question to be asked is: How did the two of them end up on the ground? And in which position were they? The last thing Zimmerman apparently said to the 911 operator was: "I lost him" before being told not to continue following. Zimmerman then reportedly was returning to his vehicle when he had to have been surprised by Martin who appeared out of nowhere, confronting him verbally and then initiating a physical attack. Surprise can be an effective enhancement to a physical blow to the head and could easily have rendered Zimmerman breathless and  balance forcing him to the ground, with Martin then falling on top of him. Based on the funeral director's response on Nancy Grace, there were no bruises on Martin, only the gunshot wound. So Zimmerman couldn't have engaged Martin with fists or other physical blows, which would have been the only way Zimmerman could have pushed Martin over and fallen on him. The Martin-on-top-of-Zimmerman arrangement, pointing to Martin as the aggressor, is what the first witness at the scene reported to the police. Would it be easier to access a hidden gun lying on your back, or  for it while hovering over someone and balancing yourself with your other arm? The fact that Zimmerman is still alive gives us the answer to that question, as Martin was likely Reaching for that gun once it came into view.

How many civilized law-abiding people do you know who would choose to attack someone as Martin likely did Zimmerman in a similar situation, annoyance at being followed notwithstanding? </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/675kpj</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ju4p</id></website><link>http://www.breitbart.com/Big-Government/2012/03/30/New-Video-of-George-Zimmerman-Casts-Doubt-on-ABC-Report</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:55:21+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:19:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrxk6</id><link>http://www.breitbart.com/Big-Government/2012/03/30/New-Video-of-George-Zimmerman-Casts-Doubt-on-ABC-Report#comment-480911734</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z78xc</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>