<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3bxuh/post/2012-03-29T14:42:00</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Wow! So Glad to see all the comments. It's good to have AI back in people's consciousness again. :)

Eh. I'm probably going to end up being the lone Heejun supporter, but that's fine. I've been known, in seasons past, to be 100% behind some very unpopular contestants here. I can take the Heat.

Anyway, I thought:
Best mentor every - Stevie Nicks.  Bring her back!

Colton - Ugh. Pitchy, indulgent, worthy. Pretty much one of my least favorites of the night.
Skylar - LOVE her. She's such a spitfire. She is my Allison Iraheta this season. Of course, that was totally in her "wheel house." The girl belts while moving all over the stage and really gets how to work the crowd.
Group #1 - ugh. The only one of note was Elise who sounded just like Stevie.  
Heejun - That was beautiful. Perfect song choice, lots of emotion.  Goosies. Diction issues? Actually, I think his wording is fairly precise.  But, he is Korean and English is his second language. The occasional dropped S at the end of a word might be annoying to some.  But, since I'm so used to listening to music on pop stations where Ts are now pronounced as Ds and the most common lyric is "uh-uh" it doesn't bother me.
Hollie - She's fading fast.  I wish she'd waited a few years and gotten some life experience under her belt.
Deandre - UGH Worst of the night. His falsetto isn't good enough to support a whole song, and he's too youngish. Plus, JLO skeeved me out.
Jessica - Zzzzzzzzzzzz.  That song went on forever. She can sing. She's young and cute. She'll get signed.  But, she completely bores me. She's a mimic with no real unique sound of her own.
Phillip - I liked it. One of the best of the night. To me, vocal proficiency is useless if you don't know how to sing from the heart.  Most of these kids are good but just cannot seem to break through that wall and connect with the audience. 
Joshua - Really good vocally. I love Joshua. He's one of my favorites so I want him to give another "When A Man Loves a Woman" performance very soon.  
Oh, and group 2 - Joshua, Deandre and Heejun.  Good! I liked the way the guys actually performed as a group and put effort into it rather than group 1 who just did solos. 
Group 3 - Hollie, Jess, Sylar.  Hot mess city!
Elise - definitely best of the night. But, I fear she is this season's Carly Smithson.  She was my favorite coming into the competition, but she's lost me. She doesn't make me want to root for her. 

I have no idea who is going home, but I'd send home Deandre and would put Colton and Hollie in B3. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h34ss</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q17i</id></website><link>http://www.mjsbigblog.com/american-idol-11-top-9-recap-videos-and-photos.htm</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T23:45:30+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:42:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3bxuh</id><link>http://www.mjsbigblog.com/american-idol-11-top-9-recap-videos-and-photos.htm#comment-479745049</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6kfsw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>