<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3pgqy/update/2012-03-29T20:04:55/faa83a9232ff28e5417302e0a642cc55efe32c5b202482d7b56e13dfefb29775</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>As a freshman at a Christian college, I spent weeks scooping up every copy if the college paper that my friends could find, stuffing them in my backpack and schlepping them back to our dorm room where my roommate "hid" them in his closet. Our neighbors innocently collected empty soda cans until they had a floor-to-ceiling pyramid that was the envy of all. One sunny afternoon while our Resident Assistant was foolishly away from his room, they broke in through the window, our favorite mode of access to all ground floor dorm rooms. Unfortunately, this happened on a day I had a chemistry lab, so I was left out of the game. They created a wall of empty cans against the door, then another one just inside of that, and then separated, crumpled, and piled the newspaper from floor to ceiling from the can-wall to the windows, exiting once the room was totally full, and of course closing the windows and replacing the screens. They then retired to one of the rooms on our floor and sat around listening for the Reveal. Their only problem was they forgot to shower, and having worn only cutoffs while doing this they were completely covered in ink. It was difficult to not take credit once our RA and the Head Resident started checking on the usual suspects.

As a follow-on prank, once they had put everything into trash bags under the watchful eye of our RA, they borrowed the keys to a buddy's car who was at that time unwelcome to drive on campus. Taking his car to haul everything to the dumpsters, they found an open-windowed VW that apparently reminded them of a dumpster and proceeded to fill it with crumpled newspaper. When Security stumbled upon them, they took  on foot. Our ever-vigilant Security dude took note of the parking sticker on the now-abandoned car with engine still running, and tracked it back to our buddy. No snitch he - he quietly went out and cleaned up the mess and took the Heat for having disrespected a fine German automobile. 

Then there was the time my high-school youth group buddies and I dropped by the home where our parents' SS class was having a Christmas party. We boosted the smaller guys up to where they could Reach the lights strung along the eves, and loosened all but the blue and white lights, leaving the impression that this home was celebrating Chanukah. Probably my only prank that my parents found amusing.

And of course there was the time at High School Winter Camp when we had been given "special assignment" due to some (probably true) accusation of some misdeed or other. I crawled into the overhead storage space and spoke into the rear of the adjoining cabin's PA speaker, announcing that there had been a mistake and that cabin 6-B, not 6-A, would be responsible for setting up chairs on Sunday morning for our final service. They believed the announcement, and showed up to do our work for us. When our youth leaders looked at us questioningly, we trotted out our well-worn innocent expressions, and they were savvy enough to not ask many questions.

Then there was the ... no, probably shouldn't go there.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zyqam</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/qvwn</id></website><link>http://www.jonacuff.com/stuffchristianslike/2012/03/apologizing-after-an-april-fool%e2%80%99s-day-prank-%e2%80%93-the-terror-level-color-coded-apology-system/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T11:03:47+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:04:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3pgqy</id><link>http://www.jonacuff.com/stuffchristianslike/2012/03/apologizing-after-an-april-fool%e2%80%99s-day-prank-%e2%80%93-the-terror-level-color-coded-apology-system/#comment-480050757</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zhrvv</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>