<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwix1m/update/2012-03-31T08:40:07/04de7215133f8a009f241e43df5acb2ab7568466bf82c048b9bf58d3e8d7c012</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwjano</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gssxc</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>&lt;i&gt;But what about those of us in between who don't toot the religious horns much but don't dismiss the possibility that one or more dieties exist?&lt;/i&gt; 

It sounds like you are saying your agnostic without wanting to come out and say it Max.. Which is understandable Max given the agnostic admits having a 'lack of knowledge'. Please don't  take offense if you think I'm picking on you as an agnostic because I'm not - I'll only be explaining the problems with a stance that claims a 'lack of knowledge' about the existence of something never proven to exist. The modern definition of agnosticism turns around a lack of knowledge about the god question. The word a-gnosticism itself means not-knowing, just like a-theism means not-belief in god. 

Agnosticism is mostly considered a vague middle ground in the debate surrounding the god question. Some people see it as the most rational alternative, given the sheer weight of debate going on from both theists and atheists. If we examine the agnostic premise, we find that it is quite unreasonable. Agnosticism is based on the notion that we can have no knowledge on the god question. But for this to be true, the agnostic must know all possible arguments of atheism and theism, since he discards them all out of hand.  If any single argument is valid, then agnosticism must crumble. Many such arguments are available in the atheist literature, and it is disingenuous to deny them. 

Furthermore, the lack of knowledge inherent in agnosticism is self-contradictory. If we know nothing about the god-concept, then we cannot claim it exists, or discuss it rationally. If we claim not to know anything about the concept, then we still know something about it : that it is beyond human understanding, and rational discussion. Therefore agnosticism is contradictory, and must inevitably lead to strong-atheism, except for those agnostics who don't really contemplate the question.

Moreover, agnosticism must be self-contradictory, as identity is necessary for anything to exist, and there is no such thing as an undefined object. Whatever exists in reality has attributes. If we admit that we have no knowledge about the god-concept, including how to define it, then it cannot exist. Thus assuming agnosticism is true leads to a contradiction. 

Agnostics have to answer the following question, if their position is to make any sense at all : 

&lt;i&gt;How can you presume that "god" has some possible meaning if you have no knowledge about "god" ? &lt;/i&gt;

"I think it's important to realize that when two opposite points of view are expressed with equal intensity, the truth does not necessarily lie exactly halfway between them. It is possible for one side to be simply wrong" ~ Richard Dawkins' Evolution"

&lt;i&gt;I'm just trying to say that without religious tolerance on both sides, 
it'll be harder for atheists to  ground and live peacefully. I don't
 wanna offend anyone btw.&lt;/i&gt;

Religion, with such black and white absolutes from fictional god-given standards created by religious leaders, must make the adherent self-deprecating and dehumanized when the err; and must lead them to despise and dehumanize others in an intolerant and bigoted fashion when they Act badly. This kind of absolutist, perfectionist, bi dimensional thinking results in the two most corroding human emotions: Anxiety and hostility.  

What that previous paragraph means in simpler language is  that the very nature of religion leaves its religious adherents inherently intolerant... To tolerate religion is to tolerate intolerance.  For many atheists like myself, it is irrational to tolerate what is inherently intolerant.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67xzas</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ant8</id></website><link>http://www.alternet.org/story/154774/the_top_10_reasons_i_dont_believe_in_god/comments/</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:08:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T12:40:07+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwix1m</id><link>http://www.alternet.org/story/154774/the_top_10_reasons_i_dont_believe_in_god/comments/#comment-481797943</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z78mx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>