<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9tbcb/update/2012-03-17T09:58:53/cb408a2070b3d3f69d4e6028f2afdad2487a3740701c6d3986d2cb7375e19f02</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Every 'older' generation has its share of those who criticize the young. Some even use statistics.

Here's what the authors of the NY Times article missed. Youth is not a catch-all phrase. There are at least 3 clear cohorts of 'young'. 

And each will have a different view of the future - and a consequent set of behaviors. They are...

The seriously disadvantaged (born poor, often to single mothers, bad schools) who often see little relationship between effort and reward (especially when they see lucky CEOs making a bundle). This background is tough and can often lead to a sense of powerlessness and inertia. 

Their unemployment rate is very high (14%+) and modern economies aren't creating enough work for them. This is a serious long-term social issue that is getting very little attention.

The strugglers. This a majority of American youth. Smart enough to get at least some post-secondary education, faced with high college costs (and subsequent high debt), but not strong in math, science, tech, design or any of the exploding job categories. 

They no longer see the relationship between their parent's hard word - which paid  - and theirs. Most will do OK but it will feel like a struggle. A lot of their opportunity  on where they choose to live. 

The advantaged. Young people with strong math, science, design and/or communication skills who have a college degree (or are in college now). They don't have to come from well-Off families. They just need to develop the skills they have. 

The unemployment rate among this group is very low (5.5%) and they are much less worried about where they work. Even though they may have a bit of Anxiety about the future, they are fairly confident it will turn out well.

Which points us to the GIANT elephant in the room. 

In a country where key politicians ATTACK science, where over 40% of the public don't 'believe' in the theory of evolution, where there is a concerted effort to confuse science with superstition and religion in the schools - and where millions of kids are exposed to this toxic brew every day - it's no surprise that there aren't enough people to fill the science/math jobs and there are too many people to fill jobs that don't require a lot of education (even if you have it) and pay lower wages.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ghelg</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/mft1</id></website><link>http://blogs.hbr.org/hbr/hbreditors/2012/03/americas_jobs_and_wages_proble.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-16T21:12:16+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-17T13:58:53+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9tbcb</id><link>http://blogs.hbr.org/hbr/hbreditors/2012/03/americas_jobs_and_wages_proble.html#comment-467755042</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-16</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>