<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms0jzs/update/2012-03-28T15:24:42/d9331736b4c56e9bd09ed62295795ecbf27096f3a5bd83ae36a25b8b4630f556</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>A message from a citizen of Sanford, FL

It makes those of us who have lived our lives trying to love our fellow man no matter what race, creed or nationality to become jaded. Remove the hate speech from this case and here is what you have. The facts is the Parents (probably out of their pain of losing their son) and the media are lying. All the pictures they show of Trayvon are when he was a little kid. Check out his facebook page and you will see the real Trayvon Martin. Lets talk about the fact from multiple eyewitnesses that Trayvon attacked Zimmerman and was beating him on the ground and Zimmerman is the one crying for help. Truth needs to be told and not what you are hearing from activist trying to further their cause or the liberal news media trying to get better ratings. This is a horrible tragedy that has happened. A man that was afraid for his neighborhood because all of the crime that was going on in it started a neighborhood watch program. And a young man filled with rage, probably searching for significance and meaning to his young life, and for reasons we will never know happened to meet each other at the wrong time, and the worst of tragedies happened.

Make no mistake about it, I do believe that Mr. Zimmerman needs to do some jail time for involuntary manslaughter. Life is the most precious thing that we have and Mr. Zimmerman should not have been carrying a gun.

But I also am sick of people trying portray Trayvon as some little angel who was just eating skittles and drinking sweet tea. His records have been sealed from his Miami school by the families attorney showing all of his violent behavior problems. Zimmerman was stupid for having a gun and he should do time for that, but stop all of the idiotic racist garbage. White men fought, Bled and died so that no man was a slave again and that they could have freedom. Maybe instead of having black history month and the perpetuation of a victim mentality, you should celebrate my ancestors that died for your freedom and have white history month. Maybe just one time.....it would be a really nice thing to do. This kind of hate speech that is going on makes those of us who have lived our lives trying to love our fellow man no matter what race, creed or nationality to become jaded and think to ourselves why do we even bother. It seems that no matter what we do, how kind we are, how much love we show we are just targets to be shot at. Our family personally sacrifices to help under privileged children at the school where my wife works and those same kids are now calling her a racist! Where do you think they got that from???? Um maybe it was their family members who are more interested in an agenda than the truth. As long as the Al Sharpton's and the Jesse Jackson's of the world are more interested in their own political agenda and not seekers of truth than they will continue to lead those that follow them down a path of  being the victim and also hate of their fellow man. Do they really think promoting children to wear hoodies is going to make them any kind of success in life? Please stop with your agendas and spewing hate, Yes there are a few out there still that have a KKK mentality but there is also groups like the Black Panthers who are just as bad on the other side. ($10,000 Bounty on the head of Zimmerman....really) America is supposed to be a melting pot where all the ingredients come together to make us better than we ever could have been by ourselves.

I pray for our city and all that live here, pray that peace and a sincere interest in our fellow man supersedes any agenda that is set forth out of hate.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hn96x</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/28/politics/congressman-hoodie/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T16:54:48+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T19:24:42+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms0jzs</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/28/politics/congressman-hoodie/index.html#comment-478679432</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/recen</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>