<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmpbt/post/2012-03-30T09:25:14</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Profile of the Sociopath - Obama?This website summarizes some of the common features of descriptions of the behavior of sociopaths. 
Glibness and Superficial Charm Manipulative and Conning They never recognize the rights of others and see their self-serving behaviors as permissible. They appear to be charming, yet are covertly hostile and domineering, seeing their victim as merely an instrument to be used. They may dominate and humiliate their victims. 
Grandiose Sense of Self Feels entitled to certain things as "their right." Pathological Lying Has no problem lying coolly and easily and it is almost impossible for them to be truthful on a consistent basis. Can create, and get caught up in, a complex belief about their own powers and abilities. Extremely convincing and even able to pass lie detector tests. Lack of Remorse, Shame or Guilt A deep seated rage, which is split  and repressed, is at their core. Does not see others around them as people, but only as targets and opportunities. Instead of friends, they have victims and accomplices who end up as victims. The end  justifies the means and they let nothing stand in their way. Shallow Emotions When they show what seems to be warmth, Joy, love and compassion it is more feigned than experienced and serves an ulterior motive. Outraged by insignificant matters, yet remaining unmoved and Cold by what would upset a normal person. Since they are not genuine, neither are their promises. Incapacity for Love Need for Stimulation Living on the edge. Verbal outbursts and physical punishments are normal. Promiscuity and gambling are common. Callousness/Lack of Empathy Unable to empathize with the pain of their victims, having only contempt for others' feelings of distress and readily taking advantage of them.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ztuzh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6bwl</id></website><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/president-obama/2012/03/29/obama-thinks-mega-millions-lottery-unfair</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:31:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:25:14+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmpbt</id><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/president-obama/2012/03/29/obama-thinks-mega-millions-lottery-unfair#comment-480735161</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hoiok</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>