<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/234352/post/86320894/comment/327722379</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>now, district power temporarily restored, but it will not stop,louboutin pas cher, who know no end. October 17 this year, the district once again a power outage, a series of stop eight days. The owners do not ask, blackout,scarpe louboutin, sure the developers owed the cost of the power company. They only want each brilliant idea, and some also bought a generator. the cell has been used for 17 years, the number of aging facilities, direct buried fiber optic cable more damage to the home owners with broadband, cable TV can not install. Look for communications companies, the other  answer your cell poor infrastructure,jordan, was also the collective unified account the need for developers to come forward consultation. Yesterday afternoon, the reporter in the district have also seen that there are indeed a lot of ground communication cable box is broken. There are a leading home the wires are bad, and the owners at their own expense then long a cable hanging on the wall. reporter\'s inquiry found that developers Beijing WULONG New Village development company can be described as a lot of problems. Just open the court\'s judgment on Wulong company has the first mortgage residential villas for sale, resulting in a villa there are two real estate license; has also dragged on for six years of real estate license is not issued to the owners, Pipan Pei 21 million penalty payments. The recent decision shows that the Wulong due to insolvency,ralph lauren pas cher, managed by other companies, the old property and the In desperation,louboutin pas cher, the owners have to buy the 3G cards, wireless Internet access, suburbs signal is sometimes not very good. Open his television,nike tn pas cher, and can only see a snowflake. district south gate has been sealed the evening of September 25 this year, suddenly a group of people, say they are the designated management area,chaussures louboutin pas cher, with mileage property management service center\'s name. The owners said that they saw first came to this group of people with iron bars, the old property to him outside. Require every owner District south gate was suddenly the temporary electricity often pinch us reluctant to such a life of fear, and too imperfect supporting facilities,nike tn, this villa area is too \'original\' owners says with exasperation. Our reporter Xu future text and photo work in the city district south gate was hit by new property walls are a dream that one day the villas in the suburbs, if we take a big yard, would be more perfect . , an owners come up with the verdict of a Tongzhou District People\'s Court told reporters that, since 1994 the district built so far, still used for temporary power. Court as early as September 2005 decision clearly, developer Beijing Wulong Village Development Company is obliged to temporary non-industrial construction of electricity into permanent residential electricity, when the deadline 10 since the transformation is not complete,f50 adizero, because the transformation of the cost of several million dollars. share: welcome to comment I want to Because many owners do not want to live in the district,burberry soldes, the rest of the people naturally hold up the industry committee. Beijing mileage property management service center management district can only be specified by the developer, the owners said that the previous service is OK. at the same time the Court also finds that owners pay just press the power consumption Price is now $ 0.4883 per unit. Temporary electricity prices are more expensive, peak, more than $ 1 per unit,burberry pas cher, this difference between the developer should pay, but the developers repeatedly arrears of electricity. The Tongzhou supply company confirmed that from February to September this year, excluding liquidated damages, the developer has accumulated arrears of $ 45 million, they were forced to stop the power of the district. this morning,nike mercurial vapor, reporters according to the owners of the purchase contract to stay telephone Wulong Village Development Company, but the person answering the phone said Wulong company, followed by yells. many home owners also set the newspapers,christian louboutin, can each have their building, the address can only write a certain district,louboutin, postal workers just sent to the cell door. residents since the purchase of generators Sealed the Feng Lu Huang District Court is located in Tongzhou District,louboutin, Yongshun Town, a total of 158 villas, because the a variety of problems,polo ralph lauren, now only about 50 long-term residents. struggle for many years, the Tongzhou Feng Lu Huang District Court, the owners have realized this dream,mercurial vapor, but life is not so beautiful as one might expect. District, this villa built since 1994 are still using the temporary power, often because developers arrears by the power company power; owners home TV no signal, unable to install broadband barrier-mail; suddenly come home The new property, conflicts with the owners continue to the cell door was also sealed a. The owners all day frowning. dozens of owners jointly employed a staff of 20 security to defend the district,mercurial vapor pas cher, but the the chaos of a new property management microblogging recommended | today microblogging hot In yesterday morning, the staff of the South Gate is sealed because the non - collection of property costs, they can not afford a janitor salaries. Tongzhou District government departments and their consultation as well as owners deal with the situation in the district where the other cases can not be disclosed. turn on the TV a snow no signal broadband Related articles&amp;#65306; the early morning of August 13, at half past the the Shengzhou Onchidium town, Chen Laotai the middle of the night to wake up  the air conditioner, suddenly, I heard the downstairs window at a slight cry for help, they open the windows and doors viewing. In the night Chen Laotai the found the door neighbors relative to Granny lay a shadow, and issued a very Faint cries for help. louboutin &amp;#24215;&amp;#21592;&amp;#37257;&amp;#37202;&amp;#30041;&amp;#23487;&amp;#39277;&amp;#24215;&amp;#34987;&amp;#28903;&amp;#20260;&amp;#33268;&amp;#27515; louboutin The Tomb gang attempt Daowa the tomb of f50 adizero Husband extramarital children report was the wife of bigamy the makeup teacher named operation , claiming to be in high Admissions acquaintances, just to spend some human costs, to  high candidates to do so on a regular undergraduate . Operation of a score on will certainly be admitted , to Ensure that does not crash ; paying more money only if the score can be admitted to a regular university . In this way, the operation of a continuous two cheated seven parents ranging from 2,000 yuan to 18,000 yuan , a total of 51,000 yuan . 
 
[WORDPRESS HASHCASH] The poster sent us \'0 which is not a hashcash value. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:234352:86320894</id><idPostId>86320894</idPostId><idBlogId>234352</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:234352</id><idBlogId>234352</idBlogId><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog</link><displayName>Wanton Wordsmith</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/</link><displayName>The day he went away</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T10:10:29.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:234352:86320894:327722379</id><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/#IDComment327722379</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T10:10:29.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The day he went away by henry94985</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://www.vetementupoloralphlauren.com</link><idEmailMd5>b29ebd4ad8e69b17809de585c6c13442</idEmailMd5><displayName>henry94985</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://www.vetementupoloralphlauren.com"&gt;henry94985&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/"&gt;The day he went away&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>