<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msnete/update/2012-03-27T20:55:35/c49eb71410f9268f1fbc042167671897d086b18c75bf7d060e1d73f298ad16d8</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Because that is NOT what Seungri said. This live translation is from Kristine Kwak from Twitter: 
Seungri: The Sandara Park that you know is not true. She's  like "I want to end the dating " This is a complete lie. While I became closer with her during Seungri Academy, and she texted me saying "Seungri, I am lonely". I felt like I should take action, so I looked for men who are gentle and handsome~ Lee Seunggi style. I knew some people who want to be with Dara.
Seungri: Dara is past her mid 20s, so I wanted to help her not be lonely. I introduced her to man #1. She liked him a lot.

Dara: I'm not sure if he introduced me or not, but he never called.
Seungri: You didn't call, too. I then went on to #2. He is a man that is wanted by many girls in Korea. Lee Seunggi style~ 
Dara: This time, Seungri called, but CL took the phone and ended the call.
CL: I ended the call because of dating Ban, and as leader...
Seungri: #3. He really wanted Dara. This man went to the door of Dara's house and waited for her to come out.
Dara: Yes I hear this is true.
Seungri: On this Cold day, #3 man came to see her, but she didn't come out.
Dara: I was scared and I wasn't sure if he liked me because of me. I felt like he might leave me if he got to really knew me.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l0f7q</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lyjc</id></website><link>http://www.allkpop.com/2012/03/seungri-reveals-sandara-park-stepped-on-the-hearts-of-three-guys</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T00:34:42+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T00:55:35+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msnete</id><link>http://www.allkpop.com/2012/03/seungri-reveals-sandara-park-stepped-on-the-hearts-of-three-guys#comment-477952458</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ezi4x</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>