<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msw0fv/update/2012-03-28T14:45:12/8fcede5e8a68bbb0d38f800548255be0dc96363c3a2a7a10c4a10ab23e5a05ec</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>"Mistakes were made."  Three of the saddest words in our society today.  What about the present tense?  Not even Senator Durbin can monitor that.

I don't think this specifically involves the FBI, but back in 1941, after the Pearl Harbor attack, martial law was declared in Hawaii, understandably.  Courts are shut down during martial law.  During that period, a local Hawaiian somehow got abused by authorities, either civilian or military.  I'd have to look it up again.  Anyway, there was nothing he could do about it until after the war.  Then he sued.  It went all the way up to the Supreme Court, and they ruled that the Constitution guaranteed that man's rights even under martial law.  He won his case.

That's how important the Constitution is.  And how wrong the FBI was ("is"? how can we know - it's all reported in the past tense).  No one, not even in Hawaii right after Pearl Harbor - when there was an actual country to declare war on, not some amorphous concept like "terror" - is allowed to bend the law, not even when the courts have been suspended.  

If anyone values a sense of security enough to be willing to give up "a little" of their freedom...well, you can't.  That is what inalienable means.  You can't give it up.  It's all or nothing at all.  

I prefer "all," even the Headaches during troubled times like these, when I'm forced to think and make decisions on what is and isn't right, and to take responsibility for my own freedom by exercising it, and risk being called names by those who might not agree with me politically, and perhaps even risk worse from crazy people like extremists of any ilk, who seem to have a severe allergy to the idea of freedom.

I still prefer it.  "Nothing" is not very pleasant, as we saw in many places during the 20th century, and can still see in a few places today.  Not as many today, though - all those struggles for freedom back in the day seem to have led to...more freedom.  It really works.  There is hope.  Always.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h6e48</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lk8h</id></website><link>http://www.wired.com/dangerroom/2012/03/fbi-bend-suspend-law/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T10:32:19+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T18:45:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msw0fv</id><link>http://www.wired.com/dangerroom/2012/03/fbi-bend-suspend-law/#comment-478643524</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cfgbw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>