<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwh1m8/post/2012-03-30T13:53:46</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I think the Rev. makes some valid points.  What Always gets left out though is that what we are fighting is not the idea of being responsible or caring for the world we live in, but rather people who are so conceited that they believe because of their existence the earth and all living things on it should cease to change. Indeed they think at minimum the earth should stay the same as it was at the moment of that self serving individuals moment of birth. Notice I said birth and not conception as most of these folks would argue no one matters until birth.

News flash::::The earth (correctly spelled with a small e, look it up in any dictionary) has been Heating and cooling, accepting and rejecting spiecies, and generally rotating on it's axis since it was created.  Whether you choose to believe the big accident theory or creationism, the result is no diffirent.  We can be responsible about our immediate environment, but regardless of your ever important existence (environmentalists) the earth will continue to change for better or for worse.  Your percieved control of natural processes will eventually be revealed for the fraud it is.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z3dzo</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnma</id></website><link>http://www.fresnobee.com/2012/03/30/2780692/sacrificing-america.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T07:10:43+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:53:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwh1m8</id><link>http://www.fresnobee.com/2012/03/30/2780692/sacrificing-america.html#comment-481008062</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8p79q</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>