<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/migab2/post/2012-03-22T15:52:01</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/micirw</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/m7ekh</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Hey Dr. Reppert,

I do think we need to make a decision. I was just talking if we go by the arguments alone. I'm not sure what you meant in your first comment but if God is doing the dishes, having conversations with you, you might just need to grow up and take responsibility for your life and this would include medication. Take care of yourself because God will not do it for you.   It's simply my conviction at this point that people create a God helper out of insecurity. Instead of embracing death and loving themselves and others some people become obssessed with religion because they are insecure about themselves and death. I now accept the fact that I have only so much time to live and that life involves pain and separation. By embracing this I embrace life itself and accept everything about it. Depending on a belief in an afterlife or drowning myself in the moment to avoid pain is to despise reality, which is to despise life itself. I'm choosing to affirm life by confronting my mortality. What matters to me now is to live my days well and as fully as possible. I am converting the terrified, denial-type relationship to death into something active and positive as I am released from Anxieties and fearful, timid responses by embracing death and not repressing it. It's not until I started believing in myself and loving myself that I started to get confidence. Taking this love to others from a position of power instead of insecurity only reinforces my self-esteem. It's a humble self-confidence. The Bible tries to get people to doubt themselves and lower their self-esteem so that they turn their life over to God and let Him manage it for them. In such a position of insecurity people become emotionally crippled and never grow up. I believe that one must learn to take control of their life so that they can grow up. For some like me this involves taking your medicine and doing other things that are not self destructive.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6gmcjc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry26</id></website><link>http://debunkingchristianity.blogspot.com/2012/03/on-taking-outsider-test-for-faith-otf.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-16T16:22:35+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T19:52:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/migab2</id><link>http://debunkingchristianity.blogspot.com/2012/03/on-taking-outsider-test-for-faith-otf.html#comment-473887080</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/59byr</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-16</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>