<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw319e/post/2012-03-31T11:55:40</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw3a0s</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rebn0</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>BP, despite its name, is a majority owned US company.  It really is not my responsibility, as a UK taxpayer, to Cough up so that a bunch of US shareholders can avoid paying fines and damages to a US government for an accident caused by US citizens working on a US owned rig Off the coast of the USA.  Don't believe everything you hear on Fox or CNN.

I didn't rush to buy fuel, just like the overwhelming majority of UK drivers.  There are some 31 million cars on our roads, we'd have caused gridlock if we'd all rushed to the pumps.  It only takes 1-2% of drivers to panic to cause problems at the pumps for a brief period, allowing for the fact that about 5 million people top up with petrol on most days of the week. Most of us will wait until the queues subside and fill up late next week, but some people with jobs that require them to commute were concerned that they might not get to work and risk losing pay, clients, customers, jobs etc.  That's not greed, that's protecting your interest and that of your family - as would happen in the good ole US of A.

A nation of philanthropists you ain't.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67r51a</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/politics/conservative/9176237/Even-Im-starting-to-wonder-what-do-this-lot-know-about-anything.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:45:59+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T15:55:40+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw319e</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/politics/conservative/9176237/Even-Im-starting-to-wonder-what-do-this-lot-know-about-anything.html#comment-481941870</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8561q</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>