<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m340uf/post/2012-03-29T11:27:04</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Connecting the Dots…


I, Hissay P. Bhutia have been living in the city(Delhi)
for the last 5 years and working in the field of Human Development and
Childhood Studies. As a part of my master’s research project, I have visited
this small Tibetan settlement in Delhi, Majnu-ka-tilla almost every single day for
the data collection.  I  have spent hours and hours sitting down at the
monastery observing the children play and interacting with them, interviewing
the people who used to sit and chat around and used to ask me about my work and
where do i come from and stuffs. I believe everyone enjoys watching children
play as i could see people not only observe them but play along with them, "children
makes you smile...no matter what you going through...they have the power to
make you forget...it" as someone quoted... for me they made me re-connect
to my culture...which was missing...:). I do not know when did, I become a
friend...a daughter...a member of this little community. It (working with the
children) has made me go into the depth of belongingness and i no longer feel
alienated as i used to prior to my research work. I used to sit and observe
children and people to understand this rich culture and their lives in exile. I
noticed a man who used to sit at the corner bench alone...smiling at the
children quite often and as I sat down with my usual writing stuff one day, he
came and asked me the same question like everyone else...where am I from and
what am I writing on...I told him...about my work, he said " good
luck"..."can I read it", I was hesitant...I replied...maybe once
I am done with the writing...he smiled...and he left( that was the shortest
interaction i had during the research work).


26th March 2012, Monday morning, I went to Patel
Chowk to ‘see’ the protest. I was early that day (for the first time in my
life). As I looked around I could see many protests going on, what caught my
eyes was a group demanding...'say no to Koodankulum Nuclear Plant' as I started
having this short interaction with Mr. Chitarang Singh we talked about my
purpose of being there and his agenda, for sometimes later he pointed at my
back and said 'they are here...your people', as I turned around there were hundreds
of Tibetan men and women...boys and girls...mother and child...father and
mother and elderly people came marching. They were all over the place and only
Tibet's National flags, the banners that said 'Tibet is not a part of China'
and ‘Freedom is Our Birthright’ could be seen (other protesters had to hold for
sometimes). Three young men came...riding horses and fully decked-up in the
traditional clothes and I took out my lens (camera) started to capture
everything, I moved in with the crowd I was lost...lost taking the
pictures...suddenly, there was a sharp scream and the crowd started moving in
all direction by the time my focus was interrupted and I turned around to see
what it was, there was this man in flames...red hot flames covered his body and
black smoke surrounded him…I stood there motionless...my index finger still on the
button of my lens(camera)…as he ran screaming on my left the crowd of
photographers and media people ran together. It was the crowd that moved
me...moved me till I took hold of the tree, still
motionless...trying to figure out what just happened... my friend returned back
and we stood there without a word...till...he said 'let's go home'...I took
last three pictures of the people... there I saw a reporter or she may be a
photographer crying, I did not dare to go and console...because, it is not 'ok'
for what just happened. Later that day I explained to my flat mate about the
incident and like everyone else, she found the Act of self-immolation wrong too
and said it is mentioned in the Buddhist philosophy as well. It is morally and
ethically considered wrong I believe everyone is aware of it and I do not need
to look into what philosophy says but my only question is…what made him do
it…what made all those 30 individuals do it…and not judge he or they were
wrong! (I am NOT encouraging the action here). 


Three days now, what I realized is that the man
who wanted to see my writing was the same man who set himself ablaze in the
protest... Jamphel Yeshi...the man
who sat alone, observed me write and wished me luck. I wish I should have let you
see...what I was writing...and maybe you could have said
".....". Well, maybe we all can spread this issue world-wide and seek
an answer to this ongoing struggle of identity, confusion and social exclusion for
the last 53 years. 


Let us not ignore the fact
that Jamphel Yeshi did not Burn
himself but it’s the agony of every Tibetan that Burned.  



 


We have to speak NOW!!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zc63v</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/temq</id></website><link>http://globalspin.blogs.time.com/2012/03/29/tibetans-self-immolation-casts-shadow-over-brics-summit/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T05:58:14+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:27:04+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m340uf</id><link>http://globalspin.blogs.time.com/2012/03/29/tibetans-self-immolation-casts-shadow-over-brics-summit/#comment-479576581</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzeh7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>