<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mko28o/update/2012-03-26T15:00:58/1f54e4171da6d2482080b4bb64b6201bd9407a84776cca10ea14581d65424244</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Who is this Marcus Chhan and what are his credentials?
It appears he has written this article purley from the point of view that he needs to write something different for the sake of it so that people will read his article. To me it seems he thought popular opinion is bashing KD and Liverpool so I should write something in favor of them. With that in mind he copy pasted couple of facts/comments/snippets from others columns and bamm! he has his article.
This article lacks content so much, its unbeliveable. The title is 'Dalglish taking Liverpool Forward' and only in the section 'progress is progress' - the first three lines talk about the main theme of the article (except for the copy pasted shearer interview)..the rest all is either contradictory to his title or irrelevant facts posted to lenghten the content.
Bottom Line: From a player's point of view, they would want to win trophies and they might be happy with a carling cup victory (and may be that's why KD thinks cup success mattera a lot..coz of his playing experience)..but the Cold harsh truth is you need champions league to gurantee revenues/TV time/T/F budget/really good players..its all inter linked and it can only happen if you have CL qualification
So Mr. Chhan..stop selling your copy pasted article (without any value addition from you)..playing Off the countless liverpool fans' emotions by just writing what they want to hear without any reasoning whatsoever.
When it comes to writing articles..I hope you walk alone! </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rfyj4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/y62v</id></website><link>http://www.espnstar.com/editorial/news/detail/item776602/Dalglish-is-taking-Liverpool-forward/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T06:20:48+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T19:00:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mko28o</id><link>http://www.espnstar.com/editorial/news/detail/item776602/Dalglish-is-taking-Liverpool-forward/#comment-476637796</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>