<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/e6bub5/update/2011-12-06T18:01:43/fa877dcdc512ae9fb02c7fe7c81a530db35192c7029765afa73ea927dd115101</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Thanks for this . I have mixed thoughts: One one hand, keeping the tip jar &amp; merch on stage (or near it) is a great way for people to "show their love" in a visible way to the band--and keep a good eye on your goods--but there are some audiences that are a little shy and would rather not be too close to the spotlight. Maybe it's a Midwestern thing, but I think it  on the venue and what kind of crowd you draw; some people just feel awkward being that close to the action. You know your audience best, so I'd say try different things until you find the sweet Spot.

I agree with people below about salting the jar a bit. I'm in a band that has a regular monthly gig at a coffee/wine bar that is tips-only, so we bill it as "Never a cover, Always a tip jar" and remind people that their donations are what allow us to continue coming back. The venue usually throws in a 20 and the band will throw in 5-10 to start. We're also lucky in that staff also walk around with the jar. Word of wisdom to others who have gigs like this: If it's an all-ages show and you have a friend with a toddler, enlist their help in getting people to tip! We have a 4-year-old "fan" who LOVES to walk around with the jar, soliciting tips (she started doing it on her own for fun, then her mom and the band encouraged it after that). People love to make a toddler smile. I also agree with Jason Fifield below, in that personally chatting people up makes a difference in people's engagement and tip quotient. Plus, when you work a room, you're also more likely to get a repeat customer because they'll remember how friendly and *human* you were.

To Mdhastings' question: I don't know a good answer about how often to suggest tipping during a show, but I've seen several bands announce it 1-2 times per set, and it seems to work for them. Some even suggest a certain amount and pass the jar around each time they make the suggestion.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/mptmu0</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tic0</id></website><link>http://blog.discmakers.com/2011/11/the-tip-jar-effect/</link><postedTime>2011-11-15T15:52:09+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-12-06T23:01:43+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/e6bub5</id><link>http://blog.discmakers.com/2011/11/the-tip-jar-effect/#comment-380650252</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-11-15</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>