<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3i9pz/post/2012-03-29T21:42:29</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Michael Krasny and KQED - shame on you!  Your credibility  is being seriously questioned by thousands of SF residents.  Just wait until the plunder of the streets of San Francisco Reaches your neighborhood.  

When you complimented Jay on all his data, that was just buying into his "data-driven transparent" argument.  Anyone who deals with data knows that it can be manipulated to suit their needs.  His beloved, incomplete data is only a small part of the story.  He conveniently ignores other data that has been presented to him by the residents and businessmen in the affected areas.By the way, Shoup's "green" argument doesn't hold water for many reasons.  The simplest to refute is his contention that it would reduce circling by having at least one empty Spot on each Spot.  But, later he recommends circling to and in the cheaper-priced areas if they didn't want to pay the higher-priced meters.  All this does is move the circling over to less desirable neighborhoods until those meter prices are then raised according.And, BTW, I don't know anyone who is familiar with the city who expects to find a parking Spot on the street in the financial district, chinatown, and other truly congested areas.  Most of us in the NE Mission areas being targeted with the meter invasion have been able to cope with our own parking issues without Big Brother coming in and telling us what we need because they did a small, insufficient study that answered an easy "numbers" question but not ask the important "numbers" questions  or take into consideration any"who", "what" or "why" questions.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lyo4g</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zevs</id></website><link>http://www.kqed.org/a/forum/R201203271030</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T00:47:48+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:42:29+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3i9pz</id><link>http://www.kqed.org/a/forum/R201203271030#comment-480124994</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>