<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk9plm/post/2012-03-26T13:54:51</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Indeed so. What are political parties other than conspiracies to influence the results of elections? In the days that Walter Bagehot was writing, it was entirely reasonable (at least from the politicians' point of view) for all decisions to be delegated to teh MPs because communications meant that nobody outside Westminster could know enough about matters of state to make an informed decision. (Whether it is actually necessary for politicians to meddle as extensively as they do is a moot point).
With today's instant communications it is probable that nobody inside Westminster can know enough to make decisions. At base, however, is the question; Do we actually need politicians to make decisions down to the level they do? An example is policing. The Government makes laws, the police (should) enforce them and the judiciary interprets them. Police (should) know their patch, and how local people feel about the local toe-rags. The judges (should) bring to bear common sense combined with a deeper knowledge of the Common Law in sentencing said toe-rags. I feel we would be far better Off if "[so-called] Statesmen do not Itch / To interfere in matters which / They do not understand"</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r01lr</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/jolo</id></website><link>http://talkcarswell.com/disqus.aspx?id=2308</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T16:04:16+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:54:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk9plm</id><link>http://talkcarswell.com/disqus.aspx?id=2308#comment-476582407</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>