<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw1cx4/update/2012-03-30T23:38:01/8e9266df1eb33ce628533fd6cdce690f404211c1a1267361c9d320631c33f82a</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwb3xa</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/r1mwf</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>"Rewards are a good place to start"

"a good place to start"

"to start"

He's right. Rewards ARE a good place to start, but that is not the end-all be-all of the article nor of the point. Players DO want to feel some sort of achievement as they play and there's nothing wrong with that. Setting up incremental achievements/rewards/etc is a good place to start moving in the right direction. It is only the start to adding content to the game for players to get as they go. Again, this is why he references MK9 because of the breadth of content the game has. It does give you unlocks as you go, but they are secondary to enjoying the actual content of the game. However, conversely, you could also just do those things to unlock the various content (as I did) simply for the sake of having it...yet still enjoy it as you go because the game is providing a fun, varying experience. It isn't simply "Bash your head into the controller after beating arcade mode 38 times"

Onto your next point that's fairly illogical...

So fighters are hard...so if someone isn't willing to invest a bunch of time to get better at it they should not bother to buy the game? The fuck? How about this? I enjoy the shit out of KOF...I have been playing it religious since '97. I enjoy the cast of characters...the gameplay variety...and the playstyle. However, after nearly 15 years, I still am absolutely mediocre at the game. I have never been able to do high-level stuff in the games...but I still enjoy them because they're fun for me. By your logic, since I am not investing the time (which for me would apparently be hours a day considering the lack of progress I've made this last decade and change...) to get better, I should not even bother buying the game. Do you think people buy Madden (a game I've never even played so probably suck at...) with the intent to be insanely good at it? Or maybe are they (holy shit incoming insanity) playing it because it has a bunch of stuff for them to do that they consider fun? Your point has no point to it. Are you somehow saying that people that don't want to markedly improve at fighting games shouldn't even bother buying them? Or what? Seriously what is even your point. Wanting to get GOOD at a game does not equal the ultimate goal of 99% of gamers when they buy a game. They want to be (oohhhhh damn more craziness on its way) entertained. Fighters are providing poor entertainment packages for people. That is the entire point of the article.

I used this analogy before...how many people do you think would be happy to pay $11 for a perfectly Acted, really well-written, artistically shot movie that's three fucking minutes in length? that is the level of entertainment value people are being presented with in fighters (in their opinion). Yes, uber-pretentious douchie-movie snobs will say "But the lighting is so great! I've already watched it ninety times to enjoy every subtle nuance of those 3 minutes! What are you complaining about? It had a character, a plot and resolution in those 3 minutes...isn't that enough?" See? In this analogy, a bunch of people on SRK who are too dumb to see how this sort of mind-set hurts the very genre they're on here to support are the pretentious douchie snobs.

And onto your last point...it seems more like you "lost" MTG for many  years btw rather than "played" it to have that attitude. The best players in the world at MTG are the best players in the world year after year regardless of whether or not Donald Trump or Bill Gates decided to play with decks they bought and crafted themselves. Give the most broken character in the world to a scrub and to a world-class player and the world-class player is going to win 10/10. Give the best deck in the current meta to a scrub and to a world class MTG player and the world-class player is going to win 10/10. Its apples &amp; apples. You're completely out of your mind if you think buying the current high-tier deck makes you auto-win. Against your scrubby friends (assuming your friends are scrubby)? Sure. But what's the difference between that and just picking 'Gief in SF4vanilla and LARIAT!-ing your scrubby friends to death? You won't LARIAT! a serious player to death...nor would a scrub with a money-deck go to worlds and beat high-level players playing the same deck. History has born this out time and time again.

EDIT: Just gonna edit in a quick "sorry". Being more snippy than I mean to be or need to be in here towards ya. Not called for...its just late and I'm being driven insane by the amount of counter-productive ridiculousness some others are Vomiting onto SRK.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zjqj5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/xspx</id></website><link>http://shoryuken.com/2012/03/29/gamespot-thinks-a-new-standard-must-be-set-to-fix-the-fighting-game-genre/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:50:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T03:38:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw1cx4</id><link>http://shoryuken.com/2012/03/29/gamespot-thinks-a-new-standard-must-be-set-to-fix-the-fighting-game-genre/#comment-481494582</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ho546</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>