<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3inbw/post/2012-03-29T21:31:45</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>You're seeing a shadow from his head's shape when he's turning.  At 1:27
 in the video you linked you have a direct view of the back of his head 
and the line is not there.



If it was a wound it would be visible there as well.  Additionally, a 
several-inch cut on the back of someone's head does not just stop 
Bleeding.  A head wound that size requires medical attention to treat 
and unless the EMTs apoxyed his head a cut that size, not even an hour 
old, would Bleed.



The amount of bloodless that you'd have from that would soak your head 
and clothes.  In the video, including at the end, there is no sign of 
blood on his clothes, no residue on his head, the 'cut' is clean and 
he's walking normal when that would have been a serious injury.  The 
amount of trauma needed to cause a cut like that on concrete would 
easily suffice to cause a concussion.  Zimmerman's dad claims his son 
was on the ground and being beaten for a minute, the damage that an 
assault for that duration would cause would be visible on camera, such 
as the allegedly broken nose.



There's no blood, the 'cut' only shows for a brief moment as he turns, 
with it appearing and disappearing relative to the position of the light
 shining in from Off right of the camera, and his face is shown clearly 
multiple times, all of which have no visible markings that you'd have 
from a prolonged assault that causes a broken nose.  A broken nose which
 also looks exactly like a normal nose.



So we have video of a 'head wound' that appears for a second and is 
missing in other frames where it'd be visible, and a 'broken nose' that 
has no swelling or dis-figuration.  This video does not help Zimmerman's
 case at all.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6za97r</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q0fi</id></website><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/29/police-surveillance-video-of-zimmerman-may-show-head-injury/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T04:19:40+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:31:45+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3inbw</id><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/29/police-surveillance-video-of-zimmerman-may-show-head-injury/#comment-480116986</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>