<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0o3rt/post/2012-04-02T06:15:05</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mjgw2s</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5pg5m</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>You can not compare a spoon with construction steel, the material differences are immense. The usual spoon is made of stainless steel. this is an alloy of iron and nickel with chromium. The most commonly used variant contains 18% Cr and 8% Ni. Stainless steel is tough, has a higher tensile strength, but a way lower yield strength than construction steel. (C.S. can take more elasticity and movement then S.S.)
You are right when it comes to the steel getting more elastic due to Heat, that's a fact. I agree when u say u cant just google the melting point of steel and the Heat of jet fuel Burn and go ah ha. But plenty of calculations have been made on the situation as a whole. Not by comparing 2 given temps but taking 'all' factors into account, support force, upper mass etc and obviously all the information that is available on how steel  under extremely Heat circumstances. We can't ignore the fact that these calculations again and again point in the opposite direction of steel fatigue.
About 60% of the load bearing construction within the impacted face were destroyed, this caused a load redistribution which pushes some of the remaining columns close to their max. bearing capacity.
say that your right on: about all the Heat protective paint and layering being 'blown' of by the plane (which would be darn close to impossible for it to happen over all the floors of impact) you could arrive at the situation where the support (within floors of impact) Reaches critical levels and could fail. resulting in the drop of the top floors, but not the rest of the WTC body. That was intact and standing strong. Therefore these 'chances' do not give an explanation for the domino/free falling effect the world has witnessed, on 3 (not badly constructed) buildings. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/m2got6</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/znv4</id></website><link>http://topdocumentaryfilms.com/911-explosive-evidence-experts-speak-out/</link><postedTime>2011-09-23T11:00:56+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T10:15:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0o3rt</id><link>http://topdocumentaryfilms.com/911-explosive-evidence-experts-speak-out/#comment-483399341</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zt2zn</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-09-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>