<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/azvvhg/update/2010-10-06T21:43:18/fc01d0f8728ee394b4c92868e88342b24fd57bca8a37f53cd92209970aa72070</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Vote for the candidate that the Progressive Democrats are zero'd in on.  Yes indeedy.  Usher them right into office.  Such as Ms. O'Donnell.  And Meg Whitman.   Because these two women will clean house.  They will literally mop the floor with Democrats and their States will be the better for it.  They are getting the 'Palin treatment' now via Democratic 'witchcraft' and bogus 'maid' blather.  And the crook Democrats  know it.  They know its baloney and so do we.  Vote these women in, vote Barack Hussein Cloward and Michelle 'For the first time in my life, I'm proud of my country' Piven out on their rear ends.  Our First Lady of Apple Slices for the Astroturf, the 'Closer', is out begging around and sniffing out dollars for the awful Obama agenda for a 'New America'.  Google her list of recipients, the louses in trouble that she and the SEIU will be 'match funding' and whom are in 'tight Spots' because the Republicans have them on the run.  In my own state, she'll be passing the collection plate for the outrageous  Alexi Giannoulious.  An example of the people the Obama's consider 'good for America' and whom they surround themselves with.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/84rtkz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yjmx</id></website><link>http://www.foxnews.com/opinion/2010/10/05/bradley-blakeman-christine-odonnell-senate-witch-delaware-campaign-ad-mistake/</link><postedTime>2010-10-05T19:51:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2010-10-07T01:43:18+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/azvvhg</id><link>http://www.foxnews.com/opinion/2010/10/05/bradley-blakeman-christine-odonnell-senate-witch-delaware-campaign-ad-mistake/#comment-84748505</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8nldh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2010-10-05</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>