<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkqz6y/update/2012-03-26T01:36:15/b5b4e42316ef36e3afe5278c7bc4368cc1e16e0d8401978d49dda34d3889fa4a</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk410e</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I believe it's mostly politicians and lawyers, although you might say they're the same thing, mostly.  The bankers are willing partners, but couldn't survive as the fat cats they are without the devices of lawyers and politicians!  Just  all business donations to politicians, just allow personal ones by identified donors, and you would stop it Cold!

Personally, I'd outright  lawyers from becoming politicians if they have practiced within 6 years prior to running for office,  and ALL politicians should be precluded from  as lobbyists for at least 4 years AFTER! 

Next, I'd eliminate Congessional retirements, force Congress members to submit to the same laws as we, and allow only them two terms of office, with a minimum of one term sat out, before beginning a new try at one. Our forefathers design for government service was it would be just THAT, a service! Career politicians? Pfui! You did your obligated service for the people, then went home and took care of business!

My reasoning against lawyers, is that they are the reason we have such screwd up laws now! They Ensure laws are written so only a lawyer can travel through those mine fields without self damage! If I had my 'druthers', if you need a lawyer, even in Congress, hire one, then let 'em go when that matter is settled.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rvkvn</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/o2bq</id></website><link>http://patriotupdate.com/20307/activist-group-teaches-homeless-how-to-invade-apartments</link><postedTime>2012-03-25T19:47:14+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T05:36:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkqz6y</id><link>http://patriotupdate.com/20307/activist-group-teaches-homeless-how-to-invade-apartments#comment-476236305</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>