<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkpu5e/post/2012-03-26T16:26:31</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkpbn3</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/d81o6</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Two Points. 1. Regardless of any good or bad things said about Zimmerman, shooting and killing this unarmed kid (who was only carrying skittles and a ice tea) is outrageous and tragic, and at a minimum, the Zimmerman should be arrested., and he can ‘claim’ self defense while it is being investigate. Everyone should be supportive and demanding that this child and his family gets JUSTICE. The Federal Gov’t needs to stay involved and Ensure that this shooter is at least arrested and investigate the Fla. Police Dept. and prosecute them for any wrongdoings. If the shooter had followed the dispatcher’s orders and stayed in the car and not approach the kid, this child would be alive today . . . . . It would not surprise many if this shooter (a self-appointed watchman with no legal authority) has a history of racial bias, and he seemed to be a bully looking for a fight. On the tape he used a racial slur and it has been reported that he once committed violence against the police, but charges were later dropped. He may not be a racist (and racists come in all colors), but he CLEARLY overreacted and needs to be held accountable for his deadly actions, and the U.S. should take a critical look at the ‘self-defense’ law that can be used to murder innocent people (Shooting deaths have gone up 250% since this ‘Stand your ground law’ law was implemented in Fla.). 2. All of us have the right to defend ourselves but, based on the circumstances of this situation his claim of self-defense appears to be a lie, is extremely questionable, does NOT seem credible, stinks to high heaven, and is probably being used by the shooter and police to ‘COVER UP’ a crime and protect the shooter. Thank God he didn’t become a real cop, because no telling how many innocent people he might have murdered and claimed ‘self-defense’. When it walks like a duck and quacks like a duck.........you know the rest - This man appears to be a Cold-bloodied murderer who should be in prison for a very long time (without parole) for killing this unarmed child. , arrest George Zimmerman Now ....</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rftm0</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/26/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T06:36:28+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T20:26:31+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkpu5e</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/26/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html#comment-476714310</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/grj7l</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>