<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0esfm/post/2012-03-31T20:45:06</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>

WHEN YOU GET TO THE TOP IT IS ALL THE SAME PEOPLE. Watching the elite top echelon of the re puppy party all cluster around Money bags Romney I am reminded  of the old cliche.  Money goes to money. Those that don't have it sit at the feet of coin dispensers.That is what I see when they announce who endorsed Romney. If you asked each one of the good ol boys why not Santorum?  And they answered truthfully. They would say because he has no money. Donald Trump is an obvious example. Do you really believe that the Donald believes Romney is the best man for the job?No they are all picking the obvious winner. Bobby Jindal as far as I know did the right thing. He stayed out of endorsing anyone in the Louisiana race. The people picked Santorum. On the other side of the coin you have the demo commo elitists. Led by Bill Maher (I DON'T BELIEVE THE DONATION WAS HIS MILLION BUCKS) who took a nasty dump on the state of Mississippi mocking a great people for being poor. Yet never mentioning that his elite handler Obama has vowed to put the entire South out of work. Especially the Gulf Coast. Obama who has had personal experience with white prejudice all the way to the White house. Having listened to the words of Old man river with his own ears.  So on the one hand you have the re puppy elites, the Bush's, the Doles, the Trumps and Fox News.on the other hand Obama has, Steve Jobs for the Chinese minimum wage, but no one is going after big Ipod or big GE or big Pornowood. Did I mention the entire news media in printed form and on the airwaves. CNN, NBC, all the times papers and the Mexican killing gun running justice department. Through the BS maze we are supposed to believe that my vote counts. If my vote counted Rick Santorum would not be blacklisted by the media on both sides. Rick Santorum would not be mocked by pimp comedians. His wife would not be labeled a crazy by Don Imus. His down syndrome child would not be a Bill Maher joke. He would not be mocked as his Catholic religion is by Aids to Chuck Schumer on Fox.  So why is this inconsequential loser fro Pennsylvania a millstone around Romney's neck?  Moneybags got rid of Bachmann and left her a million dollars in the red. The demo commos got rid of Cain using a status seeker who lives in the same building as David Axelrod but they never met for tennis. Mr. seller I'll take two Brooklyn bridges. The guy that can order in Chinese ran out of yen. Rick Perry who was the butt of another nasty Bill Maher joke that went like this. If Rick Perry was black Sarah Palin would have f'd him. If I was Todd Palin I would convince Israeli intelligence that Bill Maher is an Iranian nuclear scientist. Oh the beating he would get in my Irish neighborhood for what that rat did. After the soccer team got finished, then the hurling team, then the choir. While the pipers played nearer my God to thee. So what have we now says the fine old woman?  We have a nation on the way to the crapper. We have two parties that have no intentions of cutting the budget that makes us working slaves to the Chinese,  the congress, OPEC, and a president who hates the country that gave him everything. Which goes to prove once again If you did not earn it you don't appreciate it. Forty days before 911 forty eight senators voted to Burn the Flag including Match McConeel, 40 were demo commos and 8 were re puppies. This is what you have running the circus. Speaking of circuses Romney saved the Olympics with Government grant money.If it is from Massachusetts it will hurt you. Paul Revere moved his grave to Louisiana. IF YOU WANT YOUR VOTE TO COUNT.  IT HAS TO BE SANTORUM. HE IS THE ONLY ONE LEFT THAT REPRESENTS YOU. ALL THE REST ARE REPRESENTING THEMSELVES. WHEN THEY ARE IN POWER THE OFFICE DOOR CLOSES FOR FOUR MORE YEARS. THIS IS THE ONLY CHANCE YOU GET TO BE HEARD. So lets look at the line up.The demo commos team. and their valuesunions and their goalsPeta communistsGreen crap communiststhe communist environmentaliststhe Black community 92%The Hispanic community minus the Catholics and many stand in line immigrants. 51%the gay community 95%the welfare community 95%the legalize drug community 99%The prison population 95%the communist party 100%occupy wall street (see the communist party)Runaway Catholics 25%Al Queda vote 90%THE ALGAE PEOPLE 98%THE PBA CROWD 100%THE MILITARY 5%THE KGB 100 %CAIR 100%ATHEISTS (SEE THE COMMUNIST PARTY)  ON THE SANTORUM SIDE.CATHOLICS 60%EVANGELISTS AND BAPTISTS 90%ALL OTHER RELIGIONS EXCEPT AL QUEDA 85%MOTHERS WITH CHILDREN 85%COAL MINERS UNION 98%OIL RIGGERS AND RELATIVES 98%THE MILITARY INCLUDING THE ABSENTEE BALLOTS THE DEMO COMMOS CAN'T GET THEIR HANDS ON 95%THOSE WHO SWITCH FROM ROMNEY TILL CONVENTION TIME 74%TRUCKERS IN SPITE OF BEING THREATENED BY  JIMMY HOFFA JR. 80%FARMERS 95%FISHERMAN 95%HUNTERS 99%ANYBODY WHO HAS BEEN SCREWED BY THE EPA 100%ANYONE THAT HAS BEEN SCREWED BYOSHA 100%ANYONE WHO HAS BEEN KILLED BY THE DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE MINUS 2 THAT WE KNOW OF.AND 50,000 DEAD MEXICANS KILLED BY AMERICAN DRUG ORDERS.BOY SCOUTS WHO  18 YEARS OF AGE 95%GIRL SCOUTS NOT BRAINWASHED BY THE COMMUNIST PARTY 50%STUDENTS WHO WILL FAIL IF THEY DON'T VOTE FOR OBAMA 30%PEOPLE WHO LIVE IN HOODS CONTROLLED BY THE NEW BLACK PANTHERS 10%WORKING TAX SLAVES 98%PARENTS WITH 3 JOBS 100%PEOPLE WHO DON'T LIKE THE STATUS QUO 100%TEA PARTY 90%REPUBLICAN ELITES 10%FOX NEWS EMPLOYEES 10% THE REPUPPY SIDE.THE FINEST VOTERS MONEY CAN BUY. THE GIVE US THE SOS CROWD.THE DON'T ROCK THE VOTE CROWD.FOX NEWS. OREILLY MADE US DO IT.THEY CAN'T SEE ME I'M INVISIBLE CROWD. REMEMBER SCHOOL WHEN THE TEACHER CALLED ON YOU?I WAS ON BILL MAHER BUT NO ONE SAW ME CROWD.I WAS ON DANCING WITH TOM DELAY.I INTRODUCED GEORGE BUSH TO BILL CLINTON THE TOPIC WAS LIBRARIES.IF THAT IS A ROCK I'M CRAWLING UNDER IT UNTIL THE ELECTION IS OVER CROWD.I'M AGAINST BIRTH CONTROL PILL PAYMENTS BUT VIAGRA SHOULD BE COVERED.TWO LOG CABIN REPUBLICANS IN SEPARATE ROOMS. WHO WANTS ROMNEY THE MOST? OBAMA !  WHAT DOES THAT TELL YOU?OBAMA REFUSED TO DEBATE GINGRICH WITHOUT A VENTROLIQUIST. IT HAS TO BE SANTORUM. I HOPE NEWT THROWS IN WITH RICK BUT I FEAR THE ROMNEY OFFER OF I CAN HELP YOU WITH YOUR PERSONAL DEFECIT WILL OVERWHELM HIM. WHICH WILL BE SAD.  SANTORUM COMES WITH NO STRINGS ATTACHED. HIS WIFE IS A NURSE AND A LAWYER PLUS THE MOTHER OF SEVEN KIDS. THAT IS A BIG WHITEHOUSE TO FILL.  THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN BUSH AND OBAMA IS BUSH LISTENED TO HIS GENERALS. IN EIGHT YEARS HE LOST 461 AMERICANS IN AFGHANISTAN. OBAMA LISTENS TO HIS POLITICAL COMMISARS AND HAS ALREADY LOST 2,000 AMERICANS PLUS SEAL TEAM SIX 22 MEN. BIGGEST SEAL TEAM LOSS SINCE WWII. WE STILL HAVE THE RUN OUT TO DO.  BEING SHOT IN THE BACK BY GITMO DETAINEES OBAMA RELEASED. ERIC HOLDER HAS SUPPLIED THE NARCO TERRORISTS WITH 2200 WEAPONS THAT WE KNOW ABOUT. HE IGNORES CALLS FROM CONGRESS TO COME CLEAN. HIS WEAPONS HAVE ARMED FOUR REGIMENTS 500 EA OF GROUPS WAGING WAR AGAINST THE MEXICAN GOVERNMENT. RESULTING IN THE DEATHS AND BODY MUTILATIONS OF 50,000 MEXICANS. BUT TO OBAMA THE MEXICANS DON'T COUNT HE SAYS LOOK ONLY TWO GRINGOS DIED. HE HAS WASTED TRILLIONS OF DOLLARS AND PRECIOUS TIME. HE HAS MADE ISRAEL A GO AHEAD TARGET FOR IRAN, RUSSIA AND CHINA. THE ONLY THING HE TRADES WITH RUSSIA IS AMERICAN AND BRITISH NUCLEAR . HIS SECURITY IS SWISS CHEESE. A PRIVATE HAS LEAKED 80,000  DOCUMENTS TO WIKILEAKS. HE INSPIRES RACE RIOTS. FOUR MORE YEARS OF THIS GUY WE WILL NOT HAVE A COUNTRY. WHO CAN DO THE BEST JOB? WHO WILL TRY THE HARDEST TO GET IT RIGHT. SANTORUM.DON'T LET THE COMMUNISTS PORTRAY HIM AS A RIGHT WING NUT. IF YOU DON'T TURN THE NUT TO THE RIGHT THE WHEEL COMES . THEY SAY HE IS A RELIGIOUS FREAK. WHY? BECAUSE HE GOES TO CHURCH ON SUNDAY? JESUS IS HIS ROLE MODEL. WHAT IS WRONG WITH THAT? OUR RELIGION WAS FOUNDED BY A RABBI WHO WENT TO TEMPLE AND FOLLOWED THE LAWS OF MOSES GIVEN TO MOSES AS HE LED HIS PEOPLE OUT OF SLAVERY. WHAT POLITICIANS CAN'T FATHOM AND NEVER WILL IS THAT THERE ARE NO AMMENDMENTS TO THE TEN COMMANDMENTS.  GET SANTORUM TO THE FINISH LINE. YOU WON'T REGRET IT. MAYBE YOUR VOTE WILL COUNT.WWW.MEDIACRAPMATTERS.USWWW.CAPTAINSBLOG.USWWW.SPIRITOFAMERICAPARTYTADIOSHOW.COMYOUTUBE 911 DANNYBOYYOUTUBE FLAG BURNERS OF RECORDYOUTUBE I PLEDGE TO THEE BOYCOTT NBCOne Nation under Tim Tebowe, only fooling.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67j1nm</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ogrn</id></website><link>http://godfatherpolitics.com/4473/conservatives-being-locked-out-as-romney-ascends/</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T11:10:09+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-01T00:45:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0esfm</id><link>http://godfatherpolitics.com/4473/conservatives-being-locked-out-as-romney-ascends/#comment-482372107</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/citt7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>