<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/8134up/update/2011-03-08T23:02:30/39290b413f486a88d6408cf20cb703e64b11d89b2c96824eb041da5190c8c9be</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>"The College’s approach also includes an amnesty policy that allows students to seek medical care for alcohol-related illness with no fear of disciplinary action."

This is the policy on paper but here's the reality.  If you over-imbibe and go to UHS, even if you take yourself there, you will receive an email the next day from your Resident Dean requiring you to go in and talk about the incident.  You will then be sent to talk to Ryan Travia or one of the other people over at the Alcohol and Other Drug Services Office, where your drinking habits will be questioned, recorded and filed away.  You are told in no uncertain terms that if you do not do either of these things, you will be ad-boarded.  If this reoccurs one or two more times at any point in your college career, you will be asked (read: told) to take a leave of absence.

How is that not disciplinary action?  You tell us one thing but practice another.  After one experience with UHS, I will continue to drink but I will certainly never seek medical attention for alcohol from there for myself or any of my friends unless they literally stop breathing.  Instead I'll do the same thing a doctor would do: keep an eye on the drunk person, hydrate them, don't let them choke on their own Vomit.  Worst case scenario, I'd take them in a taxi to Boston where we'd be out of the Deans' Reach.  My experience with UHS has taught me one thing only: don't trust the Harvard administration.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/5cjgk8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ags</id></website><link>http://www.thecrimson.com/article/2011/3/8/alcohol-drinking-students-more/</link><postedTime>2011-03-08T05:12:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-03-09T04:02:30+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/8134up</id><link>http://www.thecrimson.com/article/2011/3/8/alcohol-drinking-students-more/#comment-162806969</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-03-08</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>