<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xw1v/post/2012-03-29T14:14:50</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>To paraphrase Peter Drucker: 'The purpose of business enterprise is to serve societal (mass customer) needs. Society endows businesses with wealth-producing resources (e.g. capital and talent) in order to serve customers.  Profit does not explain or cause business behavior and business decisions, but rather attests to their validity.'

Purpose-serving businesses can do much more than sell stuff.   In the U.S., we have had enduring problems (societal needs) in energy, clean air, clean water, affordable healthcare, nutrition, education, transportation, homelessness, crime, poverty, substance abuse, waste management, resource conservation and more, for decades.  If, over the past four decades, any of these areas had improved as much as a tiny fraction of the convenience and cost per minute of a voice or data connection, or the cost per byte of data storage, or the cost per gigaflop of computational capability, then millions of additional people would have had the opportunity to contribute to the greater good -- i.e.  something much bigger than themselves.

Until business enterprises recognize that knowledge workers have practically unlimited capacity for productivity  in meaningful work, it will remain difficult for those who must work to keep food on the table and a roof over their head to "overthrow themselves".

Some who have been RIFed by their former employers have necessarily become independent contractors; but, they still must Depend on business enterprises for their livelihoods (engagements) and to cover the loss of their benefits, as well ... not very liberating, as they also have to spend time to maintain their pipeline of work.  Moreover, as knowledge workers, many must now compete directly with the global pool of talent, which includes many skilled workers with decidedly lower costs of living.

Umair, your post is Spot on. However, even purpose-seeking individuals will have a tough time getting out of the practical equivalent of indentured servitude.

r.melrose@vision21.us</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zlpce</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/mft1</id></website><link>http://blogs.hbr.org/haque/2012/03/overthrow_yourself.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:57:34+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:14:50+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xw1v</id><link>http://blogs.hbr.org/haque/2012/03/overthrow_yourself.html#comment-479715280</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/r9x0a</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>