<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3wspr/post/2012-03-30T02:28:21</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>we have a dog that's now 6 years old and we got him as a puppy. before we took him the people at the kennel told us he had been returned to them 3 times by 3 different people. my dad and sister took him to puppy school and he passed (the trainer actually wanted him trained for jumping competition because he's a high energy dog that can jump very high at a stand still, my dad had said no though because we don't want Riley to learn he can jump the fence).

most of the time he is a good dog, but he's a barker with bad separation Anxiety. he refuses to stay in a room by himself and will follow the last person out of them. when we went to have his picture taken with santa at petsmart my sister was holding him while i filled out the form and the second i had stepped just a few feet away he started barking and pulling the leash until i went back toward him, then he stopped and wagged his tail.

he also seems to be afraid of the wind and barks at the smallest sounds and at anyone that stands outside the gate (even us). he also has food issues, he barks at us when we're eating or tries to steal food  our plates and growls at us when we tell him no. i just don't know what to do about this. it can't be food aggression because we've trained him from his puppy days to not be. we can Reach into his food dish when he's eating and he lets us do whatever we want with his food dish and the food in it. this has only started up recently too.

when we wanted to rescue a Basenji from the pound that had gotten attached to my sister and i we had our dad come with us and Riley to meet the dog, Riley greeted the dog kindly with tail wagging, but the Basenji's hair was standing up from neck to tail, and tried snapping at him. very aggressive. after Riley ran away to hide behind my dad, the Basenji came over and jumped up on me wagging his tail, but i was so stunned at his reaction to Riley that i stepped back. they tried to get the dog to greet Riley friendly again but he reacted the same way. 

my sister had her eyes set on a Pug mix too, so they brought that little dog in to meet Riley, but this time Riley stayed behind my dad, when my dad tried to get Riley to meet the Pug mix Riley started to growl at the Pug. obviously Riley was afraid of the little dog (which is strange since Riley is large dog. the person supervising even made a comment, saying "for such a large dog he's coward"). the Basenji isn't the first aggressive dog Riley has met (there was another dog before the Basenji). now i'm kinda worried because Riley has NEVER growled at another dog before. could it just have been because we tried to have him meet another strange dog so soon after an aggressive one? the Pug was not aggressive at all but Riley seemed so afraid of him. 

as for the Basenji, when we were walking back to the cages to put him back, he started crying and howling when we stepped out the door. we couldn't help but feel guilty as he seemed to have attached himself so strongly to us after we spent a few hours with him the day before we brought Riley in. after we left i just kept thinking about his face when he jumped up on me, wanting me to pet him and i wanted to go back so bad to say goodbye. we had checked up on the Basenji and found that others had tried a meet and greet with their dogs and he had reacted the same way, growling and snapping.

about a month after that we had the santa pictures trip. Riley seemed fine and friendly again, no aggression towards other dogs, he only showed a little fear when a Great Dane came up to him and sniffed him, but even then, he only stepped back, no growling or an other aggressive reactions. does this mean he only showed aggression towards the Pug mix because it was so soon after the Basenji? i'm just worried that those two dogs behavior might affect Riley's way of interacting with other dogs.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6cymua</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/u68i</id></website><link>http://www.dogster.com/lifestyle/euthanasia?_view=all</link><postedTime>2012-03-14T00:55:06+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T06:28:21+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3wspr</id><link>http://www.dogster.com/lifestyle/euthanasia?_view=all#comment-480319391</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-14</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>