<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5iwxkd/update/2011-08-23T14:33:56/ebddb020dd719596ac62dbceae1530992a02d71b5992b6ef52e40cbe0f467273</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I'm a Registered Nurse, I'm also a Burn survivor who has clocked a lot of time as a patient. I admit, there's a lot hospitals can do to improve the patient experience, but you are not staying in a hotel. You're staying in a hospital. There ARE hospitals that provide a more "luxurious" patient experience, BUT, you're going to pay more money for those. I saw nowhere in your blog where you offered to pay additionally to have this experience. So if you're not willing to do that, you're going to continue to have the same experience. The government is cutting the payments hospitals receive at least yearly. So if a hospital is going to chose between state of the art equipment and art in the rooms, or fine linens, the choice is relatively easy.

I work for a non profit, public hospital, and honestly, your blog was hurtful. I often change linens on my patients up to 8 to 10 times a day. Sometimes more. Not the CNA, me, your nurse. So all of those linens should be high quality? If you're hearing shrieking, yelling, and carts, you're probably hearing an emergency taking place while someone fights for their life. I like to joke that I do more by 7 AM than the Marines do by 9. It's not really a joke. By an hour and a half into my shift, I have probably bathed, medicated, charted, and started discharging the 5 people whose lives are in my hands. Or if I don't have discharges, I'm doing wound care, teaching, and charting, charting, charting.

My hospital did make big changes several years ago. We added room service style dining, which has improved how my patients eat. This was huge, and involved a lot of hiring by my hospital. Again. Public. Charity. Hospital. I'm so  my patients can eat when they feel like it, but hospitals don't get increased reimbursements by increasing how "nice" the hospital stay was. We also work hard to prepare patients for discharge from admission onward, which helps to discharge people when they, and their families are ready. We've placed noise cancelling tiles in the ceilings to help contain noise from the nurse's station. We also changed our art. Every piece of art in my hospital was donated by the employees of the hospital. It saved our hospital a ton of money, and showcases the abilities of our employees.

Please remember, this is our JOB. You don't want to hear a nurse laugh at the nurse's station? You don't laugh at work? Are you the same patient who is going to complain that your nurse wasn't friendly enough? We understand that these are some of the hardest days of your life, but I also expect that you and your fellow patients do NOT create a hostile work environment for myself by causing me physical or emotional harm. As a nurse, I've been punched, I've hurt myself catching a Fainting patient who ignored my request to use his call light. I'll have pain the rest of my life. This is the job. I'm not going to stop laughing when a brief moment of  comes by, and if I need help because someone might be dying, I'm going to hit alarms and yell until I get enough people in the room.

A good hospital stay? At my hospital? Getting your surgery, getting in and out without added infection.  being on dry, clean, linen, even if it isn't the best quality. Not getting a pressure sore because your nurse had time to make sure you were changing your position when you were too groggy or ill to do so. Getting discharged early in the day so you have plenty of time to get home and get settled, and not discharge during rush hour. Frequent purposeful rounding to make sure you don't have to hit the call light to go to the bathroom, get pain meds, getting your water refilled.

Forget what you've heard about bringing candy to your bedside. I don't eat anything that comes out of a patient room, and I round on my patients hourly regardless of how friendly or unfriendly they are. I push myself to check on unpleasant patients MORE frequently because they tend to be the people who crash, which requires a lot of shrieking and running and clamor. Evidence based practice is encouraging frequent rounding so patients KNOW a healthcare provider will be in each hour to check on them.

I will give my list of suggestions to people who go to the hospital for an elective procedure.

1) If you have to pay for a private room, try to save and do it. Bring your own pillow, and don't let anyone take the pillow case.

2)Ask your nurse or CNA to use bacteria killing wipes on your bath basin before giving you a bath.

3)If you have someone who can stay with you and encourage you, have them there. (make sure your hospital allows this ahead of time)

4)DO limit the number of visitors you're going to get. If you're not walking, not doing your breathing exercises, or blocking the nurse from assessing you because you have 5+ people in the room who refuse to leave, your stay WILL be extended. You WILL be worn out from attempting to play hostess to a parade of people. They can come see you AT HOME.

5) Don't hand out the nurse's station phone number to everyone you know. Don't hand out your privacy code to everyone you know. Select one or two people and have them disseminate information among your family and friends. I've gotten more than 20 family phone calls in a 12 hour shift. If each phone call is only 5 minutes long, well, you do the math.

6) My last request. If you see your doctor or nurse, coat on, bag in hand, don't ask that person to go get you items. Use your call light. They are leaving because the next shift is there.  When we put on our coats, when we walk out of the hospital, that's when we pull ourselves out of the hospital headspace and try to shake Off the day as we head home to make dinner, do laundry, make beds, and see our families. Please don't stop us. Let us go. Most of us have less than twelve hours to get home, rest, and come back to caring for you and your loved ones.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/e5yoxw</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/qj7o</id></website><link>http://www.kevinmd.com/blog/2011/07/hospital-comfortable-patients.html</link><postedTime>2011-07-27T14:02:58+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-08-23T18:33:56+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5iwxkd</id><link>http://www.kevinmd.com/blog/2011/07/hospital-comfortable-patients.html#comment-293867828</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yt9kk</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-07-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>