<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzdzv/post/2012-03-30T14:19:12</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>THEORETICAL PROBLEM FOR SUBSTANCE DUALISTS.

 The following is not meant to be a trap, just a genuine inquiry into how those of you who believe 1. consciousness does not  upon the brain and 2. some NDE`s occur during neural flat lining, can reconcile the two positions.

 Let me elaborate.

 One of the most obvious arguments for the notion that consciousness is dependent on the physical brain is the observation that it literally Vanishes when the brain enters particular physical states ( eg non dream sleep, deep anaesthesia ). To all appearances then, consciousness is not a separate enduring entity, but emerges from an appropriate type of brain activity and disappears again when this activity ceases.

 First question; if you are a substance dualist, how do you account for periods of Unconsciousness?

 Now the most commonly suggested solution to the above problem is the very counter intuitive one that we are in fact never unconscious  (though our physical bodies may be still and inert ), but that to remember something  in our waking state, a memory impression must be made on both the immaterial mind and the physical brain, and this just cannot occur for the brain when it is not in an appropriate physical state. In other words, upon physically waking up we experience complete amnesia of our experiences while apparently unconscious  (during which time we would be employing the memory forming capacities of our mind only ).

 Now the above may logically be correct, but then we would experience complete amnesia of our NDE adventures if they occurred during neuronal flat lining, as in this state the brain could clearly not lay down memories ( though presumably the disembodied mind could ).

 So...you cannot believe rationally in both the amnesia theory of apparent Unconsciousness and that NDE`s occur during neuronal flat lining. If the latter could be demonstrated, it would disprove the former. What I am curious to know is how those of you who harbour hope that NDE`s offer evidence of an afterlife explain periods of Unconsciousness.

 </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6m3wfy</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcf8</id></website><link>http://www.skeptiko.com/165-dr-caroline-watt-defends-there-is-nothing-paranormal-about-near-death-experiences/</link><postedTime>2012-03-20T15:09:18+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:19:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzdzv</id><link>http://www.skeptiko.com/165-dr-caroline-watt-defends-there-is-nothing-paranormal-about-near-death-experiences/#comment-481034248</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>