<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3441x/post/2012-03-29T10:59:56</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>It takes a government to screw things up totally. For actual civil war to break out, things would have to get so bad politically, economically and socially, that brute force would be seen as the only viable method of reigning in the outlaw elements.  And, when it comes right down to the flash point, where bullets fly and people die, it is the fanatic who readily opts for war, anarchy, chaos and destruction.  And, can you imagine the absolute insanity that would exist if this nation went to war with itself?  No boundary lines - few supply lines - military intervention via martial law - perhaps even paramilitary organizations to to the dirty work - not to mention a host of scumbag predator nations gleefully aiding the bloodletting.  It would be a nightmare of death, destruction, disease and agony - and dare it be said, there won't be healing anytime during the 21st century.
There is another danger - that certain factions that want to tear down this nation are underestimating the Resolve and - forgive me for saying this - the Cold-blooded attitude that compels killing the enemy - them - as many as quickly as possible.  That's war - and it's mankind at his worst.  Unfortunately, that's what it takes now and then in the course of human events.  Let's hope we can avoid it. 

  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zcqqy</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yv37</id></website><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/2012/03/m-the_republic_if_we_can_keep_it.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T06:13:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:59:56+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3441x</id><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/2012/03/m-the_republic_if_we_can_keep_it.html#comment-479554581</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/r7v8c</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>