<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkh8rk/post/2012-03-25T14:18:49</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mnyf3l</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/csntp</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> The following Black towns were either obliterated  the face of the map or Blacks pushed out/terrorized by evil, jealous Whites because they were successful:

-Fort Mose, FL (North of St. Augustine),
-Rosewood, F L
-Seneca Village, NY (settlement destroyed to make way for Central Park.  Both Irish and Africans lived there in peace -something I'm sure you could NEVER abide by could you?)
- Five Points District, NY - lower Manhattan. Despite the depiction as told by Whites only in "Gangs of NY", when the various groups came here to occupy the area they met Africans here who BUILT IT in the first place just  like they built the wall on Wall street and fought on both sides of the way and were ENTREPRENEURS in and of course had to fight every day of their lives to survive.  
- Weeksville, NY- Brooklyn, NY - Established by freed Blacks.  They had to run there after all the lynchings, rapings and horror stories of the fabled "fighting Irish" who sought to do this to the BLACKS THEY MET HERE ALREADY during the draft riots in 1861 during the Civil War. 
- Greenwood, OK- Negro Wall Street.  Because this area was filled with too many successful descendants of  Africans who were too ambitious and the poor Whites especially couldn't do for themselves they decided to get in planes and throw malotov cocktails from above reminiscent of WWI and Burn down the homes only AFTER THESE WHITES LOOTED THE HOMES/BUSINESS OF THESE SUCCESSFUL BLACKS who would have been happy to live amongst themselves and never see a White face again as long as they lived.  But NOOOOO as much as the lot of you can't stand us you just can't help but stick your nose where it's unwanted can't you?  Now everywhere you see us you want us out of there!  

-Freedman's Village, VA- destroyed to make way for Arlington National Cemetery and part of the Pentagon

- Allensworth, CA- set up by Col. Allensworth to be an All Black settlement so that we could live in peace but of course evil Whites decided to  that water lines would not go there and cut Off the Santa Fe railroad line to the town.  So of course it's now a state park. 

- Freedman's Town, TX - lots of freed slaves bought land and built homes here.  It was the Great Depression that did the most damage because if White American catches a Cold, Black America catches pneumonia!  

-Davis Bend, Miss. - established by slaves.  Once again a poor economy and maniacal Whites interfere.  The founders son established  a town nearby.  I'll bet some of your greedier, more sinister cohorts would like to gentrify that out for the fun of it. 

- Muchakinock, Iowa - Blacks were recruited to work in coal mines.  Of course they established communities but once the company failed, that community was disassembled. 

-Buxton, Iowa - Majority Black town where Blacks held office, etc. but once the demand for coal lessened the town died.  Blacks were able to live in peace there which I'm sure rankles some people. 

- New Philadelphia, Ill. - Pioneer town that would have thrived but of course the railroad was kept from coming there by (roll the drum please) Whites, the town eventually declined. 

- Pin Oak Co., Ill. - small township established in 1818 to fuel western expansion and tortured the Native Indians because everything jealous Whites set their eyes on they seek to destroy. After the Civil War many moved to other areas. 

-Blackdom, NM - established by Blacks who did quite well until severe drought caused them to abandon the town.  I'm sure they town they went to was fillled with miserable White who took a delight in torturing them.  

Now the above commentary was not for all  White folks, but only for the miserable ones like YOU who continually come on our sites and troll around where you're both unwanted and have absolutely nothing to add.  I just want you to know that since your kind can't  seem to leave us alone in our areas even to this day in 2012 we have no choice but to be a thorn in your side.  One fine day you won't be the majority here.  Hope to live to see it.  Don't worry APaige I'll be fair, I'll tell the truth, the Whole Truth and NOTHING BUT THE TRUTH about the history of your people in this stolen nation ESPECIALLY on National Native American Day when Native People worldwide talk about your contribution to their demise and about the others who tried to stop it.  Since there are more people of color in the world than you, it will be interesting to see your voices ignored, drowned out and to see us, the majority on your discussion boards putting our two cents in.  Interesting future don't you think?  


 </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ys0kbh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t26w</id></website><link>http://newsone.com/newsone-original/abanjoko/san-fran-youth-in-a-state-of-perpetual-grief/</link><postedTime>2012-03-05T17:28:40+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-25T18:18:49+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkh8rk</id><link>http://newsone.com/newsone-original/abanjoko/san-fran-youth-in-a-state-of-perpetual-grief/#comment-475940875</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mrsn9</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-05</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>