<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miyu0z/post/2012-03-22T20:51:59</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Okay, I need to say this: stop trying to qualify Zimmerman's race, everyone.  Firstly, it doesn't change what he did, and a Latino man shooting a black kid in Cold, racist blood is no better than a white guy doing it. 
People who keep pulling the "he's not racist because of his relatives" stuff--junk it. Junk it now. You can be a minority and be racist to other minorities. It's how some mentally give themselves a leg up. 
Also, you can be both white and Hispanic at the same time. That's why the selection on the FCAT has white-non Hispanic as an option. You can also be a very dark-skinned kid with Japanese blood or a blond-haired blue-eyed kid whose parents both emigrated from the Middle East (and for the record, I've met both)
Likewise with the "I think he's Jewish because of how his name is spelled" thing up there. It doesn't matter if he is or is not--he killed a boy in Cold blood whether he's Jewish, Evangelical, Catholic, Hindu, or whatever religion you can put. 
I do not deny this was a RACIST killing, which makes me so upset with people looking at Zimmerman's race or ethnicity or speculated religion like it changes anything. He was a racist who killed a boy. Possibly-being a minority does not change that, if it had been an Asian-American man killing a black kid like that I'd be just as furious. If it had been a black guy killing a Latino kid. Or an Italian-American killing an Irish American. A blonde white woman shooting a brunette kid. I can keep going.
Hate crime can be done by anyone and it is worse than the 'normal' crime itself. Stop Acting like some tiny fact about Zimmerman's race or religion could change everything. That has no beaing on the case and I'm so tires of hearing "what race is he" or "it wasn't racist because he's actually part minority/related to a minority". 
It was racist, it was a hate crime, it was MURDER, and this man should be in jail. That is all there is to it. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ybcfy</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ydw9</id></website><link>http://motherjones.com/node/168681</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T16:19:16+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T00:51:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miyu0z</id><link>http://motherjones.com/node/168681#comment-474102698</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/he54u</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>