<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mibo2k/update/2012-03-23T15:07:20/d5a62783bf5710f4a58259c764e1357f603d90dc7a91e78423e0a7de02d54925</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mixkuw</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>So you believe that once our Star, the Sun, continues to get hotter as it ages and grows from a Yellow Star (what it is now), into a Giant Red Star, which is a much, much larger and hotter version of our little Yellow Star, a process that we think will take anywhere between 1-4 billion years for this transformation to take full effect; That we will not be inhabiting the Planet because there will be no solid land to stand on due to it all having melted away, literally, because of the vast amount Heat felt from our Giant Red Star? And then from there, our Sun will either  Super Nova, or become a White Dwarf? If it becomes Super Nova, it will then either become a Neutron Star, or a Black Hole? If it becomes a White Dwarf, it will stay as so? At this point in time, all of our Planets will stabilize at a nice cool temperature because our Star will only be roughly the size of Earth today, and barely generate enough Heat to start a basic fire? And if it becomes a Black Hole, then it will suck everything in around it?

So you pretty much agree with what 99.99% of all scientist's think today. Even though none of them have seen this process take place from beginning to end. They have only captured glimpses of varying solar systems within their varying stages of existence.

I'm merely proposing some other ideas to provoke a bit of different thought on the subject.

It's rather obvious to me the Earth has been growing. I find it strange that people don't think about this more often. We both cannot argue that our Planet was indeed smaller when Dinosaurs roamed. Correct? You also mentioned that our Planet only grows due to whatever meteorites hit our surface. Would it not also grow due to all of the life that is on it, which then dies? Think of it in this way. A seed is planted, and then grows into a giant redwood. That redwood did not subtract from an equal amount of mass from the Earth in order to  that size. But when it dies, it does indeed add its additional mass back into our planets mass. This same theory can be said for all other living things. Like the billions of people for example. This is one way that the Earth is expanding is size.

Another idea for what is occurring would be considered as silly as believing in God, to some. And that is that our Earth is as alive as we are. It's location within our solar system, expanding at a rate that is quicker than the rate of the expansion (growth) of our Sun. We have absolutely no other planet to compare to ours. We are as unique as is as far as we can see. Our planet, Acts and behaves in every way that  nearly every other complex chemical compositions do. That is, it mimics operational behaviors similar to other living organisms here on Earths surface. Therefore, if we grow, and Earth is alive as well, then why would it &lt;u&gt;not&lt;/u&gt; grow as well? One things for sure. You have no other planet within any other solar system to back up any other claim otherwise.

&lt;b&gt;Source:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;i&gt;I am a visionary.&lt;/i&gt;</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6681ly</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5zaa</id></website><link>http://www.tgdaily.com/node/62271</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T09:21:08+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T19:07:20+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mibo2k</id><link>http://www.tgdaily.com/node/62271#comment-474714463</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>