<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mje2r9/update/2012-03-19T07:45:56/333fb683648858d33de312b95a0265aedf924b90b41a7477b26cbfcb54eb9969</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I was struck by the line “people treat her love of teaching as a naïve preoccupation, one that she’ll outgrow once she’s in the real world.”  Something I've observed in the course of my long career is while some colleagues Burn out, others grow to increasingly love teaching.  I have theories about why this is so, but here I’m simply going to point out that if you’re an effective teacher you get rewards and positive feedback every day in class and in other interactions with students.  The rewards and feedback for research and publishing are much more likely to be few and far between.  Yes, a solid publication record tends to lead more quickly to tenure and promotion and the value of these is not to be denied, but on a day-in and day-out basis, the Joys of teaching can be vastly more fulfilling.  My last book took eight years of dogged work and two and half years later the reviews still trickle in, each giving me a brief bump of pleasure.  But a class full of students with wide eyes, papers that show intellectual growth, and visits from former students who tell me how my class affected them come consistently, and provide me with vastly more satisfaction than anything I’ve written.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6e1fj3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/b0vv</id></website><link>http://www.insidehighered.com/node/36504</link><postedTime>2012-03-19T01:11:14+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-19T11:45:56+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mje2r9</id><link>http://www.insidehighered.com/node/36504#comment-468893222</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-19</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>