<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwcjjj/update/2012-03-30T05:13:40/14e285865d25cede0b0c5e38247fd8ac552fe9b5666a422c75a860d99e35fe6b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Syrian Network for Human Rights Report | Casualty Report

Thursday, 29 March 2012

[FORMAT: Victim number. Victim Name (City, age (if available), Method of Killing (if available)]

The Syrian Network for Human Rights documented 49 victims killed by the regime’s forces on Thursday, the majority of them Homs and Idlib.

Dar’aa Province | 6
1. Bilal Ismail Al-Nassar (member of the Free Syrian Army)
2. Mohammed Al-Heraki (defected soldier killed in Al-Qusair, Homs)
The regime’s forces Burned a building where four young men from Alma and As-Soora were hiding, killing all four of the young men:
3. Abdallah Ahmed Al-Hariri (As-Soora)
4. Omar Ra’aid Al-Hamidi
5. Ismaat Hamid Haroub
6. Alaa Foua’d Al-Hariri
http://youtu.be/yXrVtiFjpv4
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yB8bZ_P_H9g&amp;feature=youtu.be 

Idlib Province | 11
1. Ahmed Amouri Al-Sheikh Mohammed (Talmns) http://youtu.be/m9SjKNRdRgw
2. Khawada Abdel Hadi Abdel Majeed, female (Talmns, Ma’arat An-Numan)
3. Hamdo Saleem Al-Issa, male-child (Jerjanaz, killed by a mortar)
4. Ahmed Mohammed Gameil Al-Abd Al-Salam (Al-Ghadafa, 17)
5. Mohammed Wasel Dayoub (tortured to death)
6. Colonel; Fouad Abdul Salam (Taftaz, killed in Aleppo)
7. Ammar Ahmed Shaaban (Saraqib)
8. Mohammed Saleh Shamrokhi (Saraqib)
9. Mahmoud Al-Ibrahim (Saraqib, died from his wounds)
10. Mussab Husain Haj Ismail (Saraqib)
11. Six month old unidentified baby from Jerjanaz

Homs Province | 17
1. Unidentified old man because the body is in the street and the residents cannot  it
2. Iman Hori Al-Tellawi (Bab-Al-Sebaa, killed, shot by regime’s forces at a checkpoint)
3. Yahya Abdel Razaq Sabouh (Baba Amr) https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=350636854972426&amp;set=a.232721470097299.51488.222839144418865&amp;type=1
4. Anas Abdallah Hamat (Old Homs) http://youtu.be/ItpRaZbIRwY
https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=244412258988301&amp;set=a.182608958501965.38366.182241635205364&amp;type=1&amp;ref=nf
5. Amaar Abdel Halim Jamoul
6. Abdel Hameed Ridwan Al-Awad (Arrjoun killed by a mortar) http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wvG3j1mH-tE
7. Fatima Bakdash (Arrjoun, female)
8. Ahmed Al-Hamad (Baba Amr)
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m8uoXxG-2bI
9. A child transported to a hospital in Lebanon to treat his wounds died ten minutes after arrival
10. Sumaa Musa Al-Damour (Talbisah, 47, female, died from her wounds)
11. Mahmoud Al-Jadei Saleh Al-Omar (Al-Wa’ar, male, 17)
12. Yahya Ahmed Al-Dalibi Al-Omar (Al-Wa’ar, male, 16)
13. Salibi Al-Salibi Al-Omar (Al-Wa’ar, male, 31)
14. Giath Juria (Wadi Al-Arab) http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XQPyH89Xjj4
15. Anas Al-Sofi (Wadi Al-Arab)
16. Raeid Zaarour (Al-Qosoor neighbourhood)
17. Abdel Hadi Al-Sheikh (Al-Qosoor neighbourhood, shot by a sniper)

Damascus Province | 3
1 – 2. Security forces planted a bomb in a taxi cab, killing at least two people during the same time of the Arab Summit in Iraq. They orchestrated this attack near the Daraya Conditioning Company. After the attack, gunfire was heard. Not even minutes after, state-sponsored television channel crews were on the scene filming in order to weave a web of further propaganda. The area where the explosion was orchestrated had been sealed Off by the regime’s forces since early Thursday morning by brick checkpoints, as reported by activists living in the area.
3. Muhammad Ahmad Ghanem (shot to death by the regime’s forces during a peaceful demonstration)

Hama Province | 5
1. Dr. Mohammed Abdel Rrahman Omar (Al-Madeiq)
2. Habib Al-Turk
3. Mohammed Hamadi
4 – 5. Two unidentified young men were killed when a mortar fell on their motorcycle (Ain Altaqa Village)

Aleppo Province | 5
1. Abdo Ismail (Izaz, shot by a sniper)
2. Mohammed Ahmed Al-Kabisi (male, 14)
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T6-UEURbt8o&amp;feature=share
3. Mohammed Sheikho (Izaz, shot by a sniper)
4. Anwar Kazalo (Izaz)
5. Mohammed Ahmed Aakoush (Al-Atarib, shot by regime’s forces)

----------------------------------------------------
الشبكة السورية لحقوق الإنسان - لندن
Syrian Network for Human Rights - London
Website: www.syrianhr.org
Email: press@syrianhr.org
Skype: Syrianhr
----------------------------------------------------
Working to protect human rights in Syria
DISCLAIMER
This email has been sent by the Syrian Network for Human Rights in London. Internet communications are not secure and therefore the Syrian Network for Human Rights does not accept legal responsibility for the contents of this message. If you are not the intended recipient you must not disclose or rely on the information in this e-mail. Any views or opinions presented are solely those of the author and do not necessarily represent those of the Syrian Network for Human Rights unless specifically stated. Electronic communications including email might be monitored by Syrian Network for Human Rights for operational or business reasons.
This email has been scanned by the Symantec Email Security.cloud service.
For more information please visit http://www.symanteccloud.com</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zsoxz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/m70c</id></website><link>http://www.enduringamerica.com/home/2012/3/30/syria-wired-the-latest-from-social-media-and-eas-readers.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T06:53:59+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T09:13:40+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwcjjj</id><link>http://www.enduringamerica.com/home/2012/3/30/syria-wired-the-latest-from-social-media-and-eas-readers.html#comment-480546135</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g5x7z</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>