<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kwny/post/2012-03-29T23:01:46</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Ok, Ok Sam41 &amp; Dollarbillphil. Maybe I am incoherent, I haven't re-read what I wrote, since you both said I am incoherent. So I hope that what I present will come out better. Maybe I really have been feeling high. By now you guys know that I am Jamaican, so maybe this energy thing that I have been on is really having the ability to mystically send a trail of weed through the air! (lol) I don't know how to explain it, but I just see and feel that a new day is really  and I guess I really went overboard trying to make others aware that we can start feeling hopeful again. I have  said I write for the young person who might come on these sites, and want to hear something different from what he's  been told. It took me most of my life to lose feelings of: hopelessness, uselessness, shame, and fear of God's wrath. You don't spend 45 years experiencing crippling depression and repeated Suicidal thoughts, and now get high on life, once you kicked depression by changing the way you think. I get mad a lot that I didn't know about these free things before; and it amazes me that my two sons survived my parenting and ended up sane and and whole. Of course they had a father in their lives. 

In any case, when I was depressed (in a country away from family) they really got a raw deal. So I guess I respond to the pain of young black men from the position of a woman who understands how these kids are often doomed from absent parents, who may be in the home everyday, but not really there in mind. Coming from Jamaica with the same or worse conditions for young black men seem to bother me a lot more than it bother some I know. I can't help it. Its just my nature, except now it doesn't get me depressed. From my personal experience I know that many mothers really need help that others around them fail to see. Many of us in that position are seen as strong because in spite of all the dysfunctions in our minds, we  seem to work, even if sporadically as in my case. I believe that its Ida B. Wells or another of those great women who once said she wished she could collect her people and fly away with them from the oppression she saw. That is how I used to feel everyday about the plight of young black men. Maybe its guilt, that I could've done a lot better with my two, and now they're grown, I need to find others to impart things to, that would help them better negotiate life at their youthful age. I know that they're really good inside, but they're in situations that just beat them down, and the elders around them are beaten down too. 

Maybe I get on my soapbox, because I know without a shadow of doubt that its our hearts that we need to work on first. I didn't make any significant changes until I overcame my fear of God, and letting go of God completely and feeling no more Anxieties about it, or having even the least doubt about it, did not happen in one shot. I know the struggle that one goes through to let go of that nonsense. And I am quite sure that I deliberately display irreverence, because I want those young persons to understand that they're not going to be struck down dead if they follow their minds. I never believed the abundant nonsense that I was taught, but could get no one to even entertain the questions I had about God. Had I just had one person to listen to me and talk about God, growing up in Jamaica, the dysfunction and wasted life I endured would not have occurred. And then again, maybe it also has to do with caring for the elderly in their homes. People with more money than God I jokingly tell them sometimes, yet they're on all kinds of medication for Anxiety, depression and you name it. It blew my mind that people who could've been so good at accumulating wealth and God, got to the end of their lives and are so unhappy, while I come into their lives as the complete opposite without a penny but telling them that I am happier and younger the more years I add.

As I see these things I have come to know that something is wrong about how we've been taught to live our lives. Sure money and faith in something is important. But what good is all of those if people just accept it as normal to get worse in body and mind as they add years. I am here to say its not necessary, and if young people could start thinking that way, they'd have less fear that leads them into crimes. I see black people all over the world having such short lifespans while so indulged in God. I see everyone thinking that we should all be on pills once we hit age 50 and our hair should be white and we should be hobbling about. I see these things and know without a shadow of doubt that people are not being taught to think right, so maybe I get high in trying to impart what I know without a shadow of doubt. So honestly guys, if I sound incoherent and like a kid, maybe I'd knocked Off a couple more decades of age and didn't realize. If not we'll just blame it on P.M.S. and I'll try to be a bit more respectful to people's sky God. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zq95i</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ewhe</id></website><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/trayvon-martin/trayvon-martin-case-frank-taaffe.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:02:34+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T03:01:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kwny</id><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/trayvon-martin/trayvon-martin-case-frank-taaffe.php#comment-480181689</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ahv96</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>