<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/migpxl/post/2012-03-22T16:35:46</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I've Always believed liberals were the new fascists and they prove it every day. In fact, the 20th Century demonstrated that big government socialists, commies, national socialists Nazis, and new age progressives have a common modus operandi of lying their way into power and then for the sake of their emerging "utopia" they silence anyone else who doesn't bow the knee before their statist ideology.

BTW, American liberals are the biggest patronizing, paternalistic racists on the planet. That's the reason they built the entitlement plantation at taxpayer expense, to warehouse their most dependable voters. Liberal bigots never miss a chance at demonizing conservatives and Republicans with utter trash that they themselves are guilty of ... it's called projection. And it's these same Bleeding-heart tightwads who define their alleged "compassion" by how much they can empower government to fleece taxpayers in hopes of birthing their abominable "utopia". Liberalism fails when it runs out of other people's money. Liberals give true liberalism a bad name. The founding fathers were liberals in that they believed in individualism, that the state has limited powers, that our unalienable rights are a gift from God and cannot be taken away by a stroke of the pen (the First and Second Amendment rights being the most fundamental rights after life and liberty itself), and true power rests in the People themselves and not in overreaching government that can kick in doors or tax a person into oblivion. Modern liberals embrace bureaucratic fascism which is a more antiseptic way of stealing everyone else's birthright and wealth. Liberals worship covetousness, envy and entitlement under the banner of "social justice." </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y4m1z</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zmzu</id></website><link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2012/mar/22/radio-campaign-next-step-against-rush-limbaugh/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T13:20:42+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T20:35:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/migpxl</id><link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2012/mar/22/radio-campaign-next-step-against-rush-limbaugh/#comment-473923344</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h8xhi</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>