<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/myqqzv/update/2012-02-14T17:05:42/ad93b2e64a86611f45eab212b37f76532fbda3a57eb324a5f8d5240302e9d20c</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>
I have started to believe that it is tough to make friends once you left the college, specifically in US. I have studied in Canada more than a half decade and moved to Chicago  4 months ago, because there are much better opportunities for professionals with advanced degrees in technical fields. Indeed, I have found a job I would like to advance, but the atmosphere made me sick both at work and outside the work and could not survive the probation period eventually.
Being alone and not having friends and family in the city was an added struggle. I had to visit my physciatrist twice already in 3 months. I feel extremely upset that I lost my job, and I am back home now, on the other hand, I also feel relieved that I do not have to take depressing office enviroment with white cubicles, very narrow windows, white flouresenct lights, white tiles; and very boring lunctimes in white and Cold cafeteria with my manager (with lower degree than mine) who have exhibited chain of wierd attitudes after I have asked one hour early leave (I was coming one hour earlier in the morning and leaving late most of the time) to rent an apartment and other executive stuff including fake HR manager with her fake husband exported from far east in expense of US passport or a secretary who was watching me throwing the garbage to the wrong bin and only socialize with other simple-minded people. I do not even want to count the other very low educated technical personnel (as opposed to my shiny PhD Degree) who sees me entering the lunch-room but turns the head as I sit the table, never say hi/bye in a firm with less than 30 employees in spite of sitting across my cubicle, or stare at me from the far end of the room while I was filling my plate with free food offered during  meeting.

I did not have the opportunity to try to make friends and apply what has been suggested above, however, after I breath the workplace, and be the target of improper intentions of a few people I traded business on craiglist, I do not have much regret. All along my 15 hrs flight, I have imagined what if? as in the movie sliding doors but could not find a resolution, although I have played the the scenorios over and over again in my mind. It is though to make friends in North America and most of the people stick their old friends like high school friends or families after leaving college. Being  quite open-minded it is though to be around simple-minded people who marries, makes kids and perfect houses with trimmed bushes and tons of other details meticioulsy maintained every single day and it is that depressive to know that your young collique relates being not married and having not kids a right time to go to grad school (especially seeing that she is overweight and not supergorgeous to be grabbed in the air very soon in addition to being restricted to pick prospective husband and baby giver among small group of guys due to the ethhnical reasons.) 

There were many friendly buddies in my building but they are mostly very old and not even functioning properly. They were also very lonely like me and I have sensed that they were sitting or hanging around the lobby to say hi and bye to whoever comes and goes through the doors, inside the elevators, outside the elevators enthusiastically. I felt good at the beginning and had the illusion that people in my building are friendly. Then, I have realized it is because they are old, really old. I was bumping into some younger people, they were nicely saluting, but it seemed hard to initiate friendship since they are busy and not really as professional as I am. I am modest, however you would like to be surrounded by people who have similiar mind  as mine to be understood and not feel so awkward while asking yourself am I a good fit in this city?. One incident made me really ignore old people even specifically avoid them.. One day I was coming from home happily after I have visited whole foods and exposed to very intellectual neighbourhood called Oak Park. I was couple of walks away from the enterance of my apartment with a smile in my face and heavy canvas bag filled with natural food in my shoulder. Then, I saw they were carrying a someone on hospital bed. Immediately noticing that the whole body and the face is coverd with faked red blanked and black long car, I have concluded it was a dead body. I turned back and walked away faster with a punch in my stomach and a heart rate, entered from the back door.There was a fear and worry in the girls face from housing office. I was about to say that some one has died and then I wanted to hide in my apartment. It was sickening to feel that a dead body passed that loby minutes ago. In the elevator, there were white cotton pieces and bandages on the floor. They were definitely dropped from a body, maintained with difficulty and no effort has been made in rush or confusion to pick them. I have tempted to took the other elevator, but I did not want to bump into some one from housing. Then I have entered my newly painted apartment with a stinky smell of the paint on empty walls. My heart rate was very high. My body was trembling and I have the similiar sense just before Fainting. My aparment without a soul  and my sunday night after a lonely weekend was depressing enough already! What the hell was that!,I was trying to get rid of panic attacks and Cheering my lonely life in that apartment. I have turned on the tv and started to calm down as I have watched some shows. That was the moment I did not want to get attached to older people in the building. That dead body might belong the guy who was sitting in the corner every night or a lady who carries her dog in babycar and once took my shot with a christmas tree mounted in the lobby whole through the month of December. These old people were dying and left there in these bachelor apartments to spend their last days until death and their son or son in law move their butts from the coach one cozy night in their amazing big houses as the phone rings to carry their bodies outside of my building through the elevators. That is why I did not want to attach them and be part of their life  more.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/cnlgr7</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/h7z4</id></website><link>http://www.lifehack.org/articles/communication/how-to-make-a-bunch-of-new-friends-in-any-new-city.html</link><postedTime>2008-11-24T13:00:24+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-14T22:05:42+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/myqqzv</id><link>http://www.lifehack.org/articles/communication/how-to-make-a-bunch-of-new-friends-in-any-new-city.html#comment-439291384</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hlaa0</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2008-11-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>