<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwn8wd/update/2012-03-30T19:15:01/76b119d402265ea925d5956ea03176e3dee6f6051002de482abc042b2f543c55</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwtvx8</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/590m5</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I do see your point as well. The issue is that the parent in question was NOT okay with a grown man having relations with her MINOR daughter. The real damage was done when a grown man took advantage of a young girl, willing or not. . Our children  need us to be in their corner whether to discipline when wrong and correct the bad behavior, or to be in their corner when wrong is done to them. Being a supposed mature adults, if it was true love, or what not, they should have respected the mother's wishes and waited until she was of consenting age, not hide it. Why do people hide things? Because they KNOW its is wrong.

You say that they were two young lovers and making her out to be a victim can create depression, etc. How about those who were conditioned to think something like this is okay and they are NOT victims. Depression, Anxiety, and thoughts of suicide will exist as well. I look at it this way, if it was MY child/children under MY roof, that I take care of and raise that I am responsible for Lord help the person who tries to take advantage of my children's young age they will wish they lived in Maine and gotten Off so light. All those that think it is okay for a grown man to sex up a child using the "she wanted it" excuse are sick. That excuse is what is used by 99% of serial rapists. 

I too respect everyone's opinions, while they are only opinions and everyone is entitled their two cents worth so again here are my 2 cents. (: </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zbd2g</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dngw</id></website><link>http://bangordailynews.com/2012/03/29/news/bangor/mother-unhappy-with-2-month-jail-sentence-for-daughters-sex-partner/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:51:51+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T23:15:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwn8wd</id><link>http://bangordailynews.com/2012/03/29/news/bangor/mother-unhappy-with-2-month-jail-sentence-for-daughters-sex-partner/#comment-481307120</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7yhm</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>