<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/324020/post/128003889/comment/329093174</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Thank you for posting this.  For the last week I have been writing a list of necessary expenses and the near impossibility of living a half decent life on a $1000/month budget to copy and send to state officials just for any feedback and recognition.  I have been living on my own since I was 14 and had to live a not so proud life in order to survive.  Needless to say I was incarcerated at 17 and when I was released at 21 I could finally join the work force because I honestly had no desire for the lifestyle I had to live.  With the only things on my resume being a GED and a criminal background my work options are very, very limited and the pay is Always small.  To be honest though it was easy to live under those conditions in the early 2000&amp;#039;s, I had a selection of cheap apartments in &amp;quot;bad&amp;quot; parts of town that could go as low as $150/month rent for 2 bedrooms and without a/c the utilities would usually amount to maybe as high as $150 all together when the weather demanded use of cooling or Heating.  That left plenty of play room for cable/internet and car necessities.  Whenever times got a little rough I could donate plasma for ~$200 a month and Im also handy with cars and working on houses so I coul also take an odd job here or there.&#13; 
&#13; 
But at some point that all came to a screeching halt.  Now the cheapest studio apt in town is $450 a month in the &amp;quot;gun shot&amp;quot; district and with the gas crisis you can kiss about $400 to $500 away just on gas and utilities.  Now I stay with 3 other roommates and although one of them is my best friend I&amp;#039;m miserable and unmotivated.  Maybe it&amp;#039;s my character flaw but I just can&amp;#039;t function right and I get easily frustrated when I&amp;#039;m constantly surrounded with other people.  I want to get a small place to myself again but even after I come out from the debt I accumulated when trying to hold on to my old place I look at what is available and I just don&amp;#039;t see it working.&#13; 
&#13; 
Thank you again for pointing this problem out and it has further motivated me to complete my letter and maybe, somehow, find out why it is that realtors have been deregulated. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:324020:128003889</id><idPostId>128003889</idPostId><idBlogId>324020</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:324020</id><idBlogId>324020</idBlogId><link>http://www.sooverdebt.com</link><displayName>So Over Debt</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.sooverdebt.com/how-do-people-survive-on-minimum-wage/</link><displayName>How Do People Survive on Minimum Wage?</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T09:11:29.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:324020:128003889:329093174</id><link>http://www.sooverdebt.com/how-do-people-survive-on-minimum-wage/#IDComment329093174</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T09:11:29.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on How Do People Survive on Minimum Wage? by Christopher</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>2e70c0d9066bbfaef5721283a44cb5a6</idEmailMd5><displayName>Christopher</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>Christopher commented on &lt;a href="http://www.sooverdebt.com/how-do-people-survive-on-minimum-wage/"&gt;How Do People Survive on Minimum Wage?&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>