<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4oov/post/2012-03-30T17:58:11</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>My message to the Supreme Court:
This country needs universal  health care – NOW. Before it is too late. 
The fact is, we ALL have pre-existing conditions. At some point, we all get sick and die. And a myriad of things happen to our bodies along the way. Those who manage to snag health care through an employer are lucky. But we are all just the loss of a job away from no health insurance - because our insane system ties our health care to our jobs. For no rational reason.  It just happened that way. This not only harms those of us who have no insurance through our jobs...but the whole economy because many people with insurance keep bad jobs and don't take new or innovative opportunities (particularly with small firms what cannot afford to offer health insurance). The loss of productivity because of this stupid system must be astounding. Not to mention the cost of the Anxiety most of us have over whether our health costs will be covered. I don't know about you, but I HATE to open any letter I care from my private health insurer -- I'm sure it's to tell me they won't cover this or that. I had a job with a university for 20 years. The pay was lousy and the hours long. But I had health insurance. I used to tell people, I was working for my health insurance, not a pay check (which was far less important). I turned down many other jobs that might have been better for me and the economy because I couldn’t afford to lose my health care –and most of these jobs didn’t offer health care.  The ONLY solution not only to the problem of 1/3 of Americans being uninsured -- many more under insured, and all of us potentially uninsured, is a single payer universal health care system that we carry with us throughout our lives wherever we go. We all pay into it, and we all use it when we need to. That's the whole point of insurance. You pay it and hope you never need to use it. People who don't want to pay because they think they are 'healthy' (and this is what the supreme court is deciding right now), have no right to opt out of this gamble. They are just as likely to become sick as anyone else; and when they do, SOMEONE will have to pay for their care. Thus, they MUST be in the system by virtue of being alive and living in our country. Once this system is in place, and we get rid of all the private middlemen and all the paperwork and bureaucracy and time spent on figuring all this out, and the pain and Anxiety and high cost of SO MANY people being uninsured or  underinsured -- we will see the costs come WAY down, the efficiency improve, and the happiness of Americans swell. Imagine being able to take any job you wanted -- anywhere in the country -- without the worry of whether you will have health insurance. Imagine walking into a doctors office and not spending an hour filling out forms and photocopying cards and making sure if this doctor or care unit accepts this insurance or that -- in this state or state. Imagine how much more time doctors can spend on health care and less on administration or worrying about bill collecting. Hospitals won’t have to spend all their time trying to bilk insured patients to pay for the uninsured or underinsured. It is so obvious and clear and it is the ONLY long term solution to this mess. It does require the dismantling of private insurers. We don't need them. They have just ONE purpose -- to NOT provide health care in order to make money and therefore they only wish to cover people they deem healthy. Who needs that? Why pay for that? Insurance is quite basic -- you share the risk, and the bigger the shared pool, the lower the cost to everyone. We understand this concept VERY WELL with roads. Should the supreme court rule you should not be taxed for roads you never drive on? Should we all just pay for the sections we use? Or pay nothing if we think we don't use them (which of course we do because everything we buy comes on these roads). A bunch of mainly old white out of date men, all with health insurance, on this SUPREME court making such a stupid apparently difficult decision? I will tell you this, if they do not allow universal care to move forward, we will have a health crisis in this country that could cause the overthrow of this entire system. I predict MOST people, in a few years, will not be able to get affordable insurance. When it's 60 or 70% uninsured -- will we still keep the system we have? To keep a few old white guys rich? Just because the system has  been this way so why change it? I wish I had a direct pipeline to this supreme court. They might make a BIG TIME screw up here that we will NEVER get over. Could be the demise of our economy -- if that hasn't already been sparked by the illegal, unfunded wars we got ourselves into. This issue DOES NOT BELONG in the hands of the supreme court. What a scary place for it to be. They are Always 50 years behind the times. They do not understand the needs for us to move into the future global world. I do not trust them to do this right. Not at all.
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/675v4n</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tsjl</id></website><link>http://truth-out.org/opinion/item/8202-the-savage-arithmetic-of-the-pre-existing-condition</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:35:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:58:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4oov</id><link>http://truth-out.org/opinion/item/8202-the-savage-arithmetic-of-the-pre-existing-condition#comment-481247296</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6i7pz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>