<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3q034/post/2012-03-29T12:24:40</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Things Our "Flexible" President May Do When He Is Re-elected
Barack Hussein Obama is so cocksure of re-election that he is making plans for 2013-2016.  
Obama made that surety obvious when he pulled yet another gaffe in South Korea by not realizing he was speaking with a hot mike as he whispered to the outgoing Russian figurehead President Dmitry Medvedev. 
The surreptitious exchange: 
Obama: On all these issues, but particularly missile defense, this, this can be solved but it’s important for him to give me space.
Medvedev: Yeah, I understand. I understand your message about space. Space for you…
Obama: ( over and putting his hand on Mr. Medvedev’s knee): This is my last election. After my election I have more flexibility.
Medvedev: I understand. I will transmit this information to Vladimir.
America’s commander-in-chief essentially promised to give away America’s European missile defense  to Russia after he wins in November, that he would share vital, military information with the incoming Russian fraudulent President Vladimir Putin since he will have fooled the American electorate once again. 
That treasonous plot with the nation against which we waged a decades-long Cold War and which Mitt Romney called America’s “number one geopolitical foe” has raised suspicions on what else Obama has hidden up his sleeve, as if outright presidential treason were not enough.   
Based on the president’s words and actions over the past four years, here are some educated guesses on what Americans can expect by 2016 or sooner should he win four more years to perpetrate more treason, wreak havoc with our economy, undermine our international standing, and convert the country into a Third World nation: 
.  Israel will be abandoned despite Obama’s Pledges to the contrary, Venezuela will become a trusted ally, and the 50 year old sanctions against Cuba will be lifted.  (Obama and his administration have frequently demonstrated an antipathy to Israel and an affinity for all things Islamic, have indicated they want Hugo Chavez to be a buddy, and have a special affection for Communism.)  
.  The United Nations will be recognized as the preeminent authority to dictate America’s foreign and domestic policy.  (Obama is a professed “One-Worlder” who sees the U.N. as the one organization capable of insuring peace and tranquility throughout the planet.)  
 .  Attorney General Eric Holder’s racist and corrupt DoJ . . .(Read more at http://www.genelalor.com/blog1/?p=19397.)</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z7ttv</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q0fi</id></website><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/29/obama-touts-higher-taxes-on-oil-companies/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:54:58+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:24:40+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3q034</id><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/29/obama-touts-higher-taxes-on-oil-companies/#comment-479623590</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/pem</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>