<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwwipi/post/2012-03-31T12:58:15</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I am inventing a modern fable to be read by the posterity in all schools of the world. What would be an appropriate title for that historical fable? I’ll see to that problem after I have written it.
1) The fable began by the election of Barak Hussein Obama as the President of the United States of America in November 2008. In January 2009 Mullah Obama, a Marxist Muslim from Kenya, was inaugurated. Immediately after that he nominated some 35 komissars as his White House advisers and placed them in total control of all federal government departments.
2) Over the first 4 years of his rule he printed some 7 trillion paper dollars in order to finance his re-election in 2012. He then nationalized huge chunks of American private enterprise: automobile factories, many banks, mortgage companies, student loan industry, hospitals, health insurance companies, and set up further nationalizations by means of the global warming hoax, aiming at oil and gas companies, coal mines, transportation companies (airlines, trucking companies, railroads), electricity companies (especially those Burning coal and gas, and of course nuclear power companies). Some 7,000 new regulations have been issued in order to squeeze private businesses into bankruptcy to be then taken over by his system of local soviets (as community organizations were known in the defunct Soviet Union).
3) After his re-election in November 2012 assured by massive vote fraud in all 50 states, he will assume the name of Abu Hussein al-Mombassa. He will aid and abbet the destruction of Israel by the Iran’s nuclear bombs and thus solve that intractable problem that has plagued the world ever since 1948. The entire Muslim world will agree to his new title. Not a single Jew will ever more be able to desecrate the Muslim world – all Jews will be exterminated in a few weeks of celebratory pogroms.
4) As a consequence of runaway inflation amd massive unemployment Abu Hussein will declare the state of national emergency thus giving him dictatorial powers. His system of local soviets (i.e., community organizations) will be given arms and authority to quell any local disagreements. All judges mentioning the Constitution will be simply fired by means of another executive order and replaced by more reasonable choices recruited from the ranks of ACLU, Sierra Club, Institute for Policy Studies, Greenpeace, Union of Concerned Scientists, Environmental Defense Fund, various human and environmental rights organizations, Amnesty International, Human Rights Watch, etc. Various United Nations organizations will be given direct authority in approving the US budgets and allocations. The 65-year old problem between India and Pakistan will be solved by assigning Kashmir to the latter. China will be allowed finally to solve the festering Taiwan problem by the UN approval of an adequate military expedition. The danger of the continuing war between the North and South Koreas will be  peacefully by annexation of the southern portion of that state into a single jurisdiction. 
5) At the end of his second term, due to the continuing economic crisis and sporadic armed resistance by various enemies of the people, Abu Hussein will proclaim himself dictator for life, under a new name of Ayatollah Barak. His direct rule will be replaced by temporary interventions via “dictates” that will enlarge the Scope of the sharia laws into all facets of modern life. He will then live the rest of his long life while waiting to be proclaimed as the 12th Immam.
Finally – what about the title of this fable? I will gladly entertain the submissions of my readers, and will then bring my judgment as to the most appropriate one.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67iyan</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/o6hq</id></website><link>http://conservativebyte.com/2012/03/obama-grabs-more-executive-power-again/</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T13:55:07+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T16:58:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwwipi</id><link>http://conservativebyte.com/2012/03/obama-grabs-more-executive-power-again/#comment-481996434</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hzgqz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>