<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3pkgb/update/2012-03-29T20:48:49/f95f7365a50693e2ce0d56212831a45f61b72182420ebb92933f500fa69410fd</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I think even skilled engineers don't know the precise mix of tactics among those you list that will be best. However, here's my take:

  -- adapt the grid: this is the most important. As you note, the current paradigm makes assumptions that don't work for many renewables. We need to adapt the paradigm.

Obviously it will be very difficult to change consumption patterns, though electric vehicles do stand to help a great deal there when deployed in large numbers (allowing vehicles hooked to chargers to absorb excess generation capacity during non-peak times). More generally, we just need better ways to store energy and use that storage to accommodate fluctuations in demand.

Yes...surely we are smart enough to accomlish this goal.  :)


  -- efficiency: this is important for other reasons, but I don't see it as addressing the mismatch between capacity and demand.

  -- convenience/density of fossil fuels (including natural gas): whether we accept this or not, it is not sustainable to continue using these. Even in the best case, they run out, and of course in the worst case we have to drastically decrease our use of them lest we continue to Heat up the world.

So I consider this another moot point. We need a solution that doesn't use fossil fuels.

  -- consider nuclear: I think it's a huge mistake to NOT consider nuclear. The Japan earthquake freaked everyone out, and yes there were significant environmental impacts. But I think most people have taken the wrong lesson from it. Fact is, the event was nearly absolute worst-case and yet percentage-wise, the nuclear industry in Japan weathered it pretty well. Especially considering how old the affected reactors were, missing a variety of safety features new reactors would have.

Nuclear has the potential to be very dangerous, but it can also be very safe, and it's certainly got an impressive investment/output ratio. From a "body count" perspective, even including the Japan earthquake, I doubt nuclear has killed any more people than other energy production.

Harnessing enough energy to meet our demand is Always going to be somewhat dangerous business, no matter where that energy comes from. We just need to be careful.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zti1i</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/amtr</id></website><link>http://www.treehugger.com/renewable-energy/farming-wind-teaches-us-about-future-energy.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:41:03+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:48:49+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3pkgb</id><link>http://www.treehugger.com/renewable-energy/farming-wind-teaches-us-about-future-energy.html#comment-480083962</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/r70q2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>