<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0j4j7/post/2012-04-02T03:43:38</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrauf</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> With all due respect, Samari Vindctus,  H., and you chiyam whatever,

My comment has nothing to do, with mweya wesvina,  my comment has nothing to do with being nasty, my comment has nothing to do with stupidity because one way or the other, I have every right to be stupid but those who have the balls to call me stupid are the ones who are abusing that privilege of being stupid.

My comment has nothing to do with a person who looks at it from a United States or  based perspective but from a Zimbabwean point of view.

My comment is talking about a very corrupt system which even if Martin Luther King were to raise up from the dead 2day and say I have a dream that one of these days I see a corrupt free Zimbabwe, he will be lying to his grave.   My comment is about how corruption is rearing its ugly face everywhere, in the mountains, in the rivers where the waters run deep.  Everywhere you step your feet there is a red tag of corruption.  It has gotten in the heads of the learned, the not so learned and the young and the restless.

My comment is saying this corrupt system will not end unless you and I as a people raise up and shake Off the existing system and come up with a new one that suits us better.  This is most valuable and sacred  right, a right to which we will make Zimbabwe a corrupt free country again.  Unfortunately this will not work while you and I are basking in the glory of  a foreign country while Zimbabwe Burns.

In as much as I would have loved to give constructive advice to the victim somehow I had my reservations and I ended up saying what my truthful brain was pushing me to say.

I looked at the victim’s situation and I said to myself, there is a policeman who goes on to write a detailed report of what happened at the scene of the accident. There is the victim who was maybe careless enough not to double check whether what the policeman had written was based on what transpired at the scene and to put his signature in agreement.

With  the corrupt system in Zimbabwe yu have to pump out a couple of dollars to get witnesses to testify.

The perpetrator goes to the police soon after the accident, the victim like a zombie walks into the police station two days after the accident only to be told sir you are now the perpetrator not the victim. This means the victim was not jerked up from the inset and now he is being chewed by the system.  That is why I ended up saying kana ukaroverera mota yako in a country like Zimbabwe, sinura, kana kutobata munhu akuroverera bhurugwa nebhandi kusika zanaka, kwete kuita chikristu nesika, nekuti munhu anosanduka kana aona mari.  Thank you.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67cttd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/94p1</id></website><link>http://www.newsdzezimbabwe.co.uk/2012/03/my-encounter-with-corrupt-cop.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T12:47:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T07:43:38+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0j4j7</id><link>http://www.newsdzezimbabwe.co.uk/2012/03/my-encounter-with-corrupt-cop.html#comment-483333819</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>