<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwojy5/update/2012-03-31T06:13:41/3ec3a4f386ff1a23d8667d0324d87adeb0aa4e896ee847e96f6213cf0f4d63b8</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The war on (some) drugs fuels violence because the “WAR” on drugs IS violence. It’s the policy of sending men with guns to confiscate sellers’ profits, destroy their inventories, and lock them in cages. All of the other violence that surrounds the (non-alcohol, non-tobacco) drug trade is fundamentally a REACTION to that initial state-sponsored violence. Prohibition renders contracts unenforceable and makes it impossible for competitors to use the courts or the police to challenge intimidation or settle disputes. Those conditions promote violence. There are plenty of legal businesses that might love to “kill the competition,” but that only becomes a viable strategy under the black market conditions that prohibition creates. (Note that nobody from  or Pepsi actually gets killed as a result of the much-hyped “Cola Wars.”) Prohibition also raises the prices of illicit drugs and hence their profitability. (Econ 101: risk demands compensation.) This only increases sellers’ incentives to do “whatever it takes” to capture market share. Today you don’t see rival beer distributors engaging in deadly shoot-outs over turf, but you USED TO — during alcohol prohibition. Run a Google image search for “U.S. homicide rate graph” (not all together in quotes). Take a look at the murder rate before, after, and during alcohol prohibition (1919-1933). Tell me when you Spot a pattern.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/679zsg</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/mx4f</id></website><link>http://www.kentucky.com/2012/03/31/2133547/war-on-drugs-has-long-been-lost.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T09:49:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T10:13:41+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwojy5</id><link>http://www.kentucky.com/2012/03/31/2133547/war-on-drugs-has-long-been-lost.html#comment-481711864</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ymn8j</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>