<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw3vbr/post/2012-03-31T11:43:09</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Thank you for bringing clarity to this issue. I had missed the airing of the marketplace episode on Cold fx, but heard from a colleague of mine that it had been reported as a scam. Being a daily user of Cold fx, and also a firm believer in it's benefits, I had to see the marketplace claims for myself. Although I do not watch hockey and am not a fan in the slightest of Don Cherry, I am with him in regards to this matter. It works very well for me, and although there may be some who say it doesn't work for them, well then sorry about their luck. Considering the marketplace's pick and choose method in the gathering of their alleged evidence against Cold fx, and I believe I read that CBC had aired Cold fx commercials at one time, I think maybe CBC has a different motive for the attack on Cold fx. As I already stated, it works well for me, and that's what I care about. I've had so many pharmacists recommend  to me for relief of a migraine Headache, but I can take 5 or 6 with no affect, but two  and  in 15 to 20 mins...gone! Doesn't mean that Advil is a scam, it just doesn't work for me. Thanks again for posting what people should see about this product.

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/d3yn9i</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/y9cq</id></website><link>http://jeejeebhoy.ca/2012/01/14/marketplace-posits-a-theory-about-cold-fx/</link><postedTime>2012-01-15T04:24:49+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T15:43:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw3vbr</id><link>http://jeejeebhoy.ca/2012/01/14/marketplace-posits-a-theory-about-cold-fx/#comment-481931363</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-01-15</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>