<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwksz9/post/2012-03-31T10:10:48</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Thank you once again, Patrick J., as your presentation of the facts, as usual, is Spot-on.
("The Death of the West" indeed)
This country would be MUCH better place had Mr. Buchanan been elected POTUS 20 years ago.
(but then, would we Buchanan supporters public servants-to-be embrace being pilloried like Trent Lott for celebrating the life of the aged Strom Thurmond?) But, I digress ...
That Said -
The Race Industry in America has been resuscisitated by the likes of paid race hustlers who don't pay for their actions or their fall-out, neither in the court of public opinion, nor in the Court system. Exascerbating this ginned-up "situation" are the  are the usual suspects. Even a "reverend" in Detroit said that the "City will Burn" if the White Governor appoints a "financial manager" for the perrennially corrupt and bankrupt City of Detroit. "Rev. Al" and Calypso Louie Farrakhan are all for it - As IF there is ANYTHING left to Burn in Detroit! Take a peek, Leftists, you've already ruined MoTown.

Harkening back to the incessant (and major) political Heat taken by former NJ Governor Christine Todd Whitman who was accused of ordering the State Police to "profile" those coming north into Jersey from the South who are likely transporting drugs and/or firearms. She was CORRECT 62% of the time. The felons just happened to be black. Is THAT not good enough to keep her State safe(r)? I Axe you.

It's time to get over Marxist Conflict Theory, America. (sometimes called: "critical theory"). "The Man" aint out to git y'all, we just want our communities protected from reprobates. We "bitter clingers" will never surrender to the State writ LARGE. And "The Man" can take that to the bank ...
As if they don't already know.
SPQR
~(Ä)~</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z1tbk</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry2d</id></website><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50546</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:44:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T14:10:48+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwksz9</id><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50546#comment-481858514</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/exjtk</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>