<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kjtp/post/2012-03-29T22:49:09</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>George Zimmerman was the guy out of control. Who the hell appointed him a security guard? A guy walking along is accosted by this fat slob and doesn't like it. This offiacious police wantabe gets punched in the nose by a guy smaller then him. We don't know all the details yet, but this case was put to bed way too early. There are too many police who think they are the Gestapo. My uncle was a Milwaukee Policeman for 30 years. He hated writing tickets and arresting people. In fact he would turn his ticket book back in many times without ever writng a ticket for a year. He used to say. " I told the sargent writing tickets is bad public relations for the police. " With all the fist fights and bar room  brawls  and numerous Heated verbal confrontations, I was in. I am sure as  no one was packing Heat. Our esteemed host Pat Buchanan, beat up a policeman when he was in college. I am sure for good reason. Perhaps he knows about what I am talking about. This case needs cool heads and honest and open investigation. It doesn't need a bunch of pimps like Sharpton, Jackson, Santorum and Gingrich spouting Off and raising tensions.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z1tbk</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry2d</id></website><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50546</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:44:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:49:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kjtp</id><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50546#comment-480172529</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cm50g</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>