<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk112y/post/2012-03-26T11:44:56</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>"If you like sports, that’s a great icebreaker too if it’s a guy."
But if it's a girl this will be a rubbish icebreaker because girls totally don't get sports.

"Any racist remark or female-bashing, is a no-no for me."

uh-huh. So I see. Still, I'm  that male-bashing is still OK.

Pet peeves about the latent sexism in the software development world aside, this article left me unsatisfied. This is probably partly because recruitment is one of the most difficult things you will have to do in business so trying to summarise it in one article is  going to be difficult. But there is more to my dislike of the article than that. There is the fact that Wessel has taken a number of prejudices and opinions and proposed them as generic rules for recruitment (e.g., being late, wearing shorts, some reasons for previous gaps in employment). There is also the fact that the method he outlines - a 45 minute chat - has never been a reliable way of finding good candidates in the past for me.

If you were interviewing for a chef, would you get them to explain some great omelettes they have cooked before and ask them technical questions about making an omelette? Or would you get them to cook the omelette and see what it tastes like? Hiring developers has some similarities - they will be taking their skills, knowledge and experience and using it to create something. The only way to know how good they are is to get them to do it. If you are hiring a PHP developer, get them to write some code for you. Better yet, get them to work with the team to write some code. The most effective interview technique I've found for developers is to get someone in for 1 day to work with the team doing the job you expect them to do. This is expensive and difficult to organise it, but hiring the right people is such an important task - especially for a startup - that it is time well spent. (Of course, this doesn't guarantee that someone who looked good for one day won't turn out to be, for example, a sociopathic idiot, but no interview technique is perfect. This is what probationary periods are for.)

The other thing that Wessel doesn't mention is that it is extremely difficult to hire for jobs you don't understand. If you haven't done the work yourself, how will you understand what is required for it and whether or not the candidate knows what they are talking about. If you're a non-technical founder hiring a developer then Gaining this knowledge might seem prohibitively difficult, but that doesn't make it any less essential. If you are hiring for a role you haven't done yourself then you might as well put all of the names into a hat and pick one out at random. (Of course the same can apply to a technical founder hiring a head of sales, etc...)

On a more positive note, the importance of trying to make people feel comfortable is Spot on. The more you can get people to really be themselves, the more chance you will have of finding out if they really are a good fit. Confrontational interviews don't benefit either party.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rkn12</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/9x4r</id></website><link>http://www.rudebaguette.com/2012/03/26/recruiting-developer-series-part-1-5-interview/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T12:44:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T15:44:56+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk112y</id><link>http://www.rudebaguette.com/2012/03/26/recruiting-developer-series-part-1-5-interview/#comment-476482185</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>