<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwqc93/update/2012-03-30T18:14:53/6ca5ad03db31826f19e44559dc138b706639946168f1aa3f3721d612ed6af98b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrah5</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/m3gum</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Do you not find it a bit hypocritical to assume the outcome of said investigation and then later suggest a labour union await the results of the investigation?  After all, you've already concluded what will happen after reading just several sentences.

I recall a story not too long ago where a bunch of teenaged boys in BC were screwing around with their fathers gun and one took a bullet to the face and died.  That kid wasn't charged, are you suggesting that he too be charged for something he didn't intend to do?  what about the person in the military that had his weapon go Off?  They are probably some of the most trained in Canada with firearms.  The point is accidents happen, we can sit here all day and discuss accountability but that won't stop mistakes from happening.  I'm surprised you aren't a cop given your stone Cold nerves of steel.  I don't recall anywhere in the article suggesting this cop is going to walk freely without any disciplinary action.

For someone who claims to be a firearms instructor, you of all people should know that mistakes can happen for a variety of reasons.  google/youtube search gun range accidents, I see a lot more problems there than with cops and military combined.  I've belonged to gun clubs and seen idiots first hand do very dumb things.  In fact not too long ago some guy showed up with an ar-15 with an M320 grenade attachment on it.  Firearms instructors didn't do anything to prevent him from hitting the range.

Of course I would be remiss to sit here and play armchair quarterback considering most of the time if someone goes at a cop with a knife they get shot.  How an accidental shooting happens in an encounter where they are actually justified to use deadly force raises some questions.  

Sounds to me like your issue is more with the delivery of the story than the facts behind what actually happened.  For someone who proclaims to be a law enforcement supporter, I can't remember ever seeing any comments from you that actually supported law enforcement.  You quickly pass judgement and blame on any news story that immediately hits the wire. 

Maybe it was negligence, maybe it was accidental or maybe it was a misplaced shot.  Before passing judgement and going into a long tirade with many replies arguing your OPINION, perhaps you should possess a little patience and wait to hear what actually happened.  A handful of sentences doesn't paint a very clear picture on anything.  There's probably more letters used in this weeks weather forecast.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67e40o</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7mag</id></website><link>http://www.calgarysun.com/2012/03/30/police-investigate-after-officer-accidentally-fires-gun-during-arrest</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:10:09+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T22:14:53+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwqc93</id><link>http://www.calgarysun.com/2012/03/30/police-investigate-after-officer-accidentally-fires-gun-during-arrest#comment-481261497</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hc7nz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>