<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/g6rvv8/update/2011-09-25T13:39:23/44bc6bc98b109de46da809f330f08703c54bda9e44f2cb3be48fd0581e9e40e3</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Not only can many young people not afford to buy their own home, this very inability is being used to Bleed them dry in the rental sector.

An unexceptional flat in London that was rented for £1000 per month this year will be £1200 next year. This does not reflect increased costs on the landlord - if anything his outgoings on the property are likely to have reduced thanks to rock-bottom interest rates.

This is in fact pure profiteering by the buy-to-let brigade who were fortunate enough to have the wealth to buy at the right time and now expect to sit back and watch it multiply at the expense of the next generation. Whatever else happens, something must be done to control this.

It is already a mystery to me how anyone earning less than say £30kpa can afford to work in london. Buying is out of Reach, renting costs are going through the roof and of course living outside and commuting in puts you at the mercy of the train operators, who provide a crappy service and have a special licence from the governement to gouge the customers over whom they hold a monopoly by around 8% more every year.

Unsustainable doesnt begin to cover it.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/m2sfyp</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/active/8787057/Taxing-the-rich-is-certainly-good-for-politicians.html</link><postedTime>2011-09-24T19:20:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-09-25T17:39:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/g6rvv8</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/active/8787057/Taxing-the-rich-is-certainly-good-for-politicians.html#comment-319661570</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cm789</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-09-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>