<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34w80/update/2012-03-29T11:24:35/b040e6144f0d5402ea758449793b5828be1eb4aa46aeaf07219c4aff8f2dbf82</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This is no joke!
My family was living in West Glenwood Springs when the coal seam fire broke out to the west.
The fire looked to be several miles up the canyon. In a very short time people were needing to evacuate
and it was mass hysteria with people driving over yards and medians, etc all in an attempt to get on the
interstate and out of the area. My husband was trapped in the car with our two youngest sons and our
granddaughter who was about 2 at that time. Besides the sky blackening smoke, they were able to feel
the Heat coming  the front end of the fire (fires can REALLY MOVE) and was my husband was contemplating taking them
all down into the river for safety when they were finally able to access the highway.
Great job to this family for keeping their heads and SHAME ON the operator who told her to "QUIT CALLING"
If these people would've had to Depend on others, they would never have made it out!
My prayers are with all who have lost their lives and homes and also with those in fear of losing these things.
Until this has happened to you, you cannot imagine the terror of trying to get out and the heartbreak after you
are finally let back in, only to see your world totally destroyed! Good Luck to all of you!
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h037g</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/y4ok</id></website><link>http://photos.denverpost.com/mediacenter/2012/03/couple-talks-escaping-lower-north-fork-fire/32725/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T02:27:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:24:35+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34w80</id><link>http://photos.denverpost.com/mediacenter/2012/03/couple-talks-escaping-lower-north-fork-fire/32725/#comment-479574539</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>