<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/240793/post/72702815/comment/328087051</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>because,michael kors outlet, according to the theorem of kinetic energy,coach outlet store online, mgh = 1/2mv2. v count out is about 100m / s, Ft = mv calculated F is the force of the role of the water F = mv / t (assuming the role of time according to 0.1s, the quality of Bradley couples per person 75kg) that force F is scary. F = 75000N, is Bradley couple of their body weight 100 times. But now the best astronauts withstand 10 times their own weight. So,f50 adizero, basically is dead. So the conclusion is: the concrete can be assessed only as a reference,coach outlet, the key is the impact process,lunettes de soleil chanel, this is a very complex and related to many factors, such as the contact surface. 1972, Wei Sina the &amp;#183; Wuluo WeiXi, 23-year-old former Yugoslavia stewardess an altitude of 33,000 ft. rapid fall, but her body did not parachute pack. Serbian JAT Airways JU367 flights overflying Srbska-Kamenice over,herve leger, suffered terrorist bomb attacks (Croatian national movement, However, with the terrorist attacks Equally alarming is the Wu Luo the Weixi actually Enron survivors. Fall from a height of 33,mercurial vapor pas cher,000 ft.,louboutin, and her skull,michael kors sale, legs and three spine fracture and temporary Paralysis, but after have returned to normal, and continue the work of her attendants. So far she is a free-fall survivors Guinness record holder. car crashed into First Canyon free fall,michael kors, and then hit the tree, and finally fell to the bottom of cataract formation pools. Fortunately, they only sustained minor injuries. , the experts generally agreed that the height of 40 meters, can dies is very ugly. car into the one hundred meters deep valley However, not porcelain, stress analysis is not the top things, life and death of the key parts of the ground. For example, the husband and wife Bradley\'s car hit the tree, so that slowed down the speed of freefall and may even change the landing direction,herve leger dress, and then fell to the bottom of cataract formation pools,michael kors handbags on sale, water can be deformed ,chaussure de foot, and therefore is an instantaneous momentum. Fell on the rock next to it is absolutely survivors of the reason. Bill collarbone fracture, but still insists that his wife dragged from the car. Doty said: any possibility of his survival. The crash site of the car pool,chaussures louboutin, only 2 meters from the rock next to, if fall where they\'ll be dead. This is definitely a miracle, the kind of collision has only suffered minor injuries, was unbelievable. &amp;gt;&amp;gt; &amp;gt;&amp;gt; extension of another incredible survivors fall in the one hundred meters deep valley why can survive the from Shropshire, UK Lude Luo town 58-year-old bodybuilder Bradley Bill Doty, 57-year-old wife drove their car along the Mid Wales Machynlleth and the coast between Lani De Lois hurry hurry. As the night sky,lunettes de soleil louis vuitton, Bill\'s car unknowingly more open faster. Suddenly, the opening in the Bill in front of the car somehow a screeching halt. Unfortunately,herve leger sale, the car ultimately stopped. Bill the couple\'s car broke through the fence next to the road after crashing one hundred meters into the sky into the ravine. According to the minor injuries, they are really blessed by God In fact, this is really lucky,lunettes de soleil ray Ban, like such couples survived,adidas f50, incredible survivor ... &amp;gt;&amp;gt; event Related articles&amp;#65306; &amp;#8221;&amp;#32593;&amp;#21451;&amp;#8220;dkuwhki&amp;#8221;&amp;#36319;&amp;#24086;&amp;#35828; &amp;#21776;&amp;#21513;&amp;#23621;&amp;#20303;&amp;#22312;&amp;#23612;&amp;#27850;&amp;#23572;&amp;#19968;&amp;#20010;&amp;#20559;&amp;#36828;&amp;#23665;&amp;#21306;&amp;#30340;&amp;#23567;&amp;#26449;&amp;#24196; &amp;#29579;&amp;#26576;&amp;#36935;&amp;#23475;&amp;#29616;&amp;#22330;&amp;#31163;&amp;#33258;&amp;#23478;&amp;#21482;&amp;#26377;300&amp;#31859;&amp;#30340;&amp;#36317;&amp;#31163; &amp;#36152;&amp;#26131;&amp;#65292;&amp;#26159;&amp;#33258;&amp;#24895;&amp;#30340;&amp;#36135;&amp;#21697;&amp;#25110;&amp;#26381;&amp;#21153;&amp;#20132;&amp;#25442;&amp;#12290;&amp;#36152;&amp;#26131;&amp;#20063;&amp;#34987;&amp;#31216;&amp;#20026;&amp;#21830;&amp;#19994;&amp;#12290;&amp;#36152;&amp;#26131;&amp;#26159;&amp;#22312;&amp;#19968;&amp;#20010;&amp;#24066;&amp;#37324;&amp;#38754;&amp;#36827;&amp;#34892;&amp;#30340;&amp;#12290; </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:240793:72702815</id><idPostId>72702815</idPostId><idBlogId>240793</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:240793</id><idBlogId>240793</idBlogId><link>http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com</link><displayName>Are You Healthy?  Are You Happy?</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com/2011/01/26/do-you-have-the-post-holiday-blues-happiness-how-to-get-it/</link><displayName>Do you have the Post Holiday Blues?  Happiness:  How to get it.</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T22:09:17.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:240793:72702815:328087051</id><link>http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com/2011/01/26/do-you-have-the-post-holiday-blues-happiness-how-to-get-it/#IDComment328087051</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T22:09:17.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Do you have the Post Holiday Blues?  Happiness:  How to get it. by xixi120u1</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://louboutinenlignesfr.com</link><idEmailMd5>d366f2ee793a8f24a74cdb0051ad8f49</idEmailMd5><displayName>xixi120u1</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://louboutinenlignesfr.com"&gt;xixi120u1&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com/2011/01/26/do-you-have-the-post-holiday-blues-happiness-how-to-get-it/"&gt;Do you have the Post Holiday Blues?  Happiness:  How to get it.&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>