<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0p5ui/post/2012-04-02T06:35:02</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>YO!



"Winghunter"



Lemme guess.



You have a little beanie-copter that you wear when on the computer.. little epaulets too... ones that your mommy made for you.



You still sleep in the same bed you did when you went to grade school... peeling, yellowed wallpaper in your room with Cowboys &amp; Indians on it, perhaps some tattered pennants from all of the colleges that you hoped you had been able to go to but never even got close... a trophy for 5th place in some intramural sports event from 20 years ago (one that they give EVERY kid so as not to feel left out), even a "Certificate of Achievement" for passing the 6th grade in the lower 2% of your class.



Milk &amp; cookies by your side, &amp; a dogeared, queef-stained copy of "Going Rogue" on your nightstand, nestled on the souvenir handkerchief that you got on that red-letter day when your daddy took you to visit Howard Johnsons.



You earn a living by stuffing envelopes for direct-mail promoters, preferring to lick all of the envelopes because it reminds you of when you were being nursed, looking forward to the ‘bonanza season’ when you get to work for Publishers Clearinghouse.



Your favorite food is mac &amp; cheesewhiz (uncooked) with a side of tater-tots (still frozen) washed down with an entire 2 liter bottle of Mountain Dew (Heated).



Pegged you, yes?



Good.



Now, back to your wading pool, &amp; this time, don’t piss in it.



SCOOT!!!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6viv1m</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cusm</id></website><link>http://www.rawstory.com/rs/2012/04/01/huge-shift-among-female-voters-gives-obama-lead-in-battleground-states/</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T01:07:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T10:35:02+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0p5ui</id><link>http://www.rawstory.com/rs/2012/04/01/huge-shift-among-female-voters-gives-obama-lead-in-battleground-states/#comment-483408858</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rpiv9</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>