<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwl788/update/2012-03-30T12:57:16/3cde6c2fae94cf24172307a969f9e4864aa2a55fcb98844ab272638342358272</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3oj9d</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g1mxa</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> I do not believe there is any self-hatred involved whatsoever.  These are self-serving opportunists, who have wet their finger and put it up in the air to determine which way the wind is blowing.

Disingenuous White Liberals compose two classes of people; the higher rung of the hierarchy is a highly organized group pursuing its own agenda and the lower rung is composed of closet racial realists who have made their own separate peace with the Anti-White coalition.  It is obvious they have no intentions of being "enriched" by vibrant communities of color themselves through miscegenation, so they live the kind of lifestyle any klansman would envy.  However, they know that The Diversity demands its White Sacrifices, so they have made escaping The Diversity very expensive for the poor, working class and lower-middle class Whites

IOW, they are like the idiot who erroneously thinks he is saving his own hide by pushing others into the mouth of a big, hungry crocodile, believing it will die of Indigestion before it ever  him.  However, the big, hungry crocodile has an insatiable appetite that increases as it the big, hungry crocodile itself grows in size.  

However, thanks to the Internet, the MSM propaganda is being bypassed and more and more average Whites are waking up every day.  The Diversity may think they have won, because they have succeeded in shutting down all debate, but they better be more concerned about what the average White is NOT saying than what he is!   Time not wasted in discussion can be devoted to planning a course of action.  

I think several smug sycophants are going to be in for a rude awakening and I, for one, am going to be wildly amused to watch how quickly they scramble to get in front of the line and  like they have Always been Pro-White when the vast majority of Whites say enough is enough.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z1d3n</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f9vj</id></website><link>http://amren.com/news/2012/03/the-changing-guard-of-white-separatism-convenes-at-a-tennessee-state-park/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:31:29+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:57:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwl788</id><link>http://amren.com/news/2012/03/the-changing-guard-of-white-separatism-convenes-at-a-tennessee-state-park/#comment-480949562</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ami09</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>