<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwd1fw/post/2012-03-30T10:07:40</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>It is of Interest that Israel is not a member of the IAEA, Nor does Israel allow Weapons Inspections of any kind of their WMD'S. Yet Israel has as in the past  been the aggressor. They Bombed Iraq, Bombed Syria and now is receiving 40% of Iraq's Oil. Their Mossad openly travels anywhere in the world and Assassinates anyone they choose. While over 100 Nations have pressed for War Crimes against Israel... As Usual the US Puppets  Veto the out-come.
Israel continues to Bomb Gaza using White Phosphorus. I guess it is nice to watch the skin Burn on Children. Like the US Bombs Children in Afghanistan, (Future Terrorist's) Then one can freely Google (Reporters Shot in their Backs or Heads) In Gaza/Palestine and there is no public out cry.

Then people forget how Israel came to have Nuclear Weapons, How they hid their Nuclear Program from the Weapons Inspectors during when Kennedy was alive *The only time Israel was ever Inspected*.(same claim that Iran is doing) Yet both the US and Israel admit Iran doesn't have a bomb. Hiding their Nuclear Program 6 Stories below where the Inspectors had access behind Fake Walls. Then the Airplane that Crashed killing 43 People that was said to be carrying Flowers and Perfume, Yet was carrying the major ingredient for SARIN GAS.

This is the Truth, Not being anti-Semetic either. However, Obama has sent US Boys to all Israel's Military Bases and should Iran defend themselves if Attacked and counter strike Israel, It is clear US Boys will be killed thus dragging the US into the 3rd World War. Like Netenyahu said though, "We would RATHER the U.S. Go it alone and Attack Iran, That way Israel will not feel the full wrath of Iran." Better American Blood be spilled then Jewish Blood. This while Netenyahu continues to spread the Lie that Iran wants to "Wipe Israel  the Map." Which was Never said. Ahmadinejad did comment about Regime Change. The same PLOT the US of A has done in so many Countries destroying democratically elected governments. Like many Central and  American Countries, Afghanistan, Iraq, Libya (Syria Next) then Iran. That is all This Country does is Destroy Country after Country with first Forced Sanctions then War. Which is a War on their Citizens as a Government can  TAKE from their People and not be hurt.

We should get used to this by now. And remember that Soldiers are fighting for Our Freedoms. Keeping in mind the Patriot Act, The NDAA and now the new Executive Order 112 of Obama's Presidency to have a Peace Time Martial Law. Pre-Setup for the Collapse of the US Dollar or the War with Iran.
God HELP America, For those that Live by the Sword... You know the Rest.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zb5u5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yjmx</id></website><link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2012/03/29/bolton-accuses-administration-leaking-story-on-israeli-planning-along-iran/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:47:32+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T14:07:40+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwd1fw</id><link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2012/03/29/bolton-accuses-administration-leaking-story-on-israeli-planning-along-iran/#comment-480775462</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hw51h</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>