<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xflt/post/2012-03-29T14:01:59</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xrax</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ylfz7</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>1.  It  amazes me how "Christians" pick and choose a few verses from the Bible to support their aims to inculcate their religious stand against homosexuality or pre-marital sex in to the public square (the law), yet completely ignore the fact that caring for the poor is mentioned more than 2,000 times in both the new and old testament. I guess it is the job of government to rule over the use of our genitals, but it is not the job of government to make sure our children and grandparents have enough to eat. The "redistribution" of wealth seems fine to the "artist" when it flows up but immoral when it flows to the poor among us. 

2. The painting is hateful - perhaps if this "artist"  wants to judge people by their actions (something the Bible and the Lord prohibit) he might want to pull the beam out of the eye of the LDS Church who is one of the most hateful among us. Racism is still alive and well in the church and it seems this "artist" is blind to his own. Pathetic. 

3. For anyone who does not understand the meaning of socialism, painting Obama into that corner makes sense. The Affordable Care  patterned Off Mitt Romney's individual mandate in Massechusetts does not create a socialist control of health care - it is similar to mandating someone who drives carry car insurance - and since every single America uses health care, it makes sense to insure they carry their own insurance. - It is not socialism - not that facts matter to folks like Mr. McNaughton. Please, Mr. Artist, where is the painting of Mitt Burning the Massachusetts state constitution? I guess that just would not sit as well on the wall of the hateful right's living room. 

 4. Doug made the best point in the conversation when he asked the "artist" if it was possible to merely disagree with the President without vilifying him. I guess the answer to that is this "artist" feels inspired by "God" to make foment contention, to call names, to tear down and ridicule rather than to lend a hand extended in an atmosphere of cooperation and compromise. This of course, epitomizes the problems with that side of the table. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z8feg</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6yoz</id></website><link>http://www.publicbroadcasting.net/kuer/news.newsmain/article/184/0/1916604/RadioWest.(M-F..11AM..and..7PM)/32912.Art..Politics.and.the.Paintings.of.Jon.McNaughton</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T05:20:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:01:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xflt</id><link>http://www.publicbroadcasting.net/kuer/news.newsmain/article/184/0/1916604/RadioWest.(M-F..11AM..and..7PM)/32912.Art..Politics.and.the.Paintings.of.Jon.McNaughton#comment-479703185</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ctr9g</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>