<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miccng/update/2012-03-22T13:54:13/c9d5f63a8be3a96d1bc59008a92ece79ac51dee537a53516bfd787d89b73678e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Hello guys! I am new to the site and boy I am  I did some research about this crappy Mirena IUD. I had mine placed in Feb 2009 and just had mine removed on Feb29th after having it in for 3 years.Mine caused extremely high blood pressure I'm averaging 170/110 and I am only 25 years old, I was in immediate danger of having a stroke or heart attack. I had several Chest x-rays, EKG's, echo cardiograms, and even a renal ultrasound trying to rule out ANY medical condition to cause the blood pressure. Turns out I had NOTHING wrong with me, and I went to a new gyno and told them all this that was going on and he about had a heart attack when I told him I had the Mirena IUD. He said it needs to come out immediately, its very dangerous, theres even a class action law suit right now against them. He said that in the last two weeks he had 3 women come in with the same issues I am experiencing. He then told me that it could take up to 4 months for my body to rid itself of all the hormones (and other TOXINS they put in). Scariest thing he told me was that the Mirena has made alot of women infertile, and has damaged the lining of their uterus's so bad that there is so much scar tissue, they may never be able to conceive again. I have a 7 year old son now, I have lost 2, 1 at 3 months and the other at 5 months, so being pregnant is going to be very scary for me however I would LOVE to be able to try again. 

While having the Mirena I also experienced  extreme weight  about 35+ lbs on my 5' 3" frame  (so not cool) , I had terrible mood swings (still am while the hormones work their way out) never wanted sex, period came and went at will. Very irritable, anything would set me , I hardly ever slept. 

 Now that I have had it out, I got my first period two days ago and I cannot get the Bleeding and clotting under control. I am going right through a super tampon and a pad !! I mean this crap is HORRIBLE we are NOT the only ones going through the same things, and it really amazes me that the FDA has yet to pull this dangerous IUD Off the market.  I will never ever ever get this IUD or any IUD again.

Sorry for the rant everyone but this is a very scary and dangerous thing. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/5ij876</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zfgz</id></website><link>http://qaweb3.lifetimemoms.com/node/4982</link><postedTime>2011-05-02T17:53:32+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T17:54:13+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miccng</id><link>http://qaweb3.lifetimemoms.com/node/4982#comment-473796293</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zdzoh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-05-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>