<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk1cpo/post/2012-03-26T11:07:40</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkbl2x</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dol5d</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I don't know. I'm Always resistant to being preached at in general, even if I agree - and I didn't even agree with the message.  When asked in an interview if Mookie did the right thing, Lee's response was something like, only white people ask me if he did the right thing, and when they do, they're prizing a white man's property over a black man's life.

Which is bullshit - and absolutely infuriating.  If Radio Raheem had succeeded in killing Sal (which he was attempting to do just moments before) and the police had Burned down a nearby apartment building in retaliation, the film would be 100% against what they did.  But the film seems to support Mooki's action, even though his violence was not done in self-defense, or even as a pre-emptive strike against an aggressor, but because he wanted to see someone suffer for Raheem's death, and Sal just happened to be the nearest white guy.  It just felt painfully juvenile.

My reaction felt a lot like the one I had watching RENT a couple years ago.  Listening to those two Abercrombie and Fitch models (the rocker and the filmmaker) complain, how DARE they have to pay rent to live in the heart of New York City!?!  It just felt so entitled, so juvenile, so painfully, childishly stupid a complaint that any reasoning semi-adult would have to reject it.  I felt the same way about Do the Right Thing.  Buggin' doesn't start a strike of Sal's because there are no black people on the wall - that's just the excuse.  He starts it because Sal won't give him extra cheese for free.  Raheem has even less justification.  The only one with a legitimate complaint is Smiley, who is mistreated by Sal's scumbag son... but even then, his complaint is with Pino, not with Sal.  All three of them seem to use race as an excuse to lash out at someone who wouldn't give them something for free.

Mookie, at least, has an understandable motive.  Though I still think he should go to jail for inciting a riot, his reaction is understandable - he saw a friend get killed (ugh, those cops were such shitheads) and he lashed out.  I get it, and I'm sympathetic... to a degree.  But the movie seems to think that what he did was right, rather than understandably wrong.  And that kind of disgusts me.

I don't know.  Maybe I'm overthinking it.  Maybe we're not supposed to like anyone in the movie.  But that's not the impression that I get.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r169c</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/tell-us-about-your-popculture-weekend-march-2325-2,71393/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T05:02:48+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T15:07:40+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk1cpo</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/tell-us-about-your-popculture-weekend-march-2325-2,71393/#comment-476456032</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dq245</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>