<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwv5l0/post/2012-03-30T15:46:27</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The Pentagon and conscientious, self-interestedly enlightened airline owners are in pursuit of using today’s algae to run aircraft rather than yesterday’s fossilized algae, so as to restore the virtuous cycle of animals exhaling carbon dioxide and plants taking up that carbon and releasing the oxygen which the animals take in.

In the fifth and sixth grade the good Sisters of Notre Dame taught me that our atmosphere has wonderful gasses in it that keep us warm, greenhouse gasses.  Venus has too many greenhouse gasses: Too hot.  Mars has too few: too Cold.  Earth, over time because of the plants that preceded our own existence, has just enough greenhouses gasses like carbon dioxide: just right.

By using as fuel the carbon compounds, the coal, the oil and the methane gas that plants took with them into the ground as they died — hundreds of millions of years of plant’s carbon capture that has given us the temperate climate in which humanity has grown and thrived —  we are releasing eons of plant’s capture of carbon dioxide all at once and gradually (on a man’s time scale, rapidly in geologic terms) cooking ourselves.

Much as I wish people like the Rev. Roger Minassian could understand this, I see humanity’s only hope in his having invested in his own financial self-interest in clean energy from the sun.  Until cheaper alternatives are on offer or are encouraged by our collective will, humanity will continue to do what is the easiest and cheapest, and we will continue to cook ourselves.   </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z3dzo</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnma</id></website><link>http://www.fresnobee.com/2012/03/30/2780692/sacrificing-america.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T07:10:43+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:46:27+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwv5l0</id><link>http://www.fresnobee.com/2012/03/30/2780692/sacrificing-america.html#comment-481122323</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/800wa</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>