<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmg2e/post/2012-03-30T08:49:52</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This is the least I want to see from future titles:



A comprehensive instructional tutor experience would be a welcome 
change, but that would do little to those who already grasp the 
fundamentals (will still be nice though). For those who lack execution 
or drop combos, that experience can provide combo demonstrations, 
descriptions of why the combo works and how to approach it, and provide 
onscreen effects (like the character blinks a color, and a spark 
animation appearing) that indicates the expiration of the time window - 
which if your character blinks a color, that's correct window for the 
combo, and the spark will appear shortly after if you miss that window.



But Training mode for me can be tedious as hell sometimes. Whenever I 
feel like I've discovered tech for my character, I have to go allll the 
way back to the character select screen, make the CPU my character, and 
record it doing the tech on me to see if it really works. Since I have 
to record the CPU doing the tech (obviously, I don't access to people to
 train with), a character switch is needed for both me and the CPU 
(especially if the tech is character specific), and if it does or 
doesn't work, I have to go all the way back and switch again. Instead, 
it would be nice if the you had the option to select 2, 3, even 5 
characters, both for yourself and the CPU. This way, you can switch 
characters through the pause menu. This also great if you want to train 
against a handful of characters within the hour effortlessly, instead of
 focusing on one character for a long while. The same can be said for 
the characters you select to play as, too.



Sometimes things like practicing frame-traps and option selects can be 
weird when doing the CPU record method. Why is that? Because when you 
record, the other character is in a blockless state. We should get a few
 options of the state we can put our character when we're recording as 
the CPU, because sometimes our tech requires blocking, and it's weird 
when we are performing it on a target that's getting hit instead of the 
expected block.



Oh, and please, more games need saved states! If I'm practicing or 
experimenting with air juggles Off a complicated combo (that requires 
strict spacing relative to the corner, and/or the combo is lengthy), it 
would be a whole lot better if I could save the state when the CPU is 
coming down in the air, or being hit with the attack that initiates the 
juggle state. A queue of saved states would be cool, too.



Although I like the training stage, being in there for an extended 
period of time can really exhaust me. Following the same premise with 
the characters, it would be nice if we could select up to three stages 
from the selection screen. Training mode will start in the training 
room, which will most likely be a stripped down stage, like SF4 or MvC3.
 Then, as time progresses, it will transform into one of the selected 
stages. It will continue this as an endless cycle between your stages 
and the training stage. The training mode will have far less stagnation 
than it does when staying in one level.



As for online, an online training mode will be greatly appreciated, even
 if it can get laggy at times. The possibilities it can present is 
valuable to us.



 I wish Endless would be a tad bit better. It boasts that classic arcade
 feel, where loser gives up his Spot and waits in line. However, the 
lobby is only exciting when the other people have mics - and sometimes 
the people can be either down-right dumb, or just harsh for no reason 
(there's a fine line with being funny, a funny asshole, and a asshole). 
What I would like to see is a list of comments to choose from, like 
"Wow!", "Nice combo!", or "Skip me". The comment will be queued on the 
side of your screen, which will be initiated once you press a button 
(either onscreen or on the controller/stick). The comment will appear in
 a message bubble next to your name.



Since there isn't a lot of space on the Lobby screen, the lobby should 
be an environment instead. This will be a relatively compact space, but 
has enough room for people to be far away from each other even if the 
room is full (8 players most likely). Instead of a title plate that 
holds your name, you are an avatar free to roam in this lobby. The 
avatars could be either a set of characters or items identifiable to the
 game, or simply just generic markers (and gender is distinguished by 
color and face-profile shape).



The lobby will have 9 entryways (I'm presuming the lobby will be in a 
circular shape). One entry way for the main match at hand, and above its
 entrance is a screen that displays the account names of who is playing,
 their characters, the life each have, the current round, who's won so 
far, and time remaining. It would be nice to be able to watch the match 
itself from the lobby, but that would be too harsh on the netcode. So, 
instead, if you want to see the fight, you go into the main match 
entryway and you get to spectate it like you normally do by entering 
Spectator Mode There will be 8 other entryways which will be assigned to
 each player's account (in order of who came earliest), which will be 
their training rooms. This is to be used as expected, a training area to
 brush up before your matches. But, you can also practice with other 
people. You can go up to another player in the lobby (or select there 
name if you're spectating) and send them a Training Request. If 
accepted, your training room will open up access to the player who 
accepted (this is done so people can't just keep coming in and out). If 
spectating, you'll be transported to the training room, but if in the 
lobby, you have to walk to your training room once they have accepted 
because they will be attached to your side (telling the game that you 
gave him permission to enter). Each training room can be spectated as 
well.



The order of players is determined on who enters the main lobby first, 
however you have the freedom to remove your place (exiting spectating 
and going to the main lobby/training room doesn't remove your position).
 By removing, this allows other people to go ahead of you, and also it 
doesn't give you the notification to get ready if you want to primarily 
focus on training longer. If you're still in line, the notification will
 appear as soon as the current match has ended. You will be given 5 
seconds to to accept (which will take you to the fight room 
immediately), or pass your turn. Pressing start will bring up a screen 
that shows who is in what room, and the current order of positions in 
the fight room, just so you know  what is going on in the lobby at all 
times.



In spectating mode, there a few things you can do than just watch. When 
the round is over, you can press a button repeatedly to display your 
feelings about the round, or the player. By pressing one button, it 
plays fanfaric sounds that means you liked the match or how the player 
who won played. You can also press a different button which will 
initiate booing sounds, to show distaste. The faster you tap, the louder
 and more elaborate your sounds are. If spectating, you get to hear your
 sounds and everyone else without the volume being lower. However, as to
 not break the concentration of the players too much, the players 
playing at the moment will hear the same thing, but just a little bit 
quieter. This can be used by them to gauge if the lobby is getting hype,
 or not impressed with his performance. This is done by how many people 
are praising over booing, and vice versa. The more people praising or 
booing, and how fast they are doing it, will begin to overshadow the 
other, so the consensus of the lobby can range from total hype, mixed, 
hate, and even total disinterest (no sounds).



All of this is so that the lobby experience isn't just people waiting in
 line, but a micro-arcade Spot. You're no longer obligated to sit in 
line and fight, going in only one direction. Going to the main lobby to 
chat is an option. Going to an online training mode (but that is not 
outside of that lobby) is an option. Everyone, even the host, can all go
 to the main lobby to talk if they do not want to spectate a match, 
giving it that feeling like you're in a room full of experiences and 
freedom instead of a straight line.

The comment database will be vast, but not too vast, which will be a 
collection common phrases to satisfy general questions or comments. This
 is better than screaming "Yo, you gotta mic!?" and then having to go all
 the way to your message client and sending the player a message by 
typing it in. You can select "No mic", and then "Sorry". Each category 
will serve a purpose, like general phrases, match related phrases, names (which 
will have the name of each character/item/feature of the game), and a 
category for most used sayings and recently used sayings. This is mainly
 to encourage discussion with those who do have mics with those who 
don't, and to have social interaction when the lobby is full with no 
mics.



I know this all sounds like I didn't put much thought into it, but once 
the ball gets rolling, it could be come a more robust idea for an online
 experience I find lacking.

Some of these details and ideas don't have to be exactly as I present them (because games will differ and have different ideas how to make the perfect Endless experience), but it should at least try to get to something like this in the future for the STANDARD of online playing</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zjqj5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/xspx</id></website><link>http://evo.shoryuken.com/2012/03/29/gamespot-thinks-a-new-standard-must-be-set-to-fix-the-fighting-game-genre/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:50:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T12:49:52+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmg2e</id><link>http://evo.shoryuken.com/2012/03/29/gamespot-thinks-a-new-standard-must-be-set-to-fix-the-fighting-game-genre/#comment-480703254</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ywq9n</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>