<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34u4g/post/2012-03-29T11:07:48</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ril4</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/d406g</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>First of all, welcome back! 

Second, I give these posts an A. Even if I disagree with almost everything in them.

It's obvious (really, it has been since around 302) that this season is be more manic and cartoony. I didn't mind it because I like cartoony when it's well done, and I think it's well done here. That being said, even I will gladly admit that this season's overall direction has been very hard to pin down (ironically, despite the very obvious serialization). I had some moments when I thought the show had lost its way (MM in particular), and others which made me happier than I've ever been before (RCT, Redux, Horror Fiction). Overall, there were more of the latter than of he former. I think everybody's actions are still very much in character (and I really liked Jeff's pill-fueled collapse: it's a great way to show how his Anxiety and narcissism feed each other), but I think also that the show is taking a huge gambit by using an extremely zany tone in stories that are primarily about depression, Anxiety, general confusion and disappointment (and make no mistake, this is what almost every episode this season has been about, except maybe RCT). It's a bold move imo, but it's also risky not only because it can alienate the audience, but also because it can very easily make your show resemble something &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kL3W2WDPu_4&amp;feature=player_detailpage#t=57s"&gt;iHawk&lt;/a&gt; would do. To this you add multiple season-long arcs, and the damn hiatus that threw everything Off its natural

rhythm and it's easy to see why this season is so hard to evaluate as it unfolds. I suspect it will work far better in retrospect, once it's over and everyone can watch the whole thing in one go. The interlacing, season long story arcs may have been a bad idea, both because the hiatus ruined the pacing, but also because maybe comedy (which more than drama has to give its audience a weekly payoff) isn't really meant to be heavily serialized. If anything, Harmon's circle thing is a far more interesting example of serialization than the stuff the show does now. But purely as an experiment, I still enjoy things this season: I love the bright colors (S2 was amazing, but it was also often unpleasantly murky; Epidemiology in particular was very difficult to see), and the character work is still very good. Unlike you, I don't have a very clear image of what Community should be like: S1 and S2 were very different tonally, but they were still exceptional in their own right. I had no real expectation of what S3 should be like, except maybe, that it would be different. It was, and I'm enjoying it still, but I'd be lying if I didn't say I had a little bit of doubt and fear every time a new episode begins. Last year when the show laid an egg like Wine Studies or Applied Anthropology, you knew that next week could set everything right. This time, serialization means that the show needs to see some story lines through to the end, which means that any mistake can potentially propagate through many episodes. What I'm trying to say, is that I kinda dread Chang's arc. But even so, I still think that the show is miles ahead of any comedy on network TV, and that there are only one or two sitcoms on cable that are in the same league as it.

Three more things that I couldn't fit above: 

Inspector Spacetime isn't fan pandering. Random blorgon references may be there to satisfy the fans, but the concept itself is very clearly attached to Troy and Abed's arc.

Few things the show has done so far have satisfied me more than Evil Abed's appearance. Granted, I don't know where they are going with him, but if they are indeed going to use him to explore Abed's more delusional, too-weird-for-its-own-good side, I'm all in. The one thing I disliked about AUC is that the show seemed to gloss over the fact that Abed had retreated into a fantasy and then into a catatonic state as a response to a serious crisis. The episode was cute and heartbreaking, but it also opened up a rather disquieting, almost pathological side of Abed, that was never really commented on. I hope Evil Abed fixes that.

And finally: there was a scene where Dean Pelton literally writhed on the floor because Jeff was so handsome, AND IT WAS THE BEST ONE!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yk4a1</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/contemporary-impressionists,70958/</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T00:30:37+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:07:48+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34u4g</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/contemporary-impressionists,70958/#comment-479560829</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dpa41</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>