<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/225846/post/127724427/comment/327424477</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Profile of the Sociopath 
 
Glibness and Superficial Charm  
 
Manipulative and Conning  
They never recognize the rights of others and see their self-serving behaviors as permissible. They appear to be charming, yet are covertly hostile and domineering, seeing their victim as merely an instrument to be used. They may dominate and humiliate their victims.  
 
Grandiose Sense of Self  
Feels entitled to certain things as &amp;quot;their right.&amp;quot;  
 
Pathological Lying  
Has no problem lying coolly and easily and it is almost impossible for them to be truthful on a consistent basis. Can create, and get caught up in, a complex belief about their own powers and abilities. Extremely convincing and even able to pass lie detector tests.  
 
Lack of Remorse, Shame or Guilt  
A deep seated rage, which is split  and repressed, is at their core. Does not see others around them as people, but only as targets and opportunities. Instead of friends, they have victims and accomplices who end up as victims. The end  justifies the means and they let nothing stand in their way.  
 
Shallow Emotions  
When they show what seems to be warmth, , love and compassion it is more feigned than experienced and serves an ulterior motive. Outraged by insignificant matters, yet remaining unmoved and Cold by what would upset a normal person. Since they are not genuine, neither are their promises.  
 
Incapacity for Love  
 
Need for Stimulation  
Living on the edge. Verbal outbursts and physical punishments are normal. Promiscuity and gambling are common.  
 
Callousness/Lack of Empathy  
Unable to empathize with the pain of their victims, having only contempt for others&amp;#039; feelings of distress and readily taking advantage of them.  
 
Poor Behavioral Controls/Impulsive Nature  
Rage and abuse, alternating with small expressions of love and approval produce an addictive cycle for abuser and abused, as well as creating hopelessness in the victim. Believe they are all-powerful, all-knowing, entitled to every wish, no sense of personal boundaries, no concern for their impact on others.  
 
Early Behavior Problems/Juvenile Delinquency  
Usually has a history of behavioral and academic difficulties, yet &amp;quot;gets by&amp;quot; by conning others. Problems in making and keeping friends; aberrant behaviors such as cruelty to people or animals, stealing, etc.  
 
Irresponsibility/Unreliability  
Not concerned about wrecking others&amp;#039; lives and dreams. Oblivious or indifferent to the devastation they cause. Does not accept blame themselves, but blames others, even for  they obviously committed.  
 
Promiscuous Sexual Behavior/Infidelity  
Promiscuity, child sexual abuse, rape and sexual Acting out of all sorts.  
 
Lack of Realistic Life Plan/Parasitic Lifestyle  
Tends to move around a lot or makes all encompassing promises for the future, poor work ethic but exploits others effectively.  
 
Criminal or Entrepreneurial Versatility  
Changes their image as needed to avoid prosecution. Changes life story readily. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:225846:127724427</id><idPostId>127724427</idPostId><idBlogId>225846</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:225846</id><idBlogId>225846</idBlogId><link>http://www.evenews24.com</link><displayName>Eve News24</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.evenews24.com/2012/03/29/easley-thames-the-king-of-scapegoats/</link><displayName>Easley Thames: The King of Scapegoats</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T23:03:48.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:225846:127724427:327424477</id><link>http://www.evenews24.com/2012/03/29/easley-thames-the-king-of-scapegoats/#IDComment327424477</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T23:03:48.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Easley Thames: The King of Scapegoats by SeanDrake</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>d41d8cd98f00b204e9800998ecf8427e</idEmailMd5><displayName>SeanDrake</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>SeanDrake commented on &lt;a href="http://www.evenews24.com/2012/03/29/easley-thames-the-king-of-scapegoats/"&gt;Easley Thames: The King of Scapegoats&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>