<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m05nnd/update/2012-03-31T18:18:01/3055adfa4de7ccea9fe79e0954871bf8d9c66874c0746487f1af3bd18fc8267e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwon29</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rq8n1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Edacious61 you must work for Al Amendariz at the EPA or Alisa Rich at Wolf Eagle Environmental. The Railroad Commission and Range did extensive research because they don't have the ability to walk away from a case like this. They HAD to protect themselves because the EPA has unlimited authority and could have seriously hurt the value of the company. The EPA is a joke. This is the 3rd case they have been proven wrong in their initial findings. They don't care about facts, they are just pushing a political agenda. 

I don't get why you liberals are so anti-oil and gas drilling. Do you want the price of gasoline to go to $5? Do you want the price of natural gas (which Heats your water and home) to go back to $10? Our country needs the development of our natural resources to get out of this mess we are in. The development of alternative fuels will come, but as of right now it is NOT economical. Just because it is cleaner, that does not mean we need to waste Billions and Billions of dollars on inefficient energy, especially when we are in an Economic Recovery. 

Edacious instead of making these outlandish comments against both Range and the Railroad Commission, let's hear some actual facts. Steve Lipskey deserves to be put in jail for trying to make a quick buck Off Range. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67b8c9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnmw</id></website><link>http://www.star-telegram.com/2012/03/30/3849362/epa-drops-action-against-range.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:48:32+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T22:18:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m05nnd</id><link>http://www.star-telegram.com/2012/03/30/3849362/epa-drops-action-against-range.html#comment-482263064</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cjp47</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>