<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0o31f/post/2012-04-02T06:16:07</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I just experienced sleep Paralysis last night. It actually occurred several times already. As far as I remember it started 6 years ago and I'm still experiencing it up to now. Usually my eyes are open and there is this loud noises. Sometimes I hear screams, it can also be like machine sounds(grinding) or it can be just many voices whispering in my ears. As I do remember I can see our room and the details of it, well, including my room mates. Then I started struggling to move my body, when I was not able to do so, I'll try to call on to my room mates. There are times that I can't  speak and there are times that I thought I'm  already, but they are really not hearing anything but growling. It's also accompanied by difficulty in breathing, as if there is something heavy over my body. In terms of time., it can occur as early as 3 mins. after I closed and up.About waking up, sometimes I'm awaken as my room mates touch me as they hear my growl, other times as I move my head. It is scary when your experiencing it but I Always remember that its just temporary and that I have a God who is watching over me. There is nothing to be afraid of but the Sovereign God.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/erotyu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/nuu0</id></website><link>http://www.pickthebrain.com/blog/sleep-paralysis-what-it-is-and-how-to-avoid-it/</link><postedTime>2011-08-10T21:58:47+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T10:16:07+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0o31f</id><link>http://www.pickthebrain.com/blog/sleep-paralysis-what-it-is-and-how-to-avoid-it/#comment-483399817</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-08-10</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>