<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwledo/post/2012-03-30T12:46:04</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>DAMASCUS // Two months after tanks retook Saqba from rebels, the 
district in eastern Damascus continues to protest against regime control
 and the Free Syrian Army (FSA) is making a gradual comeback.


 A powerful force involving thousands of troops assaulted Saqba at the
 end of January. The operation to reassert authority coincided with the 
Arab League's decision to freeze its observer mission to Syria in the 
face of escalating violence.


Troops from the well-equipped and ultra loyalist Republican Guard, 
commanded by the president's brother, Mahar Al Assad, seized the Sunni 
majority suburb in little more than 48 hours, according to regime 
supporters who saw the attack take place.


It had been held by the FSA, a small band of lightly armed defectors 
who, in preceding weeks, had wrested it from government control, pushing
 out the feared  police.


Since the assault, army checkpoints have been established at 
entrances to the district, and security forces have set up ad hoc bases 
in some of the concrete residential blocks that, together with hundreds 
of furniture workshops, make up much of the suburb.


 At night army units patrol through the area, residents say, often 
shooting into the air or at stray cats and dogs, or chanting their 
loyalty to the ruling Assad family.


Much of the anti-regime graffiti scrawled on walls during the brief 
period of rebel control has been crossed out and replaced with 
pro-regime slogans, including "Assad or no one" and "Assad or we Burn 
the country".


But while the military offensive and a subsequent campaign of Raids 
and arrests reestablished a government presence in the streets, it 
failed to deliver a decisive blow against the uprising.


Deep inside Saqba's maze of streets, alleyways and dirt lots grazed 
by goats, anti-regime messages are still written on the sides of 
buildings, rubbish bins and electrical transformer stations.


Regular protests continue. Smaller than before the military entered, 
activists admit, but still involving as many as 1,000 young 
demonstrators.


 Recently, the FSA has resumed attacks on government checkpoints on 
the outskirts of the area. On Tuesday night heavy clashes were reported 
in Saqba and neighbouring Kafr Batna by the Local Coordination 
Committees LCC), a network of grassroots activists.


A pro-regime craftsman who works in Saqba said guerrilla operations 
had resumed against regime targets inside the security cordon.


"I thought the army entering Saqba had finished everything but now 
the FSA are reborn and they seem to have a new strategy," he said. "They
 leave their weapons in Saqba, come in from outside, carry out their 
attacks and then leave again to hide in the rural areas."


"It [the uprising] is not finished in Saqba, the government doesn't 
have full control and if the troops left the FSA would return and take 
it back," he said.


 At least 29 people were killed in the January assault and hundreds 
more wounded according to Saqba activists and human rights monitors. 
They also say informants working inside the army have told them the 
location of a mass grave, although the continued heavy security presence
 means they have been unable to approach the area to check if the report
 is true.


"We have still not recovered all of the bodies, we're not certain who
 was killed, who is missing who was arrested," said a leading activist 
from the district, who is wanted for failing to report for compulsory 
military service.



 More 


http://www. thenational. ae/news/world/rebels-are-resilient-in-damascus-suburb#full 
 </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dkvsy</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cjnq</id></website><link>http://blogs.aljazeera.net/middle-east/2011/10/20/syria-live-blog</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T16:11:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:46:04+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwledo</id><link>http://blogs.aljazeera.net/middle-east/2011/10/20/syria-live-blog#comment-480938140</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zh24w</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>