<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5ejgn9/update/2011-07-15T20:48:36/ab575285caea45e8c372115e6b17a8a7e3fdea6fc409f34e25c22039eb632d81</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>SINCE WHEN IS REVERSE RACISM ACCEPTABLE....THAT IS A QUESTION, MS. JACKSON LEE.

Hahahahahaha!  What a stupid and VILE woman.  Who in holy h e l l l l  elected this miserable racce baitor to high public office?  Whomever they are, SHAME ON YOU!  The bbblack public servants that continue to liberally use the race card, indiscriminately, to further their lame social agenda's or to secure the 'freebies' they've promised and/or bribed their constituents with,  should be publicly dressed down.  Frankly, this kind of behavior is anti-American.  And that includes Obama himself.  Through Obama's silence, coupled with the very surprising inflammatory statements this radical President made early on in his 'reign' which we now know were 'purposeful' and meant to be divisive and part of the long term strategy of the Obama administration:  mainly  to pit bblacks against whites to insure a strong bbblack vote in  2012.  Knowing they were planning a sharp left turn upon  office Obama instantly working on his  ideological re-engineering of America.  

Question:  Why would successful bllack citizens want their wealth 'redistributed' any more than whtes.  I have news for you tubby...the distrust and of this President and rejection of his agenda crosses the color line.  

This administration  KNEW they would immediately alientate a good deal of the voters that ushered our current Obama nightmare into office and we are talking WHITE voters here,  an enormous white voting block of WHITES.   I blame ACORN Obama and  Eric Holder for giving  a fool like Shelia Jackson Lee the full go ahead to pull the race card without a second thought and to do it whenever needed and often.

How exactly does this insulant, unprincipled  woman account for the enormous favor someone like me, a lily white man, finds with the excellent bbblack politicians emerging on the Republican side?  That I would be proud to vote for.  Does she think because I think Obama is a madman and yet would love to see a Herman Cain or Alan West in our White House that I'm....what?  Am I racist when I'm repulsed by Obama's insane Marxist 'vision', but not so when great conservative, FISCALLY RESONSIBLE bllack politicians come along who don't want to send not only bblacks, but whites to the  'plantation' via the nanny state?'

Can anyone erase the image of this awful woman from their mind's eye when she ignored questions about ObamaCare at her bogus Town Hall?  Questions that were Too hot to handle and so she instead took phone calls and ignored the questions?  Like Obama, she's a 'plant'....a fake.  And she is famous for not returning calls to her constituents.  She should be FIRED.  She is a racist through and through just like her CEO, Obozo who WILL be fired, November 6, 2012.

Have you heard Ms. Jackson Lee?  Reverse racism is worse that out and out racism.  It's the 'lazy' way out.  A cop out.  A crutch.  A LIE...which is so typical of a Wienercrat.  Yesterday a blogger put up some very interesting information on this awful woman and her 'vote getting' tactics and it was stunning.   I hope he reposts it....Shelia Jackson Lee is not just a liar, but a crook.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/gwa1g8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6bwl</id></website><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/debt-ceiling/2011/07/15/jackson-lee-congress-complicating-debt-ceiling-because-obama-black</link><postedTime>2011-07-15T21:04:16+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-07-16T00:48:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5ejgn9</id><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/debt-ceiling/2011/07/15/jackson-lee-congress-complicating-debt-ceiling-because-obama-black#comment-253209338</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8nldh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-07-15</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>