<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3jpc2/update/2012-03-29T18:49:14/80533e3cff5810014b8f0b7ad56503f432cacdb0f86bdc742eae54371430b01a</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fb86</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rifum</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>your getting hammered for that. i read the commets. so i'm putting my bit in. and it's on your side buddy totaly agree with you again. Punk seems to own a colt on this site like you've said. but what has he done to earn a match with stone Cold steve austin? NOthing other then cut one good promo at vince. one promo and only one. What the cm punk marks fail to see is that punk is lossing rating like crazy. I call them marks because unlike real wrestling fans they are unable to admit that their star isn't good enough for this match. Sure punk is a great wrestler i won't deny that and his promos are decent but they are not in austins league. Austin needs brock or taker or rock any one of those three would be worth the match. I'm not totaly sure that compairing orton to austin is totaly right but i see what your getting at, orton hits rko's on anyone who pisses him Off very much like austin did. Ortons promos aren't half as good as austin but i can see your point. back to punk he's not the star for this match it won't work not with a year long buld up it still won't work punk is not as baddass as that one promo and theres nothing going for him aside from his mouth in interviews and twitter. saying austin vs punk would be worth waiting for is like titanic is unsinkable. once you hit iceberg the whole thing is going sink. austin wouldn't be able to cary the match and he wouldn't be able to get punk over enough to make it worth it..</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zbaw2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dhf8</id></website><link>http://www.ewrestlingnews.com/news/3907/steve-austin-vs-cm-punk-match-austin-comments</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:44:02+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:49:14+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3jpc2</id><link>http://www.ewrestlingnews.com/news/3907/steve-austin-vs-cm-punk-match-austin-comments#comment-479987964</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/riz68</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>