<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mjt2ri/update/2012-03-19T17:50:08/0e923e0e612edc235e0f3896d0289d2ecd632fcaa9b6b260b61f2a482efe3361</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mjvhix</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/am7m7</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Well I think you realize that to some extent I am a conservative/libertarian.

I appreciate some of the intent of a stand your ground law. If some dude breaks into my house wielding a weapon, I shouldn't be punished for defending my person or property.

The real problem is that the dude who the spirit of the stand your ground provisions really apply to (in my eyes, anyway) is Trayvon. What sophisttt said earlier in the thread about Trayvon turning into the aggressor or the "threat" is ridiculous; the guy menacing him was Zimmerman, and he had every moral right to "stand his ground" and pound on Zimmerman to make sure that Zimmerman couldn't continue to menace him. 

So while the idea that a law that allows anyone who feels "threatened" to shoot to kill horrifies me (that takes the concept of "stand your ground" to one of "shoot anyone you want for whatever reason you want and then claim "self-defence"")  it really seems like everything here has been turned upside down by the police. They seem to have ignored the reality that guy who was really being menaced, and the guy with the real right to invoke self-defence and to stand his ground — even though I think there is pretty clear evidence from the 9/11 tapes —  was Trayvon.

This reality suggests a bigger picture. The problem isn't conservative lawmakers or policemen. It's &lt;strong&gt; racist &lt;/strong&gt; lawmakers and policemen, who believe that the white will  be the threatened party, and will Always be entitled to self-defence, even when the evidence is clear that they are the aggressor. If they didn't, they would have arrested Zimmerman, breathalyzed him, treated the scene as that of a murder 'til proven otherwise. 

Here's a hypothetical. Let's assume the situation was the same, but that Trayvon was the one packing Heat, and Zimmerman was still an overzealous watchman coming after him. After a struggle where Zimmerman gets him on the ground, Trayvon discharges his weapon and kills Zimmerman. Anyone in this thread (sophisttt?) wanna contend that Trayvon would not be facing the death penalty right now?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6mdaa5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/eyjq</id></website><link>http://m.theatlantic.com/national/archive/2012/03/sanfords-police-chief-is-the-real-victim-of-racism/254723/</link><postedTime>2012-03-19T17:15:50+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-19T21:50:08+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mjt2ri</id><link>http://m.theatlantic.com/national/archive/2012/03/sanfords-police-chief-is-the-real-victim-of-racism/254723/#comment-469406442</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lbgql</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-19</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>