<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miref5/post/2012-03-22T23:09:14</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi6h94</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6adil</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>It's a bad law, if you can reasonably retreat from an escalating situation where it is reasonable to believe that deadly force will eventually be used it is your duty to do so...  who makes you judge and jury when lives are at stake.  If you are packing a fire arm it is no stretch of the imagination that if you are involved in a Heated conflict that the outcome in the end may be decided by deadly force...  the law blurs the lines and both law enforcement and the judicial system are having difficulties with it.  Setting your ego aside for the moment our communities are safer without a law such as this, restoring the duty to retreat in no way interferes with your second amendment rights.

You can read more about what has happened in Florida since the passage of this law &lt;a href="http://www.miamiherald.com/2012/03/22/2708767/number-of-stand-your-ground-cases.html"&gt;&lt;b&gt;here&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; but I will quote what is to me the most significant part of this article.

&lt;blockquote&gt;In the first five years the law was in effect, it was invoked 93 times. In the last year and a half, it has been invoked at least an additional 37 times. "Justifiable homicides" reported to the Florida Department of Law Enforcement have increased threefold since the law went into effect.

Proponents say the law is working, allowing citizens to protect themselves from harm without worrying about legalities in the Heat of the attack.

But the law has also been used to excuse killings in bar brawls, gang shoot-outs and road-rage incidents.

And if history serves, it’s no wonder Zimmerman has not been arrested. Depending on how a police chief, prosecutor or judge interprets the law, which asks them to consider something as nebulous as a man’s state of mind, they may find that under the law Zimmerman was justified in shooting young Martin.

The Martin case is just an example of what can happen when there is no longer a duty to retreat, god forbid your path crosses with some really drunk 20 something year old college student who has never done anything wrong in his life, but on this one drunken binge he starts screwing with you and you decide to Stand Your Ground instead of turning and walking away.  

My father who owned guns made sure that we learned that there was nothing we owned that was worth defending by taking the life of another human being...  a value that I still abide by today..  and no he was no peacenik, to the contrary he was a West Point grad. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y9r6k</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tz1k</id></website><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/sanford-police-chief-bill-lee-steps-down-temporarily-from-trayvon-martin-investigation/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T19:43:20+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T03:09:14+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miref5</id><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/sanford-police-chief-bill-lee-steps-down-temporarily-from-trayvon-martin-investigation/#comment-474173608</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ri31t</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>