<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwyo9l/post/2012-03-30T10:58:51</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3sh8w</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zz9dr</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I agree... 1440p and 1920p isn't ready to be released yet, it's seriously expensive and takes a hell of a lot of power, plus it can actually hurt the eyes if you watch for too long. There's no need to go above 1080p, that's why I think Nintendo made the right choice - they're sticking with the trend which is: We'll do what people are comfortable with in terms of graphics and not go further than needed, but instead we'll focus on evolving gaming and ways to play because that's the most important part of a game... You don't want an amazing looking game that plays terribly and has no substance. I do disagree with you though, the 3DS is capable of the same level as the iPhone, just not in HD... In fact, it's more powerful than Wii. The only thing it has worse than the Wii is the polygon count, yet it can handle better textures than Wii can. I've Always felt (and I love modern tech and HD to death) that HD was brought in too soon - there was so much more to do with SD in terms of gaming and graphics, which the 3DS has proven with games like Resident Evil: Revelations. True, PS3 helped a bit in making HD mainstream but it would have achieved the same just as fast without HD consoles - whereas 3D needed an accessible platform to become accepted by the general consensus. Nintendo's introduction in this generation is Spot-on for me personally - speaking from a technological and strategical angle.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zoiry</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/z5xv</id></website><link>http://www.zeldainformer.com/2012/03/is-the-wii-u-really-more-powerful-than-current-gen-hardware-or-just-as-powerful.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T03:08:53+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T14:58:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwyo9l</id><link>http://www.zeldainformer.com/2012/03/is-the-wii-u-really-more-powerful-than-current-gen-hardware-or-just-as-powerful.html#comment-480827316</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ei7wq</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>