<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mj2mcd/update/2012-03-18T19:38:33/ad8d623d2859446e86674381081bc45900adb6e2faabf6b2b37ec1c8a45aa874</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m90rc5</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a4meq</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>It'd come more like a surprise than a sting. 

The guy's decidedly both less popular &amp; more unpopular than McCain was with the base in 2008, &amp; the base didn't care for McCain. In almost every state primary, &amp; definitely overall, the GOP primary contest is failing to beat enthusiasm numbers going all the way back to Gerald Ford. There's never been a flip-flopper of such Herculean prodigy as Romney, &amp; he's setting a pace for telling nationally-covered lies about the incumbent that's going to break the all-time previous record before the summer even arrives; the only thing worse would be if he belonged to a religious cult, or if he was fatally compromised from credibly opposing the incumbent on some huge social issue (like, I dunno, health care insurance). Other than the usual outliers that  arise in polling to the double-margin (A plus/minus of 5% nineteen times in twenty in fact yields higher than a 1 in 20 ratio of outliers - quite apart from some pollsters *Cough* Rasmussen *Cough* focussing on either registered or likely voters 8 months in advance of an election, using push polling questions &amp; sticking to landlines only). Plus he's right in there while his party apparatus is all it can to turn Off women, Hispanics &amp; just about every other minority that they don't think wants Iran bombed, the working class, youth, students, the unemployed, the educated, &amp; we all know they'll get around to just about every other demographic conceivable by the time the general election gets under way.

But in the Age of Teh Stupid, stupid outcomes just aren't excluded:

http://www.commoner.org.uk/10graeber.pdf 

even the loser winning (2000).</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6e4in0</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tz1k</id></website><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/mitt-romney-gop-needs-a-nominee-who-has-the-capacity-to-raise-money-to-be-competitive/</link><postedTime>2012-03-18T19:28:32+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-18T23:38:33+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mj2mcd</id><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/mitt-romney-gop-needs-a-nominee-who-has-the-capacity-to-raise-money-to-be-competitive/#comment-468622052</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7zl7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-18</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>