<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mvuomo/update/2012-02-28T09:43:02/4da0801ed862d24524ce94de9ed9e03529b7481aeba10d0ccbc48bcf5fb25d4d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Trying to get the Scientologists to provide credible independent studies verifying Hubbard's claims as a requirement for getting their stuff on the shelves is brilliant.  That's exactly the blind Spot that they cannot possibly think about or the entire foundation for belief in the cult will come crashing down.  If there's no evidence that any of Hubbard's "research" product actually makes your life better, then why are you involved in this cult that inhales every dollar you'll ever make and treats you so abominably?  

The idiotic response that your librarian received in response to his request for scientific validation is the only way cult members can cope with the Zen mind bomb of being asked to prove that any of it works -- they see the word "scientific" and they associate that with "nuclear physics" and then send in the (bogus) bio that points up Hubbard's laughably fabricated background claiming expertise in the field.  They can't allow themselves to think any more deeply than that or nagging doubt will creep in and eventually cause them to leave.  It's the mechanism behind spokesmodel Karin Pouw's cut-and-paste replies that are so creepy because the replies are triggered by simply matching words with some key words in the question instead of actually answering it.  You know, the e-mails to media outlets that Always end with something about "bitter apostates."  

The persistent e-mails from Scientology book people remind me of those annoyingly persistent Nigerian "419" scammers, the ones that send out all those e-mails in broken third-world English from Mrs. Mutawumba Makatali asking for "Dear Friend" to help moving $31,000,000 (THIRTY ONE MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS) from the RESERVE BANK OF BURKINA FASO into a US bank, for which you will receive 10% of the money.  

Some people have tried to reduce the profits of the Nigerian scammers by "scambaiting," showing interest in the proposition but putting the (often not too bright) scammers through all sorts of Herculean labors before they get the money from their victims.  The idea is to waste as much of the scammer's time as possible without taking too much of your own, so they eventually give up and quit the scam business.  There are web sites that detail how to do this, and it has turned into something of a sport.  Some of the stories of what people have gotten the 419 scammers to do before being sent the "victim's" money are quite funny.  

The cult has the cash to keep printing up millions of copies of books that will go straight to the landfill, but since their membership is declining, the weak Spot in the library scam is the  (increasingly scarce) staff time. The more staff time that librarians can waste (without wasting too much of their own) in order to get on the shelves that they will have to move on to something else.  I can see some of these librarians putting their heads together to come up with increasingly challenging hoops for the Scientology staff to jump through.  And the poor staff will have to struggle gamely to compile the needed answers to "just one more question before we can shelve your works prominently in our 'featured reference book' section, which all the students have to walk past when they enter the library."  

For example, in response to the survey asking what criteria the library would use in deciding how to shelve A/V materials, the librarians could shoot back a survey of their own: "Please provide a list of &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; college or university libraries our size who have actually shelved your materials and who have not thrown them out as we have done in the past. Please be sure to include name and phone number of a librarian contact, their length of service with this particular library, the number of undergraduate and graduate students at their institution, the population of the town where the school is located (we're only interested in institutions in small towns of under 25,000 people, like we are), and what brand of cover protectors each library has used to protect the covers of the CD's from scratching."  Then caution them that inaccurate answers to the survey questions, for example, leaving a single school out of the survey, would be grounds for permanent rejection due to fraud.  

Imagine how it would feel to be a Scientology book person telling Miscavige "we almost had a small college in Iowa put our stuff on the Featured Reference Book section at the entrance to the library, but I couldn't get them a list of all the similar libraries that had put our books on the shelves in time."   Another one bites the dust and ends up in the RPF!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yonwnx</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rpyi</id></website><link>http://blogs.villagevoice.com/runninscared/2012/02/scientology_drives_librarians_nuts.php</link><postedTime>2012-02-28T13:04:49+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-28T14:43:02+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mvuomo</id><link>http://blogs.villagevoice.com/runninscared/2012/02/scientology_drives_librarians_nuts.php#comment-451246744</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lxzrl</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>