<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw75vy/post/2012-03-30T15:00:02</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>My local neighborhood library (Seminole Heights Library, in Tampa, Fl) is filled to the brim with tweens and teens every afternoon after school.  Sometimes kids have to wait outside until there's room for more to go in.  Most of these kids are lower income.  They spend their library hours doing homework, looking up stuff on the internet, chatting quietly together, or playing games.  Their behavior is surprisingly good.  

People who think that libraries are passe need to go to the library and see how many people are there using it--especially after school hours.  There are homeless applying for jobs, people applying for unemployment or foodstamps, people using the internet, people reading magazines, people checking out books, people asking the research librarian how to find information when Google doesn't help. 

On line, the library system offers various specialized research sites (Did someone want the OED?  How about Brittanica?  Lexus/Nexus?  All of the NYT?), ebooks. and the ability to access the catalog, order books, and manage your withdrawn books.  

In addition, a good library Acts as a "Third Place"--a place where people can go to hang out (just like the kids) and not have to spend money.  For the mom of two pre-schoolers with no money for Starbucks can sit and read a magazine while her children paw through picture books.  It's like a park, but with Heat and air conditioning, and a security guard that won't let the three year old out the door if he attempts to escape.  

The library also provides activities and events for kids and adults.  Want to learn genealogy?  How about Florida gardening?  Want to ask a lawyer who needs a will or a trust?  How about a one hour class on how to use your Kindle?

Sure, you can get a second hand computer for $50 but that's not much help to the family that has a problem buying $15 sneakers for their eight year old.  Sure, I can buy ebooks for my Kindle (and I do love my Kindle) but I read a lot and frankly, I can't afford all the books I want to read.  

Libraries are precious.  They are changing but they will continue to be essential for a healthy community.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hlgbu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/xmw5</id></website><link>http://www.theatlanticcities.com/arts-and-lifestyle/2012/03/are-privatized-public-libraries-so-bad/1583/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T12:20:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:00:02+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw75vy</id><link>http://www.theatlanticcities.com/arts-and-lifestyle/2012/03/are-privatized-public-libraries-so-bad/1583/#comment-481075785</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/m2tgr</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>