<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3y9gl/update/2012-03-29T02:17:43/f2c586e3932d33e10636632d96cc48dbaf6a3669cd39c2f560b50c25486b0927</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>My issue is that while video games do have the ability to be classified as art, they are also by their very nature a piece of software. As such that can be at least augmented taking into account the feedback of those who use said piece of software. There is really no reason that the game/software could be augmented to allow both the classic endings and a potential set of endings that take into account the desire of players who have invested time, money and emotion. The video game industry needs to take issues like this into account and needs to take them seriously. Especially if next gen video game systems effectively lock players into the games that they purchase. 

Major game studios like EA, Activision, etc seem to believe that their dominance of the game market means they can shrug  criticism, but this isn't necessarily true. There is not only the possibility of potential buyers avoiding their products due to such practices, but also the potential for a systemic effect to take place in the game market. Even in today's society in which video games are king, there will  exist the potential for an over saturation of incomplete and bad games in the market which will push players away from consoles and over the the home PC/Mac market. In this market they will have to compete against smaller and leaner studios that haven't broken any trust. 

I will be honest that I have basically written  EA, not just because I feel the ending to one game is bad, but because of how they handled the situation. The really bad part is that I will no longer preorder any title from now on, which is that systemic effect I was writing about. I have been Burned enough by a variety of studios that I will wait for reviews to come in first. Also bad news for gaming magazines, but I will no longer look to them for reviews. I will wait until I see the actual gamers speak on forums and Youtube before spending the often times near $70 to own a game. The difference between a movie and a game is that I can spend $10+ to see a bad movie and simply shrug it  as a lark. At least I only spend 2 hours, and I can pig out on popcorn and a Coke. A video game requires a lot of invested time, and a real hit to the wallet. 

EA is in a unique position of proclaiming that while games are art, they are also art born out of software that can be modded. This alone means that an original vision can stand, while opening up more interaction from the player. Interaction is what these games are about, and that is the name of the game. The true art of gaming is in the interactive experience the gamer has, and that is what is to be shrived for. When game companies forget that landfills fill of unsold copies are not too far behind. 

Just my 2 cents there.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h0hfm</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t9us</id></website><link>http://www.ibtimes.com/articles/321029/20120329/mass-effect-3-ending-fans-protest-analysis.htm</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T01:51:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T06:17:43+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3y9gl</id><link>http://www.ibtimes.com/articles/321029/20120329/mass-effect-3-ending-fans-protest-analysis.htm#comment-479144352</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ljs2y</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>