<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/e2dqor/update/2011-11-14T18:59:30/c257a896c43629f0959451181a281fc89f1b0421e098ca79b1b4e535a16aa286</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>9/11 was an inside job, nearly free fall speed for buildings that were "desinged" to take the impact of plane. Also, bulidings made in other parts of the world, in the same 1970 Era, or later have also taken simalar inccents, such as the fires that happened in the trade centers, why is it that they were able to stand after the Burning?, some up too 20+ hrs, still remain standing. The elements that are in the jet fule mixture, also do no produce enough Heat to vaoprize titanium, which is a major metal in the planes engines, which was never found, along with any other part of the plane. How is it that it just so happens that 4 planes on the same day all vaporize in accidents, all which were first, second, thrid and fourth cases known...too many odd questions left unawnsered, funny thing is people complain that the states would never kill there "own", but yet how many of there "own" have died fighting this senseless war?, created to make money for the rich, and keep the poor, poor. I live in Canada, and i think shit is messed up, all over the place...no matter what way you spin it, if you think like this your a "hippie", or unrealiztic, why is that? and why are we that? why arent you looking deeper into what your told, why live judging a book by its cover...</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/c02cwb</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/znv4</id></website><link>http://topdocumentaryfilms.com/iraq-secret-war-files-wikileaks-special/</link><postedTime>2011-02-25T18:43:03+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-11-14T23:59:30+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/e2dqor</id><link>http://topdocumentaryfilms.com/iraq-secret-war-files-wikileaks-special/#comment-363195947</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rh80k</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-02-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>