<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/cosi9w/update/2011-06-19T15:46:53/781db84144ac59b1783a2e70bf99667ae4202b5ce5c43f7e7fbbbdbd7e28cb68</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/cosjxo</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I see good alernatives.  Right now, I'm liking Perry.  I've been hoping for a while he would step forward.  Plain speaker.  Has no problem outing Obama out for the colossal liar and job destroyer  he is.  For the NIGHTMARE he is.  A successful Governor (which is what we need...not a 'fake chosen one' who served for 10 minutes in the Illinois Senate,  a radical and ex-community organizer who stold his election form one of his 'own people' and who voted 'present' so as to not 'leave a trail'.)  But he left horrendous d a m n i n g , videos which out him as a progressive, liberal radical that McCain and the lame stream press NEVER USED TO VETT THIS PRESIDENT.  Sarah Palin (a superior Governor) who should have been in the White House (save for being strapped to the back of a spineless RINO whose lips couldn't form the words Marxist, Socialist or communist) now going on her third year is not out of the running yet.  Yes sure, she's nearly been destroyed by a well planned, well funded team of assassins because she's a threat to progressive liberal ideology.  But Palini keeps grinding her high heel into Obama's instep and running over his feet with her bus and she will Always be my choice.   If not, she'll continue to rain over Obama like a ton of bricks...destroy her?  No, they created a fire breathing monsters.  

Mr. ACORN, is that your dumb a s s , singed by one little 'empty headed', lady from Wasilla, that we smell Burning?

I like Michelle Bachmann who plants herself right in front of the camera and outs Obama as a thief and liar every time she speaks.   Can you even imagine this awful President in a debate with Bachmann?   No more RINO'S.  No Wienercrats.  November 6 will be the new Independence Day from a tyrant and from big gov or this nation will refuse the alternative to this 'vacationer in Chief' and to all of his stifling, intrusive KGB policies.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/gnvcdi</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6bwl</id></website><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/mitt-romney/2011/06/19/mccain-graham-rip-romney-foreign-policy</link><postedTime>2011-06-19T18:22:19+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-06-19T19:46:53+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/cosi9w</id><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/mitt-romney/2011/06/19/mccain-graham-rip-romney-foreign-policy#comment-229960618</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8nldh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-06-19</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>