<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mww18x/update/2012-03-31T12:48:31/c2e6162f4efea097b7d4bda422f8d519e522560f2a7dc5eee057b2cc97c82380</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw114q</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8lqwk</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>In referring to the case as a complex one, I was thinking primarily about the severability issue.  The position adopted by the government was that the Court, if bringing down the mandate, should also bring down guaranteed issue and community rating.  That seems to me an unwise position, inviting the Court to mix and match provisions in the manner of a legislative markup session.  It is no  that the primary ,and perhaps even the only, reason the government took that tack was to reinforce the argument that the mandate was essential.  As I said in my initial post, if the mandate were to be struck, I would hope the government would still walk away with community rating, guaranteed issue, and the Medicaid expansion.

Secondarily, I saw potential complexity arising if a conservative majority for striking the mandate  sought to articulate a limiting principle that somehow  between "Wick-Burn/Raich" and the instant case.  If that effort is as hopeless as urban legend (among many others) think, it may suffice to say that writing the conservative side of Bush v. Gore was complex as well.  Utter junk to be sure, but complex utter junk.

As to whether "Wick-Burn/Raich" can be actually distinguished from the case at hand, I am a skeptic, but ultimately an agnostic.  A few years back, a unit of local government in Georgia decided to require that each household own a gun.  I think that such an exercise of the police power may well touch on a fundamental right to be left alone, free to decline to enter contracts one deems repugnant. I, for one, would not be entirely unhappy if a majority of the Court announced such a right.  Were it to do so, moreover, it would surely make the rule one of general applicability and there would be no need for the "this trip only" antics of Bush v Gore.  

All that said, I think the federal interest in the mandate is compelling and the mandate is narrowly tailored to that interest.  The mandate should survive even if such a right is announced.  Is the determination of compelling interest and  narrow fitting a simple one?  Not really. 

For one thing, perhaps only a catastrophic policy need be mandated.  As it turns out, the lowest coverage option under the ACA has an actuarially determined deductible which varies  on market conditions.  Current estimates of what the deductible will by range between $2000 and $6500.  Since either level satisfies the current requirements for tax favored treatment of health savings accounts, I would indeed say that the mandate is narrowly tailored to achieve the Act's objectives.  The fact that the Solicitor General did not make that very point when Scalia badgered him about catastrophic coverage is itself an indication that a full analysis of a clash between an exercise of the Commerce power and some sort of important right to be free of repugnant contracts is not so simple.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67moej</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ydw9</id></website><link>http://motherjones.com/node/170036</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:07:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T16:48:31+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mww18x</id><link>http://motherjones.com/node/170036#comment-481987677</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rycfo</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>