<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ojnd/post/2012-03-29T19:42:01</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>So far it looks like Sveum has been true to his word. The players that truly earned Spots got them, with the possible exception of DeJesus. But DeJesus is a proven major leaguer, and even tho he appears to be on the decline, his track record indicates that his ST #'s are not anything to be too worried about. He probably should not start the year at the top of the order tho. Wells, was just in a tough Spot, other than Dempster the rest of the rotation is younger than him. The Cubs do need to see how they all fare, and keep Wells ready and waiting in AAA. Same is true for T. Wood. There is no need to trade either of them. Besides, Garza and/or Dempster could be gone in a few months. I believe Campana, may still stick as a fifth OF, and just be used as a PR and sparingly as a defensive replacement. Although, he might be better Off in AAA as well to work on his hitting and his defensive skills. He still does not track a flyball very well, but he can make up for this by outrunning the ball at times. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zuhht</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lz6q</id></website><link>http://chicago.cubs.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120329%26content_id=27735300%26notebook_id=27735304%26vkey=notebook_chc%26c_id=chc</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T21:45:19+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T23:42:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ojnd</id><link>http://chicago.cubs.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120329%26content_id=27735300%26notebook_id=27735304%26vkey=notebook_chc%26c_id=chc#comment-480032648</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cs77v</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>