<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk14jk/update/2012-03-26T11:35:25/8e68c05f6c92ebf256940c67f179ef40e3e0a0e738e5ae25d5e4da7869244147</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mku415</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cxxx2</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Jeremy, I take it you have never worked in a Help Desk/IT environment. Things that us power users/geeks/etc look at, adapt to, and even think are advances are things that the average user will shun.

I work for a company at just the right size such that we have an executive who has worked more successfully over the years at preventing us from upgrading his secretary's PC as well as his own PC. Therefore, they both are still using PCs with Pentium 3 processors running Win98. The issue? His only PC need is to update information in an Approach database, and he wants nothing to do with newer database applications written in .NET, Access VBA, etc. Even though they work exactly the same, they LOOK different.

I can go further with an even more common thread, where people need shortcuts located on their desktop in very specific Spots. If you think OCD is a fairly rare disorder, go work in a Help Desk job. As soon as something doesn't work the way it has or is located where it was for "eternity", you will get a number of phone calls about where it is now for a few weeks at the least.

It is not about "us"; the people who visit these web sites and read these articles. Windows 8 success is based on what the "other" people will think about it. I have 5 PCs in various states of shipment and delivery so far for family and friends who want nothing to do with Win8 after showing them my Win8 ToGo thumbdrive installation. I have a short list of another 20+ people who I know are still running XP/Vista PCs/laptops who I need to show what is in store for them if they wait until this fall to upgrade.

Most if not many of these people also have and use tablets and smartphones. It is not an unwillingness to use or learn the features and UI. They want the PC in the house to do the heavy lifting and other things like banking that they will not and do not want to do on their tablets and smartphones. As such a PC is not meant to look and  like a tablet/smartphone in their opinion (and mine too, but I will and can deal with it). As ungainly as it might seem, they want the start menu, taskbar, and desktop just the way it has been since win95/98.

Now with a lot of this said, I do agree with you on many points you make about the benefits that Windows 8 has. However, my beef is not with what Microsoft it doing with Windows 8, but rather how everyone else if going to deal with Windows 8. Quite frankly, for my family and for a few of my friends, I will WANT to install Teamviewer in such a manner that I will not need them to do anything for me to remote into their PC. I just know between work, family, and friends that I am going to get that many questions, comments, and complaints that I will probably want to move to Siberia.

The only TRUE FLAW with Windows 8 that I see is the touch screen mentality. As someone who has suffered from carpal tunnel, and who also has a pinched nerve in his neck with make lifting my arm troublesome at times, am I the only one who thinks that touch screen monitors in a desktop environment is a situation that moves from bad to worse? As it is now, my monitor is just out of Reach of my arm. It is a littler further than average but I have really good eyesight. Again, being in IT I see monitors placed at all sort of distances, and quite frankly most of them would make using a touch screen quite uncomfortable if not impossible. I would make the assumption that moving the touch screen monitor into a range to make touch screen use more comfortable would probably then make it uncomfortable for the user to read the screen. 

So which is it? Which is preferable? Reading the monitor, or touching it? I'll bet that since everyone or I guess nearly everyone to this point has been using a mouse, will want to stick with using the mouse. Note: by everyone I mean the average non-techie power user computer person.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66dfnh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/r7w0</id></website><link>http://preview.pcmag.com/article2/0,2817,2402031,00.asp</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T15:07:41+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T15:35:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk14jk</id><link>http://preview.pcmag.com/article2/0,2817,2402031,00.asp#comment-476475403</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hp082</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>