<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msjx4y/update/2012-03-28T08:11:39/46e605cf2843cc18db870048bc1f2b3a85ac9055db724e1c9b3f9dd677316235</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msx86q</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/r2d2j</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Harvey,
When you say, "No I do that because people need it especially when loved one's have dies and income stops, ceases or is interrupted," you are telling us prayers are not being answered and gods are doing nothing.  And you are telling us you know it.  Fact is, you are so convinced that your god never has done anything and never will that you must do what Christians have Always done: do something yourself and then tell the lie that your god did it.  It is indeed a conspiracy, Harvey.  You all agree among yourselves to lie about the true causes of things to the point of lying about things you've done yourself.  You can't be truthful to yourself, each other, or anyone else.

If your god was at work we would be able to tell.

When, you say "No, I take my children to the doctor because they need regular checkups 
and i love them enough to be concerned about their health," again you are telling us gods are useless and they have no force or affects in the universe.  Christian Scientists have more faith than you do, Harvey, and here in the US every year they barbarically allow several hundred children to die from easily cured diseases and infections.  Those good Christians, using even more lies about faith, stand by as their children die of things like diabetes, urinary tract infections, ear infections, appendicitis, Flu, epileptic seizures, and meningitis.  When you have the good sense to demonstrate your true materialism by turning to completely materialistic medicine, those worthless bastards are clinging to the powerlessness of Christian faith.  People like you will scream that a human embryo must be forced to go full term and be brought into the world, but when you fellow Christians in their exercise of faith allow a living, breathing, already-born child to die you do nothing.

You said, &lt;blockquote&gt;Let's see, I've seen him raise the dead, heal the sick...in fact I have a
 lady in our church that was diagnosed with an autoimmune disease by her
 doctor. We prayed regarding that conditions specifically and she 
produced the medical record that that disease is no longer in her body. 
In fact the doctor had never seen anything like it before. So I can only
 say that God did that. He's done many other things as well, you don't 
have the time and I don't have the energy to tell you here in this 
forum.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

This is a lie, Harvey.  The Christian Scientists have website of cures following prayers, but they are meaningless.  If your god was of value in healing the sick doctors would use it first, your god would be the go-to guy.  But, that's not what's seen.  In circumstances like you outlined here, the Christianity lie-machine goes into full gullibility gear and Christians just accept each other's tales of miracles and answered prayers.  These imagined miracles derive from ignorance, credulity, and superstition-thick social circumstances.  If your god was actually working, Harvey, the numbers would show that praying leads begets miracles more often than not praying, but that's not what is seen.  Income begets miracles.  Education begets miracles.  Praying does nothing.

Some fundamentalist Christian friends recently had a nephew die young of cancer.  The doctors predicted him to live six months; he died in three weeks.  That was no miracle, but they would have claimed a miracle if he had lived six months after a three-week-to-live prediction.  You Christians are just lying to each other, Harvey.

And, do you really think you can say "I've seen him raise the dead" and get away with it.  Harvey, you lie to prop up your Christian social superstitions.  You lie more than some Christians and less than others.  But, the lying costs us all dearly.  People, like you, who cannot accept and deal with the world as it is hinder humanity's capacity to make the world a better place.  Pathological hope is a defect, not a virtue.  Allowing your ignorance to be the basis for something you so desperately want, miracles, means you have reserved a special place in your mind for ignorance.  It is ignorance which makes the miracle-making in your Christian social club possible.  Take away the ignorance and the miracles and answered prayers go right along with it.

If you claims were true, we would all be able to see it.  We scientists would be right their identifying how to best structure your prayers for optimum affect.  As yet, however, no prayer has ever been answered supernaturally, so there is nothing to study.
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l5xdh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry26</id></website><link>http://debunkingchristianity.blogspot.com/2012/03/more-criticisms-from-dr-reppert-on-otf.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T19:51:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T12:11:39+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msjx4y</id><link>http://debunkingchristianity.blogspot.com/2012/03/more-criticisms-from-dr-reppert-on-otf.html#comment-478298529</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dl6hi</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>