<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3bh6y/post/2012-03-29T14:32:17</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This is not a new concept and from someone who sold cars, you're inviting a lot of game playing and a Headache.  Do a little research on the internet. There are several excellent websites that you can get pricing and invoice information from.  You can even find out what people in your area are buying them for.  I would not give two $hits for any client who bought from me this way.  I would only take mooch deals, like his, if I could fit it into a weekend bonus.  You buy the lowest price, you are practically guaranteed the salesperson will do anything for you, but give you the keys. I might just take the stickers Off and send you on your way, because you didn't pay for a cat wash or detail.  If you have any questions or issues, go pound sand. You didn't pay for any type of customer service or customer care.  That easily works for a small majority, but the reality is most people need help with financing or some shred of customer service.  Additionally, if dealer financing is what you need, that low price you paid will cost you in financing.  This pathetic mooch just gave you the tip of the iceberg.   Suck ever cent of profit from the transaction and see where it gets you.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/d9l9xe</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/b703</id></website><link>http://bigthink.com/ideas/41819</link><postedTime>2012-01-05T18:56:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:32:17+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3bh6y</id><link>http://bigthink.com/ideas/41819#comment-479734209</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-01-05</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>