<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m7n35b/update/2012-02-26T14:32:22/ea279deb1e352b34f22a36fc8bad70588d244b59770e98747ccce87349979fa0</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mzi914</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ltjsi</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Rod no need to be so pessimistic.   If it were the dark ages I would be tied on the stake next to you as we were both about to be Burned to death for blasphemy.  

I truly believe organized religion is on it's last legs.  In 25 years when is will be more socially acceptable to be an open atheist and not have to worry about truly hurting your grand parents feelings that your going to be sent to a place to eternal torment by their piety, insecure and jealous god.  A god who is smart enough to create &amp; design the entire Universe but  seems short on cash.  

Religion is going to morph into some cotton candy feel good new age spiritual  hippy let's smoke some bud and listen to some happy music.  The fire and brimstone types will make noise but no one is going to pay attention to them and their tin foil hats.   

We live in an amazing Universe that is filled with more wonder and awe then anything thing I have ever read in some 2000 year old book about the mythology of middle eastern sheep herders.  

Life Always finds new ways to survive.  I am not saying we should trash the earth.  I have a feeling in 500 years history will look back at us as the "locust generation" who only cared about ourselves not thinking that we needed to be stewards our or precious world.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yfkom7</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/hwbb</id></website><link>http://www.time.com/time/health/article/0,8599,2107544,00.html</link><postedTime>2012-02-24T11:56:15+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-26T19:32:22+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m7n35b</id><link>http://www.time.com/time/health/article/0,8599,2107544,00.html#comment-449433526</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dgeex</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>