<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3s85w/update/2012-03-29T23:08:09/30eee5452db887d7ef9d98767dab34dc89334af04bb76431f6686082bd6b7d5f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>In my experience, it's definitely true that many doctors hate being questioned, and often become offended or annoyed if you question them at all. And that they sometimes prescribe unnecessary medicine. But for those who might be coming to Japan, don't worry that you are doomed to have a bad experience! (And I speak from many bad experiences).

I've probably visited doctors more often here in Japan in just a few years compared with most foreigners coming here. Two long stretches because of mysterious illnesses and a third due to pregnancy and childbirth. I found that most doctors I saw were actually very forthright in telling me what they "thought" was wrong, even though nearly all of them couldn't find anything wrong (and most of them hadn't studied overseas or anything). They kept telling me it was all in my head and that I should see a psychiatrist, even though I knew there was something wrong. (This was actually when I had labrynthitis, a deep inner ear viral infection, and it took months and a trip back to the States to finally get a diagnosis). You're right though, in that if/when I questioned the doctors at all, they got upset. If I said I had seen another doctor about a second opinion, they told me bluntly I should just see that other doctor. I think some of it has to do with the fact these are men with egos, as the women doctors I've seen in Japan aren't like this at all and much more helpful (but I've also seen a handful of helpful/kind male doctors). My case was kind of extreme, and we didn't live in a major city like Tokyo, so we had less options too (and I saw maybe 4 or 5 ENTs, on top of various other specialists, got an MRI and other tests done at the hospital). 

One thing too is that some doctors won't tell you they are doing something before they do it. When I was giving birth, they said they wouldn't do an episiotomy, but ended up doing it without telling us (and I wasn't thrilled). They needed to do it, understandably, but at least saying something like "OK, I need to do an episiotomy now" would have been nice. I also had an issue from a toenail that had been pulled up from playing soccer, and grown back more ingrown, and one side had become swollen and red so we went to a podiatrist. He looked at it, and before I knew what was happening he had grabbed it and clipped  the ingrown part (which hurt incredibly bad as it was swollen/tender). Perhaps for a lot of people this kind of method could actually be a good thing, so I'm not necessarily bashing it, but it isn't for me. 

However, some of the doctors, including the OBGYN we ended up going with (we saw two before deciding to go with him), was friendly and understanding, let us ask questions and such. Some of the nurses were the opposite, though, but the rest were helpful. 

As for medicine, I've never been prescribed anything with a strange number or anything like that. But I've definitely been prescribed unnecessary medicine, like antibiotics for a Cold (which I didn't take). Although I found some websites that allow you to look up the medicine you've been prescribed (mostly in Japanese, but some in English), so you can understand exactly what the doctor gave you, whether he/she or the pharmacist gave a good explanation or not. Not that the doctors Always prescribe you pointless medicine, so it's not necessarily wise to just not take anything they give you, but if you aren't sure about it, it helps to look it up. Or even, ask your doctor from your home country if that's something they prescribe. I've written up something about those websites though, if interested. They've definitely been helpful to me!

Anyway, I should also say that I've had just as many bad experiences with doctors in the U.S. (the ones that also hate being questioned). You would think the point is for doctors to try to help people, but so many seem to take their position to their heads or something. In my experience, you just have to keep looking until you find the helpful/kind ones, because they are out there! Even in Japan. 

But, sometimes I wish I could find one like Dr. House...</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ztgyt</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/8hh</id></website><link>http://www.tofugu.com/2012/03/29/why-arent-japanese-doctors-telling-the-truth/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:08:57+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T03:08:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3s85w</id><link>http://www.tofugu.com/2012/03/29/why-arent-japanese-doctors-telling-the-truth/#comment-480186322</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8coly</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>