<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0ozeo/update/2012-04-02T05:17:23/fdba698a1b5ad8639dc2bdac894efe87bb26621c390f808d7a75adc72235e5d4</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This and previous regimes have fooled themselves into thinking that loud mouthed selfish minority pressure groups represent the majority. Employ the services of lobbyists with special access and you get policy enacted and changed. The government has become nothing more than a representation of minority self interests and insider trading via lobbying. He who  loudest gets heard, and there are plenty of narrow minority groups that have very loud voices, get enough rent a rabble on the streets and you get your way, smash up a city centre Burn down enough buildings and you suddenly get the attention of the ruling class. 

Think of all this social democrat regimes policy 'initiatives' thus far, they are almost all deeply unpopular, they are almost exclusively designed for and on behalf of small minorities. What policies can you think of so far enacted have majority public support? Oh yes cutting government spending you say, and yet the regime is spending and borrowing more than ever, the EU/Euro/CAGW fraud/banksters/quango empires/the foreign aid scandal, spending money like its going out of fashion.

Everything this social democrat regime stands for is anathema to the majority of the British public, a regime built on and supported by lies, a ruling class elite who look on the vast majority with disdain bordering on outright hatred, we the majority are being ignored and abused as minorities prosper as never before. Its time we showed this ruling class elite who is really in charge, its time we took collective action to knock these Puffed up ponces down a peg or three.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6v932u</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/politics/david-cameron/9179475/Tory-MPs-round-on-David-Cameron-and-George-Osborne.html</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T20:56:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T09:17:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0ozeo</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/politics/david-cameron/9179475/Tory-MPs-round-on-David-Cameron-and-George-Osborne.html#comment-483374548</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8w0iq</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>