<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/237539/post/79176265/comment/328431242</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>WASHINGTON journalist Qi Meng Zhu correspondent Zhang Hui) Early in a flame claiming the Guangqumen High School Class Hongzhi students Cui is  to a house. The face of teachers and students $ 80,000 donations,though insufficient to re-built homes,merely Choi is  apt feel favor a lukewarm spring. Meanwhile, he likewise made a unbelievable decision: retain only five million donation to rebuild their homes, and 30,000 yuan donated to the school to help more needy students. The school said that the money to set up because dreadful blaze night lost their homes Guangqumen High School is a Class 2 of the Hongzhi Health Cui  who lives among Miyun County, Gong Zhuang village Early that daytime a sudden flame amid his family and the home of a pleat scalded only a few walls. fifth day morning I was Hongli wake up and base that the household has a Burn a man destroying open the window and ran out of watching the raging fires, the grandfather said: emancipate took the newborn writing Come rescued. In the annihilate our home dresses were flamed to the ground who had pillaged several textbooks. Burn Cui  a lodging by the kin of the grandmother. subsequently school teachers amongst family visits telephone that the situation immediately with rice,hermes bag, flour and condolences to Kim arrived by the Miyun Gong Zhuang village When the educate educator inquired apt wear one hundred dressing Choi and his parents are  apt have any difficulty in school apt assistance parents in plain equitable advert three things: children\'s paperback Burning did not school uniforms,educate Class Hongzhi tube Orchestra hair saxophone Burned do not know the school can assistance solve. School chairmen apt make emotionally Cui pleased a: Guangqumen High School and the school of two thousand teachers and students, what do never be afraid. brotherhood valuable contributions to attempt apt others February 13, 2009,mulberry handbags, the 1st daytime of Guangqumen High School CHUI is pleased to an initiate activities,impartial one a m to heave $ 500 million donated by teachers and students love money. In addition apt the money, teachers and students spontaneously bought blankets, winter dresses shampoo and other daily necessities, handed Cui pleased the hands. Guangqumen High School Vice-Chancellor Li Zhiwei,understand Cui  to re-build a house,as well because students and parents to donate bricks and furniture. a night lost their homes,mulberry bags,yet receive eight million amid donations,mulberry bags, Cui  not to Anxiety plan how to use the money to cover their own dormitory But after a discussion and parents, made a amazing decision: adopt only 50,000 yuan of donations apt rebuild their homes, the remaining $ 30,hermes kelly bags,000 donated apt the school to assistance extra needy students. Guangqumen High School Vice-Chancellor Li Zhiwei, said the school will admire this decision of the children and parents, the school want be Cui  surrounded the nominate of the establishment . According to reports,hermes Birkin handbags, this is the 1st time that the secondary educate aboard behalf of the individual students apt establish scholarships. In addition to donations, the CUI is pleased ambition all contributions chapter of the alive materials handed over apt the educator apt handle with. moved to migrate,but not amazing moved,hermes handbag,merely never surprised, because the Class Hongzhi students have one characteristic: appreciation and willing to share, According to reports,hermes bag,mulberry outlet, the such instances namely not the circumstance within Class Hongzhi. Last anniversary the students of a Class Hongzhi principals scholarship of two,000 yuan,merely likewise come up with $ an,000 donated to schools. There is likewise a student received only 20 greenbacks of royalties donated 10 dollars But the Hongzhi students have graduated many years,work to work ambition contribute to the educate aboard a natural foundation experience prefer this one incident,hermes kelly bags, Cui pleased and did never convert depressed,yet surplus happy and sun, because he felt the maximum sincere adore and consideration and he was willing apt give their adore correspondent academic that the boarders,mulberry, Cui is pleased apt current life and learning have been restored apt customary Guangqumen High School Cui namely  apt provide free school uniforms and textbooks, students spontaneously filled the study notes and repeat materials. share: greet to comment I absence to microblogging recommended | hot microblogging todayRelated articles&amp;#65306; The junior lofty educate propped up lying aboard the layer 3 elderly , 15,hermes handbag, Taihe County, a nearly seven year\'s age man suddenly fell among the middling of the road,bubbling by the jaws six minutes, the digit of vehicles and pedestrians from passing Seeing the situation for bell that getting himself into hardship and must detour. Taihe County, the national secondary educate two girls pedestal rapidly approached the aged propped up and the alarm Subsequently, they and a team of children to assistance the police aged filled onto the vehicle sent to the hospital,quietly left the scene. The plenary process happens by a roadside a member of the public using a mobile phone down. two media school girls amid the rain propped man March 15, Taihe County, temperatures plummeted,ponderous rain, the subsequently block the road became very sleek 50 minutes at 12 noon, a cilia sparse messy face bearded tramp hobbled, walking among Taihe County,hermes kelly bags,hermes outlet,accordance of East Road. Suddenly, the age man leaned over and fell within the Cold medium of the road. Saw the age man bubbling along the mouth face quite painful, and two girls as their side of the erase his mouth Vomit,while asking its how. The two girls seeing this,quickly  110. Subsequently, the two arm the elderly let it sit on the floor,await until the police arrived, and to assist the police to the elderly carried apt the automobile until watched the age man was rushed to hospital, only to noiselessly abandon the scene. He saw the two girls agitate there are several students around apt come aboard the implementation of relief apt the aged For moving, he makes a cell phone camera by the scene,hermes Birkin handbags,barely who the two girls of the 1st apt lend a helping hand, his namely never explicit monitoring behind the first six minutes no one helping hand incident, have alleged that the daytime of rain,mulberry, the road fewer traveled so age people fall aboard the road has been folk relief. To this end the reporter from the public security department as the transfer of matter section of surveillance movie movie display: 12 o\'clock 51 minutes and 40 seconds the same day the aged surrounded this section of the staggered hike amongst between the vehicle 12:52:28, the two cab aged caught within the middle of the road. When the age man walking apt the side of the road, somehow suddenly fell surrounded front of a cab The driver rushed out, bypassing the aged and galloped Off,mulberry bags,mulberry, and turn never far away,evaporated surrounded the monitoring. reporters in the surveillance movie apt perceive the after six minutes,hermes, came by automobile cordless cars, motorbikes and additional not fewer than an hundred,mulberry outlet,hermes Birkin handbags,only they turned a blind eye to the aged or rapidly goes amongst,alternatively rush bypass the pedestrian bell apt avert less 12,virtually 58 minutes and 20 seconds, a girl of two crossing direct toward the elderly the elderly propped up. Subsequently, there are several umbrella of the folk around him. According to eyewitnesses,mulberry handbags, these people are students, 13 5:2, police received the disturb rushed to the scene, taken apt hospital as the aged Subsequently, the children have departed the scene. earnest users quested morsel girl. After educate hours surrounded the afternoon, According to reports, they labeled Young sweet, and the other a man named Li Yuxiang, the educate are two classes of ninth-grade students. At the same time they told Yafeng, the phase to lend a helping hand, there are a few students, some people they do never know. to find several additional students, the afternoon of March 16, Subsequently, the two girls per person award-winning 600 Taihe County National Secondary School Teachers,hermes handbag, Young sweet and Li Yuxiang commonly man and appealing academic performance namely also good Same period he told reporters,if necessary friends, Learn from Comrade Lei Feng \', we want apt pay tribute apt a comely March 22, the reporter was informed that liberated the aged namely a tramp,mulberry uk,back hospital treatment, has been discharged,Related articles&amp;#65306; Related articles&amp;#65306; The the Ren Guilin </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:237539:79176265</id><idPostId>79176265</idPostId><idBlogId>237539</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:237539</id><idBlogId>237539</idBlogId><link>http://www.noticiasmotociclisticas.com.br</link><displayName>Not&amp;iacute;cias Motociclisticas</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.noticiasmotociclisticas.com.br/honda-2/seriam-as-cinco-motos-esportivas-mais-confiaveis-do-mundo-da-honda/attachment/honda-cbr600rr/</link><displayName>Honda-CBR600RR</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T10:33:15.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:237539:79176265:328431242</id><link>http://www.noticiasmotociclisticas.com.br/honda-2/seriam-as-cinco-motos-esportivas-mais-confiaveis-do-mundo-da-honda/attachment/honda-cbr600rr/#IDComment328431242</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T10:33:15.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Honda-CBR600RR by xcfgmgla</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://hermesbag-handbags.com</link><idEmailMd5>02bda8e82584ae50bf5530723fa75f76</idEmailMd5><displayName>xcfgmgla</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://hermesbag-handbags.com"&gt;xcfgmgla&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.noticiasmotociclisticas.com.br/honda-2/seriam-as-cinco-motos-esportivas-mais-confiaveis-do-mundo-da-honda/attachment/honda-cbr600rr/"&gt;Honda-CBR600RR&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>