<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmruc/post/2012-03-30T08:59:47</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Telugu brahmin here. yes!! From that other South indian state only.. 
As a Mint reader, i'd like the editorial team for once to stick to the one thing that IMHO sets them apart from the rest of the papers in this country - a thorough factual check on this article. Before going to press, get the author of this article to get  his horse and provide sources/ links/ references to the following facts he is establishing: 1) "The average southerner can assess a performance of his classical music better than the average northerner can." .. isn't that probably the vaguest statement i've heard in a long time? Bet you the Bongs are not pleased about being left out!2)  "Their canon makes south India’s classical tradition like that of Europe’s"... I'm Blushing right now. Thank you for the kind comparison, Mr. Patel but pray, please first educate us on  European classical music. I am proud of my background but would not like to see it sullied by dragging it into sweeps of generalizations. This "European classical music" better be up to the mark. Is that why we idolise A.R.Rehman and call him "Mozart of Madras" or something like that?

3) " ... most part the southern Muslim’s culture is low church, and therefore unappealing to the outsider" ... References of any academic/ scholarly article from author here, please? Or should the reader be carried Off by the author's own sense of self-importance to pass this frivolous opinion so boldly?

4) ... oh wait! WHERE IS #4?? Aah, i get it. that's just to prove us that this article was actually NEVER proof-read. Hence this entire process of printing this piece is a subtle message to Mint reader that the editorial board too has to put up with Patel's bufoonery at times! Got it? No? But i have an opinion too and therefore i have the right to get someone's support for it!! Come on now. SUPPORT ME!!!!!! start trending now = #WHEREISTHEFOURTHPOINT?

5) "It is true that the middle-class Marathi is different, but he has no voice"... Oh boy. I now at least ONE person in MUMBAI who needs to be shut up. That kind of compensates for the entire middle class. Anyways, Mr. Patel, quickly please submit references for that statement as well.

6) "My hypothesis is that this is so because its culture is dominated by the Brahmin" ...  finally an admission that this entire thing is a personal rant! Congratulations! progress has been made. On this one point, i am not sure on who'se side to take. Clearly, you have clubbed a thousand years of society and bottled it up so tightly that there's no sense of sanity/ purpose left in it. What do you mean by culture? Yes. education is a priority for Brahmins. Is *that* your point? or have dinner table conversations suddenly turned into the new census report?

Ok, Mr. Patel. I'm done for now. Your turn. 

#WHEREISTHEFOURTHPOINT </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zz5lm</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ebhf</id></website><link>http://www.livemint.com/2012/03/29200444/Why-it-is-better-to-live-in-th.html?google_editors_picks=true</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:55:23+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T12:59:47+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmruc</id><link>http://www.livemint.com/2012/03/29200444/Why-it-is-better-to-live-in-th.html?google_editors_picks=true#comment-480711855</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>