<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpbqtc/update/2012-03-21T21:45:28/c88283b9af4793248a990d140c5d57896683209afae182e4e4296e0a1f7c145e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpbhf0</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ccyzk</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Yeah - they've said they were surprised by the aggressiveness of the reaction. The biggest problem the fans had was that they couldn't understand where these two came from all of a sudden. The fact they were written to be disliked just compounded the problem.

Weird coz they introduced them many many episodes ahead of time. They weren't just plonked on us. We had a very long episode arc to get used to them (over half a season).

Oddly enough, it was the fans that wanted to get to know the background characters a bit more and the writers are in a tough Spot. IF they had written them to be liked, then they (a) couldn't have killed them Off so spectacularly, and (b) would have had to integrate them into an already saturated main character line-up. It was kinda lose-lose.So they went with dislike, but with a strong narrative that was woven from much earlier episodes including the crash scene. 

Ultimately I think it was again a case of an incredibly vocal minority of fans who just Bled hate and loathing for the two that drowned out the many voices of reason. Either way, it did lead to Expose which is one of the most fun episodes.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/65t714</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gvov</id></website><link>http://lostpolls.blogspot.com/2012/03/what-episode-do-you-love-to-hate-most.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-15T16:08:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T01:45:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpbqtc</id><link>http://lostpolls.blogspot.com/2012/03/what-episode-do-you-love-to-hate-most.html#comment-473023767</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l8w1u</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-15</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>