<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kd70/post/2012-03-29T22:14:05</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Good morning,

I Always read your posts with interest. Of course, vaccination is very emotional... But after reading the tragic story of Callie Grace, here is what appeals to me, if you do not mind me giving my appreciation of the facts stated.

Appearently the Doctors this poor baby met with while having whooping Cough could not give a proper diagnosis. They had probably read the baby's file -if they did not, they should have asked about vaccination (that's usually what the Doctors I meet with for my children ask first) and not assume that she had received all her shots -specially knowing your figures : "13% of Americans are spacing out vaccines". They shoud have known she had not received DTaP shots. Examined her. Ruled out -or not- whooping Cough. After all, they are professionals, and their high fees enforces their specificity. Dont' you think, as a Doctor yourself ? Still, they never thought before a few days after she was dead that maybe she had caught whooping Cough, thus, they never treated her for the disease she had -maybe, relaying so much on vaccination prevented them from learning how to give adequate treatment ?- thus, whatever the decision of the parents, I feel thatin the end, the Doctors were responsible for not being able to give Callie Grace adequate treatment. In my opinion, they are the ones who failed eventhough parents, in this specific story, had made a mistake in trusting the ability of Doctors to treat deseases.
Learning is an obligation. Parents still have the choice not to send their children to school as long as their kids learn the basics. Parents also have the choice not to vaccinate, appearently only as long as their kids do not catch these diseases. If they end up ill, families are punished, the hard way : Doctors will not treat them properly as they should not have caught the disease. As Callie Grace's story enlightens, it is death sentence in some cases. Do you think it is right ? Is this why Doctors became Doctors ? so as to have the right of life and death on their patients and their families and punish them for not having followed sacro-saint advices of scientists ? These people even end up becoming example among the community. Somethings make me Shiver in this world of ours... But maybe, my interpretation of Callie Grace's story as stated at the bottom of your e-mail is wrong... And I still want to thank you for all the advice you provide us with on weekly basis. They are indeed very usefull.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zhsma</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/o5vj</id></website><link>http://www.myhealthbeijing.com/2012/03/should-doctors-fire-parents-who-refuse-vaccines-for-their-children/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:45:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:14:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kd70</id><link>http://www.myhealthbeijing.com/2012/03/should-doctors-fire-parents-who-refuse-vaccines-for-their-children/#comment-480147839</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>