<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mww3ke/post/2012-03-31T13:02:53</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw1mf0</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gjit3</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>"Did you just leave an Obama rally by chance?"
Wrong. Obama  and Dems want to CUT spending and INCREASE taxes, just like Republicans.  The GOP horror is Dems want to the PAIN we experience in the private sector to be somewhat less and more drawn out.
Whether Dems do it or GOP does it, it's still a CUT to private sector wealth.  OK, fine you want LESS money.  Why not just Burn it or give it away?

"Wow. That was so crazy that I'm counting down the minutes until the Reverend jumps in to agree."

What's crazy is listening to all the "economic experts" who were responsible for causing OUR crisis in the first place. 

Not the govt's "fiscal crisis" (which exists on spreadsheets at the Fed).  OUR crisis.  OUR American businesses shutting their doors and filing bankruptcy.  OUR businesses laying .  OUR homeowners facing foreclosure.  OUR citizens unable to pay bills.  The US Treasury is not in a slump.  WE Americans are in a slump.

Where did the money come from for the Iraq War, including "-budget" Emergency spending?  Did Bush have to apply for a credit card with China?  No, Congress just "allocated" the money and the Treasury issued it, and the Fed applied it to the accounts of whatever agency or department or private military contractor got the allocation, including soldiers.

Where did China get those surplus dollars buy Treasuries with?  They didn't print them on HP Deskjet printers they manufacture.  ONLY the US govt creates dollars.
OUR economy lost $11 Trillion in real and intangible wealth when the Bubble popped. 
 The Treasury's Constitutional powers to create money for whatever 
expenses Congress deems important (bombing Yemen and Pakistan, preparing to bomb Iran, paying 180 military contractor corporations) was not crimped a penny.

The federal debt is not "inter-generational", regardless what those goombas say.  OUR prosperity and technology *IS* inter-generational.  Education and tech created by past generations serves us today.  Our taxes don't pay Off what they borrowed.Clue:  If you hand a stack of $100 bills to the IRS office, they credit your account and toss the money into a shredder.  Literally.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z1fw3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/v4oj</id></website><link>http://www.ohiomm.com/blogs/da_kings_men/2012/03/29/budget-plans-to-nowhere/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:58:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T17:02:53+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mww3ke</id><link>http://www.ohiomm.com/blogs/da_kings_men/2012/03/29/budget-plans-to-nowhere/#comment-482000370</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5gdhy</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>