<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0adfx/update/2012-03-31T15:08:24/12720a04316a45e35da7819f0196eb3d9b2790cadc8e9aec3229800fbd889fe4</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwngt5</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I actually worked on the first iTunes ad campaign, and it was not revolutionary at all. There were several media players available prior to that with the same features. As far as comparing the new TV to the old I was merely pointing out that Apple has a serious history of failing half the time especially without Jobs, plain and simple. The Newton is another example as was the G4 cube. I remember that the iMac, a computer the company I worked for invested in heavily, was horrendous. The optical drives never lasted more than 6 months under heavy use. And they tended to Overheat on a regular. If you go to Grainger, a company that actually sells Apple components you will find that Apple desktops all have the same power supply, no matter what's inside. Unless you're very careful your desktop will either be vastly overpowered or severely underpowered. The former is a waste of money, the latter murders computers as it makes them run hot.  But that's what Apple does, they make these machines that have some good features but fall short on others (I guess everybody does that). They also have created an operating system that requires little or no actual knowledge of  how things work in order to use it. As a consequence Apple user take whatever they say as law without ever realizing that the playing feild is far more level than Apple would ever admit to. As we speak many Apple users are forced to install Windows just to play AAA games because Microsoft is still holding out on Direct X. So Windows is migrating to Apple's hardware and yet Apple's OS is not doing the same. But Apple users 'think' that Apple computers are 'state of the art' and that they actually have this awesome library of games. They do not. They're using a graphics API that Microsoft developed for DOS (Open GL) which isn't bad, it's just not the best and has more in common with an Atari 2600 than 'state of the art' games. As far as the puzzle goes there isn't one, not for a TV anyway. It's just like the iPhone. People buy it but the real issue I have is 'Does it make a better phone call? That's what I buy a phone for. The answer is no. The Apple TV will sell. But can Apple maintain it over years. Samsung has already gone well into Ultra-HD territory with sets that are 16 times the resolution of HD having been showcased as much as 2 years ago. There is no ceiling to resolution. HD is somewhere around what the film industry calls 2K. Actual film ranes from 5K - 8K. Red video cameras shoot at 4K. And TV manufacturers have stated that they intend to double TV resolution every few years. I can go into my editing suite and create a project that is 1 million X 1 million if I so choose (there is no video card that will render it but that's not the point). I honestly think all of this is Apple returning to the old format. Apple gear only works with Apple gear - all of which is very expensive. Think about the $50 thunderbolt cable and expect to need several to fully accessorize the  and you've already spent more than enough to buy a mid-range desktop that will do 10 times more. The truth is 'state of the art' hardware is never - ever small. A 'state of the art' graphics card was bigger than an IPad a year ago. The new generation is still bigger. The goal is to create something that will give you the same quality graphics as a movie in real time. Not only are those graphics constantly evolving, we're nowhere near that goal so don't expect to get the same quality graphics from a tablet that you can get on a desktop ever. At least not until you can control a desktop remotely with a tablet. But then again you can do that with Wondows 8 right?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zl5c5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/hb4c</id></website><link>http://www.slashgear.com/apple-television-talk-reignites-with-sharp-patent-overlap-29220528/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:24:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T19:08:24+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0adfx</id><link>http://www.slashgear.com/apple-television-talk-reignites-with-sharp-patent-overlap-29220528/#comment-482107737</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/y1nst</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>