<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3dmcb/update/2012-03-29T00:01:46/9386f84dcbc414635ad8138e9e1136cb2989d591f9b6f89b3439a26d05d80135</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Spot on, Andrew. Mervyn King and the other idiots on the MPC encouraged banks to lend foolishly and individuals to borrow foolishly by keeping interest rates far too low for far too long before 2008, during the boom times. Now their stupid solution to the problem they created is to keep interest rates far too low for far too long. As you say, this prevents markets from working and misdirects capital and investment. In particular, on top of the ZIRP, QE has allowed financial institutions to get out of low-yielding bonds, but instead of investing in manufacturing or creating jobs, they have instead invested the new money in commodities and other forms of speculation. That's partly why oil and other commodity prices are so high, damaging growth across the developed world. A classic case of misdirected investment. So as well as raising interest rates to normal levels, they should start unwinding QE ASAP. It would also help if the utterly discredited Mervyn King and his inflation proofed Ivory tower cabal at the BoE were fired immediately and somebody who understood the real world was installed instead, rather than the hopeless academic waste of carbon that King represents. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lfacp</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ms5i</id></website><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/finance/andrewlilico/100015883/the-bank-of-england-should-raise-interest-rates-next-week/</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T15:37:33+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T04:01:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3dmcb</id><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/finance/andrewlilico/100015883/the-bank-of-england-should-raise-interest-rates-next-week/#comment-479073010</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/co2ov</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>