<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3s9nw/update/2012-03-29T23:52:01/e8f4da214ca0f017d678da000339d575a8de75039165913e300e1c337b73f2ce</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Democrat leftist oblamers, they don't live in reality.  They have no moral fiber or moral core.  They are not smarter by any stretch.  They're not as smart as you are.  They have shut themselves Off from learning.  You and I, for example, can explain liberalism to somebody.  They can't explain conservatism.  They don't care.  They're not interested.  It doesn't matter.  It's beneath them.  As such they're not informed.  It's like Geithner was up talking to some congressional committee about reducing the deficit.  He said, (paraphrasing) "Well, we don't really have a plan.  All we know is we don't like yours."  But Geithner doesn't know what our plan is.  He doesn't care what our plan is.  The fact that it's ours is enough for him to reject it.  That is arrogance, that's conceit, and that's who they are. 
They're bullies.  They don't know half of what they think they know.  And when they are confronted with hard, Cold reality as they were before the Supreme Court this week, their media members, their lawyers, their bureaucrats, when they're confronted with reality, they're lost.  They can't explain themselves. They can't justify their issues.  They're never able to do that. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zuhzy</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yjmx</id></website><link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2012/03/29/us-ambassador-hints-russia-is-spying-on-him/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T21:45:21+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T03:52:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3s9nw</id><link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2012/03/29/us-ambassador-hints-russia-is-spying-on-him/#comment-480218002</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzfny</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>