<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5kt4kw/update/2011-08-24T19:43:49/a7641c3ec983b8b4e88b6be3f766c6a31260770875475d22b43ce78447a4f265</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5kvb1s</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5y0no</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>The Left vs. Right.  Non-believers vs. believers.  All this leads to what I call "The War: JESUS VS. MARX."  Both of their disciples are spreading the word around the world and with electronic devices for the first time in world history therefore  almost every person on Earth.  

WHAT WORDS ARE NEXT TO MARX AND COMMUNISM IN THE DICTIONARY? 

In 1917, believers in Marx, "There is no God," Burned down and ransacked churches and many countries followed their lead and Banned religion. 

In 1979, a new Soviet mission began and with the help of our Communist Party USA.  LIBERATION THEOLOGY took hold in Central America! CPUSA fronts, disguised as "peace" groups, tried to equate Marx with Jesus and many Priests began to believe that.  The deceptive Marxists then raised money in all of America's churches, and in the Home of the Son of God and from believers, to fund an ideology that says "There is no God!" 

Jesus had his own weapon against this Mother of all Deceptions: POPE JOHN PAUL II! The Pope, FROM COMMUNIST POLAND, was highly critical of Priests who preached Liberation Theology.  There were several religious events, that I won't mention here, that led to the beginning of the end of Communism with the help of the Pope.  

RELIGIOUS SIGNIFICANT EVENTS against Communists:  Protests in East Berlin started inside St. Mary's Church in September 1989 which eventually led to the fall of the Wall. (I visited the church in 1995 and had Communion there.)  Nicolae Ceausescu was shot to death on Christmas Day 1989.  At 4:00 Eastern time on Christmas Day, 1991, Mikhail Gorbachev announced LIVE ON OUR TV'S, the end of the Soviet Union.  JESUS WINS?

BLACK LIBERATION THEOLOGY taught by Rev. Wright, who himself was a supporter of the KGB/CPUSA takeover of Central America, began his RACIST preaching blaming Whites for all of the Blacks problems! BLACK VS. WHITE! Obama, also a KGB/CPUSA dupe in the 80's and who surrounded himself with Marxists and Communists all his life, sat in the pews listening with Michelle and the girls.  "God damn America!"  His FAKE support of Christians and Jews is only for votes!

THERE IS ANOTHER WAR BETWEEN JESUS AND MARX! Believers vs. non-believers.  Right vs. Left.  The most hateful things are being said about believers by the non-believers. The ACLU, started by Communists and now led by Closet Communists, have their War on God, Jesus, Crosses, Christmas, and prayer. 

WORD NEXT TO MARX, the father of Communism? MARY, the mother of Jesus Christ. 
WORD NEXT TO COMMUNISM? COMMUNION, the body and blood of Jesus Christ. 
MOSCOW, MOSES and the Ten Commandments.

That "Random-Amber" is your "left" and today it is led by Barack Obama!

That "Ann Coulter" is your "Creation vs. Evolution." 

MY CONCLUSION: Tea Party/Republicans/Conservatives/Moderates/Independents/Blue Dogs vs. the Communist/Democrat Party! The War is On!  But do I mean violence? Of course not.  The War of Ideas. 

"The only power that can bring the Dam (of Communism) down, is the water behind it." Steven Chavez  We're already in the Ocean of Freedom and we can't flow up stream to tear the Dam down or "Tear down this Wall.".  But the water behind the Berlin Wall and Iron Curtain brought their Dam down.  Communists learned that the Almighty Power of Gravity, or Nature's Freedom, was unstoppable! (I was in Berlin in 1972 and again in 1995 so before and after. People Power brought the Wall down.  I have pieces of the Berlin Wall. It's more than concrete.)</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/eqmdgh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry2d</id></website><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=45747</link><postedTime>2011-08-24T21:53:25+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-08-24T23:43:49+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5kt4kw</id><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=45747#comment-294750430</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ajkck</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-08-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>