<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ns76/update/2012-03-29T13:17:12/5287f0fc0cce77e8dbba648581238395a2ec6b825bff5b27e1709a522bd22b67</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Cdns. might want to read today's Reuters Exclusive: "U.S. sees lifetime cost of F-35 fighter at $1.45 trillion" (ref. http://af.reuters.com/article/worldNews/idAFBRE82S03I20120329?pageNumber=1&amp;virtualBrandChannel=0&amp;sp=true ).

Two excerpts that I'll briefly comment on:

"The Government Accountability Office last week projected it would cost $397 billion to develop and buy the planes, up from its earlier forecast of $382 billion." This concurs w/ the Feb. 14/12 announcement by Pentagon and Lockheed Martin officials that the cost of the Joint Strike Fighter (JSF) will rise.

"The new baseline forecasts the average cost of the F-35 fighter, including research and development (R&amp;D) and inflation, at $135 million per plane, plus an additional $26 million for the F135 engine built by Pratt &amp; Whitney, a unit of United Technologies Corp.

"In 2012 dollars, the average cost of each single-seat, single-engine plane, including R&amp;D, would be $112.5 million, plus $22 million for the engine."

These cost no.'s are for unmodified F-35s. Modifying a  of F-35A's for Canada - w/ the correct mid-air refuelling system, drag chute, and SATCOM (satellite communications) equipment that works in the Arctic (as reported in the past 14 months), and a Cold weather operations kit (presumably) - would be millions extra per JSF.

Folks, we're talking about a warplane that could EASILY cost us $145+ MILLION per copy, not the Cons' fantastical $75M. At that price, we'd be on the hook for a 65-aircraft Joint Strike Fighter  for more than $13.5B, 50+ percent MORE than what the Harper Cons. have been telling us since the summer of 2010.

If the Harper govt. is going to cap the procurement at $9B, the RCAF will be LUCKY to get 35 modified F-35A's, not the 65 jets that military planners have said are needed to protect Canada &amp; participate in intl. missions.

And to think that in early 2010, the Con. govt. rejected Boeing's amazing offer of new F/A-18 Super Hornets - good enough for the U.S. Navy &amp; Aussie air force, BTW - for as little as $55M apiece, per the June 7/10 Le Devoir newspaper report (Google "Avions de chasse: l'armée a fait son choix" to read it &amp; use Yahoo Babelfish to translate, if required). 


 </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zr81k</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/4r1e</id></website><link>http://fullcomment.nationalpost.com/2012/03/29/michael-byers-stewart-webb-buyer-beware-the-f-35/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T12:31:07+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:17:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ns76</id><link>http://fullcomment.nationalpost.com/2012/03/29/michael-byers-stewart-webb-buyer-beware-the-f-35/#comment-479665702</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/r7ppx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>