<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzz13/update/2012-03-30T14:27:05/35227b265f2bb054f9432ad5b9d15d0e5086e3c432a0abdea11e0eade5906f22</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xgdr</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hmqju</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Erin: You certainly put it much more reasonably than the race hustlers have in the lamestream media. I live in Pinellas County six months out of every year and travel about the State widely. I don't detect any such racial animosity among the decent folk I encounter--regardless of color or ethnicity.  Maybe you have. But nothing comes to mind. I get along well with everyone I meet.

You could call Central Florida the heart of the Bible Belt in the State. There must be 3 religious radio stations for every music channel on air.  And it is gun country, for sure.  People tend to be very polite as a matter of course--and it's really way Too hot to be a fulltime dick to people, in any event. IMO.

Vigilante, huh? Was it vigilantism when Trayvon was allegedly atop Zimmerman and bashing his head on the sidewalk?  Teaching George a lesson about being nosey? Just asking.

The only witness to the beatdown described just such a scene to police--at length--in a written statement.  Has he recanted under pressure since this story broke? If not, the burden is on defenders of Trayvon to explain why he was atop Zimmerman in the first place. 

In my view, Zimmerman may have been nosey. He may have been a pest. He may have been unduly officious in his approach....I dunno...I wasn't there. Neither was anyone else rabidly calling for Zimmerman's head. But does being nosey and irritating justify assault and Battery?  Is that a proportional response to a neighborhood dick? Take your time before answering.  Let's not convict a man before he's been officially charged and tried.

 Zimmerman is presumed innocent until proven guilty in a court of law. Now, say it ain't so.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h321f</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q0fi</id></website><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/28/a-post-racial-lynch-mob/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T23:15:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:27:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzz13</id><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/28/a-post-racial-lynch-mob/#comment-481042401</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/az6hu</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>