<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39vpp/post/2012-03-29T17:38:16</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>We adored Nandito Ako. We watched it worldwide and it got 59 world wide twitter trends in 25 days. We're hoping a commercial release of subtitled DVDs. Nobody expected great  out of David because he never  before other than as himself, and he had the difficult job of reacting to lines in a language he doesn't know based on what he was told they would be about. There are some rough Spots but he was often really good, even in things shot early like the crying scene in the cemetery. And OMG the bunny suit haha.  And I loved his stormy relationship with Anya and Holly's relationship with him. And the beach scenes!  Not to mention his beautiful voice singing the two themes of the show. And of course he's nice to look at too. I enjoyed everyone's  and the story and locations. David did not agree to do Nandito Ako to prove he had  skills.  He did it because he thought his fans would enjoy it and he was so right - we were thrilled.  And we were grateful too because we knew that very soon David would be leaving on a 2-year mission for his church. We were grateful not just to have Nandito Ako to watch and enjoy, but also grateful that David got to spend time all the nice people who made Nandito Ako and that he had a chance to do something exciting and new before he left.  David started his mission yesterday.  His video message It's Not Goodbye can be found on his official site and Youtube. His own twitter is DavidArchie but while he's away his manager Kari will post any messages from David there.  Thank you Philippines, TV5, Ivory Music for Nandito Ako and the Forevermore CD.  #DA2014 I'll Be There</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zlad2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/c4r8</id></website><link>http://entertainment.inquirer.net/34887/hoping-against-hope</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:20:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T21:38:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39vpp</id><link>http://entertainment.inquirer.net/34887/hoping-against-hope#comment-479925425</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l5rds</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>