<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gyfedj/update/2011-09-23T17:13:47/1739edba7b1c70f799495f0dde18bbd363509d70e1be6e220efb50362c27f777</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I know Alma personally, she's a great woman, she's brave, she's wise. and i didn't like one jackass comment below, note to you: This world has its different spins for everyone, not everyone has the priveledge of having a roof over their head or food in their stomach and have been left to strive on their own without any help from people close to them or have noone close to them. Before you go and Act like you have experience being homeless and think its so easy, i'd like to see you have everyone and eveyrthing stripped from you and you start from the bottom pit, it's not as easy as you think, don't be ungrateful or critical to something you're unfamiliar with as it makes you look like a Cold-hearted a-hole. Alma has been working hard towards a goal and we all know today education gets us a better lifestyle in the end, and she will make it, and look back at all her trials knowing it made her who she is today. Don't look down upon homlessness, they don't want your pity either, they just want to be heard like anyone else.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/e7vm1k</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/8koz</id></website><link>http://invisiblepeople.tv/blog/2011/08/alma-homeless-grandmother-college-student-winnipeg-canada/</link><postedTime>2011-08-17T15:34:25+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-09-23T21:13:47+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gyfedj</id><link>http://invisiblepeople.tv/blog/2011/08/alma-homeless-grandmother-college-student-winnipeg-canada/#comment-318621915</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-08-17</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>