<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ev4n91/update/2011-12-20T04:16:58/a3d768ebc9add04048f7a379489283883c3a2ec639ad221ccb9b52d7361bd8a1</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I am a marine biologyst, researcher at the University of Ghent, Belgium. I have been already on 2 expeditions to Antarctica for my research and I am also taking part for the organization of the 2013 meeting for the Antarctic Treaty where also matters as tourism will be discussed. From my point of view, which is a quite close one, I strongly argue that TOURISM should be BANDED from Antarctica completely. We have already seen the appearance of big fields of yellow flowers which are tipical of the American Continent..how? the shoes of the tourists are bringing them along...moreover, tourism is mainly based on the formula "satisfied or money back" which means the tour operators  take tourists in the hot Spots of biodiversity such as rockeries of penguins or places where seals group together to give you the best picture ever...this means that the animals are stressed in very delicate moments like reproduction and it has been alreadey recorded that stress can lower the reproduction ability of the birds..another arguement I can provide is that most of the travelling is carried out via ships and then zodiacs to the landing Spots or around the ocean...well, this is a lot of gazoline released in those very delicate and extremely peculiar waters...if degradation of pollutants is already slow in temperate regions where water temperature is higher (the higher the temperature, the higher the metabolism) then imagine how slow it is in 0°C waters....I am sorry, but to be honest, I would band research as well from Antarctica, but  course, that's somehow an important activity to take place in such a precious and unknown ecosystem since there are still loads of thing we can learn from Antarctica...but I would say that if you say "I want to go to Antarctica because I love nature", well, be honest enough and ask yourself why you really want to go there, because if you love your child, you would not give him/her a sigarette or alcool to drink..;you would like him/her to reamain as pure as possible...therer is no way we will prevent Antarctica from dramatic losses if we are about to go there more and more...just to give you some numbers, each year 40 000 tourists go to Antarctica, mainly the Peninsula sice it is easier to access and less extreme and it holds (unfortunately for itsenf) the highest biodiversity of the Continent...and Off course, nevertheless, it is experiencing the highest changes due to global warming)...and to compare that to scientific activity, we have about 6 000 scientists each season (austral summer) in the WHOLE CONTINENT....so guys...think about it, because every action you take on this Planet comes back to each one of us, animals and humans...Francesca Pasotti  f.pasotti@gmail.com </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/g8uk4x</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7smk</id></website><link>http://matadornetwork.com/trips/how-to-travel-to-antarctica/</link><postedTime>2011-05-18T09:03:21+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-12-20T09:16:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ev4n91</id><link>http://matadornetwork.com/trips/how-to-travel-to-antarctica/#comment-390537600</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-05-18</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>