<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwdzpg/update/2012-03-30T09:54:28/629f40ee2061486237170a3d08513db0610a0fa93cb9b73fb45b3242e0f953e2</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Interesting that the study lists only the existing wind project's nameplate production, which is but a fraction of the real production, but no real figures.  These machines have been running long enough to provide actual energy figures.  The fact that these production figures are being called "proprietary information" by the developers raises a big red flag.  If they were actually powering thousands and thousands of Maine homes, they'd be trumpeting this to the newspapers on a daily basis.  Are TransCanada's Kibby turbines still Off-line due to internal problems caused by gusting mountain winds?  No doubt this is proprietary information, too.  I hope the Canadians aren't all living in darkness beause their Maine source of wind energy is broken.  How many local residents (jobs, jobs, jobs!) are currently being employed full time by these existing projects once they're up and running?  How much energy has actually been CONSUMED by these tubines which require "winter Cold weather modifications" (heaters) and flashing lights when the wind isn't blowing between 28 and 40 miles an hour, which it rarely is here in Maine?  If we taxpayers are funding a big part of these projects, that makes us stakeholders.  We deserve some real answers.  The REAL science based cost/benefit analysis of industrial wind needs to be brought to light.  A moratorium should be placed on all projects until these facts are known.  Maine's tourism based economy has far too much to lose to these greedy multi-national carpetbaggers and their false claims.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zou6k</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rvdh</id></website><link>http://www.pressherald.com/news/state-to-fall-short-of-wind-power-goal-studies-say_2012-03-30.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:56:28+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:54:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwdzpg</id><link>http://www.pressherald.com/news/state-to-fall-short-of-wind-power-goal-studies-say_2012-03-30.html#comment-480762617</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c7rdp</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>