<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3blzo/update/2012-03-29T14:31:20/10d104ba7efe3b8069d4be69c52feccaa3f3a3b354020784d94749ed43614fa5</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>As Spring training is quickly winding down and the 2012 season is about to open many Cincinnati fans are eager to see the Cincinnati Reds in action especially with all the new additions to the team this  season. 
 
It was disapppointing that we lost our closer, Ryan Madson, already before he even got to throw one pitch this year - eight and one-half million down the drain - and no insurance either. Maybe the Reds will have to re-think one year contracts - especially any that are big ticket ones. In additon, Nick Masset another closer is on the Disabled list for what period we do not know and there is Mat Latos who strained his right calf who landed in an awkward Spot on the mound. So, a starter and a relief man are down. 
 
Well, we thought that pitching was going to be much better with all the trades this  season and we have high hopes but in analyzing the stats of all major league teams this spring the Reds are nearly at the bottom in  - 28 out of 30. The Reds  is an abominable 5.30. So, it seems apparent that our pitching this year is suspect and our dreams of a pennant maybe just a dream. But, we do have a couple of bright Spots with Chapman, Ondrusek and Latos. All three have good ERA's 1.50, 1.74 and 2.41 respectively. The biggest question mark going into Spring Training was Chapman and he's showing that he's coming into his own - especially since his walks are only two in twelve innings - a mark improvement over last year. Maybe by not pitching in winter ball he's allowed his arm to rest which is definitly a good sign.
 
But, let's look a bit further...on defense the Reds are 8th out of 30 and that is above average. In offense the Reds are 20th out of 30. But let's delve into those numbers a bit further and we see that the Reds lead all 30 teams in STRIKEOUTS with 242 and the closest pursurer is the Padres with 209 and no other team has struck out more than 200 times this spring. That leads me to this thought - if the Reds are striking out more than 25% more than any other club - what's going on? To put a microsope on this fact one has to look no further than the batting instructor and manager. What are they teaching?  I see that no team should lead by that large of a percentage no matter what the circumstance. Conclusion - philosopy on hitting is the problem! 
 
Adjusting the microscope a bit further, we see that the leader in strickouts is Votto with 16 followed by Heisey, Francisco, Stubbs with 14 each, then Bruce, Frazier, Jones, Ludwick and Phipps with 12.  Oh, in how many at bats do they have? Okay, Votto in 42 which equates to .380 Heisey .340, Subbs .341. No these are not there batting averages but stikeout average!  My point here is that if you do not put the ball in play you have a minimal chance that something good is going to happen. For you can not advance a runner along to another base with a strikeout but instead a double play may result.
 
Now for some pluses: Cozart is having a super spring batting .413  and shows no problem with his tommy john surgery.  Also, Rolen has done well both in the field and in hitting with a .308 average. As you know both Cozart and Rolen were big question marks at the beginning of Spring Training along with left field. And, as left field goes it is still a question mark as of this writing. For neither Heisey nor Ludwick have shown any signs of winning the left field position outright. The other position that was a big question mark was the catching Spot and offensively the question still remains can Mesoraco hit big league pitching. As of this spring, he has not demonstrated that he can by hitting his weight - .212.
 
So, in conclusion, the Reds are going to have a hard time in winning their division this year because of their philosophy of hitting. For you can not just go up to bat and swing for a home run every time. Sometimes, you have to play little ball and do all the things necessay to win ball games which I feel the Reds manager is not capable of teaching. Time and time again Baker has shown his limitations in managing. 
 
But, I'm still a Reds Fan - Go Reds!  Will be attending many games this year regardless of their record. My only hope is the Reds find a good Manager for next year. 
 </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hsu8y</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lz6q</id></website><link>http://cincinnati.reds.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120328%26content_id=27702504%26vkey=news_cin%26c_id=cin</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T22:53:33+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:31:20+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3blzo</id><link>http://cincinnati.reds.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120328%26content_id=27702504%26vkey=news_cin%26c_id=cin#comment-479733076</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gaaz4</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>