<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi69w9/update/2012-03-22T22:28:43/0d02a91aff9112fa399166e18ae1c7080deaaa1ab284cb21d5444f7baad036d1</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This tragic killing is troubling in many ways.

It took a federal investigation to get charges on the shooter, as you can apparently "accidentally" shoot and kill people while illegally/legally "hunting" and not be charged with something--reckless endangerment, or involuntary manslaughter, or something, under Georgia law...if you say it's an accident and aren't really drunk or drugged up.

That hunting with night vision optics--which can be some Chinese made blurry '--- and night hunting AT ALL on public lands, is legal is very disturbing. Can't George Bain, Supervisor of the Chattahoochee Oconee National Forest, which includes this equestrian [day use only] trailhead parking lot,  night hunting on the national forest. He's not elected, like our legislators the NRA controls...let people shoot their hogs on their private farmland at night if they must, but don't let me or you or yours get shot at while in the public woods...

The Georgia legislature, instead of passing "Chris's Law" in honor of the killed conservation officer Chris Upton, and  night hunting on public lands in the state, instead is about to allow hunting with silencers and carrying concealed weapons by 18 year olds, who can't even buy handguns under federal law. How stupidly reckless and dangerous. They have already bypassed the decades old mandatory hunter education course by offering a three day "hunter apprentice license to "try it and see if you like it" even if you have no clue and are a menace to everyone else in the woods while you think you are hunting.

Last year, the Georgia legislature passed a budget that cut the state DNR WIldlife Resource Division budget by 40%. We're over 130 state officers short--the back-up for these half-dozen federal officers. New "conservation officers' won't be trained to be law enforcement officers, either, but just wildlife techs who will be expected to call county deputies for arrests, if they have cell or radio coverage in the outback. How ridiculous. Do all the legislators think hunting only goes on in "canned hunt camps" that lobbyists pay for? We need more conservation officers to protect the game resources of the state--we are all owners--and to protect our right to go to the woods and not be endangered.

Just look at the weekly DNR enforcement reports online to see how many criminals the game wardens deal with in the woods--felons, armed and poaching, Burning stolen copper, hunting from vehicles, stripping cars, firing into private property, baiting fields...countless criminal . These are brave law officers, and we need more of them.

Georgia, and our neighbor in the race to the bottom, Alabama, are about the last two states around that don't afford federal law officers with statewide police powers and protections. This makes the work of federal officers like the officer that was killed very difficult--they have to waste time and resources in taking those arrested to federal jails, and aren't supported when making arrests  federal land. This goes back to Prohibition, and is stupid and wasteful. Officers like the late Chris Upton are some of the best and most highly trained and professional out there. Especially Ranger Upton--he was very skilled and brought a lot of experience to the job.

With a legislature that promotes hunting over bait, "canned hunt" farms, silencers for hunting, night vision, using dogs to hunt bears, and letting anyone not [yet] a felon carry a gun concealed with no legal training, Georgia looks like the epicenter of dumb. We need more courageous conservation officers to hold the line on the barbarians marauding around in the woods, and to protect the rest of us from confrontations with such stupid people. 

Remember, this killer drove into a day use trailhead parking lot, at night, got in the pickup bed, and shot and killed the person that he saw in his 'Scope with his high powered rifle. ANd let him die.

Thanks the the FBI and Justice Department for getting to the bottom of it. If it had been left to the GBI and locals, these people would still be out there "hunting". May this law officer be remembered, and justice be served.

</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y4hnj</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dndz</id></website><link>http://www.macon.com/2012/03/22/1956724/hunter-who-killed-federal-officer.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T13:28:25+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T02:28:43+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi69w9</id><link>http://www.macon.com/2012/03/22/1956724/hunter-who-killed-federal-officer.html#comment-474153218</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lh6dh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>