<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpwkq0/post/2012-03-22T09:58:25</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp1quf</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I feel obligated to point out to you that the very link you provided on a previous post has the story about the ACCIDENTAL shooting of Gary Kern by someone other than Dave Haeg. You want to talk about rational? Or credibility? How about false accusations?

I've taken the liberty of copying your post from yesterday;

on April 28, 2012 Rally And March In Your State And Unite Against The War On Women ~ Politicalgates 12 hours ago 
Godamn it, I know I'm  topic and I shouldn't even go to Shay Tripp's website, but today, she has a plea from a big game hunter, David Haeg, that was hired to shoot wolves aerially and got in trouble for going outside of the boundaries of his game units to slaughter wolves from airplanes and now his life is "sniff, sniff" very bad and he's sad and fighting this for all it's worth and she put his plea on her website for people to show up at the Kenai courthouse tomorrow and support this Cold-blooded trophy-hunting gun-for hire idiot.  Who would support a person like this?  I almost want to take  work tomorrow and throw a bucket of blood on him at the courthouse!  Number one:  Big game hunting for rich 1%'s, BAD in my book.  #2:  Big game hunters hired by state to cull our wildlife, even WORSE!  I am so pissed Off about this I'm having trouble typing  If these are the types of people that Ms. Tripp supports then why should she expect any of us to support her?  Was he a client?(Now, I'm waiting for Patricks YouTube of Nuts being crushed under the wheels of a car.....I promise I won't mention her again but this just was the final straw...Shay Tripp might be where she is today because she seems to attract some VERY strange bedfellows.)Here is some press on this douche of a person, he apparently just doesn't kill big game, he kills people too!  (Perhaps we should send him hunting w/Cheney???):http://www.wolfsongnews.org/ne...http://www.wolfsongnews.org/ne...http://www.adn.com/2008/05/17/... Thanks for listening to my rant...I'm supposed to be working and now I'm going to have to work until 8pm! I'd say that a majority of reasonable people reading this would conclude that you are not rational.  Who in their right mind would throw a bucket of blood on anyone? Do yourself a favor   Go get anger management counseling asap</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y5eu7</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/h94c</id></website><link>http://shaileytripp.yolasite.com/blog/come-support-the-courthouse</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T23:19:57+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T13:58:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpwkq0</id><link>http://shaileytripp.yolasite.com/blog/come-support-the-courthouse#comment-473599295</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>