<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3idy5/update/2012-03-29T21:10:32/03f3f44b73057380cf15930015edd6c5b0cfe906af7d0a5c6bccdd85e7da5fcf</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>OK! Here goes, one day early........

THE BIG MISS.[Chapter one]"The Last Time"...............................................................It is obvious from the outset that Haney has a great respect for  and his golfing ability. In this chapter, he discusses an incident on the practice rangeprior to 's 4th round in the 2010 Masters. He knows that he is now finished as his coach. The ignoring of his presence and the body language tellshim it is time to move on. This is the last two paragraphs." I doubt anyone has a greater appreciation of how great  is than I do.He's a genius in the most exacting sport there is--- physically, technically, mentally, emotionally. Nicklaus might have the greatest overall record, but noone has ever played golf as well as  Woods, and no one has ever been better than his competition by a wider margin. He's the greatest.But life is about loss. With the Cold part of my mind that keeps sadnessmomentarily wall , I make the call. He's become less of a golfer, and he's nevergoing to be the same again".I see nothing in this chapter that shows Haney is going to give  any shots.It is obvious this book is going to be about Haney's time with Tiger, and I doubtthat he will give away any semblance of gossip. Loved the first chapter and I amlooking forward to the remaining seven..</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lb4oi</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/9dd2</id></website><link>http://www.golfchannel.com/news/golftalkcentral/discussion-did-hank-haney-violate-unspoken-trust-with-big-miss/</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T13:41:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:10:32+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3idy5</id><link>http://www.golfchannel.com/news/golftalkcentral/discussion-did-hank-haney-violate-unspoken-trust-with-big-miss/#comment-480100936</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l0asy</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>