<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwnze1/post/2012-03-30T19:34:51</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>&lt;0850&gt;
Hegerl

hi gabi.....some suggestions in haste

for the oceans...daily averaged near surface (10m?) wind stress 1950 on (at least).  also daily averaged Heat budget components at the ocean surface. stuff like this for baroclinic components of change.  i assume sea ice is a given.  hi freq data to look at storm track changes.

over land....add daily snow cover and major river flows into the oceans if the models have them.  add soil moisture, probably monthly.  with will have lots to do with hydrological cycle. start from 1950 at least

global...let's see those clouds.  they are supposed to be 'the' key climate variable, models do them poorly and we have new satellite data sets to see just how poorly or how well.

runs....beyond D&amp;A...yes i agree we need a whole set of runs with different future GHG forcings.  since the memory is in the ocean and that partially determines the response time (what's in the pipeline) we need emission reduction scenarios to see what track we are on as we begin to
reduce co2.  e.g. how much do we need to reduce emissions to Ensure Lake Mead does not go dry?  in the future there will be lots of stress on 'what do we have to do NOT to exceed some threshold"

yes continuous runs 1900-2100.

the actual forcing data is a must.  right now we have some famous models that all agree surprisely well with 20th obs, but whose forcing is really different.  &lt;u&gt;clearly, some tuning or very good luck involved.  I doubt the modeling world will be able to get away with this much longer....so let's preempt any potential problems.&lt;/u&gt;</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hthio</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ms5i</id></website><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/jamesdelingpole/100147742/queensland-turns-the-tide-of-environmental-lunacy/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T16:15:26+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T23:34:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwnze1</id><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/jamesdelingpole/100147742/queensland-turns-the-tide-of-environmental-lunacy/#comment-481321680</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cqs72</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>