<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xqep/post/2012-03-29T13:53:17</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xdyv</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lwvs1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>what stones have I thrown? are you referring to the notion that I didn't get on my hands and knees to worship ? Is it not enough that I said he was the favorite?
I agree with you, that the Masters will be awesome. 
I take nothing away from any other players. I specifically asked for someone to start talking about other contenders. And I now thank you specifically, that you mentioned Rose, Mahan, Haas. This is what I asked for, and you partially delivered. Thank you!
I am not convinced you read my entire post, but I will give you the benefit of the doubt.
Throwing names out there :
Garcia - Hot and Cold, but is still one of the best ball strikers, and with a hot putter, could win his first major this year
Jason Day - Played exceptionally great in all majors last year. He is very young, but lives in the shadows of Rory.
Adam  - Has played consistent, hits the ball nice and high, and can stick the greens at Augusta.
Charl Schwartzel - Is he, or is he not, the defending champion? I'm pretty sure he birdied a bunch of holes down the stretch to win, with a dozen players in the mix. 
But then again, golf coverage showed nothing but Tiger Woods last year, who was unable to continue his unbelievable play on the back 9. When Rory snapped his ball left on 10.....there were a dozen guys with a chance to win, and the golf commentators were unable to build a story line. Hopefully they don't make the same mistake this year.

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h0lho</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/9dd2</id></website><link>http://www.golfchannel.com/news/golftalkcentral/couples-offers-thoughts-on-augusta/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T01:48:49+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:53:17+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xqep</id><link>http://www.golfchannel.com/news/golftalkcentral/couples-offers-thoughts-on-augusta/#comment-479695205</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zr9ha</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>