<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw9ef0/update/2012-03-31T02:32:20/52c69c3719aac7bc59bb7faa77212bb42a761d2702e8462c2dfdd7f24d03cc4b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Hello, i'd like to report 3 bugs i've encountered:
1) When laser painter + guided missiles equipped in Scout choppers, you don't make any damage to the enemy chopper you've locked on and fired to. not a single hit maker, had to switch back to Heat seakers because of this.
2) Jet guided missiles used against enemy laser locked attack chopper has the same result as last entry; no hit makers and no damage made.
In both cases the missile looks to go up on the sky and come down to try to hit the enemy but Always goes past him (ex: aerial view, the chopper in the middle of the screen and the missile goes past him on the right/left/back/front side of it without hitting him). This two bugs were found after the server update that made the EA's official custom servers available on consoles.
3) Lastly, when you're engineer and have RPG/SMAW and fire it to someone and you get instantly killed after firing, your rockets banishes in the air, never hits target, the smoke dissapears too and of course, no kill points or hit markers. I've encountered this from trying to take down a building on someone, to vehicle fights, to shooting at a soldier that's about 4fts away from me. I've been suffering this one since the first day playing battlefield 3.
Hope this is helpfull, congrats on the great game.
Battlefield PS3 user Unbor_MX</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zvn83</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tuk8</id></website><link>http://www.gustavhalling.com/2012/03/29/battlefield-3-march-patch-bug-reporting/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:42:30+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T06:32:20+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw9ef0</id><link>http://www.gustavhalling.com/2012/03/29/battlefield-3-march-patch-bug-reporting/#comment-481591943</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>