<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkuu33/update/2012-03-26T10:36:47/4b9ec93020bef63d5b6eefa7b41100a5c953877db28b2afb42f0aed0c9b6103d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>In order of obnoxious culpability - Agliotti, Nassif, McGurk, Smith and lastly Schultz (as he has the mentality of a twelve year old psychotic anal abuse victim, and actually should by all rights and norms be in a padded cell) - all of these egregious ugly criminal psychotics are going to see their asses. Let me detail the ways they could go down. Any one of them could be ripped to shreds in a revengeful hail of hot lead, any of them could lie quivering in a rain wet car-park Bleeding out after a brutal knife attack, any of them may even lie on the side of some nameless suburban street gasping like a fish out of water from bomb fragments through their bodies or, my favorite, a simple 1000m long range sniper round through the back of the head (This death suits Agliotti the best) as he leans over his braai in a garden of laughing gangsters, the whack of the bullet and the pink mist blowing over the salad even before the sound of the shot  them, all scrabbling for cover in their stupid Polynesian Island picture shirts, all yelling and crawling around while fat Glen hits the deck and Bounces once, twice and then lies still, one hand with the tongs still twitching, the big greasy sausage on the grill smoking and Burning. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r3d4w</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/jn2h</id></website><link>http://www.iol.co.za/saturday-star/kebble-hitman-schultz-fingered-in-series-of-crimes-1.1264109</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T14:07:33+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T14:36:47+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkuu33</id><link>http://www.iol.co.za/saturday-star/kebble-hitman-schultz-fingered-in-series-of-crimes-1.1264109#comment-476435445</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zag9d</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>