<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3idm9/update/2012-03-29T21:10:28/11a8148e1c73715284a12c0ad55c0398ffdc4bb1572902b0220276a205fe44fc</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I'm  that you have taken the time to evaluate this popular tool for evangelism and I am sorry I missed the Shepherd's Conference this year...I would have attended your session. We recently employed this material in our church and I thought maybe I was the only one who noticed the same concerns you mentioned. It does seem to be a "canned" one-size-fits-all model, but it is not too different from many evangelistic methods that have been popular over the years... I wonder if you remember DJames Kennedy's Evangelism Explosion from some years back? Though the script seems fine in a training setting, in "real life" it is often far different... One of the things I liked about TWOTM was the brief clips showing realistic evangelism and not-so-pliable lost people. Those brief examples showed that your point about the Gentiles not knowing (or caring) about the Law or the Ten Commandments was right on. This too exposed the trouble with this method

However, it is the method itself and its genre that troubles me. As you mentioned briefly, the Holy Spirit doesn't seem to have a very prominent role at all in TWOTM... What is not so surprising is that He very seldom has a role in many evangelistic methods! There is too much methodological ju-jitsu wherein the "lost sinner" after answering a few questions finds himself turned around or backed into a corner ready to cry "uncle" or at least "give 'em what they want so they'll leave us alone" responses... This doesn't sound at all like the work of the Holy Spirit Who uses all sorts of circumstances and sorrow to bring someone (or lead someone, or grant someone) repentance that leads to life. How we can assume that our technique will usher in the Holy Spirit to work His "magic" and zap someone with eternal life is beyond me... It seems we leave Him out of the picture entirely until "we're ready"...

What is also troubling about many evangelism methods is that so much focus is spent on the how of evangelism or the technique that it drives me back to Scripture to find those texts that teach such an approach to evangelism... I must confess that I don't find any! What I do find in Scripture is a treasure trove of texts that explain and exhort believers to live godly lives, to pursue (hunger and Thirst after) righteousness, to be zealous for good deeds, and to be busy with good works that glorify our Father in Heaven... Is it just me, or does the New Testament seem to take a different approach? First, faith. Then obedience. Then godliness. Then lives that testify of the change God has wrought. Then opportunities to give an answer for the hope that is in us (and can be seen by the way we live out that hope in the midst of this world of lost people). Like the fruit of the Spirit that should Always precede the use of the gifts, so too should godliness and righteousness precede the proclamation of the gospel...

I am excited about evangelism. But I am more excited about true Biblical obedience that leads to godliness and a "sound" witness both in lifestyle and theology. What the saints need is more biblical exposition of the Way the Master wants us to live in the power of the Holy Spirit and leave the results of evangelism up to Him. For when we are obedient to the Savior we are useful to Him especially in evangelism! And when we understand the Biblical role of the Spirit of God in sanctification as well as justification we will be better positioned to be useful to the Master in spreading the (correct) gospel. Not only that, it will be easier to be filled with the Spirit than to be grieving Him or quenching Him when we seek to employ our own (fleshly) methods rather than allowing Him to move in and through us.

Sorry for the length of this comment.... you would probably cover these issues a bit later on, but I just had to comment. Thanks for your contributions to Cripplegate! May God bless your ministry as you seek to glorify Him.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z5a6y</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tit5</id></website><link>http://thecripplegate.com/concerns-with-the-way-of-the-master/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T06:44:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:10:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3idm9</id><link>http://thecripplegate.com/concerns-with-the-way-of-the-master/#comment-480100886</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>