<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m09wgx/update/2012-04-02T01:59:15/82cc702d2c3244d699a592c738c4d1a2ca774a9d7d0bdee771861e8fe72c0b16</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Great show overall,a few Hiccups but overall a very solid PPV

Bryan/Sheamus: Seriously,WTF WWE? They might have well just been the preshow match again. 0stars

Orton/Kane: Solid match,it was exactly what I expected it would be. Surprised Kane got the win. **1/2

Rhodes/Big Show: Again,mostly what I thought it would be. Nothing special but it accomplished what it was suppose to do, give Big Show a WM moment. **

Divas match: Whatever,went for a piss N/A

End of an : What can I say? This match entirely delivered on every level. Full of emotion,drama,physicality. My only complaint is I wished they would have utilized the cell a bit more. It felt like a repeat of last years match with an oversized caged surrounding them. Still,very very good match,best of the night. ****1/2

12 man tag match: I thought this match would have been a complete mess but they managed to get it together, had a few good Spots,dumbass ending but a predictable outcome. ***

Punk/Jericho: I loved this match! I am so  they gave it time because I knew Punk and Jericho would deliver,which they did. The best pure wrestling match of the night full of back and forth action. I was skeptical about the stipulation but it just fueled the story even more. Solid match. ****

Rock/Cena: Awesome main event that had me and the crowd at the edge of their seats. It was technical in any sense but it didn't have be as they crowd was in it the entire time.Shocked and Glad Rock got the win,it seemed to obvious that Cena would win so this was genuinely welcomed surprise. Even though Cena lost, he still got the rub from Rock. Overall a hyped match that delivered. ****

A very solid PPV with some dud moments but all packed with spectacular ones. A mass improvement over last year by far. 

Overall ****1/2 stars.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6v4wf8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7d9s</id></website><link>http://tv.ign.com/articles/122/1222056p1.html</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T14:04:46+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T05:59:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m09wgx</id><link>http://tv.ign.com/articles/122/1222056p1.html#comment-483307113</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g1gqy</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>