<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m943xq/update/2012-03-17T12:10:09/da33b8e0a6d43fc64cdcc44bac3d430ff0636b196a6600c1e8e5371b15aea78d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9e7mn</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>We have a federal government that is running rampant over everyone and everything. The Department of Justice is interfering in states rights. I'll give you an example. The SUPREME COURT has ruled that voter IDs are constitutional, but this administration has blocked South Carolina and Texas from establishing theirs. VIOLATION OF STATES RIGHTS as I see it. We recently had a supreme court justice tell Eygpt that our constitution was not a good example for other countries to use. There is nothing wrong with our Constitution. I served this country and retired with 30 years of military service. I swore an oath to defend the Constitution of the United States of America. I don't take that lightly. Obama's policies are socialist and that is just the Cold hard facts. The federal government will get as many people as possible  on their handouts and then continue to eliminate individual rights; such as the Second Amendment. Our forefathers had good reason to include that one. The federal government is way to large and out of control. Our forefathers never wanted that to happen. They experienced the British Empire and didn't like it.

Our state governors have become puppets to the federal government. They do what the federal government wants or the project funds will be cut Off; so the governors kowtow to the feds.
There really are no individual states or reason for state pride; such as it was before the Civil War.

The Obama Administration is dividing the classes. We're told that successful individuals; who worked for their success are the problem. They need to divide their success with others less fortunate. Remind you of anywhere else? The Soviet Union perhaps? I have an older brother; who is very very successful. He worked hard for what he has and his family benefits from it. I chose another route; which gives me a comfortable living. Neither of us sat on our butts, with our hand out demanding other peoples success be shared with us. We planned our life and worked at it.

I imagine that the Romans, Greeks, etc. felt that they were to big and powerful to crumble. I bet you think that the United States of America is eternal and couldn't possibly suffer the same fate.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yzp6mi</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/h7jj</id></website><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/infocus/2012/02/the-civil-war-part-1-the-places/100241/</link><postedTime>2012-02-08T18:30:48+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-17T16:10:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m943xq</id><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/infocus/2012/02/the-civil-war-part-1-the-places/100241/#comment-467816599</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-08</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>