<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3vk9g/post/2012-03-29T09:13:24</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Wow, a lot of quotes in that atricle. Difficult to get through to the facts. Main fact seems to be that we are talking only about 2 out of 8 proposed reactors here. Also the companies that own the Horizon project are trying to find a buyer.

Also they say that it was not the project viability, but their own internal issues that stopped the project. Could just be PR but who knows?

Usually silly response from environmentalists regarding "green energy" and disappointment from unions because of job losses.

I'm pretty sad about this 'cos, as an engineer (a real one) I can appreciate, along with others commenting here, that nothing, and I mean nothing at all that the "renewables squad can come up with can replace the huge mount of eletricity generated by the nuclear and fuel Burning generators. Its fuel Burning, nuclear, or power cuts.

The German's will not abandon nuclear power for the same reasons. German elections coming up soon. See what happens after that.

Always remember: if the UK stopped all CO2 generating activities (except breathing) ie no electricity or Heating of any kind involving combustion, no motorised transportation, no flying. It would make no difference whatsover to the world's CO2 beyond 48 days. Because that is how long it would take China/India to replace it with their own new power stations.
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zymxu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/earth/energy/nuclearpower/9173253/UK-energy-plans-in-tatters-after-Npower-and-E.-ON-nuclear-plant-withdrawal.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T10:46:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:13:24+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3vk9g</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/earth/energy/nuclearpower/9173253/UK-energy-plans-in-tatters-after-Npower-and-E.-ON-nuclear-plant-withdrawal.html#comment-479478173</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8ogmu</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>