<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39xac/post/2012-03-29T17:43:59</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I saw this episode of Mad Men--this is not a favorite show of mine.  It is a phony show about phony folks--perhaps true to life but the water bombs exemplified for me the arrogance of the upscale liberals of this land, who prided themselves on their bohemian ways and avant-garde sexual mores.  But they were merely pedestrian and stupid, these high class executives and their trophy, vapid wives and girlfriends, dressed to the nines and heavily preoccupied with their sexual conquests and coquetry.  They existed in an alternate dystopia, far removed from the agony of their fellow minority citizens.  

Mad Men fails for me, precisely because it touches on the fringes of this repugnant universe without delving into the consequences of its depravity and debauchery.  The story gives sex a bad name and it leaves the interesting and irrepressible common black people of that Era in the Cold.  To me the beautiful white folks in Mad Men are lost and misguided imbeciles who accepted the segregation of their times, from their Madison Avenue perch, as the norm.  What difference between them and the plantation owners?  

I watched it once, for the first time--the first episode of the fifth season.  I won't watch it again because its dialog is shallow, its ad men don't seem to work and are in a state of perpetual priapism and its women are Bacchanalian fools.  I am not ready to dismiss this as a true to life portrayal.  It seems more like gratuitous sensationalism and prurience.  Give me Archie Bunker, the Jeffersons or Sanford and Sons or even any of the day time soaps anytime.  At least the latter are not marketed as finessed and fine takes on the lives of the successful rich.  

And by the way, Terry Gross of NPR interviewed the producer of Mad Men and he pontificated about the sexual proclivities of his shallow characters as though he were conducting a Socratic debate (debacle?) for NPR listeners.  The man needs a brain transplant.  Currently he owns the siminan kind.

So marchers in Baltimore got pelted too, like the NYT reported long ago, like in Mad Men?  Between Trayvon Martin and the West Side roller skating saga of Baltimore--between the Mad Men of yesteryear from Madison Avenue and the Mad Men of today from The Vue of Baltimore--juvenile delinquency is rampant among the privileged and the clueless-- in that malady let's include the ones behind Mad Men--laughing all the way to the bank.      </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zlyvw</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/fddz</id></website><link>http://blog.baltimorebrew.com/2012/03/29/bigots-waterbombing-protesters-a-scene-in-mad-men-and-real-life-baltimore/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:31:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T21:43:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39xac</id><link>http://blog.baltimorebrew.com/2012/03/29/bigots-waterbombing-protesters-a-scene-in-mad-men-and-real-life-baltimore/#comment-479930871</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>