<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3uugn/update/2012-03-29T15:28:24/c334ed1fbf4128ed506c0e807fd1f3afcec7571387ead6582b2803f81c2a453c</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Again, I could see Jessica as maybe a shock B3, but not a shock boot. She's not Pia. Pia did not have national pride *and* a very specific genre in her corner. Jessica's one of the only people that trended last night. Lots of people who love Beyonce and were really familiar with Sweet Dreams (it was an urban radio hit) loved her rendition. Ditto Deandre... people who love Eric Benet tended to really like him. I can't see Jessica taking last, maybe Deandre but not Jessica. Her day will come but it won't be this week.

Now Sklyar and Hollie both sang signature songs from iconic country singers and neither nailed it, so I can see them being in danger. The country audience seems not to take kindly to seeing their classics mishandled (ask Lily Scot LOL). Hell country week is Always good for a surprise boot, no? Both have been on a downwards swing and both went early....

Then again, Heejun, Deandre and Josh are all R&amp;B balladeers basically, so there could be some vote splitting with the other 2 seeming to be more in need of saving, leaving Josh out in the Cold...</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z4ues</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q17i</id></website><link>http://www.mjsbigblog.com/american-idol-11-top-9-power-list.htm</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:15:59+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:28:24+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3uugn</id><link>http://www.mjsbigblog.com/american-idol-11-top-9-power-list.htm#comment-479793656</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6i6ya</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>