<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3t8b9/update/2012-03-29T09:27:30/14258830f430635113751b21ba6e75d1f1505f9debb6902043c890713f6c2ba5</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The hypocrisy of MSNBC is beyond stunning. Sharpton et al have tried this matter in the court of public opinion with the slant of blatant race politics.

Where were these clowns while young black folk are being killed in droves by other blacks? Where were they when young white folk were attacked by blacks for merely being white? 

Never let a crisis go to waste...racism, guns, profiling, Palin, hate crime, Jeb Bush, WWB in a GC, hoodies, NBPP , trademark the slain, vandalism, truancy, tweeting home address, "white" hispanic, etc.

"If I had a son he'd look like Trayvon." Thanks, Mr. President, for calming the waters. I don't recall Obama reflecting on the plight of Melissa Coon's 13 year old son after being set afire by several 16 year old blacks. That child didn't look much like the President and wasn't worth similar sympathy? It would appear skin color matters to some in the media and government.

What happened to the post-racial presidency and media? Oh, right, it was all BS if it got in the way of political Gain.

A hispanic registered democrat who took the time to lead a neighborhood watch kills a black youth in apparent self defense. Never mind the witnesses, wounds, or inherent right to self defense reinforced by law. MSNBC has led demonstrations that unequivocally condemn a racist "white" man who profiled and murdered in Cold blood a hoodied defenseless black "child" for being guilty of walking while black in a gated community. Skittles!

Yep, sure is politicized by "white" conservatives.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zrobb</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/4847</id></website><link>http://www.therightscoop.com/msnbc-defends-charges-republicans-are-politicizing-obamas-comments-on-trayvon-martin/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:08:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:27:30+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3t8b9</id><link>http://www.therightscoop.com/msnbc-defends-charges-republicans-are-politicizing-obamas-comments-on-trayvon-martin/#comment-479487122</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hspb5</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>