<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/129639/post/127780677/comment/328189397</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Yes, different metals other than lead that get into the mixture can cause sparks, but lead isn&amp;#039;t one of them.  Copper jacketed bullets, and other variants can and do cause sparks, but for those of us, which sounds like most of us, we can all agree that any small fire that would start would be quickly put out as there isn&amp;#039;t much left to Burn up there.  The trees are probably 30% lead and 70% wood.  The sparks would be created by a bullet on car, or refrigerator or whatever junk may be placed there at the time, but you are right as you think about it, the fires related to that area that have grown any larger that something a few guys couldn&amp;#039;t contain are all in the areas where the -roading goes on.  Gas Spills, full tanks that someone doesn&amp;#039;t realize is dripping fuel and Burning.  Random events like that.   In many cases, the person that gets the fire started doesn&amp;#039;t even know if its theirs, are long gone by the time its a blaze and in many cases don&amp;#039;t even know there is a fire until they come back on the same trail, if they do.  Its just part of the sport and using gasoline in machines out in the back country.  Its of course  possible, but the # of arsonists vs those of us that really would prefer to not have things Burn down are pretty thin, even better, 99.7% of them don&amp;#039;t travel less than a mile from where their car is.  In other words, they are rare.  
 
So just my comment which I agree with you about why we need to check bullets is basically this, and yes I did cut and paste from another post as they had the same question.   I addressed this as a possibility to help folks learn.    
 
Here is what I wrote about that in being a little more verbose. 
 
 
I mentioned someone to check bullets because there are a few different types.  Obviously tracer rounds, full metal jackets, etc, are going to be bullets that should be  on shooting days as yes, the data shows that regular lead bullets don&amp;#039;t spark on anything.  If you were the sharpest shooter on the block you probably only have a 5% chance of starting a self-lighting match if you hit it just right.  So that was my point about someone checking.  Its cheap, probably we could have volunteers that in the end not only know the shooting rules, the places to shoot, checking your ammo to make sure its not &amp;quot;sparkable&amp;quot;, letting you know how many people are up the trail from you, and the conditions.  No need to sign names, its public land, but as a service from one good shooter to the next, even if we had 1 volunteer per weekend day over the spring, summer and fall, were talking about 30x2 days = 60 volunteers who would probably be able to help a lot of people.  It wouldn&amp;#039;t be against the law to walk past them if you didn&amp;#039;t want to talk, we aren&amp;#039;t trying to be big brother, but knowledge is what most people lack and most people want to learn, especially when its quick to the point and free.  Even 1 guy every weekend for 2 hours in the morning is better than nothing.  I think with a lottery we could get something setup and probably be able to not only get folks up there, but pay them lunch, or have someone deliver a sandwich and soda for lunch and pay for their gas and maybe a box of rounds for them to close the canyon out with nightly.  
 
Cheers </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:129639:127780677</id><idPostId>127780677</idPostId><idBlogId>129639</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:129639</id><idBlogId>129639</idBlogId><link>http://www.dailycamera.com</link><displayName>Daily Camera.com:</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.dailycamera.com/boulder-county-news/ci_20283798</link><displayName>Forest Service to close Lefthand Canyon Off-Highway Vehicle area due to fire danger - Boulder Daily </displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T01:49:18.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:129639:127780677:328189397</id><inReplyTo><link>http://www.dailycamera.com/boulder-county-news/ci_20283798#IDComment327894186</link></inReplyTo><link>http://www.dailycamera.com/boulder-county-news/ci_20283798#IDComment328189397</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T01:49:18.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Forest Service to close Lefthand Canyon Off-Highway Vehicle area due to fire danger - Boulder Daily  by super_boulder</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://intensedebate.com/people/super_boulder</link><idEmailMd5>d676b510320c1324dc0dad0b80b02560</idEmailMd5><displayName>super_boulder</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://intensedebate.com/people/super_boulder"&gt;super_boulder&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.dailycamera.com/boulder-county-news/ci_20283798"&gt;Forest Service to close Lefthand Canyon Off-Highway Vehicle area due to fire danger - Boulder Daily &lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>