<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mizem5/update/2012-03-23T04:22:54/7a27374dfb398e53af00ed7f6d42c1492c0c6749b17b3de24cf14da5e2f5383e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mircg8</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> In the case of the fishermen in Kerala, it happened on a location where India claims it has locus standi.

In the case of Baby Falak, it is because it is an entirely Indian issue. 

In the case of Sri Lanka, no doubt there was a genocide but there is a limit to which India can go. 

This is exactly we are (were) against when Musharraf Bled for fellow-Muslims being targeted in India ( of course by overstating convenient facts and by being selective)

As I asked elsewhere, what if some small group of people in Kerala appeal to Pakistan to support them in forming a separate nation based on Islam? Will you allow Pakistan to interfere? Whatever you say about human nature can apply here also.

The solution for Tamils in Sri Lanka is to be found within the constitution of Sri Lanka. If there is a prejudice in Sri Lankan constitution that does not assure equality there are forums fuming at its mouth all the liberal froth..it has to Resolved through them. If we compare South Africa and Sri Lanka, the former has suffered much more than Tamils in Sri Lanka but were able to garner international support due their balance approach in solving their problem. The problem with the Tamils and Ealams and Karunadhis is that it all emotional, giving enormous satisfaction immediately, but detrimental in the long run.

But to ask India to intervene in a matter that does not directly threaten India, it is full of danger. It is a double edged sword.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ysc6c</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/776o</id></website><link>http://www.firstpost.com/politics/karunanidhis-eelam-dream-is-a-curse-on-lanka-tamils-253154.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T01:13:42+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T08:22:54+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mizem5</id><link>http://www.firstpost.com/politics/karunanidhis-eelam-dream-is-a-curse-on-lanka-tamils-253154.html#comment-474312928</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>