<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gbgxj6/update/2011-10-19T20:24:25/b4ae1d2b1f2c9ae2eae08cc0ca87c362afcd645db25650add32cb63e1d1319d4</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Okay.

Honestly? Time for me to express my opinion. Before I start, I'd like to say I completely support gay rights. Hell, I'm not even straight myself. Regardless, I may get some comments for this one.

However, there are WAY more important things to get angry over than words and phrases. This goes for EVERYONE. Not just you, pretty much everyone. I don't like the term "that's so gay" much either, and clearly, neither do you. It's pretty simple, then. DON'T USE THAT PHRASE. Wow, crazy, right? It's honestly that simple. If you tell people Off for using a word or phrase, chances are, they're not going to stop.

If it's a friend, I understand, but really, OP, you're not going to stop everyone you encounter from using the term "that's so gay". You're not. Nobody is. Accept it and move on.

If the girl said something directly mean about gays (I think all gays should Burn in hell or something along those lines) or was making fun of a gay kid (or anyone, regardless of sexual orientation or anything like that) I would understand a lot more, but, pick your battles, OP.

Get used to the fact that people are going to say phrases and words that offend you. Face it, you've said something that could offend someone else. It's life.

This is probably harsh, but when people overreact to words and phrases, I get annoyed. I understand the dislike of the phrase, and there's a lot of words/phrases I really don't like, including that one, but people need to pick their battles, as I said earlier.

You'll have to deal with offensive things for the rest of your life, and a lot of them will be worse than "that's so gay".

/endrant</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/mziz9f</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dypr</id></website><link>http://www.sixbillionsecrets.com/view/Love/1335033</link><postedTime>2011-10-20T00:06:42+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-10-20T00:24:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gbgxj6</id><link>http://www.sixbillionsecrets.com/view/Love/1335033#comment-339543910</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ydkjg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-10-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>