<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qhnw/update/2012-03-29T11:49:00/90a86396f7e7d388fa0cda18516a82adf6a89cd98baa5639ff58f533d84bf13d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>BIG SPOILERS

One thing that strikes me about DS9 is how they use their season finales.  In a rarity for post-Best of Both Worlds Trek, they're never really cliffhangers. There's never some big new plot twist problem sprung from nowhere to be solved within 40 minutes next year (See Locutus, Klingon Civil War, Evil Data, Voyager getting hijacked, etc.). Instead, they shake the plot up enough to show where the series is going while tying up what's been running through the season. ITHOTP leads into The Circle Trilogy, because while the Station's come together, the planet below hasn't. The Jem Hadar threats leads into The Search's introduction of the Defiant and further introduction of The Dominion. The Adversary is all about how big a threat the Founders really are--something that's relevant when the Klingons invade Cardassia thinking the Founders are behind it in the S4 premiere.    Even Call to Arms, where the station's loss would normally be a cliffhanger, is the summation of two years of the Dominion Cold War and sets up both a six episode early arc and the two year plotline of The Dominion War.  It speaks to their more complicated plot setup and the maturity of their writing.  It's funny how the quietest finale, S4's "Broken Link," is the one most cliffhangery with the revelation that Gowron's a changeling after 40 minutes about Odo and his existence.    Unlike countless Voyager cliffhangers (or later TNG ones) DS9's finales never feel gimmicky and Always seem to have plenty of foresight. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zzdur</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/in-the-hands-of-the-prophets,71184/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:00:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:49:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qhnw</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/in-the-hands-of-the-prophets,71184/#comment-479594626</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/y4axp</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>