<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/136753/post/26057847/comment/329723011</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body> branding.  on. You searched for \'louis vuitton\' Here are some results for the search term on this website Randy Branding: Skincare Porn, Louis Vuitton Condoms &amp;amp; the Week in Sexy SexSuper Bowl Ad Tracker: GE Spurns Humor,louis vuitton site officiel, Touts US Manufacturing and JobsSuper Bowl Ad Tracker: Rainn Wilson for Chevy,louis vuitton borse, 50 Cent for Suzuki, a Kia Fantasy and more It\'s sexy sex time,sac louis vuitton woolrich artic parka Early winter skin care 5 Step,louis vuitton site officiel,woolrich artic parka,sac louis vuitton! Not to be outdone by all the sexing sex talk between Catholic leaders concerned with religious freedom and the Obama administration\'s mandate on providing birth control,sac vuitton louis vuitton sito ufficiale European multi-countr, brands got into the prophylactastic fun. Are you ready for an almost-entirely NSFW post? Okay,moncler outlet! First,sacs louis vuitton sacs louis vuitton Stunned!, there\'s the Louis Vuitton condom that wasn\'t. When Twitter lit up with claims that Louis Vuitton would be offering a characteristically-branded LV condom for around $ 68,sac vuitton, squeals of delight could be heard from Essex to the Jersey Shore. Sadly,sacs louis vuitton, the designer rubber was just a Dec. 2011 World AIDS day project by a Georgian designer looking to raise funds and awareness for AIDS research. The URL originally hosting the condoms ( louisvuittoncondom) has since been shut down. (The next question: Was it by Louis Vuitton, a brand that also sued the sextastic film The Hangover 2 earlier this year when the production used fake LV luggage instead of the real deal,sacs louis vuitton, or the artist?) In other condoms-for-causes news, in honor of National Safe Sex Awareness Month,louis vuitton sac,louis vuitton sac, their protection efforts. first clinically-approved polyisoprene condom on the market. each strip of photos to raise awareness for safe sex. condom brand for not passing on the obvious just because it\'s obvious. Thanks to a whole new product endorsement by the family,sac vuitton,moncler donna Guangzhou La Perle Louis Vuitton sto,sac louis vuitton,sac vuitton,louis vuitton borse Arctic Cold invasion of Europe, more tha, for the first week in history, if you Google results. Fashionista, meanwhile, asks,sacs louis vuitton, p&amp;gt; We suppose it Depends on what you mean by &amp;gt; Even London\'s historic Wallace Collection museum is turning to sex to market itself. Advertisers that shelled out for the Super Bowl need to get their money worth. With that in mind,sac vuitton,moncler donna, Kia Motors put together a looped video running five straight hours of &amp;#8234; Adriana Lima &amp;#8236; waving a checkered flag and then posted it to the brand\'s YouTube account. Think of it as a sexy version of the Yule log some TV stations run on Christmas. Finally on the marketing with sex beat comes one of the top three unicorn making love to a dolphin commercials you will ever see. And yes,sacs louis vuitton, it is obviously NSFW. Happy Valentine\'s Day,woolrich outlet,sacs louis vuitton Arctic Cold spells, Electricite,sac vuitton! </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:136753:26057847</id><idPostId>26057847</idPostId><idBlogId>136753</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:136753</id><idBlogId>136753</idBlogId><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com</link><displayName>HOCKEYCENTRIC</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-canucks-are-more-than-one-line-and-luongo/</link><displayName>The Canucks Are More Than One Line And Luongo</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T04:55:09.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:136753:26057847:329723011</id><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-canucks-are-more-than-one-line-and-luongo/#IDComment329723011</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T04:55:09.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The Canucks Are More Than One Line And Luongo by 811hsj9332</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://sacsmagasinfrance1.com</link><idEmailMd5>74d17ba2fc249dc379a063ebdc92bc82</idEmailMd5><displayName>811hsj9332</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://sacsmagasinfrance1.com"&gt;811hsj9332&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-canucks-are-more-than-one-line-and-luongo/"&gt;The Canucks Are More Than One Line And Luongo&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>