<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31zwq/update/2012-03-29T16:03:03/f6d57ecda5cc4beb1e2f92349053ae8be54ab54a56f0ddae4582d079e65253bf</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3bb09</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6u7nc</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>The stupidest part of the articles were the implication that Romney would meet with Newt desiring for him to "pull out" um the deal would be the opposite.

and Newt gave a non denial denial.....that there was any deal he just acknowledged that they met, he denied that he offered to pay  the debt or something like that, but that might have not been their 'understanding' 

that they met in person is not the signal... we're supposed to believe Newt who said "i'm doing this with Rick to stop Romney!!!"  so they either bash Rick , which implies Gingrich is the liar.....

or they think Gingrich a man who cheats on everybody..... is to believed when he says something to the cameras...

Those promoting this in OT are useless...and out of touch with reality ...
They're stupid. I don't even think they watch Rick, he's in this for the long haul..one of the people section9 for instance thinks Rick is doing this for a VP Spot, LMAO...."i'm certain"

 he is Always wrong. He was wrong in reading Palin's actions...because Romney would throw everything and the kitchen sink in spending in states he wasn't supposed to spend much in, at someone who was supposed to 'help ' him. Romney has to go back for even more money and endorsements stilll....

At least C4Pfan,  and some others in the OT don't fall for it....

The OT is now just another disengaged form and offchute of Freerepublic. Out of touch. No longer freewheeling, just a school of fish reacting to news cycle shadows...

Freerepublic is filled with some normal logical participants, but overall that place promotes weirdos....just a mirror version of Democratic Underground. Political kneejerkers and  groupthink...</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66urtu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7e99</id></website><link>http://conservatives4palin.com/2012/03/open-thread-254.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-24T07:00:46+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:03:03+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31zwq</id><link>http://conservatives4palin.com/2012/03/open-thread-254.html#comment-479829691</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gdloz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>