<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3s2b4/post/2012-03-29T23:05:28</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ok7q</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Let me explain something to you. Burning fossil fuels adds CO2 to the atmosphere. Unlike Oxygen, which is a diatomic molecule (O2), carbon dioxide is a triatomic molecule, meaning it is made up of three atoms. As a triatomic molecule, carbon dioxide produces more of a blanketing effect on our planet. Carbon dioxide keeps more Heat trapped in the atmosphere. To keep earth from becoming like an oven, the atmosphere has to radiate Heat back out into space. On the other hand, trapping Heat is a good thing to a certain extent. But when there are too many triatomic molecules in the atmosphere, the warming effect intensifies. The planet Venus, for example, which has an atmosphere packed with carbon dioxide, is a hellishly hot place, even hotter than the planet Mercury even though the latter is closer to the sun. We know what too many triatomic molecules in the atmosphere do. That's why we need to find alternative sources of energy. And even if you remove global warming from the equation, pollution is still pollution, and pollution is bad. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z7xmd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f047</id></website><link>http://thehill.com/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/219015-draft-draft-senate-again-blocks-dems-bid-to-nix-big-oil-tax-breaks</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:59:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T03:05:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3s2b4</id><link>http://thehill.com/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/219015-draft-draft-senate-again-blocks-dems-bid-to-nix-big-oil-tax-breaks#comment-480184362</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>