<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ttry/post/2012-03-29T09:55:37</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjd16</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5wi8z</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>That's a great question Nikolas.  swamp coolers and whole house fans are great ideas for the desert Southwest.

Here are a couple more:
This product uses the waste Heat from your AC to give you free hot water for showering, dishes, at least during the times of year when your AC runs.

http://www.turbotecproducts.com/Literature_files/Tribute%201.pdf

New Heat pump systems can do the same thing, and basically shift Heat from your house to your water.

Another simple one is to install low-e film on the inside of your windows.  It applies directly to the glass, and is designed to be relatively transparent to the visible light spectrum, and also relatively reflective of infrared light which limits that Heat Gain through your windows.  Especially useful on east and west exposure windows that receive a lot of sun.  But in your climate, probably useful on all sides of the house.  

And although it is almost standard practice to use low-e glass in new windows, it is somewhat of a new approach to install this product after the window is installed.  This is just to say that windows receiving a lot of direct sun may get warmer than they were perhaps designed for.  This should be reviewed with a manufacturer such as 3M.

http://solutions.3m.com/wps/portal/3M/en_US/Window_Film/Solutions/Markets-Products/Residential/Sun_Control_Window_Films/</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l2liw</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/thxi</id></website><link>http://grist.org/media/the-washington-post-speaks-the-truth-on-climate-change/?postpost=v2</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T16:37:16+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:55:37+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ttry</id><link>http://grist.org/media/the-washington-post-speaks-the-truth-on-climate-change/?postpost=v2#comment-479506149</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>