<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mircp4/post/2012-03-22T23:01:43</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>

















(Supposedly) We invaded
Afghanistan because their government, the Taliban, was harboring Al Qaeda, who
attacked us on 9/11, and refused to turn them over to us. So vengeance would be
one reason. A secondary reason is that the Taliban was an oppressive (an
understatement) regime, that denied freedoms to the citizens of Afghanistan.
Soooooo, we invaded, and made it so the Taliban no longer had control of the
country. But we never really captured or killed all the Taliban, or Al Qaeda
because they took to hiding in the very mountainous countryside, or ran to
Pakistan. Plus, the ten-years-long battle with insurgents distracted us from
completing the mission as well as distracted us from nation-building
(--training an army, police, providing safety for the new government and
re-building infrastructure). According to some, conditions in the country are
better. According to others, they are worse. It wasn't a perfect plan, or
execution. Nor will it come to a perfect conclusion (we will look incompetent
and have blood on our hands). BUT, I believe that vengeance for 9/11 and
dismantling the oppressive fundamentalist Islamic regime were good reasons for
invading Afghanistan. I believe that we should chase our enemies anywhere they
may be hiding. I believe we should use military means to Ensure our fellow
citizens of this world are not oppressed and/or denied basic human rights,
which we and hundreds of other nations have agreed are necessary. I believe
that leaving the country in a state of chaos would be morally irresponsible.
And if we are as moral as we claim to be, and I say we are, then we shouldn't
do that. I take solace in the fact that I believe we have learned our lesson.
Sadly, incidents like Burning holy books and mentally ill soldiers slipping through the filters are just the intrinsic natures of our
system.  This will make confrontations and tragedies the norm for generations to
come.


</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yia9w</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/22/justice/afghanistan-bales-charges/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T22:53:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T03:01:43+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mircp4</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/22/justice/afghanistan-bales-charges/index.html#comment-474169878</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/azoor</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>