<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m09ius/update/2012-04-02T01:41:06/a5bdbaed2408106b70bb855bde9d55d8dd6aadb270b1f12fc5bfd0cf3bcf8f38</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m09nl2</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h63na</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Please don't draw these kinds of conclusions from a Corning CES booth. You have no idea what kind of 'reinforced glass' they tested against their product or what kind of 'reinforced glass' the Galaxy Nexus has. Gorilla Glass is just another kind of reinforced glass the Galaxy Nexus doesn't have.

And the Samsung flood claim is ridiculous. Their top selling device is the Galaxy S2. Their highest-end devices (such as the Galaxy Note and Infuse 4G when it was the top-selling device on AT&amp;T before the Galaxy S2 was available) Always sell the best. They don't flood the market with devices, because almost all of their devices are carrier-specific variants of the same device. You can't buy an Epic 4G Touch from a T-Mobile store.

"Thier #1 status is only based on their number of phones sold.": According to smartphone ratings on both The Verge and PC World, 4 out of the top smartphones available are Samsung devices and a Samsung device has the top Spot on both lists. THAT is why Samsung is #1.

Metal is still a terrible choice of build material for a smartphone. There is a reason why small electronic devices (that are more likely to be dropped) are made from plastic: game controllers, TV remotes, etc. It mitigates impact forces much better than metal, it isn't malleable so it doesn't dent and deform, it's lighter and generally more ergonomic, etc. There's a reason why underneath HTC's metal skins are hunks of encasing plastic.

"That is what I have and I prefer its color corrective nature over the over saturated AMOLED as everything on it looks like an HDR photo.": HDR has nothing to do with color saturation. That aside, the color saturation on SAMOLED panels is tunable on just about any Samsung device to get a more accurate picture without losing the deep blacks and infinite contrast ratio.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6v730h</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/y2ru</id></website><link>http://www.engadget.com/2012/04/01/how-would-you-change-samsungs-galaxy-nexus/</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T11:13:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T05:41:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m09ius</id><link>http://www.engadget.com/2012/04/01/how-would-you-change-samsungs-galaxy-nexus/#comment-483302588</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l92e1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>