<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3a7vz/update/2012-03-28T16:46:57/397543724b5c2add0e61e24369c59c912cc5f73e6858ccc7d7c92662ef383cdd</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m32j95</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ywso2</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Just out of curiousity, what would you do if someone was following you? Would you confront them? I'm not trying to put you on the Spot, but this is something I've considered and asked others about to see what would be considered reasonable after information on this case came out.  I will confess that I am a parent and have a son who is the same age as Trayvon Martin. I have told him since he was just a little guy that he needs to be careful and watch out for strangers. I have put a wariness in him about anyone who might follow or watch him, so I wonder if perhaps Trayvon (whose parents seem like they would also caution their son) was Acting out of the fear instilled by parents, schools, safety programs etc. 

I do have to say, with regard to the injuries to Zimmerman, a picture paints a thousand words.  That his injuries were not enough to even justify a visit to the hospital makes me suspicious of how injured he really was. At the very least I would have expected the police to send him to the hospital to document his injuries to verify or refute any claims of self defense. Zimmerman's own camp has stated he didn't seek any kind of medical treatment until the next day. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h82l7</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dneq</id></website><link>http://www.adn.com/2012/03/27/2394284/letters-to-the-editor-32812.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T03:06:28+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T20:46:57+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3a7vz</id><link>http://www.adn.com/2012/03/27/2394284/letters-to-the-editor-32812.html#comment-478757246</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/d19m5</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>