<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mla1aa/update/2012-02-19T13:49:39/7a495b1a72862df1392db98c81b988d31ed94eb4e5f4d29c0d055e895542c9e1</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mr33gi</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>My mother could remember discreet, drab little shops that sold pills that were supposed to "bring on" menstruation. She said ~ and I suspect that she would have known ~ that they didn't work, any more than the old "cures" of hot baths and jumping up and down. The only sure way of ending a pregnancy was to find an abortionist (not easy) who might (if you were lucky) be a trained midwife or doctor, but who just as easily might not. The "procedure" wasn't pleasant, to put it mildly, and there was Always the chance that you might end up in hospital with a policeman at your bedside hoping to get your abortionist's name before you Bled to death.

A woman of my mother's generation, with little if any control over her own fertility, might just as easily regard a miscarriage as a blessing rather than a tragedy. Let me emphasise, I'm talking about a respectable married woman who was trying to bring up four children in difficult circumstances and whose last pregnancy and childbirth had damn near killed her. And this is before we consider unmarried girls, rape victims and so on. This is the reality that most Western women thought had been safely consigned to history and which male politicians and clerics want to re-establish.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yb8si4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/z910</id></website><link>http://www.patheos.com/blogs/slacktivist/2012/02/18/the-biblical-view-thats-younger-than-the-happy-meal/</link><postedTime>2012-02-19T00:04:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-19T18:49:39+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mla1aa</id><link>http://www.patheos.com/blogs/slacktivist/2012/02/18/the-biblical-view-thats-younger-than-the-happy-meal/#comment-443496421</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6v11l</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-19</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>