<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw5e56/update/2012-03-30T05:40:58/13d9e1fe43494161f1567f6a8742d49ce9ab9dc658f65e808746088dbf302c4b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The Old Hag Syndrome is so strange... I've experienced it 3 times now in my life.  The first two I was a child, and the presence was in my closet and messing with my body and that sense of evil and fear was so STRONG.

The 3rd time was just last year, and since I remembered the other 2 times it happening and I knew it was sleep Paralysis, I told myself to stay calm and that is simply what's happening.  However, the shadow behind me kept looming over me, and then it started to strangle me.  

I would tell myself that it's just the sleep Paralysis/old hag thingy and I'd be fine, but it's so real.  I finally woke up and yelled.

I had a house guest at the time, and he was there (I was asleep on the couch) and he said he didn't want to wake me but I was  so strange... whispering words and my arm was raised up and stayed still for 5 minutes (I was trying to push  the strangler in my old hag-dream).

Another time when I was a child and I experienced this, I didn't have the evil presence  in the room like normal.  Instead, an atom bomb had gone Off outside and I was laying in bed, unable to move, and thought that I was simply dead.  It was sleep Paralysis, but the presence of evil and fear wasn't there.

It's a real thangy, though I assume it's our mind freaking out from the rarity of it all...

DMC</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z6q8j</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/jfh4</id></website><link>http://www.strangerdimensions.com/2012/03/29/old-hag-syndrome-movie-now-in-production/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T12:01:31+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T09:40:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw5e56</id><link>http://www.strangerdimensions.com/2012/03/29/old-hag-syndrome-movie-now-in-production/#comment-480564730</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cygx5</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>