<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/226781/post/127258758/comment/325088245</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Wesley is so damn PRECIOUS here. His needy eagerness with Cordelia in the beginning, his researching skills, his sincere happiness when Angel turns out not to be the killer, playing sidekick in the car, getting grabbed by Penn as he tries to suavely amble into the office, jumping into Penn&amp;#039;s lair like a bounding slay-happy puppy... &amp;quot;oh dear!&amp;quot;  
  
And Cordelia is just a &lt;i&gt;really great friend&lt;/i&gt;. I love the relationship that has built up between Angel and Cordelia within the first 11 episodes.  
  
Kate&amp;#039;s initial denial is done well - great moment where she stands frozen as Angel Burns himself clutching her cross.  
  
I really like the little aside about how they were to meet in Italy, and Penn waited until the 19th century. On one hand, I  enjoy stuff like this with casual allusions to how old vampires would have a different conception of time than us. On another hand, I love the reminder of how the curse disrupted soulless Angel&amp;#039;s life -- how many people did he leave hanging, waiting somewhere for him to write, to appear... how many people lived who would have died, and how many died that would have lived (like the citizens of the Italian towns that Penn must have fed Off of for decades, when otherwise they would have long moved on)...  
  
Alas, the vampire fighting doesn&amp;#039;t work for me that well. Though I liked it more than the typical fight scenes we get on BtVS (which I personally find too choreographed -- I find sloppy brawls much more believable). </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:226781:127258758</id><idPostId>127258758</idPostId><idBlogId>226781</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:226781</id><idBlogId>226781</idBlogId><link>http://markwatches.net/reviews</link><displayName>Mark Watches</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://markwatches.net/reviews/2012/03/mark-watches-angel-s01e11-somnambulist/</link><displayName>Mark Watches 'Angel': S01E11 - Somnambulist </displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T21:16:56.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:226781:127258758:325088245</id><link>http://markwatches.net/reviews/2012/03/mark-watches-angel-s01e11-somnambulist/#IDComment325088245</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T21:16:56.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Mark Watches 'Angel': S01E11 - Somnambulist  by robin_comments</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://intensedebate.com/people/robin_comments</link><idEmailMd5>5436e9461da9a6caf05d7e0a205925c6</idEmailMd5><displayName>robin_comments</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://intensedebate.com/people/robin_comments"&gt;robin_comments&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://markwatches.net/reviews/2012/03/mark-watches-angel-s01e11-somnambulist/"&gt;Mark Watches 'Angel': S01E11 - Somnambulist &lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>