<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7h75/update/2012-03-30T15:11:44/993350e3c91e95da288a9c3076bf995d3b3f57d0489c1c52ac1fb0f7ce8e298d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Lager molecules can adsorb more energy and since the carbon dioxide molecule is larger than the oxygen and nitrogen gas molecules, it does not surprise me that global warming, because of the increase of carbon dioxide molecules in the atmosphere, is real. BUT nitrogen oxides are also large molecules and their presence is also increasing, not only due to the Burning of fossil fuels, but also due to the increased use of synthesized fertilizer. Besides its contribution to adsorbing more energy, thus contributing to global warming, the impact of 'green' rain is completely ignored. Reactive nitrogen (single atoms, thus the N2 gas molecule) is essential for plant growth, so when during wet weather green rain falls on the earth it stimulates grasses and brush to grow, while they, during dry weather, are becoming kindle wood for now uncontrollable range and wild fires.  
Probably one of the reasons why nobody pays any attention to the huge increase of reactive nitrogen in our biosphere, is the simple fact that the nitrogen element cycle is complicated and occurs in the soil, in water and in the atmosphere. Another reason may be that, when EPA implemented the Clean Water , it ignored all the nitrogenous (urine and protein) waste in sewage because it used an essential water pollution test (developed in 1920) incorrect and for years claimed that nitrogenous waste was not important. Now mainly due to the fact that nitrogenous waste (besides exerting an oxygen demand (just like fecal waste) is also a fertilizer for algae and thus contributes to red Tides and dead zones, EPA can not any longer ignore this waste. However, now it is called a 'nutrient' and blames this waste mostly on the runoffs from farms and cities. Any new program to address this type of pollution, without first correcting this essential test, so we finally will know how sewage is really treated and what the effluent waste loading is, will be again a waste of time and money, since they are doomed to fail.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zq5ar</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/thxi</id></website><link>http://grist.org/climate-change/climate-change-is-already-harshing-the-weather/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:36:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:11:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7h75</id><link>http://grist.org/climate-change/climate-change-is-already-harshing-the-weather/#comment-481087408</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cdc22</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>