<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miyw1d/update/2012-03-22T21:18:25/06080952504179486ff9ff439dd8664ece19fd454967614cd3d6291a82776f32</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>POSTED FOR ADAM:
JP once again, sorry it's taken a few days to reply.1. "From your opening statement it appears that you have no specific mechanism in mind to account for the warming you agree has been taking place in our climate. " JP please read my comments more carefully. I never said that just a single mechanism could explain 20th century climate change, but a multitude of different natural forces  on the climate like solar variation, cosmic ray flux, and oceanic oscilations like the AMO. And once again I suggest that you read Scafettta's papers which contain detailed discussion of the natural influences on the climate. And you might also like to know that he has just published a new paper. http://tallbloke.wordpress.com/2012/03/21/nicola-scafetta-major-new-paper-on-solar-planetary-theory/ "I'll be happy to get into the weeds regarding GCR theory Adam, if you will first explain one thing to me. If GCR (Galactic cosmic rays) are causing the warming we see, how is it that a solar mechanism causes warming which is more pronounced during the night than during the day?" I'm assuming that you got that from John Cook. Nights warming faster than days is perfectly compatible with natural drivers of climate change. Read this link here http://motls.blogspot.co.uk/2011/02/why-dana1981-hasnt-proved-climate.html "And if it's not GCR's but some other solar mechanism, how does it Heat the troposphere while at the same time cool the stratosphere?" Once again read my previous comments. There are numerous factors which can explain stratospheric cooling. And might I once again remind you that there has been no cooling in the stratosphere since 1995. It has also been theorised that the different lengths of the solar cycles might affect natural el nino events. This would not lead to warming in the stratopshere and is perfectly consistent with observations. Read this link http://tallbloke.wordpress.com/2012/03/16/roger-andrews-how-the-sun-caused-all-the-recent-global-warming/ "Additionally, whether cosmic rays are correlated with climate or not, they have been regularly measured by the neutron monitor at Climax Station (Colorado) since 1953 and show no long term trend. No trend = no explanation for current changes." Now that is interesting. I gave you a link showing that that statement was not true. http://motls.blogspot.com/2007/07/nir-shaviv-why-is-lockwood-and-frohlich.htmlif In fact I clearly stated "you look at the graph shown in the linkhttp://1.bp.blogspot.com/_4ruQ...you will see that for the past three decades, each of the peaks of CR flux was lower than the previous one. If the CR theory was correct, this would have caused warming." JP I understand that I've been giving a lot of links, and that it would be very difficult for you to look at all of them, but might I once again ask you to just try and read my comments more carefully. Look at this graph here of measurements of cosmic rays, compared to temps (sorry its in German) http://notrickszone.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/03/kosmischestrahlung23-1024x768.jpg "I suggest that the "solar amplification" you are looking for is CO2.When you talk about "amplifiers", you're just using a different word for feedback." JP you are wrong. CO2 has nothing to do with the effect of solar activity on climate, and it is certainly not the amplifier. CR's are the most plausilble amplifier, but it is not the only evidence for it. I recommend that you read this paper here, which provides strong evidence in support of a solar amplification mechanism http://www.sciencebits.com/files/articles/CalorimeterFinal.pdf"Last point on this first topic, you once again point me to a list of papers. Adam, you need to be specific about what paper (and what part of that paper) pertains to which argument (and what part of that argument). It's no good to hand me a pile of journal articles expecting me to pick out the appropriate reference. You need to properly cite your references. I acknowledge that you often do this correctly, so I know you know the difference."Well, I'd say that the best papers for you to look at would be these two herehttp://www.seas.harvard.edu/climate/pdf/bond_2001.pdfhttp://friendsofscience.org/assets/documents/Veizer-Shaviv,%20Celestial%20Drive.pdf""Comments in blogs and forums do not warrant a reply because any valid criticism would follow the established peer-review process of submitting a comment for publication in the same journal, which allows the author of the original paper a chance to publish a rebuttal in defense of their paper." Do you recognize that quote Adam? "Yes JP. And I understand that every author has the right to respond to the criticism of their paper. But what I am saying is that you can't simply dismiss them simply because their "opinion pieces". Just because they haven't been peer reviewed that doesn't mean they're wrong. And once again I understand the problems of the author not being able to respond, but still you can check the facts for yourself if you want. Nir Shaviv pointed out that over the past 3 decades each of the peaks in cosmic ray flux was lower than the last. This is an empirical measured FACT. And you can check it for yourself. You can't simply dismiss his piece outright simply because you don't like that it wasn't peer reviewed. And Alec Rawls also showed that for the past few decades solar activity was at it's highest in centuries. This is also a FACT, which you can check for yourself if you want. JP how about actually looking at the evidence, rather than just sorting things into categories of peer reviewed and non-peer reviewed?"For now, I'll just leave you with this quote from the man himself: "These [Scarfetta's] results, while confirming that anthropogenic-added climate forcing might have progressively played a dominant role in climate change during the last century, also suggest that the solar impact on climate change during the same period is significantly stronger than what some theoretical models have predicted." Does that sound like a refutation of AGW to you?"JP that quotes is from one of his older studies, published 6 years ago. More recent data and scientific evidence (as demonstrated in his later papers) have shown that the sun and celestial cycles did cause the majority of 20th cenury warming.Quotes from his more recent papers:http://www.fel.duke.edu/~scafetta/pdf/opinion0308.pdf"The non equilibrium thermodynamic models we used suggest that the Sun is influencing climate significantly more than the IPCC report claims. If climate is as sensitive to solar changes as the above phenomenological findings suggest, the current anthropogenic contribution to global warming is significantly overestimated. We estimate that the Sun could account for as much as 69% of the increase in Earth’s average temperature,  on the TSI reconstruction used.5 Furthermore, if the Sun does cool , as some solar forecasts predict will happen over the next few decades, that cooling could stabilize Earth’s climate and avoid the catastrophic consequences predicted in the IPCC report."http://www.fel.duke.edu/~scafetta/pdf/ATP2998.pdf"The IPCC (2007) claim that the solar contribution to climate change since 1950 is negligible may be based on wrong solar data in addition to the fact that the EBMs and GCMs there used are missing or poorly modeling several climate mechanisms that would significantly amplify the solar effect on climate. When taken into account the entire range of possible TSI satellite composite since 1980, the solar contribution to climate change ranges from a slight cooling to a significant warming, which can be as large as 65% of the total observed global warming."http://www.fel.duke.edu/~scafetta/pdf/scafetta-JSTP2.pdf"A phenomenologicalmodel based on the se astronomical cycles can be used to well reconstruct the temperature oscillationssince 1850 and to make partial forecasts for the 21stcentury. It is found that at least 60%of the globalwarming observed since 1970 has been induced by the combined effect of the above natural climateoscillations.The partial forecast indicates that climate may stabilize or cool until2 030–2040.Possiblephysical mechanisms are qualitatively discussed with an emphasis on the phenomenon of collective""On secular,millenarian and larger timescales astronomicaloscillations and solar changes drive climate variations. Shaviv’stheory (2003) can explain the large 145Myr climate oscillationsduring the last 600million years. Milankovic’s theory(1941) canexplain themulti-millennial climate oscillations observed duringthe last1000kyr.Climate oscillations with periods of 2500,1500,and 1000 years during the last10,000year(theHolocene)arecorrelated to equivalent solar cycles that caused the Minoan,Roman, Medieval and Modern warm periods""The existenceofa60-yearnaturalcycleintheclimatesystem,whichisclearlyproveninmultiplestudiesandhereinin Figs.2,6,10and 12, indicatesthattheAGWTpromotedbythe IPCC(2007),whichclaimsthat100%oftheglobalwarmingobservedsince1970is anthropogenic,iserroneous.Infact,since1970aglobalwarmingof about0.5 1C hasbeenobserved.However,from1970to2000the60-year naturalcyclewasinhiswarmingphaseandhascontributedno lessthan0.3 1C oftheobserved0.51Cwarming,as Fig. 10B shows.Thus, atleast60%oftheobservedwarmingsince1970hasbeennaturally induced.""Theplanetarymodelwouldalsobemoreaccurateinforecasting climatechangesduringthenextfewdecades.Overthis time,theglobalsurfacetemperaturewilllikelyremainapproximately steady,oractuallycool."And read his later papershttp://www.fel.duke.edu/~scafetta/pdf/Mazzarella-%20Scafetta-60-yr.pdfhttp://www.fel.duke.edu/~scafetta/pdf/Scafetta-auroras.pdfhttp://www.fel.duke.edu/~scafetta/pdf/Scafetta_models_comparison_ATP.pdf"Does that sound like a refutation of AGW to you?"I know that was a rhetorical question, but still YES his papers clearly show the evidence of natural oscillations being the primary drivers of climate change."Next in your comment, you proceed to show me some "real world data" from an "astrophysicist who has published in the peer-reviewed literature". Well why not show me the peer-reviewed data?"I have showed you peer reviewed data."You go on to say that many studies (which one's please) "... ignore the fact that in recent decades the sun has been more active than centuries." I assume you meant "in centuries"."JP papers like Lockwood and Solanski only focus on trend of solar activity. They ignore the 'pulsing' of the sun.Look at this graphhttp://www.climate4you.com/images/SolarIrradianceReconstructedSince1610.giffromhttp://www.climate4you.com/You can clearly see the LEVEL of solar activity through the past three decades being the highest in centuries. This could have caused a warming over the period."But an increase in CCN's (Cloud Condensation Nuclei) most certainly has not. "JP I suggest that you read this paperhttp://hallolinden-db.de/files/2009.08.01_Svensmark_GRL_09_Cosmic_Rays.pdf"Look at the work of Pierce and Adams from Carnegie Mellon"JP Pierce and Adams used a computer model. They did not use real world data. Svensmark has experimental evidence to back up his theory. Therre is also the very clear correlation between CR's and clouds, as well as the geological evidence for his theory. Real world data bets models every time.http://www.theresilientearth.com/?q=content/attempt-discredit-cosmic-ray-climate-link-using-computer-model"Do I get to assume he's wrong if temps don't go down in the next...oh, let's say six years? No I don't. Because trends of less than thirty years are weather trends not climate trends."JP once again please read my comments. For the last 10-15 years greenhouse gas forcing on the climate was meant to be at its maximum yet little to no warming occurred. None of the models predicted that. I also think that skeptics Vahrenholt and Luning answer your argument the besthttp://wattsupwiththat.com/2012/02/13/german-skeptics-luning-and-vahrenholt-respond-to-criticism/"Next, Feulner tries to score points by using the 30-year climate rule. In some official definitions, climate is defined as the 30-year mean of weather. While this makes sense for some considerations, this rigid rule obstructs the discussion on the mechanisms that are involved in climate. It’s becoming increasingly clear that natural decadal cycles have been greatly under-estimated in the past. For example the Pacific Decadal Oscillation (PDO) is characterized by a warm and a Cold phase, each lasting 20 to 30 years. They have a significant impact on global temperature. Should that 30-year-climate window unfortunately get placed between both phases, then the trends get mixed up and we end up comparing apples and oranges. The corresponding “climate“ results end up  more on the choice of the start point of the 30-year window and less on the real, shorter-scale temperature trends. Consequently, looking at 10-year temperature trends is not only legitimate, but it also makes sense."JP"Adam, do you honestly believe that coupled GCM's do not include changes in ocean Heat content?"I didn't mean that they didn't include changes in OHC. Merely that they don't have a proper understanding of it. Models present a very simplistic view of the climate system, and are not supported by real world data. Not one of the models predicted the lack of increase in OHC as shown by Douglass and Knox's paper"I assume by "ocean content" you meant "ocean Heat content", or perhaps that's just another example of MY lack of understanding."It was just a simple typing mistake. There is no need to be snarkey about it."Because you think my understanding is so limited, please translate Mr. Rodger's sentence for me. "I clearly explained it you in my previous comment. But I don't see why that one sentence is so important. If you want more information, then I suggest you contact Norman Rogers and ask him."You say that if "stratospheric cooling were due to greenhouse gases, you would have expected the temperature to go down in a clear linear long term decline." Why? Did somebody shut  ENSO? "No I was simply stating the prediction of of the climate models. The models can't fully account for the effects of ENSO. But, again you keep using the 'short term trends' and 'natural variability' explanation, so here is a question to you:What scientific/empirical evidence is there that the decrease in stratospheric temperature (which ended in 1995) was due to human emissions of CO2?That's a simple question. Perhaps you would care to answer it"The upper stratosphere is going down even more dramatically. Looks like NASA was right and that would mean you were... wrong. "JP please provide a graph showing significantly cooling in the stratosphere since 1995?And there is also evidence that CFC's may have played a significant part in stratospheric cooling.http://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/01431160902821841"And in your very next sentence: "Sorry JP, I'm not the one whose been making any errors." Oh, the irony."JP once again there is no need to be snarkey. Once again please provide a graph supporting your claims."ut it doesn't stop. Adam: "It is not the number of papers repeating an argument, but the actual data and evidence." And again, three paragraphs later: "What I was trying to show was that there are indeed numerous papers showing that the sun is the dominant driver of climate." So it's "not the number of papers", except if they're "numerous"? Like a farmer plowing a field Adam, you need to turn around every so often, and see where you've just been."JP you are taking my phrases out of context. It is clear that I was not using the simple fact that there were "numerous" papers supporting solar driven climate change as an argument, but the actual EVIDENCE AND DATA which was provided in those studies, especially in Scafetta's. Please try better to understand my arguments." Because there has been no quantification of the effects of a mechanism that could be a solar feedback (e.g., GCR), there is no way to include such a mechanism in a model. If (and when) such mechanisms can be confirmed and their effect quantified, they would surely be incorporated. Until then, what are climatologists supposed to do; assume there's such a mechanism and guess it's radiative forcing. "Exactly. You've just acknowledged that the models are too limited to have proper understanding of the true nature in which natural forces control our climate. JP these simple facts about what the models are missing clearly show that they are not a reliable source for predicting climate events."If you want to exchange your, or other's, hypotheses; with specific references to observations; I'd be interested to see them."I did give you specific references to papers supporting the major role of oceanic oscillations in climate. If you looked at the links I provided you would see that. And Chris De Freitas' talk was based on a paper he has published in the peer reviewed literature."Adam, I've looked at more than two hundred links you directed me to. I ask you now to see this one video. It's less than two minutes long."I watched the video. And once again, might I say that short term trends of 2-3 years is cherrypicking, since there is the power of natural variability on the long term trend. But 10-15 years is not cherrypicking. Once again I refer you to the statement by Vahrenholt."Okay, Muller is not what he says he was. He's what YOU say he was. It must be great to know more about other people than they know about themselves."Once again. PLEASE READ THE LINKS. Muller was quoted numerous times stating that he believed humans were causing GW. DO you deny thst he said this?"The BEST studies account for UHI. It's not even that difficult. Read how they do it. What study or studies of GST's do you think are accurate? I'm guessing none, because they ALL AGREE."Once again you have STILL not answered all of the points that was raised regarding the BEST data in the links I gave you.""Temperature Trends in the Lower Atmosphere: Steps for Understanding and Reconciling Differences. "The report identified and corrected errors in satellite temperature measurements and other temperature observations, which increased scientific confidence in the conclusion that the lower atmosphere is warming on a global scale: "There is no longer a discrepancy in the rate of global average temperature increase for the surface compared with higher levels in the atmosphere"."There conclusion is not supported by real world data. Once again please look at the graph I provided of GISS temps to UAH temps."For example, skeptic Roy Spencer provides a graph of the UAH/MSU data which he updates monthly. He  shows the running 13 month mean AND the third polynomial fit. Others add least squares. Each gives a little different view of the trend. The same fit over different time frames is simply a way to view rate changes. "Roy spencer was plotting the long term average over that period. He was not simply cherry picking his start dates and applying multiple trend lines as was done in the IPCC's report. What he did was completely different."Do you know what the temperature difference above and below a Halocline can be? Easily 2 degrees C, and sometimes more."Yes, but that's irrelevant. There is still no way the IR supposedly Reaching the Earth by CO2 could pass through the first 700m undetected and just magically show up below it. You'd still show the first 700m to show a very clear Heating pattern. You have still not answered this."As for your assertion that the top 700 meters would necessarily contain more of the excess Heat from AGW, considering that NOAA states that the average depth of the worlds oceans is 4,267 meters, you might want to reconsider that calculation."Once again, how is the total depth relevant? The IR would have to pass through the first 700m, in order to warm the area below it. Fact."Remember, it's the CHANGE in Heat content within both bodies that is determinative."Yes, but the change is not what is predicted. Once again I refer you to Douglass and Knox paper."Could you explain this sentence please: "I think that you've scored an own goal with that comment there." Does that mean I won?"No that does not mean that you have won. Do you know what an own goal is?Anyway JP, I'm going to be going away for a week, so I'm not going to be able to continue this debate. If you want to continue next week, or just agree to disagree, then that's your choice.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6m57ch</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/jz8w</id></website><link>http://tucsoncitizen.com/wryheat/2012/03/19/water-vapor-and-the-climate-why-carbon-dioxide-is-a-very-minor-player/</link><postedTime>2012-03-19T14:30:42+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T01:18:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miyw1d</id><link>http://tucsoncitizen.com/wryheat/2012/03/19/water-vapor-and-the-climate-why-carbon-dioxide-is-a-very-minor-player/#comment-474116552</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hei6l</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-19</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>