<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmmdu/update/2012-03-30T08:53:13/f5e37807c1b9eb73ac9ee534cd048366efd81ddc85ff8af3f65b19191a2df04b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Edward is really not given enough credit if you ask me Rolling Stones #70?? WTF!!  He should be #1 or at least #2 behind Hendrix at the very least. Shows what Rolling Stone knows about virtuoso guitar playing.... nothing!!  If you ask me there were two real game changers in rock guitar playing, Hendrix and Van Halen period. We can debate the skills of Clapton or the impact of Townsend and Page, but if your a guitar player like I am for 30 years, you can look deep into their ability and skills and see it for what it really is. This is why he jumped 62 Spots when being judged by other guitarist's. Eddie is still so good, we would all shake in our boots to play in front of him. Even the people that grew up on Clapton and Page gotta admit they were great for their time but neither can hold a candle to Edward from a technical standpoint. But there is more to Ed than technical skill and like Hendrix this is what takes him beyond all other players. He's like the Michael Jordan of Guitar Playing, he can do it all. Really it's pretty clear he's the greatest rock guitar player ever. Even players like Yngwie Malmsteen,Steve Vai and Paul Gilbert with all their incredible skills are missing a little bit of the magic Ed has Always had.  Ed is the King!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zklg8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/fbtm</id></website><link>http://www.vhnd.com/2012/03/29/preview-how-great-is-eddie-van-halen/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T05:37:42+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T12:53:13+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmmdu</id><link>http://www.vhnd.com/2012/03/29/preview-how-great-is-eddie-van-halen/#comment-480706151</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>