<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpttcc/update/2012-03-21T17:07:00/735e227c2aaf4afd597c9a41eb39f881a53a1d55c85316e10521fd25b2e2726c</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp72lf</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c8mwp</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>You really need to catch up on this story. A  birth, a Secret adoption in another state, all premeditated and planned and an ongoing deception while the adoption process is completed is about as close to legalized kidnapping as it gets.

He was never okay with the adoption, he never changed his mind, he has fought for his rights from the very beginning.  People are inventing these allegories to help you understand but there's really no need.  This story is cut and dried and your position is complete nonsense. The more you defend the state and the parents the more ignorant you sound.

 I get that you're arguing from the position of the child's emotional well-being but this case is bigger than even that. This case should send a message that the relevant laws in Utah are highly skewed, if not entirely unjust.  It may take time for her to get close to her father but it will happen, he obviously loves her very much.

This is a visceral issue.  Like many fathers out there I put myself in his shoes and I would do EXACTLY the same thing for my daughter. I would fight for her until I were face down on the Cold ground.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6d39oz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6rx1</id></website><link>http://www.sltrib.com/sltrib/news/53764171-78/manzanares-birth-adoption-court.html.csp</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T17:55:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-21T21:07:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpttcc</id><link>http://www.sltrib.com/sltrib/news/53764171-78/manzanares-birth-adoption-court.html.csp#comment-472787391</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5f90i</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>