<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/234352/post/86320894/comment/328438022</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Through the years,UGG Bailey Button Kids Boot 5991 Sand ugg boots, it\'s aggravated a lot of people in her sport when she\'s appeared cavalier about the very thing that has brought her fame and fortune, but simply because she has been able to distance herself and find other outlets may explain why she\'s not yet Burned out,louis vuitton outlet, physically or emotionally. It\'s not just that so many of us love sports so and can\'t comprehend someone who\'s in the game not caring for it all that much. Rather, I think,Burberry Uomini, there\'s a lot of envy involved. Why, fans have even been shocked at the recent revelations that several ice hockey goons really didn\'t enjoy being goons. The irony is, in my experience, that for those athletes who do make it to the top, a passion for the game does not necessarily best light that path to glory. Now, when somebody from another glamorous profession &amp;#8212; an actor, say,burberry sito ufficiale,Chicago Blackhawks Hockey Clubhouse - ESPN, or a model &amp;#8212; walks away from success, there isn\'t the same intensity of either jealousy or bafflement because not so many of us tried to Act or model when we were growing up. Ahh, but how many of us kids played sports and dreamed of being a star? So many people &amp;#8212; girls as well as boys now &amp;#8212; grow up playing sports and loving them and ultimately failing at them; and so when we see someone who achieved what we couldn\'t,Sac Hermes 2011 New, we\'re all the more put out if they can blithely turn their back on it. In fact, at the age of 30,sac hermes pas cher, Serena is old for a tennis player, and she may still be a contender only because she has not loved tennis so much. While her confession might have surprised some,Nike Mercurial Vapor Elite, I suspect that even more were irritated, actually angered, that an athlete &amp;#8212; a great champion,ghd france! &amp;#8212; could utter such blasphemy. When Tiki Barber wanted desperately to come back after five seasons, nobody wanted him. Youth may be wasted on the young, but in sports, the most telling truth is that youth must not be wasted. On the other hand, it\'s also my experience that a lot of the more restrained athletes who do quit before they are done only find out afterward how much the game really meant to them. Now that Tim Tebow is out of hearts and minds, and we can actually turn our attention to other things, let us go clear to the other side of the world. There, a short while ago, while preparing for the Australian Open, Serena Williams said: \"I don\'t love tennis today,Burberry Lady Bags, but ... I\'ve actually never liked sports.\" We sometimes also hear the sentiment that we\'d like to see an athlete quit near the peak of his career, but when Tiki Barber, the running back,WolverineNation - Michigan Wolverines Football, Basketball,,borse louis vuitton, did just that a few years ago,louis vuitton damier, he was utterly astonished at the reaction of so many fans. They all but berated him &amp;#8212; how dare you leave the game! 
 
[WORDPRESS HASHCASH] The poster sent us \'0 which is not a hashcash value. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:234352:86320894</id><idPostId>86320894</idPostId><idBlogId>234352</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:234352</id><idBlogId>234352</idBlogId><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog</link><displayName>Wanton Wordsmith</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/</link><displayName>The day he went away</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T10:46:21.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:234352:86320894:328438022</id><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/#IDComment328438022</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T10:46:21.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The day he went away by hljfeos5828e</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://borsebburberrysito1.com/</link><idEmailMd5>09fcdf1d035b181eb145774c49545e60</idEmailMd5><displayName>hljfeos5828e</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://borsebburberrysito1.com/"&gt;hljfeos5828e&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/"&gt;The day he went away&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>