<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk89il/update/2012-03-24T17:08:56/dddb312743cc216e085aa718ecc59c42d2b26b83e7f3b295b5f3d5b053d3cd07</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Levels of violence are relative and unique to the viewer. I read another review that hammered the film for being too violent. Clearly, the violence upset that reviewer but not this one.  Whether or not the violence upsets is more a function of the viewer's preferences, not the filmmaker's. 

This reviewer clearly sets forth individual opinion with the statement:
"If you're in the market for a terrific film that revolves around teenagers murdering one another...".  So, this reviewer seems to come from the standpont that watching teenagers murdering each other is pretty sweet.  But, it's an opinion.

I will probably see the film. Likely, I will consider it to be very violent, because I have little tolerance for viewing violence. Thus, I may consider the filmmaker to have captured the violence of the book well enough without becoming a gory slaughterfest that might make me Vomit and have nightmares for a couple of weeks; but, that's my preference. Many other folks will think differently. 

So, just read smartly. Understand where the author of this review is coming from, make your own decision, and Act accordingly.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6euqtu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ydw9</id></website><link>http://motherjones.com/node/168156</link><postedTime>2012-03-18T23:57:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-24T21:08:56+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk89il</id><link>http://motherjones.com/node/168156#comment-475459428</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zebrx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-18</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>