<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ptvr/update/2012-03-29T20:25:07/7df56b402ce0ca7d074a001e71028e2d0db27e2df72b95d4e77448ace6d032c5</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>As someone with first-hand experience, I can tell you that you couldn't possibly understand what it is like.  I thought I had overcome a meth addiction as a young teenager, but towards the end of college I began taking pain killers due to a car accident and bad Headaches.  During this time I watched half of my family get sick and die and the other half fall apart.  I was young, middle class, attractive, smart, and talented, but the physical pain and the mental pain became one.  I just didn't want to be in pain anymore, and it escalated.  It didn't help that my Mother also became addicted to Oxycontin after a back surgery (but I believe her pill-popping stemmed mostly from emotional pain also).  Pretty soon it was cheaper to snort heroin, and smoke heroin, then I was just going to "try" shooting heroin.  When you are young it is easy to feel like it won't happen to you.  I thought because I had quit crank on willpower alone that I wouldn't become addicted to anything else, I was just experimenting.  But once you feel that withdrawal I can attest that there is very little someone wouldn't do to get "well".  It is a very fast slippery slope where you can suddenly become the complete opposite of who you thought you were going to be.  Don't think that looks, money (not that I ever had a lot of it, but I know people who have), popularity, and intelligence make someone immune.  It is that kind of attitude that keeps us from coming up with the solutions that we need: better, affordable treatment.  It  bothered me so much that I would get on these waitlists for treatment that were months and months long, and because I didn't have money to pay for it they had very unrealistic expectations to stay on the waitlist.  "So just stay clean and come to the center that is 20 miles away even though you don't have a car for an hour twice per week" is the attitude you get.  Yet if you can afford to pay for it you are in by the next day.  Don't get me started on the rich-people rehabs on the beaches of Malibu and the like that are more like the best vacation I can't afford!  On the beach, swimming pools, jacuzzis, massage, acupuncture, state of the art gym, private rooms, etc. for only $30k for 30 days!  What a bargain...

Anyway I am getting Off track, but the most important thing is we can't pretend this is something that only happens to someone else.  Bragging about your willpower or how YOU personally haven't been an addict gets us absolutely nowhere.  Everyone has or will be touched by addiction at some point.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hec56</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnm3</id></website><link>http://www.sacbee.com/2012/03/28/4371717/heroin-use-surges-in-suburban.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T07:05:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:25:07+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ptvr</id><link>http://www.sacbee.com/2012/03/28/4371717/heroin-use-surges-in-suburban.html#comment-480066203</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzbvf</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>