<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi60ta/update/2012-03-22T22:50:28/4aa2acfe366b55e3f57ecd56a5b8dbab7353eeb90f4d9fe1a9eec07ee891d349</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Wow.... i Had a SO SIMILAR EXPERIENCE, it's frightening.

  A few years ago, i think ...3 maybe, there's this GUY that comes from the big town; you gotta know that i'm from a town (120 000 souls) in the province of Quebec that is actually split in three really distinct sub-towns with their own circles and stuff, but the RPG community is quite united all around. For such a backwater place (it's like 300 kms from Québec City, and more than 750 kms from Montreal!), the gaming community's still pretty big, totalling some 120 players from the three sub-towns (hey, backwaters are good for hobbies!). So MOST of the time, it's split in like three "gangs", let's say Center, West and East, with center being numerous and diverse, west being more hardcore and tightly knit and then east being kinda emergent and ..."young" (west was MOSTLY over 35 years old in general, the "Old Bunch").

  So the GUY comes in town, and we ...well we're ALL impressed. He went to the BIG LARPS with THOUSANDS for WEEKS in Europe, and he's got a gods damned real handmade armor, personally crafted; he's familiar with ALL the games, and i mean ALL from the obscure indies to the Classics and News D&amp;Ds and the OLD Paladiums and Robotech and GOD he's seen it ALL! One of my gaming partners at the time said he was our geekie equivalent of the "Artistic Revelation of the Year" award winner; it was mostly true. EVERYBODY wanted that GUY in his games, in his LARPs, in their circles; He was f'ing AMAZING! Charismatic! Smart! Strategic! Incredible Actor, Poet and Improv MASTER! A Hundred and twenty people litterally had a RPG-Crush on the guy! And HO his bombshell of a gf did NOT made it easy to just shrug him  either: hot, gentle and (larps be blessed) a REAL CLOTHES DESIGNER specialized in VINTAGE AND COSTUMES! They were SPLENDID!

  And SO, the GUY gets in EVERY circle; West, Center and East are RAVISHING the man and plugging him in ALL the games, creating settings around this AMAZING character he has been carrying for a couple years in differents larps, tabletops and whatnots. In 1 month, this guy got invited in the SIX most renowned larping groups AND in the four main games that are running at the time ...and through luch, the dude gets to crash at MY place one night, and i talk to him about MY game that's been running for two years and he's ALL   GOOGLY  EYED   AT   IT!!! He asks for a place in; my two friends/players in the living room go "YES!" and i'm "Sure, man that would be GREAT!" *thinking OHMYGODTHISISSOGONNAMAKEMYGEEKIEREPGOUP!*

  And so we start having him at home almost three times à week, he's really researching this character for the game, inserting himself into our little casual larp group (mostly, we're just 6 palls drinking and smoking shisha at larps, being haughty jerks to everyone's enjoyment ;), getting real close real quick with most of us and fitting in just well.

... and then.

  The guy takes time during game breaks, NEVER DURING GAMES MIND YOU (as he said), but he starts taking time during game breaks, in MY living room, with my friend from guadaloupa just leaving and my wife being there, PLAYING WITH US while HIS girlfriend is back at their appartment sewing his suits and costumes, he thus starts spreading neo-nazi-AND-misogynistic propaganda every  single   setence     for      HOURS! Nonstop. Their is NO other subjects in his mouth; he's not "hateful", he's "Just so Emminently Superior" that he doesn't need to hate, just to spread his gospel.

   I am frozen for 10 minutes. Completly taken aback. Nobody says ANYTHING. For HOURS we heard his comments ringing in our ears and whenever we would take a pause, he would spam the hate again. 



The GUY has INFILTRATED US!



   Next days, we don't see him but GOD we talk; was he high? Joking? Mad with anger at someone? WTH?!

   Anyways... we go on, the rpg community goes on, the games and larps and shits go on and he doesn't talk about it anymore. ...until a few days later, maybe 10, some 60 persons break camp after the big larp where the 3 gangs are starting to meet up (it's a new really classic fantasy one with swords and stuff that is starting to get real big, real quick at the time, his PERFECT setting) and   he    starts   AGAIN! HOURS while guys are STUCK packing tents, fetching lost items and gear he talks to the YOUNG ones and he's spreading his nazy-macho gospel!

   So NOW people are getting on to him; what we five have been whispering in disbelief for days is true, the guy is SPAMMING the community with Hate-speach! WTF?! So we TRY, and GODS we TRY to get him OUT of the games; he gets killed in 2 larps, he's sent on weird solo errands on tabletop games and i'm essentially calling him last minute possible every game so he CAN'T talk to us before, and i'm doing my best to expulse him (or say, we all go at the convenience store and hey, let's seperate now that we're here and you guys are halfway there anyway, ok all, yeah good, bye! and wink at the accomplices...) right as the game is done 'cause we were SO enthousiast about him in the first games that he's become central and ESSENTIAL to the plot, so we can't KICK him out of the GAME, but i'm sure as hell trying to kick him out of my APPARTMENT!

   And guess what, it works! He guesses i want more time with my then engaged girlfriend (now wife) and willingly gives us space, by his own words. As the weeks go by, his presence is slowly fading from the plot, we can slowly relegate him to a token role (i know, not the most human thing to do, but that game had been going on for 17 months with our best pals! IT STILL IS like 20 months later!) and he finally gets bored and, on a fancy, he moves away, like that, back to the big City where he'll try to catch a cougar to sugar-mommy him (not even a joke, he sent messages and updates on his status that he was getting fed, housed and groomed to bang some lady 23 years older than him ...for weeks).

  That would have been an acceptable, if weird, ending to the chapter.

  Somewhat...

  But he's a recurring character; we implanted him too well. I did it would seem!

  I realize that fact, a couple months later, when he "for old times' sake" wants to come around in town and ask to crash at my place; only natural, no? After all, it's the first place he did while around these parts and he got really engaged in our games, friendly terms and stuff, so ...yeah, i'm thinking "come on, he's not ...well, he's not ALL bad". So we let him in (the fact that he WAS standing in the rain, 11pm, with only a second pair of shoes and two shirts in october did kinda matter; in october, it gets to 16fahrenheit during nightime so it WOULD be bad to leave him to wander the streets...). Never. Let. Them. IN. EVER!

  He stayed for 4 days, days during which no games were running, no larps were active and no questing was possible. So he talked ...Bitched mostly; about black people, women, his ex *yeah the awesome designer girl who's still our friend? he cheated on her AND stalked her for months at the same time, while BOASTING, classy!)*, my softy-pink relationship and the no-balls rolists around here who aren't up to HIS standards and so he chose to quit their games...

  And he left. Leaving me with borrowed dirty clothes and a constant mental Nausea.

  Then did it again twice i think, but only a day, then only a few hours (i was getting Colder and Colder and clearer that his hate-speach was NOT ok here, at which point he would joke or simply laugh  my comments), then he disappeared completely.

   ...for a couple mounths. Then appeared with his BROTHER at my door, asking for hospitality. I promptly pick up a Risk 2210 game so he'll have to concentrate and shut up! but GUESS WHAT, he doesn't. The BROTHER is SO, SO not happy with the shameful talk of this little brat brother of his, but he doesn't SAY so, he just looks SSSSOOOOOOOOO SAD whenever the GUY opens up his hate-hole. I'm pitying the poor older bro and let them crash... again... god i'm a pushover. Or i've got a week Spot for those i had a (RPG)crush on in the past...

  So, they leave next morning, for there IS nothing there for them *why were they here anyway?*: no one who CAN let them stay anylonger, dudes, i WORK, and nobody wants them in any circle for ANY thing, even binge drinking among the bar pillars ain't possible (yip, they were NOT allowed inside and i do NOT want to know WHY they still recognized him months later).
  
  Did i ALSO mention that we learned the guys has been training in Muai Thai and Krav Maga? I didn't mention it, but everytime he knocked on my HUGE WINDOWED DOOR, i remembered it. Nobody wanted to EVICT him, or lock a door in his face cause he had a history, we discovered, of assault and forced entry (many injunctions still bar his way from MANY girls neighbourhoods). So when he's FINALLY left, i send a quick note on his email/facebook, and while it could have been MUCH nicer, he realizes that my "inferior ways will never be compatible with his drive and charisma", and to this day, we haven't heard of him again. And we Moved 12 kms away. And i made sure he can't find me on facebook or anywhere else. And my phone number's not published in the book. And my real name doesn't appear anywhere on the internet, i check monthly (he DID broke two of those injunctions, and corresponding windows, after all... lucky the girls weren't there).

  So WHAT have we learned here? Well... that some GUYs can be both pretty cool on the onlook, and god awful when you scracth the surface; that i'm positively afraid of GUYs who can kill four people in 5 seconds and manifest both interest and pride in such things, but hey, i'm not sure THIS is bad; that you will hear the most terrible things come from the places that seem the most unlikely, and god damn, that this year's new trendy fashion or idol MUST be and asshole, SOMEHOW! DON'T LET THEM IN! SHUN THE NEW STAR, IT MUST BE EVIL!!

...oh, and that with a high enough Intelligence+Performance extended roll, you can steer your game AWAY from the ball-hungry star that you HAVE to bench away for your team's sake ;)


  Other funny things: i'm now know among gamers around here to be both great AND merciless at storytelling/DMing, having been adept at removing him flowingly AND keep the game going; it was a greater achievement than including him, as so many game crashed once he trampled all over 'em. That and the official Discriminatory Discourse = XP(~quarter a level) Yellow Flag then BAN Red Flag at my house and games: i'm the respect-fascist now! BEWARE HATERS, I HATE YOU MORE!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6821vz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gd1l</id></website><link>http://spoonyexperiment.com/2012/03/12/counter-monkey-the-importance-of-wearing-pants/</link><postedTime>2012-03-12T11:33:40+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T02:50:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi60ta</id><link>http://spoonyexperiment.com/2012/03/12/counter-monkey-the-importance-of-wearing-pants/#comment-474164245</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zdpcm</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-12</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>