<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mbid4k/update/2012-03-10T14:43:41/f2694b8937834411d5f5a5ddc49dd63c03fc2f5fdd0c654c295de902a55e962a</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mbpf8h</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l69v4</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Good summary, but there's more: recent signs &amp; pronouncements from the Ayatollahs, who after all really run the joint, show quite hopeful progress towards the 'grand bargain' that Bush-Cheney had in their grasp back in 2002-3 but rejected. The sanctions led by the U.S. have made things nearly unbearable in Iran, but the sort of runaway inflation experienced in Argentina in the 1980s, &amp; the Ayatollahs are trying to break the Basiji-militia monopoly over the markets there. Ever since 2003 that's been played out as a contest between Ahmahdinejad &amp; Khameini over who could sound more authentically anti-American(an understandable goal, given our history of meddling in Iranian politics going all the way back to WWII), but lately it's narrowed considerably: to the idea of a trade of 1. full UN/IAEA access to Iranian nuclear facilities, plus a commitment to no nukes, plus favored-nations status to the U.S. &amp; the Euro Zone in accessing Iranian oil, in exchange for 2. a U.S. commitment to refrain from pursuing regime change, not just directly but indirectly thru any proxy state (*Cough* Israel *Cough*), Big 8 assistance in developing Iran's peaceful use of nuclear power (Canada &amp; France are the big players in this area, with their history of CANDU reactors in India being a model for obtaining full UN/IAEA access there), graded removal of sanctions &amp; thawing of frozen Iran assets in the U.S. 

There's actually reason to think such a grand bargain is achievable, given the main goal of the ayatollahs is to  continuing hegemony of the "Islamic" part of the republic (in contrast with the Basiji-militia goal of emphasizing the "Republic" part, down-grading the status of the Supreme Ayatollah in particular). And it's not just Israel, or even Israel as the sticking point nation, that makes the negotiations difficult: that "Islamic" before "Republic" principle engages the idea of hegemony of Shi'ia over Sunni sects, meaning that the Saudis are at least as important to work out a solution with. But there's precedent for thawing Iranian asset in the U.S. - Reagan did it between the 1980 election &amp; his being sworn into office in January 1981 in order to obtain release of the several hundred U.S. hostages. 

If Obama can pull this Off, then he'll have earned that Nobel Peace Prize (as well as justifying the Nobel committee's inclination to make "aspirational" choices). But if there's one person not helping in this process, it's Mendacious Mitt.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/629zcc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tz1k</id></website><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/southern-radio-hosts-confront-mitt-romney-with-mormon-questions-in-tense-interview/</link><postedTime>2012-03-10T16:28:50+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-10T19:43:41+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mbid4k</id><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/southern-radio-hosts-confront-mitt-romney-with-mormon-questions-in-tense-interview/#comment-461625511</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7zl7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-10</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>