<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0au58/post/2012-03-31T15:30:50</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>My cousin is a very dark skinned UFC fighter, he had his nose broke and you could see the purple look bruise on his face, he also had a gash on the back of his head once and wouldn't you believe that it Bled on his shirt and turned purple around the area where the cut was, a few mins later it started to swell up. I ask how is it possible for Zimmerman not to have dark bruises on his face if Tray repeatedly hit him? 9 times out of 10 we as humans carry food or anything else in our dominant hand, so i'm supposed to believe that tray 137lbs knocked George 200+lbs down with his weak hand the beat him in the face with his weak hand while holding a pack of skiddles in the other hand? then with only one hand he slammed the head of this 200+lbs man in the GRASS and it left a 2 inch gash on the back of his head? IN THE GRASS! but Zimmerman has no grass stains, blood, swollen nose or bruised head? I'm willing to bet that he saw this kids walking to the store in America where you can freely walk where ever you want and it was then that he waited looking out the window until Tray passed back by like he did every other day, so I'm hearing it was the hoodie it was the hoodie it was the hoodie, so if he had on a white t shirt he would still be alive? this murder was planned for the start and is filled with Zimmerman lies and he fears nothing because a black kid was killed for "LOOKING" suspicious however NOT reported as doing ANYTHING wrong, no drugs, no money, no weapon, no argument, just simply on the phone with his girl walking home, is this really a crime? how is Zimmerman FREE? but they say that race has nothing to do with it? how many people walk down that sidewalk to that store everyday? what security company does Zimmerman work for? where are the medical records for his broken nose and gashed head? where are the pictures? where is the blood? if not on him surely is was in the soft grass where his head was split open! Tray had no bruises on his hands and the other had held on to a pack of skiddles without damaging the bag? he had no dirt on his knees from squatting on Zimmerman while he beat him badly with his weak hand, and Zimmerman could not push Off a less than 140lbs kid? the 911 calls clearly show a kid screaming at the sight of a bigger man hold a gun as he begs for help and instantly the cries stop after a gun shot is fired, when was the last time you heard of some one on top of a bigger person beating them with one hand and screaming for help? point a gun at anyone black or white and they will more than likely run away, this kid was on the ground from the very start and the sad part is that he will get away with premeditated murder and maybe kill again in self defense? self defense he says and hes the one who disobeyed the 911 police, cocked his gun and gave chase after a kid who had already passed Zimmerman's house with doing anything suspicious! and still there are people defending this guy. what a sad ass fucking world we live in. R.I.P. Trayvon  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yc1ny</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/u6cr</id></website><link>http://www.worldstarhiphop.com/videos/video.php?v=wshhUF2b7NPa6wd7EXRI</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T22:50:42+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T19:30:50+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0au58</id><link>http://www.worldstarhiphop.com/videos/video.php?v=wshhUF2b7NPa6wd7EXRI#comment-482126402</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rgal9</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>