<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjghi/post/2012-03-26T14:15:10</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mktry2</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>EDIT:

It seems to me that Capcom is trading one set of fans for another. And though the action-orentied fans may make up the majority -- at least according to wherever they got that info -- it leaves devoted fans out in the Cold. I just don't understand the logic behind this; if they wanted to Reach a broader audience they ought to just develop an entirely new game for said audience. I mean, if I wanted to play a Call of Duty-esque game, I'd probably play Call of Duty. I know that a lot of people enjoyed RE4 -- some even considered it the best in the series to date -- but in my option that was the beginning of the end of the series, or at least the series that I fell in love with. I'm sure the games made after RE3 would be great as stand-alones, but when you have a devoted fan base of a particular genre (survival horror), why would you screw up the formula? Like others here have already stated, Dead Space is a great example of what RE could and should be, at least where the horror/action ratio is concerned. I just hope that the series can be redeemed and returned to its former glory, otherwise they'll be losing a lot of fans, myself included.
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66z6cm</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t9us</id></website><link>http://www.ibtimes.com/articles/318760/20120323/resident-evil-6-release-date-operation-raccoon.htm</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T19:43:48+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:15:10+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjghi</id><link>http://www.ibtimes.com/articles/318760/20120323/resident-evil-6-release-date-operation-raccoon.htm#comment-476598018</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>