<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwsl4s/post/2012-03-31T10:39:17</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>g1dkFhV1U1OckhpYzU2ojyA8Mlz2brfSo5LBSz1dAufqvnU53f5csUjjiWxVb1MC
But who is to blame? Out there, supposedly at the beck and call of government are good works of intelligence-gathering carried out on Boko Haram by voluntary Nigerian individuals. A quick processing of emerging facts from these resources points in a common direction; the revelation that Boko Haram is not only Westernphobic, it is also secularphobic and has as its main mission a veiled intention to Arabicize and Islamicize the entire Nigerian state at all cost - a very dangerous ambition. Hence the incessant bombings, killings, abductions, choosing to speak Arabic as the main language of communication, and recently the pronouncement that the twelve Northern-Region States be Sharianized. All these are means by which Boko Haram planned to realize its dangerous ambition. If Heat of intelligence work had been turned on permanently on Boko Haram after its first attack in 2003 when its religious extremism ideology  first came to light, as would have been done in advanced countries, things would have been happening differently today.Now, it has advanced from religious extremism to political Islamism, acquiring the political power to demand, negotiate, reject or even force its own condition on us. It makes good sense to reason that after nine years of terror with impunity, Boko Haram has surely got the better of us and should therefore be accorded the attention it deserves. This should simply translate to inviting its leaders for a dialogue, to know who they are representing; who they are; what exactly they want. If there is a place for their demands within the modern, democratic society, why not grant it!   That should not be seen as a sign of weakness on the side of the government; it’s the only right approach to adopt now to Reach a meaningful end.Putting the possibility of this in a more politically correct perspective, however - given that Boko Haram’s demands turn to be more reflective of a North’s agenda, then that indicates that Boko Haram’s activities are signs that the looming crisis Nigeria has long been sweeping under the carpet is imminent; there is one last way to  avert it - a well representative National dialogue (whether Sovereign or not). Afrterall, each of the six geo-political zones that make up Nigeria has its own agitation or demand on the central government pending, or unattended to somehow. If Boko Haram succeeds getting its demand using violence, the instruction cannot be more clearer to others. If it fails, or this massacre continues in anyway, the instruction is equally getting clearer to others. But to avoid further accelerated drift of our co-existence into chaos and conflict, let’s think, as a matter of urgency, will it not be better to usher in a National dialogue where we can determine the terms and conditions of our continued co-existence?</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ekvd36</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/x7uf</id></website><link>http://watchdognigeria.com/bokoharamwhyfederalgovt.html</link><postedTime>2011-09-15T17:29:42+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T14:39:17+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwsl4s</id><link>http://watchdognigeria.com/bokoharamwhyfederalgovt.html#comment-481879400</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-09-15</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>