<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwp7ih/update/2012-03-31T07:11:55/5d961c078223a2d5e6aaffd673265ca1d73694ed2a82c2b4d2c3b42e9cd1bad7</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw985y</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lzwmk</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>It's a lanyard, not a camera strap. For one thing, it's way to thin to hold her SLR. And, she would have to take the strap  for the profile pic to be a self-portrait. There's no way to get that shot with the strap around her neck, because the strap around her neck would keep the camera way too close. And she apparently never takes the lens hood , which would be touching her nose. Even with an extremely small lens, like a fixed 18mm, there's just no way. With anything smaller, there's be fisheye distortion. Plus, we'd see the strap in the shot, not lying flat.

Same with the weird mirror self-portrait which does not illustrate Weight loss, , or anything about her body at all. If the thing around her neck were a camera strap, it would not be resting against her chest, it would be attached to the camera and we'd see it attached to the camera.

The black line on the right is her tank top. It's hard to tell from the picture how she looks in the tank. Her arms look fairly thin, but as people have pointed out, that's how the picture is designed. I personally never felt comfortable in tanks, even before I Gained weight. Now a huge part of the reason I prefer sleeves is so I don't have to keep reapplying sunscreen. I don't find not having sleeves to be much cooler, but then again, there is hardly ever any humidity there I live, so I guess I've lucked out.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67dfgx</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7fwk</id></website><link>http://mwopblog.com/2012/03/weekend-open-road/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:50:46+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T11:11:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwp7ih</id><link>http://mwopblog.com/2012/03/weekend-open-road/#comment-481743733</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yw78f</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>