<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrqwz/update/2012-03-30T12:17:37/730ab97b13ed88bbf4bab5df1de9193857dfd5aae6b44f242ab508b64cdbb8cc</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3sbjl</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zywb0</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Thank you for providing those things about Trayvon. My nature craves those stuff. I want to know more about his parents, more about Tracy's fiancee who by default must remain in the background. I am not just satisfied on the crime that has been committed; without which, I wouldn't be needing those biographies in the first place.

From a standpoint of life being a one-time shot, in which we're here to focus and please God more than we focus on; and help each other to find happiness here on earth, we naturally feel that a greater loss has occurred when someone as promising as Trayvon goes so soon. I used to say the same thing too.

But if we could think from the background that whether or not there is a God, and whether or not this is our first incarnation, or if life is an inalienable eternal process? Regardless of all of those questions; we're all here already, and we all must find the best ways to negotiate this journey called life. We know that it is better to feel happy, hopeful and empowered at every moment; than sad, hopeless and dis-empowered; and with assiduous mindfulness, we'll end up being happy and empowered more often than not. I know that now with absolute surety, because that's who I have become. And believe me, I had never known anyone to be more dysfunctional, depressed, you-oriented than myself. Matter of fact I would bet that God or whatever power is there would not have allowed more than one as far gone as I was, to reside in every City. (lol) 

So, if feeling empowered all; or most of the time, is what we all prefer, then it makes sense to  that any thought or philosophy we're holding onto, is one that can ignite and maintain that state of empowerment on demand. It really doesn't matter if we go down on our knees and pray to God, Allah or a stone. When we get back up we really should feel more happy, empowered and energized. We shouldn't have to fake it until we make it, when dealing with any power called God. And that power should be able to gradually reduce and remove our grief, even for our most beloved loved one.

Every human already fears or is uneasy about our mortality; I know that. I think that psychiatrists now have a special designation for this universal fear called Terror Management Theory. It seems that fear of our inevitable ending, causes a lot of people to do a lot of evil things, and for that reason alone, I think that humanity deserves a more improved paradigm for life. Obviously; like everything else people experience different degrees of fear and coping.

For me; once I started to get a glimmer of the understanding that my life is already eternal and can be no other way, all of the burdens in my life really started to leave. Up to that point I would spend many hours thinking about how I could execute the plan of capturing, tying-up and castrating the people whom I thought at that time had ruined my life, due to the sexual abuse. I had it all planned out, it would be executed with a Cold dull knife. Had I not left Jamaica I probably would have harmed those people. But then again; I was one of those who'd kept those experiences suppressed, until I arrived in Chicago in 1982. Oprah came there in 1984 and started talking about such things, and my sleeping memories awoke. I became incensed, and was consumed with thoughts or returning home to exact my revenge. Obviously I didn't. In 1984 I was also introduced to the Buddhism that Tina Turner practices. For the first time in my life I heard the idea of life being eternal, and that whatever is happening to us now, is due to causes that we made in the past. Instantly my inner soul connected to that idea. Gradually I accepted the possibility that in a previous life I was the abuser, and that my abuse in this life, washed-away my sins, and I now have the start to customize my future lifetimes, in better ways. Still it was a struggle to let go of all the baggage that had held me in mental hostage for all of my life. Today I am no longer a practicing Buddhist. It gave me what I needed to start healing. It was great. I still believe the overall philosophy, but I have moved on. The same way with Christianity. I know without a doubt that a lot of wisdom is still in the Bible, but it has deliberately been corrupted over millenniums, for: racist, political, social and other reasons. so that it compels a majority into fear, for the few to maintain control over their lives. Many can find the wisdom in the Bible, and thus remain empowered; without having the abundant nonsense seeping into their awareness, and contaminating. I do not have that kind of tunnel vision focus.

In any case, from the standpoint of life being already eternal, and that each of us has been here before and can be here as many times after, if that is what we choose; death is seen as a natural transition, and not a loss. 

That does not mean that one does not still feel the pain from that death. That does not mean that one does not still wish the person didn't leave so soon. But from a death like Trayvon's, one sees the way that we can all consciously make the world a better place, because of feeling the loss of someone who'd demonstrated so much good in his short life. If we're all eternal, then shouldn't it be more important what kind of evolution or heaven we're creating with each moment, year, and century of our collective time; rather than putting all of our focus on what is lost. Can't we all now multiply with our conscious efforts the good Trayvon had started? 

Even though he and his parents were demonstrating how we can be of service to each other, how many of his peers had followed suite? How many of his parent's friends were doing what they did? Don't you see that even if guilt is what will now Propel some, many more can now get positively involved in their community, and more communities will be better, thus the world will be exponentially better from those trying to honor Trayvon? And isn't that what we all want? More individuals doing more good as the default condition of life? And if happiness is the ultimate goal of living, then would we not be chronically happy remembering Trayvon that way. If life is eternal, then we're securing a happy world for his return. And while we cannot prove that, thinking about it has more potential for our present happiness than worrying if his soul can still be saved by God, or for that matter if we can be safe in this world. 

Would grief not be shorter and and have less of a destructive impact on our system, if we could easily get ourselves to look at life this way, since the Bible tells us that our good works are not guaranteed to save our souls?

So while you still may disagree with me, can you better appreciate where I am coming from? Can you see that I am not coming from a place of coldhearted, uncaringness? </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zq95i</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ewhe</id></website><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/trayvon-martin/trayvon-martin-case-frank-taaffe.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:02:34+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:17:37+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrqwz</id><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/trayvon-martin/trayvon-martin-case-frank-taaffe.php#comment-480909254</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ahv96</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>