<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkq3ch/update/2012-03-26T03:04:47/39d97daf5e1e26fb54dedb85b998f8010e3f19d3aa116c24c51c949bd4be06e1</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mibjg4</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Very true. I am 28 and have been single my entire life, not even having had a dating relationship. Not for lack of trying, or lack of loving, but just unlucky. There have been 3 or 4 times something almost worked out, but didn't. After so many years, there  a point where you realize "I've come this far, and I have had happy times, and I've been reasonably well overall, so I will obviously be okay" and you Gain confidence from that. Knowing you don't need any one particular person makes you more comfortable and caring.


Still, we are social creatures, and half of that social biology is dedicated to loving a mate. I have a lot of love to give, and it's a profound aspect of being human. Sometimes being single just sucks, and in those times self-therapy helps about as much as thinking of a warm summer day in the middle of a bitterly Cold winter. Embracing how bad it feels, experiencing and knowing your pain, and then watching as it eventually passes is what truly gives you strength. These emotions come and go, and I think truly knowing that prepares you to better love someone else, as any married person can tell you passions are not a constant.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y0yvx</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/c0o0</id></website><link>http://tinybuddha.com/blog/the-art-of-being-happily-single/</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T05:11:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T07:04:47+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkq3ch</id><link>http://tinybuddha.com/blog/the-art-of-being-happily-single/#comment-476260681</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>