<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkoof9/post/2012-03-26T15:42:31</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Republicans have already cut health care benefits to hundreds of thousands of veterans who served during the Vietnam War . In 2001, the Republican Congress controlled the House Senate and White House and passed what the Republicans laughingly called the Deficit Reduction . I was personally affected. I was drafted during the Vietnam War and was lucky enough to spend my  obligation in an artillery unit in Germany. I was  eligible for VA Healthcare but never signed up for it as I  had employer provided health care. I considered VA Healthcare a safety net that I would use if I ever lost Healthcare benefits. I was forced into early retirement by a corporate merger and would not have healthcare coverage for five years when I would become eligible for Medicare. When I went to the VA to sign up I was informed I was no longer eligible for VA Healthcare. The 2001 Deficit Reduction  changed the eligiblity criteria for VA Healthcare. Eligibility was restricted only to Vetnam War  veterans who had won the purple heart, or were a POW or lived below the federal poverty level.

I was drafted and served along with other Cold War and Vietnam War Era politicians including such diverse people as Ralph Nader and Ron Paul. Mitt Romney, Newt GIngrich and Dick Cheney all avoided the draft by fighting for and getting draft defferments for such excuses as a religious exemption (Mitt Romney) or school and marriage  exemptions (Dick Cheney, Newt Gingrich). There is a reason they are called 'chickenhawks', they would lead patriotic parades in 'support of our troops' waving the biggest American flags and fleeing to the back of the parade as soon as the bullets started flying.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r1ryu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gfhw</id></website><link>http://newsok.com/article/3660143</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T05:03:57+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T19:42:31+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkoof9</id><link>http://newsok.com/article/3660143#comment-476674910</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ay3w8</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>