<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mjwqh1/update/2012-03-20T10:28:25/2cb15f96ff6e924e95a4c2668cae1f1b8edb15fe1dcc4719f3fa210ae0da04d9</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>You don't get a 36mp body only to downscale the images.  D800 will hog up memory cards, slow down the transfer process, and fill your stack of hard drives in no time. Not to mention that RAW workflow will be slower in PP when working with 36mp files, which, technically, shouldn't be downsized until the very end in one's workflow.  Even then, you're gonna want to keep the original RAWs, so your storage requirements just doubled.

Besides, I think it's unrealistic to expect monumental leaps in ISO performance like we've seen with D2 -&gt; D3.  If every generation of cameras improved 1-2 stops in ISO, then in another 10 years, we'll all be shooting at base ISO of 12,800.  The laws of physics can't be broken, and I think we're starting to see a gradual leveling-Off when it comes to cameras and Light sensitivity.

D4 and D800 are two different cameras for two different markets, but most people seem only fixated on ISO performance. 

It's like looking at a Chevy Camaro and Porsche, and comparing only their 0-60 mph times.  It's only once you drive one do you realize where all the extra $$$ went.  

Whether or not the tougher build, better weather sealing, more durable shutter, full grip body with a secondary readout, and extra features of the D4 are worth the expense over the D800, that's an individual decision.  For me, it was a no brainer.

But I totally agree, that for 8 out of 10 people, the D800 will fulfill their needs more than adequately. And for Nikon to release such an all-round capable camera is fantastic.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6mt9d9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/789q</id></website><link>http://fstoppers.com/d4-buyers-may-want-to-give-the-d800-a-second-look</link><postedTime>2012-03-20T01:59:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-20T14:28:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mjwqh1</id><link>http://fstoppers.com/d4-buyers-may-want-to-give-the-d800-a-second-look#comment-470224284</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hljkp</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>