<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpb5nn/update/2012-03-21T21:20:05/e2b8c99d54aeb4863e140e88d6dc933f9897637d2d93af054c3ad39cc00586be</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpzamb</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ycrni</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>You're right in that this isn't just a pagan problem, although pagan journalism suffers it more acutely because its sort of a new industry. Journalism in general really hasn't found a sustainable business model to replace what it had when I entered the field back in the early 90s. At that time, and for a couple centuries prior, the whole thing worked on the concept of selling limited real estate on sheets of dead tree.
    That model worked, really, really well. If you wanted to get your advertising to the right eyeballs, you paid whatever the newspaper could command based on circulation and other options, or lack thereof. Readers also understood that they would have to pay something for their news, even if it was a fairly nominal portion of creating it.  The Internet has effectively gutted the old revenue system entirely, and not replaced it with anything else. Advertising space is an infinite commodity and can be targeted in much better ways than the old model. At the same time, a whole generation has come up who can't even get their head around having to pay anything for "information." 
   This is not a sustainable model, and journalism as an industry has been in a death spiral since at least the beginning of the decade. I had to leave the industry three years ago, and not one in 30 of the people I used to know in the business is still making a living at it.
     I believe this is a direct result of giving away the product for nothing. There were all these ideas about how pop-up ads, revenue from "hits" and social media "buzz" was going to make up for it all, but it hasn't. The math simply doesn't work, and never will. Real, boots-on-the ground journalism will die in this country, and it will never really get up and running in the pagan community if we persist in the idea that something can be had for nothing. Don't get me wrong, I'm blown away by the dedication and professionalism of Jason and Star and the lot of you, but journalism can't be done the way it needs to be done on a part-time volunteer basis or a rickety charity economy.
    You need to have at least a core of people who can do it as their 9-5 (or midnight)! gig. You need to be able to put people where and when news is happening, and be able to dedicate the time to cultivate the sources, to sift through documents, to file the FOIA requests, to spend hours and days doing background research and talking to people for no other reason than to get the lay of the land with an issue. In many ways, journalism is like intelligence work or research. 
    You don't get results by working in a reactive catch-as-catch-can basis. You get results by investing in and maintaining an excellent infrastructure of people and other assets. It simply doesn't happen on a "love offering" or crowdfunding basis. If we want pagan journalism, or any journalism, that is both wide and deep in Scope, we've simply got to get over this "information is free" nonsense.
    Blogs like Jasons, and this one, ought to have some sort of subscription or pay wall component. I know no one has money to Burn these days, but we don't expect to eat, or drive, or go to the movies for nothing. If its something you need or want badly enough, you budget for it. I have in front of me a pharmacy journal that runs me about $5 a month, for much less content and much less fun content than I get here. I pay it because its important to me at some level. I wouldn't pay it if they were kind or fool enough to give it to me for nothing. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dk0ct</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lpw5</id></website><link>http://www.patheos.com/blogs/pantheon/2012/03/supporting-pagan-journalism/</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T16:33:57+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T01:20:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpb5nn</id><link>http://www.patheos.com/blogs/pantheon/2012/03/supporting-pagan-journalism/#comment-473004452</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>