<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mqp0b4/update/2012-03-05T00:17:30/db83f3447ced82d5a956a864873f204ff33c25d5ae4dd37e8b2889b61642ca4a</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Wow, the author here is A) Prudish, B) Judgemental, and C) Honestly doesn't know her BDSM.
May I just add, that I read - a lot, and everything - I'm just as big a fan of Jane Eyre as I am of say, JR Ward and Sherrilyn Kenyon. It just Depends on my mood. You made the odd suggestion of picking up a KINGSOLVER book!? Seriously? Because when you are pal-ing around with your home-girls, you are totally thinking, "Well, I just can't believe the plot of that amazingly, depressing book I read." 
When was the last time you did anything even NEAR what goes on in the romance genre? I will admit, I was a skeptic, not a fan of a good bodice-ripper. But you know, I wouldn't sit in not-too-silent judgement (which, let's face it, that's what you are doing here) of those who like them. 
It's called "brain candy." I don't know...Ladies? As women, would you rather deal with some post-modern, wannabe lit, all the while  feeling your soul being sucked through your eyeballs, due to the fact you are SUPPOSED to feel something for the main characters, only to have to "fake it" (so to speak ;) later with your pals? Or, would you rather have a nice, relaxing, easy read, which later on, you and your girls can say, "Did you READ what they DID!?" 
Personally, if I have to hear one more person ask me, "Have you read The Help?" or some other dumb Oprahs Book Club pick, I'm going to Vomit. I will not read "Heaven is Real" or "The Love Dare" or anything that makes me "improve my character." I did that in college!! Real life is boring, monotonous, day-in, day-out drivel. Why, in any way, would I want to read about someone else's dull life?
I will take my bodice rippers, my comedic mysteries, and my paranormals and wend my way happily into them, enjoying that no, I won't sleep with the most gorgeous man on the planet (I'm quite happy with my husband, thanks). But if I can't, at least in someone else's imagination, they have made him available to me, 24-7, day or night. 

And I don't have to cuddle later. ;p</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ysrtbt</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/twef</id></website><link>http://www.thefrisky.com/2012-03-04/fifty-shades-the-%e2%80%9cmommy-porn%e2%80%9d-book-that%e2%80%99s-sweeping-the-suburbs/</link><postedTime>2012-03-04T19:02:20+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-05T05:17:30+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mqp0b4</id><link>http://www.thefrisky.com/2012-03-04/fifty-shades-the-%e2%80%9cmommy-porn%e2%80%9d-book-that%e2%80%99s-sweeping-the-suburbs/#comment-456575130</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hjgwf</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-04</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>