<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xee2/post/2012-03-29T13:32:35</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tf8v</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8wr7u</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>The police surveillance video of Zimmerman being brought into the police station after he incident shows none of the injuries that were later reported. EMS came to the scene and did not treat Zimmerman for any kind of head injury at all - they treated him not at all. Even a small scalp laceration Bleeds profusely; there is no blood on Zimmerman at all. But the evidence of where Zimmerman's injuries came from - if there were any - will show up when a proper investigation (as opposed to a cover-up) is done.

You seem more than happy to jump onto the "poor George was attacked by a gang-banger!" story that has been circulating without evidence, based purely on Zimmerman's testimony. It must fit in with your preconceived notions of how black teenagers "". You love to ,since every one of your posts is full of CAPITAL LETTERS. Will you Shout your apologies when it is revealed that you have calumniated and slandered a young man who was walking down the street, minding his own business, when a vigilante who ALSO thought that all young black men are guilty until proven innocent, chased him and gunned him down?

Did you mean to say that Martiansaresmarter than you? because that is the effect that your screen name has - not to mention leaving the impression that you are too scared to put your real name onto your opinions.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z6vrl</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yzhx</id></website><link>http://www.miamiherald.com/2012/03/29/2720590/sanford-police-threaten-to-arrest.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T11:57:15+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:32:35+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xee2</id><link>http://www.miamiherald.com/2012/03/29/2720590/sanford-police-threaten-to-arrest.html#comment-479678328</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/anmmr</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>