<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwga07/post/2012-03-30T06:42:07</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>There is nothing wrong with being a prostitute.  Yes...not many of us want to see our daughters or son's grow up to be one, but they are out there.  On the street on behind closed doors of massage parlours &amp; escourt agencies.  It's time we take them in and take care of our own.  Place them in "brothels", give them the security and safe sex options.  Give them the addiction councilling they need to get Off the drugs they use to "forget" what they do for a living.  As long as it's a forbidden no no, their confidence will lack, the dates will be bad and more will die.   I am sick and tired of hearing how bad the women are who do this.  I think their smart!  $100.00 an hr sounds pretty damn good to me (not that I'd do it) but to those who do...cudo's!  Now take that $100.00 and tax it.  Take out the 30% that the feds and prov's tax the rest of us and it's still a decent wage.  Take out the cost of "renting" or "leasing" your Spot in the brothel and the cost of the security person.  It still leaves them with a good chunk of cash and now they can hold their heads up because it's not done in a dark corner of society, instead of cowering and hiding.  Yes no one wants it in their neck of the cities..but think of this.  Now their not walking around your neighbourhood, leaving a trail of condom and other garbage behind them.  Now their not sitting in a dark car in your back alley.  Now you don't have these men chasing your wives or children wanting "sexual favours" from them.  Maybe your mom, sister, aunt, cousen, or child won't end up in an unmarked grave from some sick f**k....</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z95tx</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7maa</id></website><link>http://www.edmontonsun.com/2012/03/29/parliament-paralysis</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:22:30+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T10:42:07+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwga07</id><link>http://www.edmontonsun.com/2012/03/29/parliament-paralysis#comment-480606027</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6rr31</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>