<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mimg14/post/2012-03-22T17:43:28</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Robert Shaw, one of the absent when the meeting started due to VERY serious illness BOT's, came in after he was called and had to be helped into the building and up on the dias in order for a quorum to be  for a vote. He literally looked like the walking dead.  It was truly sad.  

  Votes aren't traditionally made on anything during a "WORK STUDY" meeting of our School Board.  Lots of people are questioning the legality of this as when a meeting is called to order and a quorum is established, those BOT's that aren't there are not available TO vote. Mr. Shaw was not there when the meeting was called and when Dr. Proctor and Mr. Huckaby courageously walked out, THAT action made a quorum impossible.  Did our BOT President Joe Adams officially close the meeting and then reopen it when Mr. Shaw arrived? 
 
How desperate must a School District Superintendent be to have to railroad this through to  MAKE a VERY ill gentleman come into a meeting in order to cast a vote?  This is the same Superintendent who fired teachers a year ago WHILE school was taking place causing children to witness their faculty and staff crying and being visibly upset at being fired DURING their work day.  Those same children took to the streets to rally, protest and THAT was unsafe, causing disruption to their education process.  How ironic that the very children we teach have a better grasp of what is right and wrong versus those adults that are in Administration!!  What's worse is that there were punishments threatened to the children for their actions but no punishments for the Cold and callous Administration who  without a care in the world for the feelings of teachers.   

Can you say unprofessional?  Can you say Katy ISD doesn't care about you, Mr. or Ms. Teacher Wanna Be, here?  A word of advice to those even thinking of applying - DON'T.  There are FAR better places for you to teach.  
 
When a Superintendent has NO regard for the mental and  physical well being of children HE is ultimately 100% responsible for, the teachers and staff HE employs and a VOLUNTEER who ran for public office as a member of the Board of Trustees, HE has NO business being employed.  

Our hope and prayer is that we can find a way to effectively remove him from office and out him in such a way that no other School District in the nation EVER has to endure this man as Superintendent.  He has ruined our School District.  Remember, "Big" AL - "it isn't Always the crime that gets you, but the cover up!"</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ye3lr</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/jzav</id></website><link>http://www.texasbudgetsource.com/blog/katy-isd-protects-administrators-%E2%80%94-not-teachers</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T02:15:07+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T21:43:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mimg14</id><link>http://www.texasbudgetsource.com/blog/katy-isd-protects-administrators-%E2%80%94-not-teachers#comment-473985666</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>