<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/276915/post/104218228/comment/327889021</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>2012 POWERADE FAB 50 Baseball Rankings: Week 2RK (LW)SCHOOL (CITY, STATE)RECCOMMENT1 (1)Bishop GormanLas Vegas, NV0-0The first games for the Gaels will be this week and over the weekend in their Desert Classic Tournament.2 (2)JesuitTampa, FL9-0The  continued their fast start last week as they defeated Lakewood Ranch (Bradenton, Fla.) 4-2 and Berkeley Prep (Tampa, Fla.) 7-4. This week, they take on Bolles (Jacksonville, Fla.) and Gulliver Prep (Pinecrest, Fla.).3 (3)Mary CarrollCorpus Christi, TX10-0Behind Texas-bound senior Courtney Hawkins, the  continued to roll last week. Josh Cruz also is ripping the cover  the ball and is leading the team in RBIs.4 (4)ColumbusColumbus, GA7-0The top-ranked Class AAA team in Georgia defeated AAAAA power and then-No. 26 Parkview (Lilburn,Burberry Uomini, Ga.) on Monday and Alabama power Russell County (Seale, Ala.) last week. Columbus takes on previous No. 50 Brookwood (Snellville, Ga.) on Friday.5 (5)Spanish ForkSpanish Fork, UT1-0The Dons opened their season with a 3-2 win over Layton (Utah) and will take part in the Dixie Sunshine Classic this weekend.6 (6)CalallenCorpus Christi, TX15-0The Wildcats took all three of their games last week in impressive fashion, recording two shutouts and outscoring their opponents 24-2. They have five players hitting over .400, with Lee Gonzalez leading the way at .579.7 (7)OwassoOwasso, OK7-0Coach Larry Turner\'s team has posted a pair of wins over Florida teams Lake Wales and Winter Haven. The Rams play in the Blue Devil Classic this week.8 (8)John W. NorthRiverside, CA6-0After going 5-0 at the Redlands Invitational, the defending  Southern Section Division I champs added to their win total with a 4-2 triumph over Thousand Oaks (Calif.).9 (9)Don BoscoRamsey,John Wall Stats, News, Videos, Highlights, Pictures, Bio - Washington Wizards -, NJ0-0The Ironmen will stay put in the FAB 50 and at No. 1 in the East Region until teams in that region start their seasons.10 (10)Providence SeniorCharlotte, NC6-0The Panthers capped  a 3-0 week with a victory over Alexander Central (Taylorsville, N.C.).11 (11)NovaDavie, FL9-0A 12-0 blanking of St. Thomas Aquinas (Fort Lauderdale, Fla.) continued the unbeaten season for the Titans.12 (12)Broken ArrowBroken Arrow, OK8-0The  are rolling through their schedule early on this season and have also moved to 6-0 in district play. In their latest two wins, they had to rally to beat Edmond Memorial (Edmond, Okla.) and Bartlesville (Okla.).13 (13)Huntington BeachHuntington Beach, CA5-0After the team\'s big win over preseason California No. 1 Mater Dei of Santa Ana, the momentum continued in wins last week over Tesoro (Rancho Santa Margarita,burberry sito ufficiale, Calif.) and Palm Desert (Calif.).14 (19)OlympiaOrlando, FL10-0The top-ranked team in the Orlando area remained spotless with a 6-1 win over Bishop Moore (Orlando, Fla.).15 (22)Christopher ColumbusMiami,ghd france, FL9-1The Explorers defeated Belen Jesuit (Miami) 6-4 in the first game of weeklong Selective Recruiting/Sir Pizza Invitational. The tourney continues this week with games against St. Brendan (Miami) and Dwyer (Palm Beach Gardens, Fla.).16 (35)Clovis WestFresno, CA10-1Ryan Soares pitched the shutout as the Golden Eagles completed a 3-0 showing at the Central California Showcase with a 6-0 blanking of Independence (Bakersfield, Calif.).17 (17)CathedralIndianapolis, IN0-0The Fighting Irish, ranked No. 1 in the Midwest Region, get things going on March 28 against Bishop Chatard (Indianapolis).18 (38)Plano WestPlano, TX11-1It was three more wins for Plano West last week, including a 12-4 victory over Plainview (Texas). In that game,burberry outlet, the Wolves hit six doubles and Billy McKinney chipped in with a homer.19 (29)James ByrnesDuncan, SC2-0The Rebels scored 11 runs in the fourth inning and rolled past Hart County (Anderson, S.C.) 11-1. The team started its district schedule this week.20 (20)Saint RitaChicago, IL0-0Coach Mike Zunica\'s team, the preseason No. 1 team in Illinois,Burberry Donne, starts its season Saturday against Oak Lawn (Ill.).21 (NR)ChurchillSan Antonio, TX13-1A win on Monday over previous No. 15 Westlake (Austin,ghd pas cher, Texas) gives the Chargers a big boost. Their only loss is to Bowie (Austin, Texas), a team they\'ve also beaten this year.22 (NR)Bishop AlemanyMission Hills, CA6-1-1The Warriors topped previous No. 18 Harvard-Westlake (Studio City, Calif.) and have moved to No. 1 in the  Southern Section Division III rankings.23 (NR)Saint FrancisMountain View, CA8-0Senior outfielder Braden Bishop homered and doubled and had four RBIs in a 10-1 romp past Palma (Salinas, Calif.). The Lancers also won last week against Aptos (Calif.) 7-1 and Menlo School (Atherton, Calif.) 4-3.24 (23)George WashingtonNew York, NY0-0The Trojans are expected to be the team to beat in the greater New York City metro area. The season won\'t begin to get really serious for this squad until April.25 (24)MaizeMaize, KS0-0The defending Class 6A state champs start the season on March 24.26 (37)Oak GroveHattiesburg, MS8-0Oak Grove remained undefeated by defeating Sumrall (Miss.) 7-0 on Monday for its second win over Sumrall this season.27 (NR)GreenbriarEvans, GA6-0The Wolfpack are the top-ranked Class AAAA team in Georgia.28 (27)Saint Louis UniversitySaint Louis, MO0-0The Junior Bills start the season this week against McCluer North (Florissant, Mo.).29 (NR)FlanaganPembroke Pines, FL7-1This perennial national power is at it again. Heading into this week, Flanagan was on a seven-game win streak that included a 9-0 win over previously unbeaten West Broward (Pembroke Pines, Fla.).30 (NR)HamiltonChandler, AZ7-1Tyler Erwin and Sean Rackoski combined for a no-hitter in a win over Vista Grande (Casa Grande, Ariz.) last week.31 (NR)Elk GroveElk Grove, CA2-0The Thundering Herd haven\'t played as many games as other top teams in California, but their 7-1 win against Valley Christian (San Jose, Calif.) helped them rise to No. 6 in the state because Valley Christian was unbeaten at the time.32 (NR)Valley ChristianSan Jose, CA7-1Cameron Stewart, a 6-foot-9 senior pitcher, has been a major force so far this season for the Warriors. One of their wins before a loss to Elk Grove came against previous FAB 50-ranked Jesuit (Carmichael, Calif.).33 (31)ValenciaValencia, CA4-1The Vikings did not play last week after they went from unranked in the FAB 50 to No. 31 the previous week.34 (33)Jefferson CountyDandridge,Washington Redskins vs. Buffalo Bills - Box Score - October 30, 2011 - ESPN, TN1-0Coach Josh Warner\'s team will start to find out if it\'s among the best in Tennessee in games this week.35 (34)James RiverMidlothian, VA0-0James River kicks  its season this Friday against Glen Allen (Va.).36 (NR)PelhamPelham,History &amp;amp; Society NPR, AL14-0So far this spring, the Panthers are routinely winning games by either shutout or with just one run allowed.37 (15)WestlakeAustin,Louis Vuitton Portafogli, TX13-1-1Before the loss to Churchill (San Antonio) on Monday, the Chaps defeated Anderson (Austin, Texas) and Westwood (Round Rock, Texas) last week.38 (16)El CapitanLakeside, CA2-1The Vaqueros have already lost a game to Bonita Vista (Chula Vista, Calif.), but their wins against Rancho Bernardo (San Diego) and Rancho Buena Vista (Vista,Burberry Lady Bags, Calif.) are against two teams that also are highly ranked in the San Diego area.39 (NR)Pensacola CatholicPensacola, FL9-1Coach Richard LaBounty\'s team has wins over teams from Mississippi and Alabama and the only loss came by a 6-5 score to Navarre (Fla.).40 (NR)La CuevaAlbuquerque, NM7-0The dominant program in New Mexico has had no close calls so far this season. The team\'s seventh win was 10-1 victory against Highland (Albuquerque, N.M.).41 (NR)JupiterJupiter, FL12-1This team received a bump into this week\'s rankings by recording a win last week against previous No. 40 Palm Beach Central (Wellington,burberry borse, Fla.).42 (42)Lakota EastLiberty Township, OH0-0Ohio\'s preseason No. 1 team is scheduled to open Wednesday against Springboro (Ohio).43 (43)Parkway SouthBallwin, MO0-0The Patriots were a top team last year and have some solid pieces returning to the lineup.44 (44)FarragutKnoxville, TN0-0The third season for the Admirals under coach Matt Buckner should be another good one. Buckner has done a fine job since replacing Tommy Pharr, who is the coach credited for building a program among the best in the nation.45 (45)Gloucester CatholicGloucester City,burberry borse outlet, NJ0-0The Rams are coming  a 31-2 season and hope to remain among the best in the Garden State.46 (46)Poly Prep Ctry. Day SchoolBrooklyn, NY0-0The Blue Devils, along with No. 24 George Washington (New York), could help make it a great season in New York high school baseball.47 (47)WestviewPortland, OR0-0Westview is set to open the season on Wednesday against West Linn (Ore.).48 (48)RockfordRockford, MI0-0Coach Ian Hearn\'s squad starts the season No. 1 in Michigan and could move up fast with early success.49 (28)Edmond Santa FeEdmond, OK13-2-1A double-header split with Choctaw (Okla.) drops the Raiders 21 Spots in this week\'s rankings. But they weren\'t dropped completely out and have the opportunity to move back up quickly.50 (18)Harvard WestlakeNorth Hollywood, CA5-2-1Since the Wolverines\' loss and tie last week was to a team -- Alemany (Mission Hills, Calif.) -- that is now higher in the rankings, they don\'t drop out of the FAB 50 completely. And despite the loss of star right-hander Lucas Giolito to injury, it\'s still a team that can be successful against tough San Fernando Valley competition.Dropped out: Previous No. 14 Mater Dei (Santa Ana, Calif.); No. 21 Buchanan (Clovis, Calif.); No. 25 Desert Mountain (Scottsdale, Ariz.); No. 26 Parkview (Lilburn, Ga.); No. 30 Flower Mound (Texas); No. 32 Pace (Fla.); No. 36 Fairhope (Ala.); No. 39 Jesuit (Carmichael, Calif.); No. 40 Palm Beach Central (Wellington, Fla.); No. 41 Park Vista (Lake Worth, Fla.); No. 49 Rancho Bernardo (San Diego); No. 50 Brookwood (Snellville, Ga.). </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:276915:104218228</id><idPostId>104218228</idPostId><idBlogId>276915</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:276915</id><idBlogId>276915</idBlogId><link>http://www.cinefamily.org</link><displayName>The Cinefamily</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.cinefamily.org/blog/qa-archive-4-combat-shock/</link><displayName>Q&amp;A Archive #4: "Combat Shock"</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:30:32.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:276915:104218228:327889021</id><link>http://www.cinefamily.org/blog/qa-archive-4-combat-shock/#IDComment327889021</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:30:32.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Q&amp;A Archive #4: "Combat Shock" by hljfeos4322m</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://www.borsebbrits.com/</link><idEmailMd5>fabe3f3f2af466765c3ced9cdef8be71</idEmailMd5><displayName>hljfeos4322m</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://www.borsebbrits.com/"&gt;hljfeos4322m&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.cinefamily.org/blog/qa-archive-4-combat-shock/"&gt;Q&amp;A Archive #4: "Combat Shock"&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>