<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzkbq/update/2012-03-30T14:48:45/4dd47e8278c2acef5d89a8dbe711ad3950f4a73adf2e16470744514d6c491e39</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This news sucks the life out of me and turns me into a crippled, soulless shell of a human being. 

Okay, maybe not that bad, but it fucking blows. We were finally looking at real, tangible OLine continuity and it gets blown up by a freak injury to our (arguably) very best player. I feel bad for Jason Peters, more than anything. But I trust in Mudd, and I trust in the decision to bring Dunlap back.

One thing I do not want is to hit the panic button and make the knee-jerk decision of drafting an OT in round 1(or even round 2). It will probably be another 18 months until Jason Peters is "Jason Peters" again... but his career is not over. We are not suddenly in dire need of a franchise tackle. We simply need someone who can fill in. That can be obtained in free agency, later in the draft, or in-house(Dunlap). The timing of the injury is fortuitous because it gives the organization time to explore all of their options and make the best move possible.

But Riley Reiff is a pure RT, Jonathan Martin is soft, and Adams is a boom-or-bust pick with questionable work ethic. Do any of those options scream "pick #15" to you? They certainly don't to me. Not to mention, if we picked one of them at #15 they'd become a man without a Spot in 2013. Do you cut the guard you just gave a big-money deal to? The RT you just extended long term? Your young, viable RG or OC? It would be a major waste of resources and a major panic move. And panic moves are Always, without fail, a bad business move.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/676iep</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/xiyd</id></website><link>http://igglesblitz.com/philadelphia-eagles-2/sucker-punch-2/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:31:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:48:45+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzkbq</id><link>http://igglesblitz.com/philadelphia-eagles-2/sucker-punch-2/#comment-481064347</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yn4zc</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>