<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/278853/post/127946460/comment/329837594</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Even the patriarch of Jerusalem surrendered the city on similar terms. The fear of religious compulsion on the part of the heretical emperor made the promise of Muslim toleration appear more attractive than the connection with the Roman Empire and a Christian government, and after the first terrors caused by the passage of an invading army, there succeeded a profound revulsion of feeling in favor of the Arab conquerors.&amp;rdquo; (p.55). This is the evidence given by a Christian scholar on Islam. What is it then that the Christians fear from Islamic rule? 
 
It may be that the Christians are afraid of Muslim fanaticism. If this is true, it seems that they have no idea of what fanaticism is. Here are a few examples of fanaticism. Courts of inquisition set up by the Christian Church were primarily meant to exterminate the Muslims of Spain. The said courts tortured Muslims in a monstrous way, which had never been experienced before. People were Burned alive, their fingernails were pulled Off, their eyes were put out and their limbs were amputated. This torture was inflicted in order to force the people to change their religion and adopt a particular Christian creed. 
 
Have the Christians of Islamic East ever suffered such treatment? 
 
Massacres are carried out for the extermination of Muslims in Europe, Yugoslavia Albania Russia or countries under European rule such as North Africa Somalia Kenya Zanzibar or in other countries like India and Malaya. Such massacres are staged sometimes on the pretext of the purging of ranks and sometimes for the maintenance of peace and security. 
 
Another significant example is the treatment of Muslims in Ethiopia which has ancient historical, geographical, cultural and religious links with Egypt. It has a mixed population of Muslims and Christians. Although Muslims account for 35 to 65 percent of the total population there is not a single school where Islamic faith or Arabic is taught. 
 
Private schools, which the Muslims open at their own expenses, are subjected to exorbitant taxes and inconveniences that lead to their closing, thus disheartening those who may think of opening new schools. In this way, Islamic teaching is confined to a primitive way of teaching. 
 
Until very recently &amp;ndash; just before the Italian invasion &amp;ndash; a Muslim who could not pay a debt to his Christian creditor was taken in slavery by the Ethiopian Christians. The Muslim was caught, sold and tortured within sight of the government. It goes without saying that there is not a single Muslim in the cabinet or in any key post to represent one-third of the population. Have the Christians of the Islamic world ever experienced such a treatment? Would they accept reciprocal treatment? 
 
That is real fanaticism. 
 
The Communists believe that the real existence of man is essentially an economic existence. If so, have the Christians living in Islamic countries ever been denied the right to acquire and dispose of property or to amass wealth? Have they ever been denied, on account of their religious belief, the right to have education, to join public service or promotion to higher public posts? 
 
As for the moral and spiritual existence, it should be stressed that the Christians living under Islamic rule have never been subjected to any form of religious persecution -- with the exception of the very rare incidents engendered by the British colonialists for sowing dissension and diversion. It is alleged that the imposition of tribute on non-Muslims is the result of religious discrimination. The best refutation of this baseless accusation lies in the words of T.W. Arnold, who says: &amp;ldquo;On the other hand, when the Egyptian peasants, although Muslim in faith, were made exempt from military service, a tax was imposed upon them as on the Christians in lieu thereof&amp;rdquo;. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:278853:127946460</id><idPostId>127946460</idPostId><idBlogId>278853</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:278853</id><idBlogId>278853</idBlogId><link>http://www.faithfreedom.org/wordpress</link><displayName>FaithFreedom.org</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.faithfreedom.org/articles/islamic-jihad-articles/in-the-words-of-the-imams/</link><displayName>In the words of the Imams</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T09:09:53.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:278853:127946460:329837594</id><link>http://www.faithfreedom.org/articles/islamic-jihad-articles/in-the-words-of-the-imams/#IDComment329837594</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T09:09:53.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on In the words of the Imams by shabeer</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://www.nicheoftruth.org</link><idEmailMd5>0ce76c45b95a7c9679e9c56191351261</idEmailMd5><displayName>shabeer</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://www.nicheoftruth.org"&gt;shabeer&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.faithfreedom.org/articles/islamic-jihad-articles/in-the-words-of-the-imams/"&gt;In the words of the Imams&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>