<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mbewpw/update/2012-03-09T07:34:39/b7155cd1092e0188d7592096c057c409fa185c3f0833c87b70b5d53beceefc86</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>oh shit, being bushies this is all we ever do, we can't even have a mcdonald's party! 

I ,  make the cake and make a huge mix so have two that stack and throw tonnes of lollies on top. 

We  have too much food- dips and biccies and party pies and sausage rolls and whatever freezer to oven to mouth crap I can buy. then bbq sausage sandwiches or a big pot of spaghetti. Gotta do the ice cream and soft drink! 

I hate party bags and just have treasure hunt wrapped choccies and chocs in the pass the parcel. 

One suggestion for summer parties is a slip and slide -works a treat (plus we have a pool). And in winter we 'Burn baby Burn' BONFIRES in the paddock which can become a bit wild- boys will throw anything in a fire! They are so damn easy- all the paper cups, plates and shit just gets Burned- the kids make sure there is nothing left hanging around!  (We supervise very carefully and have put the time into these kids and most of their friends so they know how to be safe around open fires)

We usually do sleepovers which instantly cuts down the numbers of kids- they lay all over the floors in the family or lounge room with their own sleeping bags and they can watch the disney channel all night, or MTV or whatever they want- though I do put the rating lock thingy on- I don't want any kids saying they watched ANYTHING UNSAVOURY!!!!. At the first hint of 'I want my mummy' the parent is called and the kid goes home(only ever once!)

Then bacon and eggs on the BBQ followed by cake then pick up mid morning!

Oh yeah you must  have a single aunty or uncle as back up and to be the bad cop who tells the kids Off! That way you retain the fab, coolest, calmest mum label!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/y0nbsm</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lnxr</id></website><link>http://www.woogsworld.com/2012/03/catch-up.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-09T00:07:07+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-09T12:34:39+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mbewpw</id><link>http://www.woogsworld.com/2012/03/catch-up.html#comment-460539862</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zv0td</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-09</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>