<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3b3ob/update/2012-03-29T14:56:30/b74b83bdbc179184bb622ad57e712727bd711181b99749cedc7f786a0954dda7</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I live on Long Island so i don't have the luxury of medical marijuana, not legally anyway! 
When I turned 41 my health went from strong and able even though I've had two back surgeries 3 &amp; 5 years prior. It was just one thing after another, until i had lost 60 lbs and was taking a pharmacy of drugs for blood pressure, thyroid disease, cronic pancreatitis, ulcerated colitis and PAIN! UNBEARABLE PAIN! The Dr had no idea what the problem was or how to treat it. Actually the thyroid disease was one of the last things to be Dx'd despite all the evidence to point to it. Anyway When I was not treated for 3 years, turns  out your thyroid will destroy your organs one at a time. You basically fall apart. And now the opiods are destroying my bones. 
Now i am Off the pain meds but my quilty of life sucks! I've lost all the drive and spirit and energy to go on. I used weed in the past for Nausea and sleep, my kids would get it for me. Then i felt it was not a good idea to have your kids scoring weed for their parents, so i stopped using it. Now 17 years after my first surgery, my daughter is going to start sending me brownies to help me sleep and lift me up during the day. My greatest hope is that it relieves my pain and reduces my depression. 
I really wish Ny would have compassion on patients who don't want to use heroin based drugs when there is something so much better , safer, and natural. IT MAKES NO SENSE TO ME! </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hvpsc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/j944</id></website><link>http://www.theweedblog.com/what-does-a-medical-marijuana-patient-look-like/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T15:50:50+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:56:30+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3b3ob</id><link>http://www.theweedblog.com/what-does-a-medical-marijuana-patient-look-like/#comment-479760790</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>