<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mie0s2/update/2012-03-22T17:32:09/bb3829df1785a9a4a71ee10a3cc24c37ba9a7e5c832c4d4a89dbe80bf218a311</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I changed my Party affliation this year after forty years of being registered to the Democratic Party.
I have  voted for the individual that, I thought best represented the Country's interests.  Obama has ruined that for me and I for one hope he is one and done.  He has disgraced this Country so many times that for the life of me, I cannot believe that an impeachment process hasn't begun. He lies and apologizes to other nations on their treatment by America, apologizing for the burning of the Koran that was being used to hand  encoded messages to other terrorists, which the Koran opposes and continues to give foreign aid to countries, that don't like us and would like to see us wiped  the face of the Earth, much like Israel.  Look at what he has written in his own book about how he hates America and the American system and Aligns himself with his fathers beliefs, especially regarding the white race. His own words state he leans more toward the muslim faith than a christian belief. Wake up America and see what Obama is!  A leopard can have his Spots removed however; the leopard is still a leopard.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y6tzk</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q0fi</id></website><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/22/va-middle-schoolers-assigned-to-do-oppo-research-on-gop-candidates/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T05:18:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T21:32:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mie0s2</id><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/22/va-middle-schoolers-assigned-to-do-oppo-research-on-gop-candidates/#comment-473978160</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>