<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk9rqp/post/2012-03-26T13:25:19</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I also have a turbulent relationship with my mother, unfortunately it's been a very distant one since the birth of my daughter, nine and a half months ago. 

My parents were divorced when I was eight or nine, I don't remember. My mother was a very strong woman, but emotionally unstable and likely to take it out on the only person around - me. I have grown  up twisted by her social isolation, her "bubble" lifestyle that seems to live outside the real world, but takes a lot of time and effort to maintain. 

I've Always wanted to have a good relationship with her, but at this stage, I can't. I have opened up so many times to repair our relationship, and have been Burned surprisingly quickly at least as many times by her intentional meanness. It has made me very vulnerable, and trust issues shadow my relationship with an amazing man who never wants to leave me, and who has a very tough time dealing with feelings that feel outside my control. I may not be able to force my mum to want to change in any way, but I can change my relationship with the people who I care about, and have as little to do with the people who want to hurt me as possible (as painful as that can be. Short, infrequent chats/coffee together is about as much of her as I can take without falling into a major depressive/Anxiety cycle)

So yeah, mother issues. I'm working so hard to be a great mother, I don't want to fall into similar patterns of behaviour. 

Wow, what a long comment!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rpjqs</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tioz</id></website><link>http://www.edenriley.com/2012/03/all-about-my-mother.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T11:02:41+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:25:19+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk9rqp</id><link>http://www.edenriley.com/2012/03/all-about-my-mother.html#comment-476559353</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zrr9c</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>