<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwh11t/post/2012-03-30T13:54:21</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwli9g</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g2ytk</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>"There's more evidence for it than there is for the "two citizen parents" theory."

Now are you speaking about the definition of "citizen" or something else? If citizen, then please give some evidence. I have quoted the "Law of Nations" (a very well read book at the time) and the 19th amendment. What evidence have you given again?

"Nonsense; of course they can"

No, they cannot. One institution does not give individuals "rights". They may give them privileges, not rights. A right cannot be truly taken away, it can only be unrecognized. I'm sorry but the Declaration (written by a non-Christian) disagrees with you. The govt Acts evil much of the time. It fails to recognize rights throughout history. If the govt says Asian people cannot wear hats then Asian people are still just as equal as anyone else. But the govt doesn't recognize it. This is an issue with your moral relativism. As a moral absolutist (it's very difficult to logically be anything else) I recognize that govt doesn't get to dictate right and wrong, nor anyone who may change his/her mind.

"God didn't say anything about hats."

Even though he did speak on hats (read the Bible more clearly and you'll find it), this is a red herring. God gave us Liberty (that's obvious to those of us who read the Bible, though many Christians do not). We have the right to wear hats, even indoors. If govt tries to take that right away, they cannot fully as it isn't theirs to take. They may kill or imprison me but they'll never take away my rights.

You can take my hat when you pry it from my Cold, dead hands!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zf9pr</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f7e3</id></website><link>http://www.wnd.com/2012/03/the-unintended-rubio-effect/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T23:59:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:54:21+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwh11t</id><link>http://www.wnd.com/2012/03/the-unintended-rubio-effect/#comment-481008689</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lqfxs</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>