<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkue8b/post/2012-03-26T10:01:44</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Jocky Wilson was a great wee guy. He was a man who could take the brickbats and still smiled. Harry Heenan showered him with a Cold bucket of water, and they rolled about on the floor for a brief time laughing like drains in Haverfordwest, Wales. Two SDA men Eric MacLean and little insignificant me witnessed Harry's  joke. Jocky played superbly well in the international with Wales the following day as did Eric and Harry. 

There were times, when we travelled from Nairn to Fife for tournament darts that when most  of the players lost and left, Jocky needed to go home to Kirkcaldy. As friends, and me the non drinking sensible driver,  we took him there. The day after a  world title win he appeared at Livingston, probably the Football Club there in an exhibition. I distanced myself from the genial great while he felt the adulation of the locals, but Livingston and me were strange to Jocky, as he  related me to North Of Scotland ans especially to the superb Maclean brothers, who Always went close at the Classic in London. 

This might have been the first time I met Jocky with buckets of money in his pocket after his great success. He looked with furrowed brow several times before he knew for sure that I was ROBBIE from Nairn.  He approached and we chatted and hugged and I explained why I came south,  he took 40 pounds out of his wallet, and paid me for my "taxi trips" on those we dark nights when Eric and I were the last, but Jocky to leave the scene. I never "taxied" Jocky Wilson. My expenses covered my trips with a delivery in Edinburgh.  But we had mad laughs as we took 'a mate' home. His separation from Scottish Darts and the walk away of Eric MacLean were not good for the Scottish game. They were both missed, but tomorrow, if I fly into Inverness, I can still visit Eric and Donny MacLean nearby, while Jocky Wilson awaits us in the place of the KING.

God bless you Jocky Wilson. Your memories live on.
May God bless Malvina and the family.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rbcg4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/za8b</id></website><link>http://www.heraldscotland.com/sport/opinion/jocky-wilson-1950-2012-the-peoples-champion.17128374</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T02:07:57+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T14:01:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkue8b</id><link>http://www.heraldscotland.com/sport/opinion/jocky-wilson-1950-2012-the-peoples-champion.17128374#comment-476412286</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/eos38</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>