<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3f5ju/post/2012-03-29T16:35:21</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3bnqk</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yxr2x</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>It's because pop stars these days come from behind the scenes. You can see the trend in the chart success of DJs, in the way producers like David Guetta and Calvin Harris now receive top billing on their songs. The people who actually produce the music are the stars now. Lady Gaga, Kesha and Katy Perry are all songwriters who worked in the industry behind the scenes before their big break. Lesser artists like Jessie J and  Hilson have been around for years, writing for Katy and Britney. They're not great dancers because they've never had to be. The focus of their careers has never been on actually performing. This is in stark contrast to the pop stars in the 90's who had to compete for a set number of Spots by being the best performers. They had to work their way up through Disney and mall tours, both of which emphasized choreographed dance.

Rihanna is the exception that proves the rule. She can't sing, dance, or write music. But she hitched her wagon to Esther Dean and Jay-Z, who are the ones really responsible for her success (this is why Rihanna makes much less money than Gaga or Beyonce- she's not part of creating her songs beyond singing them). Compare this to her contemporary Ciara, who could sing and dance quite well, but never stayed on top of musical trends or worked with the right songwriters. So I think that Acts like One Direction are just following the path that Rihanna paved for them: if you look pretty and have catchy songs you can point your way through them and still be a success.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zt8ek</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/does-one-direction-signal-the-beginning-of-another,71617/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:05:03+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:35:21+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3f5ju</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/does-one-direction-signal-the-beginning-of-another,71617/#comment-479863139</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/60wcu</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>