<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msxb18/update/2012-03-27T22:39:13/63fa1cd6c8ad58776a7cd0428134c96f7b163cf2f1caee3dc8444bcf4fb5bc34</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mslqqi</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/czvz7</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>10 Quotes By Barack Obama About Islam
#1 "Islam has  been part of America"
#2 "we will encourage more Americans to study in Muslim communities"
#3 "These rituals remind us of the principles that we hold in common, and Islam’s role in advancing justice, progress, tolerance, and the dignity of all human beings."
#4 "America and Islam are not exclusive and need not be in competition. Instead, they overlap, and share common principles of justice and progress, tolerance and the dignity of all human beings."
#5 "So I have known Islam on three continents before coming to the region where it was first revealed"
#6 "Ramadan is a celebration of a faith known for great diversity and racial equality"
#7 "As a young man, I worked in Chicago communities where many found dignity and peace in their Muslim faith."
#8 "I look forward to hosting an Iftar dinner celebrating Ramadan here at the White House later this week, and wish you a blessed month."
#9 "That experience guides my conviction that partnership between America and Islam must be based on what Islam is, not what it isn’t. And I consider it part of my responsibility as president of the United States to fight against negative stereotypes of Islam wherever they appear."
#10 "I also know that Islam has  been a part of America’s story."
10 Quotes By Barack Obama About Christianity#1 "Whatever we once were, we are no longer a Christian nation"
#2 "We do not consider ourselves a Christian nation."
#3 "Which passages of scripture should guide our public policy? Should we go with Leviticus, which suggests slavery is OK and that eating shellfish is an abomination? Or we could go with Deuteronomy, which suggests stoning your child if he strays from the faith?"
#4 "Even those who claim the Bible’s inerrancy make distinctions between Scriptural edicts, sensing that some passages – the Ten Commandments, say, or a belief in Christ’s divinity – are central to Christian faith, while others are more culturally specific and may be modified to accommodate modern life."
#5 "The American people intuitively understand this, which is why the majority of Catholics practice birth control and some of those opposed to gay marriage nevertheless are opposed to a Constitutional amendment to Ban it. Religious leadership need not accept such wisdom in counseling their flocks, but they should recognize this wisdom in their politics."
#6 From Obama’s book, The Audacity of Hope: "I am not willing to have the state deny American citizens a civil union that confers equivalent rights on such basic matters as hospital visitation or health insurance coverage simply because the people they love are of the same sex—nor am I willing to accept a reading of the Bible that considers an obscure line in Romans to be more defining of Christianity than the Sermon on the Mount."
#7 "I find it hard to believe that my God would consign four-fifths of the world to hell. I can’t imagine that my God would allow some little Hindu kid in India who never interacts with the Christian faith to somehow Burn for all eternity. That’s just not part of my religious makeup."
#8 "Those opposed to abortion cannot simply invoke God’s will–they have to explain why abortion violates some principle that is accessible to people of all faiths."
#9 On his support for civil unions for gay couples: "If people find that controversial then I would just refer them to the Sermon on the Mount."
#10 "I believe that there are many paths to the same place, and that is a belief that there is a higher power, a belief that we are connected as a people."
True Biblical Christianity has been under attack for a long time. President Obama claims to be a Christian. I think anyone who has heard him speak who has any sense of discernment knows otherwise. Is a closet Muslim? I don’t know. But one thing is for sure the man is much more sympathetic to his Muslim heritage than to anything Christian</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l4l3w</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ogrn</id></website><link>http://godfatherpolitics.com/4397/president-obama-gives-military-aid-to-egypt-as-militant-muslims-gain-control/</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T10:00:03+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T02:39:13+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msxb18</id><link>http://godfatherpolitics.com/4397/president-obama-gives-military-aid-to-egypt-as-militant-muslims-gain-control/#comment-478020098</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ekido</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>