<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwysh2/post/2012-03-30T11:03:25</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I don't disagree with what everyone else has already said--this was a bad episode, but Rabin obviously checked out on this show and that's tainting his judgment--but I want to add that episodes like this one, that aren't even 'bad,' just phoned-in, are easier to swallow when they're still producing stone Cold classics like "Leap Day," "Enter the Tuxedo" and "Kidnapped By Danger" in the same season. And they're still better than most of that terrible third season.

What's bothering me most, however, is how much we're supposed to care about Hazel. She'd be easier to laugh at if we knew that she was staying for the next season or two, but 30 has long track records of both a) getting big and/or currently hot actors for a limited number of episodes (Selma Hayek) and b) dropping characters and actors that were supposed to be important with little or no explanation (Rachel Dratch, Josh, Danny, Jonathan, Keith Powell for a bit).

I have no interest in learning to laugh at whatever the fuck Kristen Schaal is doing here if she's going to be the next Cheyenne Jackson, who had a multi-episode story arc leading to his introduction and has now been seen three times in the last two seasons. If however she's actually going to be the new Kenneth, I can deal with it eventually, but the humor is too broad and too poorly executed to allow that kind of suspension of standard for a guest star who's going to get killed Off violently after being teased as a new regular. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zohbw</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/the-shower-principle,71447/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:40:21+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:03:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwysh2</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/the-shower-principle,71447/#comment-480832020</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/doyua</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>