<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mku9dd/update/2012-03-26T10:41:29/99fa6b3e8c8070e8ab449a72d26a8be8e3ae392db88a67c36ad1bf055137fbb6</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Since I have been working in this field for the past four years, it is a concern that the average person does not have a clue about the threats that are out there.
 
   
 This should go to every police chief, airport and entertainment security in our large cities; and to superintendents of schools.The writer is correct.  In Europe, the public is ever watchful of suspicious objects, especially at airports and public places.
   Juval Aviv was the Israeli Agent upon whom the movie ' Munich ' was based. He was Golda Meir's bodyguard. She appointed him to track down and bring to justice the Palestinian terrorists who took the Israeli athletes hostage and killed them during the Munich Olympic Games. 

In a lecture in New York City a few weeks ago, Aviv shared information that EVERY American needs to know - but that our government has not yet shared with us.

Aviv predicted the London subway bombing on the Bill O'Reilly show on Fox News stating publicly that it would happen within a week. At the time, O'Reilly laughed and mocked him saying that in a week he wanted Aviv back on the show. But, unfortunately, within a week the terrorist attack had occurred. Juval Aviv gave intelligence (via what he had gathered in Israel and the Middle East ) to the Bush Administration about 9/11 a month before it occurred. His report specifically said that they would use planes as bombs and target high profile buildings and monuments. Congress has since hired him as a security consultant. Now for Aviv's future predictions: He predicts the next terrorist attack on the U.S. will occur within the next few months.. Forget hijacking airplanes, because he says terrorists will NEVER try hijacking a plane again as they know the people onboard will never go down quietly again. Aviv believes our airport security is a joke--that we have been reactionary rather than proactive in developing strategies that are truly effective. For example: 
1) Our airport technology is outdated. We look for metal, and the new explosives are made of plastic. 

2) He talked about how some idiot tried to light his shoe on fire. Because of that, now everyone has to take  their shoes. A group of idiots tried to bring aboard liquid explosives. Now we can't bring liquids on board. He says he's waiting for some suicidal maniac to pour liquid explosive on his underwear; at which point, security will have us all traveling naked! Every strategy we have is reactionary. 

3) We only focus on security when people are heading to the gates. Aviv says that if a terrorist attack targets airports in the future, they will target busy times on the front end of the airport when/where people are checking in. It would be easy for someone to take two suitcases of explosives, walk up to a busy check-in line, ask a person next to them to watch their bags for a minute while they run to the restroom or get a drink, and then detonate the bags BEFORE security even gets involved. In Israel , security checks bags BEFORE people can even ENTER the 
airport. 
Aviv says the next terrorist attack here in America is imminent and will involve suicide bombers and non-suicide bombers in places where large groups of people congregate... (i.e., Disneyland, Las Vegas 
casinos, big cities (New York, San Francisco, Chicago, etc.) and that it will also include shopping malls, subways in rush hour, train stations, etc., as well as rural America this time (Wyoming, Montana, etc.). 

The attack will be characterized by simultaneous detonations around the country (terrorists like a big impact), involving at least 5-8 cities, including rural areas. 

Aviv says terrorists won't need to use suicide bombers in many of the larger cities, because at places like the MGM Grand in Las Vegas , they can simply valet park a car loaded with explosives and walk away. Aviv says all of the above is well known in intelligence circles, but that our U.S. Government does not want to 'alarm American citizens' with the facts.. The world is quickly going to become 'a different place', and issues like 'global warming' and political correctness will become totally irrelevant. 

On an encouraging note, Aviv says that Americans don't have to be concerned about being nuked. He says the terrorists who want to destroy America will not use sophisticated weapons. They like to use suicide as a front-line approach. It's cheap, it's easy, it's effective; and they have an infinite abundance of young militants more than willing to 'meet their 
destiny'. 

Aviv also says the next level of terrorists, over which America should be most concerned, will not be coming from abroad. But will be, instead, 'home grown'- that means having attended and been educated in our own schools and universities right here in the U.S. He says to look for 'students' who frequently travel back and forth to the Middle East . These young terrorists will be most dangerous because they will know our language and will fully understand the habits of Americans; but that we Americans won't know/understand a thing about them. 

Aviv says that, as a people, Americans are unaware and uneducated about the terrorist threats we will, inevitably, face. America still has only a handful of Arabic and Farsi speaking people in our intelligence networks, and Aviv says it is critical that we change that fact SOON. 
So, what can America do to protect itself? From an intelligence perspective, Aviv says the U.S. needs to stop relying on satellites and technology for its intelligence. We need to, instead, follow Israel's, Ireland's and England's hands-on examples of human intelligence, both from an infiltration perspective as well as to trust 'aware' citizens to help... We need to engage and educate ourselves as citizens; however, our U.S. Government continues to treat us, its citizens, 'like babies'. Our government thinks we 'can't handle the truth' and are concerned that we'll panic if we understand the realities of terrorism. 
Aviv says this is a deadly mistake.. 

Aviv recently created/executed a security test for our Congress, by placing an empty briefcase in five well-traveled Spots in five major cities. The results? Not one person called 911 or sought a policeman to check it out. In fact, in Chicago , someone tried to steal the briefcase! 
In comparison, Aviv says that citizens of Israel are so well 'trained' that an unattended bag or package would be reported in seconds by citizen(s) who know to publicly , 'Unattended Bag!' The area would be quickly &amp; calmly cleared by the citizens themselves. But, unfortunately, America hasn't been 'hurt enough' yet by terrorism for their government to fully understand the need to educate its citizens or for the government to understand that it's their citizens who are, inevitably, the best first-line of defense against terrorism. 

Aviv also was concerned about the high number of children here in America who were in preschool and kindergarten after 9/11, who were 'lost' without parents being able to pick them up, and about our schools that had no plan in place to best care for the students until parents could get there.. (In New York City , this was days, in some cases!) He stresses the importance of having a plan that's agreed upon within your family, to respond to in the event of a terrorist emergency. He urges parents to contact their children's schools and demand that the schools, too, develop plans of actions, as they do in Israel . 

Does your family know what to do if you can't contact one another by phone? Where would you gather in an emergency?He says we should all have a plan that is easy enough for even our youngest children to remember and follow. 

Aviv says that the U.S. Government has in force a plan that, in the event of another terrorist attack, will immediately cut-Off EVERYONE's ability to use cell phones, blackberries, etc., as this is the preferred communication source used by terrorists and is often the way that their bombs are detonated. 

How will you communicate with your loved ones in the event you cannot speak? You need to have a plan. If you believe what you have just read, then you must feel compelled to send it to every concerned parent or guardian, grandparents, uncles, aunts, whatever and whomever. Nothing will happen if you choose not to do so, but in the event it does happen, this particular email will haunt you... "I should have sent this to...", but I didn't believe it and just deleted it as so much trash.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rg8hr</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/o6hq</id></website><link>http://conservativebyte.com/2012/03/witness-says-trayvon-martin-attacked-george-zimmerman/</link><postedTime>2012-03-25T04:37:58+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T14:41:29+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mku9dd</id><link>http://conservativebyte.com/2012/03/witness-says-trayvon-martin-attacked-george-zimmerman/#comment-476438408</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/676gj</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>