<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/276915/post/98661990/comment/327817363</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>\"This year, I had the privilege of having a bowler in thatindividual competition not only bowling against the other 29individuals but also competing against the additional 120 girlscompeting as part of a team. Jessica was not to be denied in herfourth and final trip to state; she was determined to break into inthe top 10.\" \"We have a good core of young talent, and they show somepotential,\" Hay said. The rest of the Kahoks\' state contingent included juniorCourtney Bruncic (1,492), sophomore Courtney Otradovec (1,356),Vivid Video, A Porn Giant, Resists Condom Proposal NPR,sophomore Sammi Kassly (1,122) and freshman Lindsey Collins(346). \"It was nice to get back there, and the girls bowled very well,\"Collinsville coach Sean Hay said. \"We had some rough patches hereand there, but we responded and that says a lot about the girls\'character. We were in 17th place after the first game on Friday andthey could have moped, but they came back and bowled a couplereally good games. Senior Katie Crafton, Sarah\'s sister, had a score of 1,632.Jessica Fowler, the team\'s only other senior, bowled three games onSaturday and had a two-day pin total of 768. \"Most of the girls who rise to the top are part of a team,Business AAMCO Transmissions, andthe momentum built by the team doing well usually  theindividual to higher levels in the individual competition,\" Eastcoach Gene Barrett said. Belleville East senior Jessica Kowalski placed 10th with a scoreof 2,borse louis vuitton,621. The top bowlers for West were Emily Consevage (2,459) and PaigeShackelford (2,458). Also competing for the Maroons were KatlynLoesche (2,293), Bri Ackerman (1,750), Syleena White (1,519),Kennedy Walton (682), Nikki Dunn (158) and Samantha Kohnen(143). \"Having Sarah and Amber bowl as well as they did is really goodfor the team because they\'re just juniors. They can come back nextyear and be even better.\" \"Jessica is a relatively new bowler, but that was probably thebest set of bowling in her career,\" Hay said. The top bowler for O\'Fallon was Erin Michelfelder, who finishedeighth with a score of 2,628. Other bowlers for the Panthers wereJordan Kasza (2,607), Lindsay Kasza (2,065), Jordan Schlotmann(2,055), Raven Leflore (920), Abby Solomon (711), Alexis Toohey(545) and Kristina Greynolds (286). The Kahoks also had a pair of top 10 individuals. Sarah Craftonwas sixth with a score of 2,641, while Amber Burns was ninth at2,624. The Collinsville girls bowling team wasn\'t able to match itsperformance of two years ago, but the Kahoks still had a strongshowing in last weekend\'s state tournament at Cherry Bowl Lanes inRockford. In 2010, Collinsville won the state championship and had anindividual champion in Frannie Steiner. Last year,Rick Scott StateImpact Florida, the Kahoksdidn\'t qualify for state. With a team score of 11,981, Collinsville placed seventh&amp;#8213;368pins behind first-place Tinley Park Andrew&amp;#8213;and had the highestfinish of any local team. O\'Fallon (11,817) was eighth, andBelleville West (11,462) was 10th. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:276915:98661990</id><idPostId>98661990</idPostId><idBlogId>276915</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:276915</id><idBlogId>276915</idBlogId><link>http://www.cinefamily.org</link><displayName>The Cinefamily</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.cinefamily.org/blog/trash-compactors-i-tell-you-its-burt-reynolds/</link><displayName>SUPERCUTS: "I Tell You It's Burt Reynolds!"</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:28:19.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:276915:98661990:327817363</id><link>http://www.cinefamily.org/blog/trash-compactors-i-tell-you-its-burt-reynolds/#IDComment327817363</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:28:19.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on SUPERCUTS: "I Tell You It's Burt Reynolds!" by fasf9119j</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://www.nikefrchaussures.com/</link><idEmailMd5>d617c347feb0e7a622a94750f11e9c5a</idEmailMd5><displayName>fasf9119j</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://www.nikefrchaussures.com/"&gt;fasf9119j&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.cinefamily.org/blog/trash-compactors-i-tell-you-its-burt-reynolds/"&gt;SUPERCUTS: "I Tell You It's Burt Reynolds!"&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>