<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwugsj/post/2012-03-30T22:34:36</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwqe5l</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cgr5j</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Say what?  Name a grid that has a minimum demand of 10% of average demand.  I don't think you'll be able to because as far as I am aware there aren't any.   

I don't know much about wind power in Germany, but I can tell you about wind power here in South Australia. Last year South Australia generated 26% of its electricity from wind.  The cost of wind power increased the price of electricity by about .366 cents per kilowatt-hour, or about 1% of the retail price.  But it also decreased the wholesale cost of electricity by over .5 cents, putting South Australians more than .134 cents ahead per kilowatt-hour.  Over the six year period in which we've been installing wind, electricity consumption has increased, but carbon emissions from the electricity sector have dropped 15%.  

Wind output is predicted with over 97% accuracy within a market period and wind has not requied new backup capacity.  We already had a large backup capacity to cope with a coal plant suddenly going  line, which is a problem that wind does not have as nothing can shut the wind  without warning (our weather stations would detect any sudden dying of wind before it Reached wind turbines) or shut down all wind turbines at once.  (Well, okay, a giant meterorite hitting Australia could shut down all wind turbines at once, but that would inconvenience other generating capacity as well.)  

South Australia now Burns less coal, less gas, and imports less electricity since the introduction of wind power and has the capacity to install more wind power and increase the percentage of electricity from 26%.  Currently we don't store any electricity generated from wind and at the moment we have no plans to.  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67rfc4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/thxi</id></website><link>http://grist.org/energy-policy/more-on-ramping-down-baseload-power-and-ramping-up-storage/?postpost=v2</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:13:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T02:34:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwugsj</id><link>http://grist.org/energy-policy/more-on-ramping-down-baseload-power-and-ramping-up-storage/?postpost=v2#comment-481450923</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>