<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/8aqi92/update/2011-01-03T12:35:53/27ab343121750a4d863daaf9607bf688b3efa4e96812f7764a3b9554c61af2eb</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>But they (sniff, sniff) are liberals (sniff), and the snow was so-oo-o-o-o Cold and deep.  Why couldn't somebody stop it?  Boo, hoo, hoo........sniff.  I'm surprised the 'snow victims' out East didn't crawl up onto the their roofs and scrawl HELP on their roof tops, New Orleans style. 

Governor Christies complete candor of speech and for taking whining constituents who are not yet on his side (and the unions which never will be),  to the woodshed and for pointing out how spoiled and corrupted people eventually become because of  union   meddling remains one of the high points of current state  politics in the U.S.  Just from watching Christies administration so far makes it evident that un-checked unions could eventually  even take away the peoples ability to wipe their own a s s e s .  Of course Obama is standing by in the wings to help with that with a fistful of soft, non-abrasive 'Nanny State Tissues'.  So Christies success will mean success for all of us.  So far, he suffers no fools.

And we ALL got to see by the wonderful example of New Jersey's great Governor, that  unions are fronts for criminality, paid Off politicians and even have the power to place awful Presidents in office that will perpetuate their frightening and debilitating grip on America if not smacked down.   

Go Christie!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/cr0spf</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6bwl</id></website><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/chris-christie/2011/01/02/buck-christie-smacks-down-snow-carpers</link><postedTime>2011-01-02T19:24:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-01-03T17:35:53+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/8aqi92</id><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/chris-christie/2011/01/02/buck-christie-smacks-down-snow-carpers#comment-123538248</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8nldh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-01-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>