<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3f558/update/2012-03-29T16:34:31/a4e95b6a26fb9ef21570f2b43e7fa65f2bb39a20caa9f1471be9223c7d969b06</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The Tawana Brawley Hoax confirms that truth and fair play are irrelevant in Sharpton's continuing quest to stir the pot-of-racial-hate to go after white America and instill anger in black America for political Gain. Sickening and evil.

Look how much the hoax about  climate change will hurt the working man.  Hoax and more lies while we shut down power plants and this will cause very high rates for everyone... China and India are building hundreds of coal Burning power plants.  We have more coal than all the world combined, coal that can be made into gas and used for all sorts of power uses and products.

Yet this administration puts thousands out of work in the coal business while they tell us to use alternative fuels ...."where in the Hell are the alternative fuels"..?????

When the lights go out and stoves are not working and they sit in the damn dark in blankets after the shut down of power plants in the East and much higher prices ...will the progressives get it then?  I doubt it..  It is a religion and they are never wrong and we are racists and haters and dumbass's. 

 If in fact we shut down every fuel in this world and stopped running cars it will not change the climate one damn degree and they know it, not even if we did it for hundreds of years.

This is political Bull crap just as the victimhood agenda is and has been..no matter what government does it costs us more for less so that they can appear to help the down trodden and satisfy the idiots who pay for elections and to satisfy the UN.  Americans are last in every matter and the elites are just that ..those who live above the fray  and those who make laws and pass bills that do not include them or their favorites.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hkoel</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry2d</id></website><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50511</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T22:10:43+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:34:31+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3f558</id><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50511#comment-479862290</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/67bzy</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>