<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jnsz/post/2012-04-02T03:54:23</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jdfb</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zd18t</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Morning Mr. Bell.  I certainly agree about the improved bullpen.  However, last year, I did numerous posts that the criticisms about the bullpen were misdirected in the sense that it is virtually impossible to have an effective bullpen when you are at or near the bottom of the league in innings per starter. I was not defending the bullpen, but they were not given an effective chance to be effective.

There was a retired player last year who said something along the lines that two short starts in a row can mess up a bullpen for 10 plus days and another short start in the middle of those 10 days can really screw things up.  I can also recall Dan Plesak trying to convince Tim Johnson that he was Burning up the bullpen with warmups - Johnson  had someone warming up - often two at a time.  Plesak said avery time a pitcher warms up, it is more than the equivalent of an inning pitched and bullpen guys do not have the rest of only pitching every 5th day.

One of the scribes this morning indicated the AL playoff teams starting pitching innings were:
     - Rays - 981
     - Rangers - 975
     - Tigers - 917
     - Yankees - 903

     - Jays - 716 (that number is certainly in conflict with Chisolms above article of 965 which would place us near the top of the league and we all know that didn't happen</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6vm6p1</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lz6q</id></website><link>http://toronto.bluejays.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120331%26content_id=27801050%26vkey=news_tor%26c_id=tor</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T01:56:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T07:54:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jnsz</id><link>http://toronto.bluejays.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120331%26content_id=27801050%26vkey=news_tor%26c_id=tor#comment-483336590</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/eu802</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>