<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5hpylc/update/2011-07-26T06:11:11/95f39fa25f64c883b99f90c83e7e4eece50025553b023bf888825c53a2cd95f4</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5rzarr</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Hello Sherri, I tapered  Lexapro in one week, i.e. went from 20 mg for 7 yrs to 10 mg for a week and immediately began my Viibryd 30 day pack.  Well, I'm on day 4 of the "wonder med" and have had Diarrhea for the first 2 days, then today felt my heart racing, chest hurting, gastro disturbances, and was so dizzy ("whooshing in my head) I could hardly stand.  I don't know if it's coming  the Lexapro or starting the Viibryd.  All this is to say that tonight I took 10 mg of Lexapro in an attempt to  some control of this until I can call my Dr. in the am.  I did not know Viibryd was touted so highly, (never heard of it until my Dr. gave me the sample pack in attempt to get better results than Lexapro) so I had no grand illusions about it.  Now I'm afraid of it.  I thought tapering one week  the Lexapro was enough, but perhaps not. It seems you are having a rough time getting Off of it.   Now I feel very let down as just going to 10 mg of Lexapro greatly lessened sexual side effects.  I read one could expect even better results with Viibryd.  What to do now?  I would like to keep trying it but I'm only on 10 mg, a lonnnng way before 40 mg.  I'll talk to my Dr. when his office opens.  I'm very disappointed in the SE of Viibryd at early outset. Gee, I hate to throw in the towel on a drug with promise, but don't know if I can keep going like this, can hardly function.  Will try to post again with what I decide.  Thanks for listening.
Paula</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/gbyg1a</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ykk7</id></website><link>http://chipur.com/2011/06/22/viibryd-an-updated-users-journal/</link><postedTime>2011-06-22T23:30:15+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-07-26T10:11:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5hpylc</id><link>http://chipur.com/2011/06/22/viibryd-an-updated-users-journal/#comment-265064835</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-06-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>