<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0amo0/update/2012-03-31T15:06:56/2751d204d30ac32aeaa243b2de61b8a6157a9c69850ad7d5e13a08f8227e2f4f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I must be an outlier, given that I am anti-abortion, yet pro-choice. It's your unconscious mind, you deal with the consequences. The fact is that a life is lost whenever an abortion occurs. As long as people are brave enough to deal with this fact in an open and honest way, then I have no problem taking their pro-abortion stance seriously. Shit, my ex-wife and I even had an abortion once. Of course, I didn't know she was sleeping with two other people at the time. Small wonder why she didn't want the Headache.

Nevertheless, I find it a little odd that people don't talk a whole lot about the fact that unmarried fathers in Alberta and British Columbia do not have parental rights. American and Canadian women flock to these places to subvert the laws in their usual place of residence. Fortunately, the courts in the US are now punishing people for this. It's a small wonder why some people don't take the militant pseudo-feminist movement seriously. "What's yours is mine and what's mine is mine" is a bit ... tyrannical, if you ask me.

Anyway, thanks for sticking up for everyone's rights... when it serves your public image, that is. I'll Always look up to you for sticking it to those who extort and kidnap.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67wed9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/agg8</id></website><link>http://boingboing.net/2012/03/31/army-of-volunteers-politely-ca.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T17:25:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T19:06:56+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0amo0</id><link>http://boingboing.net/2012/03/31/army-of-volunteers-politely-ca.html#comment-482106563</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gp0b3</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>