<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miek4z/update/2012-03-22T17:24:46/f97c2e62021b3a0c5a42a467b54991f2ed4e5c047a5d2bbbe3f9ee3b6aa44078</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miajtt</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gfpe5</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>@SleepyJhonny


I think your taking this too personally. I think you need to take a little break from your PC. As I said you are entitled to your opinion as I am mine. If I think its Art why do you care? I was just calling you out on you speaking for everyone. You are stating an OPINION not a FACT. Fact is people consider Video Games art it is a long drawn out debate about it. As I said what you consdier NOT art others might feel or see it differnt.

 Maybe it's your English and you don’t understand me. I am not sure what your problem is. Maybe just maybe if you learn to understand
people have difference of opinion then you would be more understanding. I refuted your arguments and I disagree with you in many ways. I even posted links leading to reason why Video Games are considered art and why people agree/ disagree. You claim to be 28 but, you Act like a child. You insist that your opinion matters and nobody else should have one. I bet your one of the Cry babies that petitioned Bioware to change the ending also.

 Funny how you call me discriminating yet you talk about Americans and our pop culture. You sir are a hypocrite. BTW you might speak foreign languages but, you’re typing and understanding of English is atrocious.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dkfa5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7d9s</id></website><link>http://ps3.ign.com/articles/122/1221273p1.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T16:21:21+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T21:24:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miek4z</id><link>http://ps3.ign.com/articles/122/1221273p1.html#comment-473972486</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gfpe5</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>