<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miwpc4/update/2012-03-24T12:16:31/b68ea3cdcbd3283b0f3df75ff2c8a1b99096fc822ba3c545721b3ea966108065</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>At last the truth is out ! The British had coffee long
before the Italians began claiming it as their own! Anyone reading Boswell’s Dr
Samuel Johnson of over 300 years ago would have known that. After WW2,
according to an Italian impresario on SBS television in Australia, the military
option having failed, it was decided to export something that could be dressed
up as Italian culture. (I still have a recording of this). First, they began
fixing up their own cafes, which he admitted were pretty tawdry, then. Then
they began promoting cappuccino and pissa, resulting with cafes now around the
world in all the top Spots. Huge barriers on the footpath, ostensibly to offer
minimalist protection to anyone sitting out on the footpath, but in fact so
Italian names could be displayed in large letters on prominent street corners
around the world, so it would  be in your face – yuk! I am fascinated by
different cultures, but not when they aggressively push themselves onto me, at
the expense of my culture. Around the world, cafe staff are taught to belittle
the regular flat white coffee – trained to ask if you want a cappuccino, and I
say no, I want an Australian flat white coffee, the trained response is, with a
look down the nose – “oh, only a flat white!” They used to have the audacity to
charge more for the frothy muck, which meant you got less coffee: froth was
cheaper. We had gone to live in UK when the first espresso bar had opened in
Southend-on-Mud. But what I don’t like was the way Greek friends of ours, in
Melbourne (the largest Greek community outside of Greece, as with the
Italians), were forced to close down for refusing to sell Italian coffee –
despite being surrounded by other cafes selling Italian. After all, why shouldn’t
Greek cafes sell purely Greek food? Cafes are pressured into it by various
tactics, including suppliers using blackmail if they can’t achieve it any other
way. The mafia here is also very strong – my wife’s father had to close his
farm, after having been ripped  badly by those self seeking, ruthless scum.
It was in the news in Australia’s largest paper recently, that the mafia get 50
cents on every box of fruit &amp; veg passing through the wholesale market here
– and neither State or Federal governments can do anything to stop it. These
are the people Messrs Heath &amp; Wilson got you into bed with originally with
joining the EEC – is it any wonder there are huge deficits? The trouble is,
most EEC countries are catholic, and for them, Italy can do no wrong! Recent
figures in the ‘Telegraph’ indicated the Italian based mafia make 100 billion
pounds a year – these crooks still expect government services, yet pay no taxes
for them. Instead, the British are back to pre Henry VIII days, shoring up that
vast bastion of corruption. This article on London was such a pleasure to read,
it is the sort of thing the ‘Telegraph’ was renowned for. During my last 4 year
visit to England, I met the gentleman who started England’s first tea and
coffee museum, across the river from the Tower of London. I hope it’s not been ‘compromised’
by the type of tactics Italy uses towards anyone seen as getting in their
way....I have just checked the web &amp; found that Edward Bramah died in 2008
I am sorry to see, resulting in the closure of his excellent museum. Let us
hope those seeking to reopen it will not allow themselves to be bribed with
cheap coffee offers by Mussolini’s mob, as they have done elsewhere around the
world. This was a British institution, imported directly from where coffee was
grown – Brazil, though apparently it was first discovered by Europeans in
Ethiopia. When the head of Melbourne’s substantial leading training
establishment for catering staff dared to contradict a presentor on Australia’s
second largest radio station to say this, when he tried insisting it was grown
in Italy, he rudely cut the interview  just like that ! Later she expressed
surprise to me – I wasn’t surprised! She had just discovered yet another Guy
Fawkes man with his ridiculous treatment of Mussolini’s mob as though they were
sacred cows. Having myself visited Delhi in India, believe you me, I have seen
how those cows are revered! I don’t think Mussolini’s mob are worth it – esp when
they stoop to such low tricks, to divert funds and attention towards
themselves. No doubt the EEC will rewrite history to flatter the conceits of
Mussolini’s mob, at the expense of those whom they have never stopped to
undermine. We have just had the Grand Prix in Melbourne – it seems not even the
mafia can afford to bribe other drivers to let Ferrari win all the time any
more: or was it becoming too obvious? Or now Berlusconi is no longer PM there
is no one with the unprincipled influence, to ‘arrange’ these things? As soon
as we saw a Subway restaurant open in Melbourne, we knew it had to be Italian
American. No doubt the ‘high’ end (bells &amp; smells) of my church will be
rushing Off there, genuflecting as they go. But give me ‘Macckers’ or Hungry
Jack’s any day!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6mjdiv</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/europe/uk/london/9153317/London-cafes-the-surprising-history-of-Londons-lost-coffeehouses.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-20T09:43:57+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-24T16:16:31+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miwpc4</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/europe/uk/london/9153317/London-cafes-the-surprising-history-of-Londons-lost-coffeehouses.html#comment-475275726</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g2gj9</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>