<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwsuc8/update/2012-03-31T10:56:44/2d8fab8e1129826a7004df7f073ef6b94e1399a560f8921b757d0813d4209d2f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Thank you for this article. We must do this as soon as possible before an innocent American citizen is picked. It reminds me of the way the TSA started. We all know the TSA is just Obama's SS.
I was "selected" at the Atlanta Airport. The man was at least 6'4". I never had the chance to go through the regular scanner I usually go through and don't mind at all. He stepped in front of me and scared me to death.He towered over me as he looked down at me. He intimidated me on purpose. I was traveling alone to see one of my children in Texas. He blocked me from walking through the scanner. I was given the choice of a pat down or the radiation. I am definitely a southern born Wasp in appearance, and conservative in appearance. I was wearing my "under the radar traveling outfit.A white blouse,navy slacks,simple slip on shoes,no jewelry except my loop earrings and my grandmother's pearl ring.
I could go so far as to say that it was either racial profiling or political profiling.
I did just what my Jewish friends did in Europe as I am not an aggressive person. I am just what Obama hates about America and wants to humiliate and take down. My family began in America in 1630, in the Chesapeake Bay. I work and pay taxes. My father Always called me his "Bleeding heart benevolent" child. He was too. We all have been. It is the conservatives that give even when we're not rich. God bless the rich, that's where my patrons come from. They feed me.I am not rich, just truly American and proud of it. I was really frightened, all I could think of was how upset my son and his family would be if I refused and was further harassed. 
After the radiation treatment I walked out and another TSA agent said I had two metal Spots on my scan, the little screen showed little squares on my elbow and my knee. There is NO metal in my body except in my mouth. So they went up and down my arm and my leg. 
IT WAS ALL A CROCK AND THEY COVER THEMSELVES BEAUTIFULLY. It was meant to humiliate me and frighten me, as I am sure they could tell I'm just a normal gentle woman. 
I have made a decision now. I am driving to Texas when I can--14 hours from my home, or I'm driving to the Greenville, SC airport. I will never fly out of Atlanta again. 
We must stop this Law in it's tracks. This is Tyranny.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67eg82</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zmzu</id></website><link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2012/mar/30/gop-weighs-changes-indefinite-detention-law/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T14:52:41+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T14:56:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwsuc8</id><link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2012/mar/30/gop-weighs-changes-indefinite-detention-law/#comment-481893086</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/66ovv</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>