<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkfqql/post/2012-03-26T12:39:42</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkqj0t</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>"Should we cut our ties (and subsidies) with Israel,and let someone else deal with the Jewish problem?"  There is no "Jewish problem."  That is like saying there is a "Christian problem" because Pat Robertson has nominated himself to head America's Armegeddon team in the Middle East.  (If my reading comprehension is right - God is going to have something to say about that one day...)

This is not about religion for any of the self-righteous hecklers in the equation.  Unless you consider that if The Revelation is right, that Christians are being lured to the region to pick whom they worship once and for all:  God, or the Whore of Babylon:  OIL.  

The PNAC has gotten a little cliche over the years, but what was not said is that they had one goal at the "end" of the Cold War, and that was stopping the emergence of a rival Super Power.  Iran? China? I don't think so - I think it is ISRAEL.  I see us doing Israel the same we have done every other country in the Middle East.  We arm them, give them a free pass to do insane things - and then when they stop doing our bidding, our media blitz cries fake outrage and calls for our invasion to "save" the "poor opressed" peoples in the Middle East.  

Except this time, we will not have some 7th century Islamic idealogues with no home or standing military- we will have a well armed "western democracy" with an air force as good as ours, and an intelligence community that is better than ours.  Israel and the United States are not friends.  We are business partners.  And when the business goes sour - we will see how fake that "special relationship" between the US and Israel has been all along.  

I stand with the people of the United States, Israel and all the people in the Middle East.  If our founders taught us anything, We the People our our friends, and Thomas Jefferson and George Washington wrote the 1789 Alien Torts Act to prove it.  It is so ironic that people who claim to be "conservatives" in this country support our tax dollars going to pay for the EXACT  "socialist government" they are so afraid of becoming in the United States....  How is it "supporting Israel" to pay for their own demise?  Patriotism and denial are not the same thing, and nationalism and patriotism are definatley not the same thing.  Andrew Bacevich is a brilliant and wonderful American patriot.  It takes a lot of guts to tell the truth.  

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/667kic</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/u05y</id></website><link>http://billmoyers.com/episode/moving-beyond-war/</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T21:08:00+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T16:39:42+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkfqql</id><link>http://billmoyers.com/episode/moving-beyond-war/#comment-476523048</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>