<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk9m0q/post/2012-03-26T13:19:36</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>im fine with paying 60$ for a good game, im also fine with paying double for double. even if it does hurt my pockets...

i am NOT fine with lame games with obvious "shortcuts" for lack of a better term. like repeated backgrounds and dungeons (*Cough* dragon age 2 *Cough*)

short games with medium quality that costs as much as top quality games like BAC or TES or what ever, thats just wrong.


another thing that is wrong is DLC's, and more importantly DAY ONE DLC. DLC's used to be fun and a good thing, not a way to suck our money. and i may be crazy but didn't they used to be for FREE?! 
im fine with an expansion pack, coz it has meat on it and lots of gameplay hours.. im not OK with a lame dlc that offers little no nothing and costs like 15$, thats just pure greed. also the case of ME3 with the prothean squad mate that SHOULD HAVE BEEN IN THE GAME IN THE FIRST PLACE but instead was a day one dlc.. that's just insulting. 

i had another point to make but i forgot it coz i kept thinking about dragon age 2 and day one DLC and it got me mad :(


edit: oh yeah. rushed games. that disease should be terminated and be told to our young ones b4 bed to scare them from doing such horrible thing. 

they should learn from blizzard and hold it Off for even 10 years if needed be to make the game PERFECT and not "meh.. its ok.. at least we got it done on time" 

even if it means costing more money once it releases, it will be money well spent instead of a huge disappointment (yeah im looking at you dragon age 2!!!!)</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r0ilu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7d9s</id></website><link>http://games.ign.com/articles/122/1221226p1.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T16:12:02+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:19:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk9m0q</id><link>http://games.ign.com/articles/122/1221226p1.html#comment-476554735</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zgqwl</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>