<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmm2e/update/2012-03-30T08:52:51/da29a1979f5fb9fd8274ff79c913f92fcef29579c858b78614210103198e5716</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3v9ca</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8dtfx</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Calvinius... does somebody pay you to pound the boards with your negative, contrary diatribes?
The "coon" comment was somebody's biased, wishful thinking.  The tape has been reviewed until it is worn out... there was nothing but noise there.  Zimmerman lived in a multiracial household and was mentoring two black children.

Only on TV and in the movies does somebody who has been bloodied in a fight walk around for the rest of the show with their blood dripping from their face.  There is this little technique called "first aid" where people stop the Bleeding and clean up the victim.  Besides, someone could have had their face torn Off and you wouldn't be able to tell it from a grainy, distant video.

Your problem is you only choose to believe what you want to believe... and cling to what you believe even after it has been debunked.  But then... that is what you are paid for.

In the end, the main part of this story that remains unsettled to me is what happened in the initial contact... did they have words?... was there even an initial contact or just an attack?  Did Martin attack out of fear or because he was a thug who sized up an inferior opponent not thinking he was armed?

Regardless of who did what... Martin put Zimmerman in a life and death situation and Zimmerman reacted out of self defense.

</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h3t41</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f7e3</id></website><link>http://www.wnd.com/2012/03/the-medias-selective-outrage/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T23:43:19+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T12:52:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmm2e</id><link>http://www.wnd.com/2012/03/the-medias-selective-outrage/#comment-480705846</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zdix7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>