<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6epj/post/2012-03-30T11:16:44</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I have to tell you about an encounter yesterday. I had to take my two dogs to the vet yesterday. We have a bad epidemic of kennel Cough going through our city, so i felt I needed to vaccinate my dogs. We ar in contact with rescue dogs and at least 2 rescues, including the one I do volunteer fundraising for has had dogs with it. So  we went. 

There was a lady with her son and Golden Lab or maybe a German Shepherd, anyways. She saw me standing there and one of my boys, Scrappy was peeking around the corner, watching. Leo didn't even notice. I explained to her why I was standing there and she said that was fine and told me how her dog had been attacked by a group of small dogs and ever since has been skittish around small dogs. First time ever! I usually get but my dog is friendly to which I have to respond mine are not. They are great when Off leash or with their own breed (Leo is a senior long haired miniature dachshund and Scrappy is a wire haired dachshund fox terrier cross), however when on leash, Leo is aggressive which triggers Scrappy.

Nice to see a dog owner who gets it :)</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ypjseh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/u68i</id></website><link>http://www.dogster.com/lifestyle/watch-dog-close-encounters-of-the-third-kind?_view=all</link><postedTime>2012-03-01T00:33:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:16:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6epj</id><link>http://www.dogster.com/lifestyle/watch-dog-close-encounters-of-the-third-kind?_view=all#comment-480845583</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/e8r9t</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>