<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi6gyp/post/2012-03-22T21:34:25</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>"If ye love wealth greater than liberty, the tranquility of servitude 
greater than the animating contest for freedom, go home from us in 
peace. We seek not your counsel, nor your arms. Crouch down and lick the
 hand that feeds you; and may posterity forget that ye were our countrymen." Samuel Adams

This quote is so appropriate in our time of history now that America is hurtling toward a Socialistic form of government that makes peaceful protest and free speech a Felony "trespassing" criminal charge on the grounds of public government buildings. The government claims sweeping powers to nationalize any food, energy, labor, infrastructure, etc. private  companies in ANY case; national emergency, wartime, peacetime. These public servants are not working for the people of America when they stifle free speech, criminalize everything we do, and Burn our Constitution in front of our eyes and tell us to obey without question.

I like this true American Patriot, Jon McNaughton.....who as an artist will express his opinion so eloquently in the form of paintings to protest the selling out of our nation. Future historians only need to look at these paintings to understand why America was weakened and destroyed from the inside out by the very ones who swore an oath to uphold and defend our Constitution when they took office. 

I don't care who any of you vote for in 2012.....just that you go and vote to make your voice heard! The fewer people of the nation that pick our next President will Ensure that the power stays as a status quo. We are so doomed.......just as Rome eventually was.....history repeats itself!
 </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6d0neu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/opxh</id></website><link>http://cowboybyte.com/5553/painting-of-obama-burning-constitution-sparks-controversy-free-speech-offensive-or-both/</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T19:23:08+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T01:34:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi6gyp</id><link>http://cowboybyte.com/5553/painting-of-obama-burning-constitution-sparks-controversy-free-speech-offensive-or-both/#comment-474125105</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ze9mq</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>