<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwfzao/update/2012-03-31T01:11:44/0decf61b8fa87568b7b04ccbabd93917aff37f3687ad057d0c4f54e32a61b7df</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Although what you said is harsh, I won't lecture you for it. You probably feel horrible enough at this point, and honestly, we all say things we regret in the Heat of an argument. 

I'm really sorry for your loss, OP. I know, that's just a generic thing to say, but what else can I really say?

I've read several things that can give you a sense of closure regarding his death. Some things I've seen is writing a letter and Burning it, attaching a note to a balloon and releasing it, and more. You could probably read up on ways to feel better about the whole situation, because a lot of people have been in a situation where they say something (or don't say something) to someone who ends up dying, and they feel a deep sense of guilt/regret for it.

For future reference, try your hardest to think before you speak. No, it's not easy, but at least give it an effort. Because, honestly, sad but true, things like this can happen at any given time.

And, of course, if you Reach a point where you begin to cope poorly with his death, try to seek out help, through counseling or otherwise.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67by8u</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dypr</id></website><link>http://www.sixbillionsecrets.com/view/Love/1604663</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T05:00:30+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T05:11:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwfzao</id><link>http://www.sixbillionsecrets.com/view/Love/1604663#comment-481554784</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ydkjg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>