<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mnnkeg/update/2012-03-06T10:01:36/f8814a8cc5960ed32214cd5b6af5ecfc78c967c577247bad08b74ba421f21535</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mnqhid</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8fl1z</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>"These companies are putting all their eggs in the liberal basket."  
Wrong - they're putting all their eggs in the WINNING basket.  

Obama is the least liberal Democratic president since Woodrow Wilson. His closest ideological comparators are Eisenhower &amp; Nixon. You could make a non-laughable argument that Obama's been to the RIGHT of a slew of Republican presidents since 1900: Teddy Roosevelt, Taft the Trust-Buster, Ford, Bush the elder - even Reagan, at least on tax expenditure ratios (a point Paul Krugman has been making for the last week.).  

This exact same thing happened in early 2008: Wall Street starting funnelling cash to Obama &amp; the DNC over the RNC at such a ratio, it became a news story.  

A lot of American business success  on picking winners as early as possible. We the unwashed get polling that's way too specific way way too early, 'horse race' daily trackers, &amp; push polls. Business doesn't care about any of that process crap - it only cares about ending up having backed the winning horse. That's because a huge &amp; very fluid percentage of American business activity is centered around government tax expenditures, &amp; businesses that  on federal expenditures but back the loser end up losing revenues &amp; failing at an exaggerated rate compared to businesses that back the winner.  

Business takes its cues from the logarithms of American life, from the Cold, calculating dweebs who analyse data from social patterns &amp; social media: what you need, what you think you need, what you actually want, what you're Googling, your Surfing patterns, the websites on your Favorites list, who you're phoning, who you're texting, how you're using Facebook &amp; Twitter. Business is laying their bets, &amp; it's not close; just look at Intrade. 

Plus there's another factor: American business looks at likely future tax expenditure policy, &amp; the sense is that this current Democratic politician in the White House has proven that he means what he says - &amp; what he says he wants is more big stimulus, more public-private partnerships in new energy, &amp; a big push at infrastructure renewal, all of which is good for busines - whereas, in contrast, the likely Republican nominee has a reputation for saying one thing one day &amp; the opposite the next, so that the best predictor of his future tax expenditure policy is that it mostly likely will reflect current Republican orthdoxy, which is entirely made by Grover Norquist - &amp; Grover Norquist's 100% anti-tax is bad for Business.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/y3blnr</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tz1k</id></website><link>http://www.mediaite.com/online/are-advertisers-making-the-right-choice-by-leaving-rush-limbaugh/</link><postedTime>2012-03-06T12:26:35+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-06T15:01:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mnnkeg</id><link>http://www.mediaite.com/online/are-advertisers-making-the-right-choice-by-leaving-rush-limbaugh/#comment-457829069</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7zl7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-06</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>