<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk40yh/update/2012-03-26T00:27:00/4072e99cd5d0fb2ba5fbd30025545117ee2016a1830548f2c4d8e575dccd599d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkm3et</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5wkaq</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I believe that your reading of the Gospel is Spot-on. Jesus DID say to eat his body and drink his blood. The disciples DID ask him to back Off or tell them it is figurative, not literal. Jesus explicitly refused. Some disciples refused to believe and walked away. Jesus still didn't budge. 
To push the point further, at the Last Supper, he then showed the Apostles exactly HOW to eat his body and blood, literally, even when he is no longer spatially or temporally present, and told them to perpetuate it from the then until the end of the world.

I tend to think we Anglicans are calling a banana "curved yellow fruit" 
because we officially deny transubstantiation yet claim to believe that 
we are consuming the Body and Blood of Christ nonetheless. However, 
those of us in the Anglo-Catholic tradition believe in 
transubstantiation, but must call it the "real presence" to avoid 
sounding -GASP!- "romish". Yeah...the contradiction gnaws at me, I'll 
admit it.

I think you may have set me up so I would end up giving a good Catholic theology of the Eucharist, only to then spring the trap and ask me why am I not in the RCC. Sigh. I hate having my internal contradictions exposed for all to see. If so, I neither blame nor begrudge you for doing so.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66x7np</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ywkl</id></website><link>http://takimag.com/article/resisting_catholicism_nicholas_farrell/print</link><postedTime>2012-03-24T04:03:29+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T04:27:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk40yh</id><link>http://takimag.com/article/resisting_catholicism_nicholas_farrell/print#comment-476216833</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gd4vn</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>