<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jrfx/post/2012-04-02T03:07:29</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0fq6i</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8b792</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>A major lack of decorum? not really, lots of freewheeling idea's some being funny other outside the norm and some being beyond the pale.  But as I recall "Et Tu bruti"  might be an apt decriptor for you as well on more than one occasion. but I could be wrong and I have known to be wrong more frequently than a broken clock too. 

If you feel that my account should be closed all I can say in reply is that you are entitled to your opinion, I disagree but you are entitled.  and as the saying goes: opinions are like certain parts of human anatomy, everyone has one. 

May I suggest that you return to your dictionary once in a while and study, and learn the difference between, scorn, ridicule, sarcasm, satire, and ad hominem attacks. 

and lastly when is it my responsibility to single out others? it's not ever, however, I will   respond to those postings that I want to respond to.  it's okay if I do, don't worry it will be fine, trust me those three folks will not be loosing any sleep over my actions speaking truth to power is Always distasteful to some but its okay, we get to do that in America THE BILLS of RIGHTS says we can. *winks* 

peace brother, tomorrow is another day and who knows maybe tomorrow we will be in the same side of the next issue that we have a Burning desire to post about. 

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6763mo</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnm3</id></website><link>http://www.sacbee.com/2012/03/30/4378830/health-care.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:36:01+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T07:07:29+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jrfx</id><link>http://www.sacbee.com/2012/03/30/4378830/health-care.html#comment-483324681</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cztds</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>