<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwlgsa/post/2012-03-30T12:45:35</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwri3p</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ggs2q</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Agree with you on the 2 Spot for De Aza.  And the qualities that you describe for an ideal leadoff hitter are a very rare combination to find.  I cannot think of any single player ( the top of my head) that has all of these skills, hence the question.  I'm sure if I scoured the Leauge, the list I could come up with would be a short (and very expensive) one...a youngster could possibly possess the talent to be a good leadoff hitter, but finding one that had a low K rate would be the tricky part.  One that had ALL that you describe would be so rare that no team in their right mind would part with him.  I still believe Jared Mitchell could become that guy for us, he's not there now, but he has certainly appeared to have made large Strides toward the eventual goal of becoming that guy for us.  IF Mitchell could emerge as soon as next season, AND De Aza proved himself worthy of staying a part of this team's future plans...(I know I'm dreaming here, but please indulge my fantasy), we'd be looking at a Pierre/Castro 1-2 that fueled the Marlins WSC...only our guys would have much better power numbers.  Food for future thought, anyway.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zu900</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lz6q</id></website><link>http://chicago.whitesox.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120329%26content_id=27732656%26vkey=news_cws%26c_id=cws</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:04:41+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:45:35+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwlgsa</id><link>http://chicago.whitesox.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120329%26content_id=27732656%26vkey=news_cws%26c_id=cws#comment-480937681</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/csz4w</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>