<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw3cnr/update/2012-03-31T11:22:53/3469dd43abb80723c13624b4385b8a1f050391897331853f9a3cab797d36efb7</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Is Ed Milliband for against the fuel crisis? Well that's a bit like saying, is he for or against the weather?

Leaving aside this government's incompetent meddling, the "fuel crisis" as you call it, is simply an industrial dispute between the drivers of petrol tankers, and the several companies who jointly employ them. So far, so simple. In a free country (of which, more later, no doubt) a worker may withdraw his labour: people are not slaves. Furthermore, any employer is equally free to universally alter the contracts of employment between himself and his employees. As, for example, the slash and Burn economics of Local Councils, the Government's attack on the public sector, and any other employer who thinks it opportune to exploit the current economic slump by a reduction of its workforce's benefits (pensions and salaries particularly).  That's called free-market Capitalism, ain't it?

I think the real question you're fumbling for is: "Is Ed Milliband for or against a fuel strike"? That would be more accurate, don't you think?

And, of course, the answer to that question, as you well know, is a resounding NO, he isn't if favour of a fuel strike. Time and again he has publicly stated that he wishes to see this dispute  through mediation and arbitration (as nearly all strikes  are ultimately so Resolved). But then again.... the breath of sanity doesn't fit well with the Telegraph's political agenda, does it.

Neither the Telegraph's nor the Tory Party's hysterics will goad any Labour supporter, high or low, to agree with the preposterous proposition that strikes should be made illegal. That is the fantasy world inhabited by Neocons, uber-right motoring correspondents called Jeremy, communists regimes and fascist dictatorships.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hodoq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/comment/telegraph-view/9171485/Is-Ed-Miliband-for-or-against-a-fuel-crisis.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T19:37:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T15:22:53+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw3cnr</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/comment/telegraph-view/9171485/Is-Ed-Miliband-for-or-against-a-fuel-crisis.html#comment-481914443</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/64ud4</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>