<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m02h6w/update/2012-03-31T14:20:32/bc4ab25cefeaebc88ba9ab4c3736b3538616a7e78c07f24928b9193ce3b37c6e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The so-designated federal "GST" isn't really a true goods and services tax. Such a tax should, in theory, be applied equally to all goods and all services. This tax is not. When the GST was first introduced back around 1990, the Mulroney government decided to exempt the majority of typical grocery items so as to reduce the tax's impact on low-income consumers. They weren't just being altruistic. That change also helped make the proposed tax more politically viable and as a result  the opposition's support. However laudable as all that may have been from a purely social standpoint, it essentially bumped the "GST" Off in the direction of a watered-down "luxury" tax. The alternative? As Cold and cruel as it may seem, a true functional GST should be set low enough that it can be realistically charged on all goods and services with -no- exceptions. So how low is "low enough?" Likely a bit lower than now - given the current economic/inflationary climate, maybe somewhere in the area of 2 or 3%. Were that to ever happen, the government could continue assisting those with lower incomes by retaining the existing income-based GST rebate system.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67oj6v</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7maa</id></website><link>http://www.edmontonsun.com/2012/03/30/hicks-what-to-do-about-taxes</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T12:23:23+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T18:20:32+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m02h6w</id><link>http://www.edmontonsun.com/2012/03/30/hicks-what-to-do-about-taxes#comment-482067034</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l3qi6</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>