<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/57a0to/update/2011-07-27T21:55:56/b5dcf79812f62152efac4b03cc8914f9ad88b741791a9d3cc8c40afbea2ab477</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>THE DEM'S NEVER CAN SEE THE ERROR OF THEIR SPENDING AND NEVER WANT TO CUT, i.e., THE NEA.....

On C-SPAN today, the Democrats, led by Congressman Jim Moran, 8th District of Virginia are fighting to block a $10,000,000.00 cut in funds from the NEA ($145,000,000.00 budget) who got a big boost in stimulus funds if you all recall, and was granted $50,000,000 in stimulus.  That is now being challenged by Republicans.  Personally, I find the NEA subject to cuts like any other program that is not but could certainly be supported by philanthropy if it is so essential.  In the course of the last two years, we have learned of NEA (tax-payer funded, remember) funds have been distributed to projects that produced artistic, 'experimental'  (Cough)  ' p o r n ' , and art that attacked Christianity and the desecrated the image of Christ.  Furthermore, the most shocking transgression is/was, that the NEA, (or members of) who were more than happy to take stimulus funds (buy 's, I prefer) also took a meeting/calls from the White House who basically made it clear to a group of arts and/or representatives of NEA that they would like/expect their art to include 'work for the Obama' regime...political art, featuring the agenda of this Presidency.  This is documented in recorded phone calls.   So.... NEA touched the leper...Obama.   Like NPR and Family Planning, I say why should any taxpayer dollars be directed to this organization which has chosen to behave like a street w h o r e  for the money?

One 'gentlewoman' (D) from California got up and began with "I'm the coolest grandmother in the world."  Her point was that she lives in close proximity to a renowned, iconic arts organization.  She continued to bleat about what a shame it would be if (the Smithsonian, Ca.) were forced to cut back services and programs that her grandchildren delight in.  Well, dear, why don't you explain to your grandchildren that you instead chose a behemoth social program, ObamaCare.  A crippling monstrosity.  You also chose to direct hard earned taxpayer garnered stimulus funds in this sampling of  stupid wasteful  projects:

1. Monkeys Get High for Science (Winston-Salem, NC) - $144,541
2. Scientist Attempts to Create Joke Machine (Evanston, IL) - $712,883 
3. Research: Marketing Video Games to the Elderly (Raleigh, NC and Atlanta, GA) - $1.2 million
4. The Wheels on the Stimulus Go Round and Round (Clearfield, PA) - $1.4 million
5. Money for Healthy Homes and Lead Hazard Control to Ineligible Recipients - $2.8 million
6. NIH Spends Stimulus Money to Promote the Impact of Its Stimulus Projects (Silver Spring,
MD) - $363,760546
7. Whistle blower Alleges Fraud at Company Administering Child Care Funds (Kilgore, TX) -
$215 million
8. Health Insurance Grants go Unused (Washington, DC) - $142 million
9.  Army Corps of Engineers Cleaning Up Their Act in West Virginia (Burnsville, WV) - $650,00010. 
10.  Helping Drinkers Control Their Alcohol Consumption With Creative Labeling (San Diego, Ca.) 
$497,117

Explain to your grandchildren that you, a 'cool grandma', are also a big spending, big government creator and a  far left progressive, liberal Democrat that has no idea of how to budget for your country and YOUR skewed priorities are now coming home to roost with the chickens.  And obviously, the millions above far exceed the $10,000,000.00 dollars being requested by the mean, nasty Republicans.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/e5nzir</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6bwl</id></website><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/deficit/2011/07/27/jerrold-nadler-d-we-don-t-have-deficit-problem</link><postedTime>2011-07-28T01:38:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-07-28T01:55:56+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/57a0to</id><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/deficit/2011/07/27/jerrold-nadler-d-we-don-t-have-deficit-problem#comment-267151600</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8nldh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-07-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>