<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkprw6/update/2012-03-26T16:10:20/5a1858cb3ab786ba33e27cbf7f3acb91feb53a88d377497dda7052c825123c55</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>To Sparks! 

Ah yes, the long term strategies debate.

I don't know why our Primavera ended up facing  in particular in the finale, but it confirms my posts a couple of months ago about the academies in Europe and what I believe is football evolution in terms of priorities of boards and performances or identities of clubs in today's game. 

If some of you remember my talk about 's title win last season, you'll remember my remarks about the inclusion of home grown/club products in the majority of their squad. I  had this in my head; Barcelona may have the quality, but  have the style... we seem to have a bit of both. 

When you look at , their youth inclusion in the first team is a pattern from years ago. Barcelona have made it a 'choice' especially with Pep by taking advantage of the dutch founders and their style. 

It seems that the irony of fate has made it an obligation for us to use the youngsters who were waiting eagerly for a chance to prove themselves, as they also needed a change of priorities in Italian Clubs. Our last two seasons have proved that our youth academy is a solid investment that showed a clear vision from a man who trained with and under a man who gave Inter &amp; Italy the first 'young Italian' club to win the Scudetto... I speak of Facchetti under the guidance of Bersellini, or at least that is my explanation for the importance of youth Facchetti focused on. 

From my observation, I noticed that five to six players from the  youth team have already participated in the first team this season, and based on the tradition of the Ajax philosophy; some of them will be promoted to the senior squad while others will be loaned out for experience and playing time.

In our case, it bothers me that this task was forced upon our club by age and the necessities of the squad. I still remember last season when a raw and an inexperienced Coutinho was asked to participate in the world's greatest football competition of the Champions League against one of Europe giants Bayern Munich and in Bavaria no less. Coutinho, Natalino, and Obiora were shoved in dire times with the senior team, and they sometimes impressed and in other times they were under the scrutiny of the fans. That situation was a great injustice from the fans because these boys lacked what Santon had of a secure and strong environment under a 'stable' manager in Jose. 

Right now in the Inter World, and especially after the achievement of the Primavera, the supporters will demand the addition of the boys in the remaining Serie A games since the 3rd ticket is, realistically, hard to acquire. My heavens, I want to see them play, but not recklessly or as alternatives for some senior players because it will backfire on their growth. The reasonable thing to do (wish for in all honesty) is to play some of them for 15 or 20 minutes of different games in the second half. These remaining fixtures we have are quite tough considering the league timeline, teams that are fighting relegation will have their emotions high and physical play can be expected, same goes for the teams that are searching for a European Spot. That is why I don't want these boys to be injured like Santon or even like Merkel from Milan. 

The academy boys who are loaned or co-owned with other teams and are impressing and on demand to return are another confirmation that not only our youth policy is solid but that our management is... well slow tbh. 

On the managers choice, I watched a beautiful scene in the Coppa Semi Final between Juve &amp; Milan where the match director took long consecutive shots of Conte between his boys and Allegri standing calm with his players. The images of a young hungry manager are an indication of a positive direction these clubs are taking, and looking at this seasons performances; I believe Montella is the most wanted manager by Italian clubs right now after his very good season with Catania. This is why the Italian press is linking him with teams like Lazio, Napoli and remind the viewers/readers of Roma's mistake of letting him go...

Based on his results and choices, Stramaccioni seems a very promising project for a future manager in Serie A, my fear is rushing him may Burn his chances on the long run with us.

Right now, I'm hungry...</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r7arx</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/y3tx</id></website><link>http://inter.theoffside.com/team-news/juventus-v-inter-liveblog.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-25T17:53:50+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T20:10:20+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkprw6</id><link>http://inter.theoffside.com/team-news/juventus-v-inter-liveblog.html#comment-476699842</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cywfh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>