<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miph8n/update/2012-03-23T23:49:27/dc8b94192d07770f92407a93e2119c62a3f18a843860a1984f3562f91788f63e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Germany can create base load with renewables, because it's using Hydrogen for storage.   

&lt;b&gt;FEATURE-Germany harnesses green power in desolate east:

Start-up firm captures wind power, makes hydrogen&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;The Enertrag plant has been online since October after two years of construction at a cost of 21 million euros ($27.9
million). When the wind blows, its three turbines can generate
up to 6 megawatts of power.

The power is passed through water and split into oxygen and
hydrogen via an electrolyser, which is housed in a supersized
garage and then stored in five tanks. The plant can convert up
to 0.5 MW into hydrogen, producing 12 kg per hour or enough to
power a hydrogen car for 1,200 km.

This technology turns wind into a source of baseload power,
the industry's word for 24-hour supply.  The hydrogen can be mixed with biogas made from local corn waste and fed into cogeneration plants, which produce electricity and Heat. The power can be fed back into the grid at times when little or no wind is available, and the Heat can be fed into a district Heating network. During periods of low wind,the biogas plant can run on biomass alone.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

http://www.reuters.com/article/2012/03/12/germany-power-hydrogen-idUSL5E8DK40P20120312 

The great thing about hydrogen/solar is that it is a "de-industrializing" technology.   Whole categories of polluting infrastructure can be done away with by using simple fuel cells, solar-wind, and storing energy as hydrogen so base load is  there.

The Germans are not alone...Denmark for instance...

&lt;b&gt;Denmark to launch hydrogen infrastructure programme, keep fuel cell vehicle tax exemptions&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;The Danish Energy Plan also outlines a set of government analyses to be conducted to pave the way for continued efforts beyond 2020, with the aim of  100% fossil fuel independence by 2050. The joint focus of the various analyses is to  an optimal linkage between the power/Heat and transport sectors, and  optimal utilisation of the limited biomass potential.

Furthermore, the analyses will suggest solutions for energy storage of the increasing amount of fluctuating renewable electricity, which is to  a 50% share of power and Heat consumption by 2020, and 100% by 2035.

Hydrogen will play a key role in both energy storage as well as connecting the power/Heat and transport sectors. Furthermore, hydrogen can Act as a key component in the production of biofuels and biogas from biomass, thus helping to boost the potential of the limited biomass.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

http://www.renewableenergyfocus.com/view/24734/denmark-to-launch-hydrogen-infrastructure-programme-keep-fuel-cell-vehicle-tax-exemptions/</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66h8al</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/thxi</id></website><link>http://grist.org/renewable-energy/why-germany-is-phasing-out-nuclear-power/</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T18:40:42+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-24T03:49:27+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miph8n</id><link>http://grist.org/renewable-energy/why-germany-is-phasing-out-nuclear-power/#comment-475021676</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8c0a</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>