<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kqzh/update/2012-03-29T22:33:58/20da36d094e817faf708533893fcaa1e506c13887db91b29b42730918b972d12</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I believe you are very ignorant.  Nothing makes sense about anything Zimmerman "has said" nor does any of your racist comments.  
What police/BLET training academy did Zimmerman graduate from to be able to Act like a law enforcement officer?
What neighborhood watch person carries a gun on duty?
When I broke my nose, my nose wouldnt stop Bleeding but he breaks his nose it never Bleeds?
Who says your going to die tonight when someone shows them a gun?
When does police pat you down without gloves and especially when Bleeding?
Why was Zimmerman taken direrctly to the police station instead of a hospital if he was beaten so badly?
Why was a drug test administrated on a dead minor before contacting his parents of the death?
Why is the police department releasing information that would be used in the court..so a judge can throw it out?
Why is it that the offical police report indicates homicide which triggers arrest on site but Zimmerman free to leave?
Why if it was Trayvon that shot Zimmerman, he would have been arrested and still in jail from denied bail?
What is the purpose in stalking a someone who then could have turned to question you and now you claim self defense? If there is a stand your ground law, doesnt this apply to both parties?
Last thoughts, i think Zimmerman knew what he was doing by calling police (since he calls so frequently) so that they would be on his side when they arrived. He was a watchman not an officer or Batman.  He wasnt allowed in the police academy for a reason and now used neighborhood watch as the next best thing.  What young married man volunteers to do neighborhood watch and appoints themself capitan.  I dont believe he is racist, but i definitely believe he has strong biaises against black males.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ztxr5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/us/florida-teen-shooting-sanford-divided/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:29:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:33:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kqzh</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/us/florida-teen-shooting-sanford-divided/index.html#comment-480162037</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zl1q5</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>