<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mrkbtl/update/2012-02-19T03:37:10/ce778f4decba20ac86641bc81dcb1a8f5359e3445dbf7462d0c43961fbab4fe8</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mriwj8</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Wow is right - they ... that is, she ... are ... that is, is ... spectacular. It's all downhill for her from here on, baby! 

(Oh - that's actually true, isn't it? Next, she passes out of the God-dess stage; guest-flashes Letterman; gets caught having done a yuteful, pardon my French, diffusion, on Penthouse that'd make the Virginia legislature Blush; gets cast as a wiggle-on in the latest Will Ferrell spoof; flies to Cannes for the Film Festival only to get outed by Murdoch's Sun in an exposee featuring grainy pictures implying her showing up as a Lady Gaga impersonator at a Berlusconi bunga bunga hoedown on a private island  the Côte d'Azur; gets caught on video doing the horizontal mambo in a cab with some C-list girl-toy band drummer, fresh trampstamp-side up; starts a new gig celeb pitching Abshakers on the HSN; endorses "Rick Romney" for president while on a Santorum Sweater Girl promo; confesses her favorite lyrics are the opening lines to Amy Winehouse's Back to Black; gets caught by the paparazzi driving up to the side gate of the Betty Ford Center claiming she &amp; her friend got "lost looking for the turn-Off to Napa Valley"; marries &amp; divorces the latest country music bad boy all within the same fortnight of living dangerously; campaigns for her Uncle Fred; gets trashed in a NYT feature analysing the GOP's downfall as tracking to the "Bimbo Factor"; does a turn on the Wingnut Welfare Celeb Circuit; closes out the year in pre-promotion of a porn parody, Behind the Red Door.)</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ybmyxj</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tz1k</id></website><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/foxs-bill-oreilly-appears-on-saturday-night-lives-what-up-with-that/</link><postedTime>2012-02-19T05:39:37+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-19T08:37:10+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mrkbtl</id><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/foxs-bill-oreilly-appears-on-saturday-night-lives-what-up-with-that/#comment-443214480</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7zl7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-19</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>