<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0j4ui/post/2012-04-02T03:43:08</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Well, I'm thinking Cialdini and Latane and all those people here.  It is New York.  Diffusion of responsibility.  People don't know one another, you don't know the story behind it.  Incidentally, some of the intro undergrad did a similar study here in Lund, which is, of course, very very very VERY much smaller than New York (and Swedish, to boot).  One of the students carried away a locked bike.  (The hi status/low status didn't seem to matter).  Really, nobody reacted regardless. 

And, thinking about it, it is an ambiguous situation.  I've actually had to saw Off locks on a bike (that was mine), because I forgot the combination.  

Lund is also known as a place where bikes just get stolen.  Might as well have communal bikes it seems....

So, I would conjecture that there are important circumstances that influences this.  I have been at the blunt end of people thinking I behaved against norms here in Sweden (to my actual enragement - one involved not having my then 4 year old son in my lap on the bus, so as to let someone else have a seat - an older person.  Yes, I'm both enraged and embarrassed).  And, this by someone who would not benefit.  A pregnant woman once got upset with me for Coughing away, and not into my hand (ok, so that is not quite altruistic punishment, but, well....)  etc.  So it happens, but this has been in Sweden.  

(Oh, the confessions I do in the name of scientific conjecture)</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6vwj0q</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/frw3</id></website><link>http://www.epjournal.net/blog/2012/04/do-people-punish-altruistically-a-film-by-casy-neistat/</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T06:21:27+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T07:43:08+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0j4ui</id><link>http://www.epjournal.net/blog/2012/04/do-people-punish-altruistically-a-film-by-casy-neistat/#comment-483333690</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cwkf7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>