<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwxsz4/post/2012-03-30T21:07:53</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>SR2011
Rebel optimistic one bullet to prevent the massacre - the real stories of the Revolution Location: City Darya in the countryside of Damascus Time: mid-March, the current 




Days started the day in the life of an ordinary revolutionary Daria.We have put activists final touches Lavtat, and contacts were made ​​the last one who does not have the Internet to locate the assembly using the code complex to understand them completely meeting place and time, but for the listener than normal, was Recently normal. and there was a coordination of another kind also being at the same time with the army free to protect the demonstration planned. The mere existence of those elements, the rare, criminals will just stamens and the barriers preventing them from fishing as a hobby to kill, as is their habit. there were about 15 items from the army to protect the free demonstration, which  a population of hundreds of free and silks Darya. Tacit agreement with the barriers, armed on that day is not out demonstrations on the street year, but With the barrier orders from the army command to shoot, "no choice we have to disobey those orders or kill," he told an officer barrier to the rebels, who seems to have been less criminal than others. began demonstration, chanting revolutionary, and throats, blared pray for the cities under siege and the families of the martyrs, and rained curses on the family and criminal agents. Everything was going according to plan. Demonstration, organized and enthusiastic nicely, and the free elements of the army, even if a few distributors, on the four points of the demonstration.Approached the demonstration of the street and went to the so-called red line agreed upon, but has not traversed. Mobilized elements of the barrier, but the officer asked them not to fire, even with air for fear of misunderstanding and the situation turned into a battle. Indeed, when the barrier is satisfied that the rebels and its components are committed to the agreement, they pulled down their weapons, and continued the demonstration Bfagliatha. But suddenly, there were two buses and several cars loaded with SUV Boqdhir Cbihh types of volunteers and Taúfen, many weapons, machine guns, medium, and  the checkpoint. I got a verbal skirmishes between elements of the armed militia officer and the barrier of understanding that these militia bear responsibility for the barrier and the presence of this demonstration and to collude with them, because they do not shoot. And movements quick, I decided this militia coup against the barrier, which had its elements, along with the officer to move away after they ordered so it seems. began to elements of the militia stationed after disembarking from the bus with lightning speed, and has turned out that the intention is to open heavy fire on each of the demonstration, After the sound of voices Khrthh weapons of all kinds. Free demonstration Taattalawa immediately to free military personnel for the quick advice .. What do we do? Of course the demonstration and members of the military and the free time was not familiar with the detail that they have Srdtha before, they have not realized yet that there is a coup against the barrier by the militia, but calculated that the agreement exists and that these forces officer obeys orders sent from a barrier precaution. But the military sense of the individual members of the army free, Abu Bara, * paid to rapid ascent to the surface of a nearby building to assess the situation on the ground. Abu Bara is a sniper in the military free. out of Abu Bara Guenasth Mkhboha within his clothes, and extend them to the edge surfaces and viewed through Nizarha close. And quickly realized what was happening and the nature of the coup that took place at the checkpoint. It is the way the concentration of the militia turned out to him that she is preparing for a massive offensive on the demonstration. that he gave orders to withdraw the protest, the militia began shooting immediately when you notice the demonstration flight of the demonstrators back to where the militia would remain within the range of seconds long Valharat side narrow and long. Any demonstration that seems to be besieged and took place in the trap. a difficult decision, five of ten free soldier will not be able to withstand more than a hundred armed with various types of weapons, and holed up behind the barrier and buses. There is no doubt that there will be a massacre, Abu Bara realized. Abu Bara to look up his sleeve for longer shots is the tenth time that day, knowing that he knows exactly the number which does not exceed the fingers of one hand ... And think well and decided to put more of those shots brighter in his gun, as if he wanted his best to offer, there is no room for mistake now. I want one fatal blow. look through the telescope close to Venice, so he felt he stands with those monsters. Examine the expressions in their faces sordid, those faces yellowed from fear, that escaped from signs of life came in its place landmarks crime Fabled, as if those faces are criminal records carried the names of the victims of these monsters in every crease of the folds of that mask the human worn on their faces. O Lord, Slmtk myself , guided me to choose, you are throwing, but you're throwing, O Lord, muttered Abu Bara to himself touring Bnizarh between faces dirty to choose from will be held accountable, and wished if his rifle gun so he can stave  those monsters all his family and his neighbors, who did not calm down their throats until that moment, screaming words of challenge ..But he dropped in his hand, and realized that the battle is located, it will not be able to kill more than one person or two people to fall before the massacre. suddenly his attention a militia elements larger in size and Aloqdhir facies. Appeared from his movements that he had ordered them, and they Ahabonh. The development of Abu Bara signal excess of his binoculars on top of that offender, fearing to be wearing a flak jacket. And started heartbeat accelerating show Tremors away signal in excess of the capital offender with every strike the heart, and I swear Abu Bara cut up to us his story that he could hear his heart as if it strikes the drums of war, even feared that expose his place. take the same deep and nestled into a finger trigger and pressing the gun to his shoulder firmly, so that I feel has become a part of him and his anger and his cause. Then disappeared impulses and sent down tranquility upon God, as if a hand gun Rahmanah proved to him, and touched his finger and his heart and tongue together. The second coming Fastmrt an eternity, it has turned villain offender to show his face full in the telescope, as if the hand that Arahmanah-run Abu Bara to see the face of his opponent until your last pulse frequency of the heart. Drew this villain was not human being, but as the land of demons. Abu Bara closed eye for a fraction of a second to say the name of God and God is great, and remembers his mentor guidance to imprison the soul and the  of the trigger .... It issued a sniper that voice has a granular, announces the launch of Hmsh tough bullet to an estimated to be the mistake of confront, followed by the ringing voice of the empty house of the copper bullet that fell next to his foot. Face disappeared from the satanic perspective ...So he went looking for him the right or left, nothing ... Gaal looked away from the telescope, he saw a "stack" between members of the militia. Reconsidered from the telescope, he saw that Cbih a corpse, and did not wrap him one after. seconds long ago until someone realized that the leader had fallen to the ground. But they did not realize after what happened, Abu Bara Vguenash muffled sound. Rushed to his colleagues, we thought of them Akelmanh find that he signed. But when they tried to move it, they found a hole in the head! Alarmed looks and retreated back quickly, then Tlvetoa around them, until one of them realized what happened, and  ... Sniper sniper ... what was the dozens of "brave" and beast of Assad, but all the running direction, they did not know who lurks them how many, and where to shoot silent! Confused tangle, and I started to hear the half-sentences and , and even half-insults, For some reason, they do not complete insult for fear that hear them sniper and punish them! re Abu Bara feed Guenasth shot the other and back and extend them over the fence, Viz monsters almost disappear in buses and cars, Mullen backs quickly exceeded the speed of a fictional Abu Bara Ptgaym his rifle. And pulled out puppies as Ahdnahm, and loud cries of Allahu Akbar earthshaking Darya four pillars! These are my heroes of our adversaries. Bullet one bullet only 5.5 mm and is priced at only $ 8, shook entity hundred people tens of thousands of weapons and bullets. I have to make the God of my father and Bara battalion Rsasth shiny guns, defeated hundred men. But this support is divine what was to come not for the skill of Abu Bara, his training run, his weapon the past, and his determination to do what he could, and then his trust in God. lesson: invest my brothers Baknasat silent battles of the cities, Vuahdtha twenty rifle and more, she does not have a lot of ammunition. Trust in God and in God, let us down, when millions, and our faith are Vslahana Sndna. Rebel optimistic M: This true story recounted to us directly from the source were to Act with some details to protect the hero sniper</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dkvsy</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cjnq</id></website><link>http://blogs.aljazeera.net/middle-east/2011/10/20/syria-live-blog</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T16:11:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T01:07:53+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwxsz4</id><link>http://blogs.aljazeera.net/middle-east/2011/10/20/syria-live-blog#comment-481391946</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l698m</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>