<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mig8dp/post/2012-03-22T15:53:05</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mic0ru</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6onkm</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>The confusion is the refined vs crude oil.

see http://www.econbrowser.com/archives/2011/12/us_net_exports.html 

yes the US is exporting 500k net of refined product but still importing 9ish of crude.  That the US is exporting refined product is a good thing in my mind.  The US has the refinery capacity above domestic needs.  Look at 2007-8 the US was importing a net 2 mil barrels a day of refined product.  

Looking at the latest EIA figures , export refined net 1.2 to 800k  but still importing 7 to 8 mil of crude.  My point would be there is a world price for crude and for refined product.  The US is going to pay that world price.

Sorry I just can't follow your logic. I don't see why net is not the only important figure.  The US generally export diesel as it doesn't use that much compared to other countries.  Also US export refining is centered on Gulf Coast.  So it exports to markets in South America plus the NE US.  The biggest refinery in Canada , which is net neutral in refined products, exports the vast % of its production to US.  In other markets Canada imports for US so overall its neutral.

 "If Brent is going at $127/barrel, why *not* ship out rather than keep it in? "

Well I'm not a midstream guy but Brent is the price on the open Ocean.  What the price would be on the Spot market plus or minus a bit Depending on the transport cost to get it to that port.  So with so little pipeline capacity from Cushing to the Gulf coast the Canadian producers and US producers are getting WTI price which is much less than Brent.  refineries at the gulf coast where most of the oil in US is refined pay Brent.  But all of that is moot because I beleive there is a US law that prevents the export of crude from lower 48.

Any way I'm not angry at all.  I'm just trying to correct a lot of misinformation floating around on both sides.  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y8due</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f047</id></website><link>http://thehill.com/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/217405-obama-to-order-expedited-review-of-keystone-pipelines-southern-piece-other-projects</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T21:31:26+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T19:53:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mig8dp</id><link>http://thehill.com/blogs/e2-wire/e2-wire/217405-obama-to-order-expedited-review-of-keystone-pipelines-southern-piece-other-projects#comment-473887901</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>