<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwwsuk/post/2012-03-31T13:00:59</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwkot5</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/84d7h</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Right dgotshalk, What you say is valid. Israel is advanced and has achieved much that the region can learn from.

But that is a secondary point, and you might be interested in the perspective of natives in region. 

The primary point overshadowing all the nice roads, etc., is that Israel was established by decree (Balfour) and military force dan other violence during the colonial  ,under the heavy boots of a foremost colonial power, Great Britain. At the time, European colonial powers rampaged through the region setting up countries, borders  and rulers to suit themselves. It was not a matter of helping the people they dominated but to control and profit. Among the "useful" polices was to build roads etc. while carefully and thoughtfully doing everything possible to keep the peoples weak, backward and divided. That is standard colonial fare.

Israel is a pure colonial construct. As the colonial and neo-colonial Eras (U.S. is now declining) gradually fade away, it risks being left high an dry in a region in which it has failed to make itself accepted. It continues to maintain injustice and oppression against the Palestinian people which it destituted and is abusing on a daily basis. It continues to apply whatever level of brutality is necessary to deny them their legitimate rights under international law. As an essential adjunct to the brutality, it is very clever with decades of experience and an excellent propaganda machine focused on Western publics, to push the idea that Israel is good and anyone who disagrees is bad. (Your own propaganda is not bad, though I have seen better). 

So thanks for the roads but justice is more important. So israel won 8 wars? (I hope you are not counting Israel's defeat at the hands of Hizbullah in 2006. Israel did not win. As the brilliant Dr.Henry Kissinger said: If the conventional army does not win ,it loses. If the guerrilla does not lose, he wins. But hey, what you want to believe is your business.) Wonderful, it might win more. But it will be the last one that counts.

However, I hope that "bloodier than ever" last war will not be necessary. Israel is a tiny territory with a tiny population and cannot afford to lo Bleed much. I hope Israelis will see the writing on the wall. Iran will shortly have a nuclear deterrent. Then rockets can rain down on Israel at will, which means it will no longer be a functioning sovereign nation-state. 

While there is still time, better recognize all Palestinian rights, including Right of Return. Try to get out of the mess Israel got itself in, in by buying them out with billions and billions. Many fed-up countries would contribute to such a fund. With peace, Israel can enrich itself beyond measure, building roads and and selling other good quality goods and services for the hundreds of millions in the region - and Muslims beyond. That would be a far better future for all.

But Muslims will not sacrifice justice for goods and services. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67mzua</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/h8a5</id></website><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2012/03/201232710543250236.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:49:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T17:00:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwwsuk</id><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2012/03/201232710543250236.html#comment-481998811</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rv97z</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>