<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/276915/post/104218228/comment/329500092</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Business zone ,louis vuitton site officiel figures: China\'s most influential sports stars - the Yao both set thousands of pet-in-one, was criticized; body stalwart like a mountain,sacs louis vuitton, but  under a microscope to look; shoulders carrying the too many people\'s expectations, and still be strong enough to stand the man. From the point of view, Yao Ming is more than a dozen NBA level, but what is certain is that Yao Ming is already one of the NBA\'s best 5% players. [attack] Union to turn around one of the best singles ability,louis vuitton sac, in the inside to turn around and face the separate defense of any person, is guaranteed a strong lethality. Of course, now the league is indeed not very popular back body ... a large body coupled with good sense, Yao Ming has naturally become the best tool for the pick and roll, pick and roll and Barley referees to discuss the issue of law enforcement standards the power is evident. As a result, it leads to sacrifice Yao\'s playing time to enjoy the benefits of the pick and roll. However,sac louis vuitton,moncler outlet Louis Vuitton , Louis Vuitton handb, I believe,sac vuitton woolrich outlet Qianlong - Qianlong wealth - 10, in the struggle with the referee,sac vuitton, there is Always Yao Ming, his early day,louis vuitton sac louis vuitton site officiel Euro, when the ability to master the scales,louis vuitton site officiel, the referee will also become tolerant up. The external lines of Yao Ming assists meager addition to the rocket not enough good outside shooter, Yao being double-teamed, pass levels still need to improve. The biggest deficiency or bit (to deal with around the former defensive) and the ball, but each center should be subjected to the tempering process. [defense] first-class anti-back body ability to rocket inside the barrier,louis vuitton site officiel Latest Games, the defensive core. Limited to physical causes, and never expect Yao Ming to achieve the rebound level of fat, but increase or certainly can. If only the improvement of the experience, but also allows him to more than to grab a few rebounds. Defensive player in moving, Yao Ming,sacs louis vuitton, there are many areas for improvement, such as caps / made the choice of the offensive foul. psychological qualities we can not remember the the Yao critical moment in the fourth quarter mistakes, but also noted his amazing hit rate in the fourth quarter. As a center, Yao Ming is not suitable for the final word in the last few seconds,sacs louis vuitton, but in the early few minutes, his psychological qualities definitely be able to hold up one of the most stable point of the score. [physical] he will need every year to play about 100 games,louis vuitton site officiel, a clear need for long internal forces backing. We can clearly feel the Yao Ming of the absolute physical enhancement in the third year, this can be seen from his end of the season and the postseason. The reinforcement of the power forward, after the decline in their own foul and experience to the level to increase the playing time so it is not so difficult. the on the court,sac louis vuitton sacs louis vuitton So Cold cloud, Yao Ming,sacs louis vuitton, trained hard,sacs louis vuitton,sac vuitton, tenaciously, to improve skills; outside the stadium, his attention to their image and behavior, treat others,sac louis vuitton,sac vuitton, self-discipline. Yao\'s performance, in 2005,sac louis vuitton, he won the honorable title of Yao is becoming more and more tall, and the distance of the people seems to be farther and farther. However, the ad-Star Yao Ming is not on TV every day, nor is it unattainable figure in the Beijing Capital Airport,sac vuitton,sacs louis vuitton, dozens of huge advertising sign. In fact,sac louis vuitton, Yao from our side,sac vuitton,sac louis vuitton, from our most familiar with the CBA. He and our other athletes in the CBA league play with, few people could have predicted his current achievements. It is said that every one of our athletes and Yao Ming, the distance is not far away. Each of our athletes should be like Yao Ming to seriously treat himself and his career,louis vuitton site officiel louis vuitton borse Stand - alone game download, sustained on the sports they engaged in a relentless pursuit. If every athlete can treasure their own, even if you will not become him, you will obtain their satisfaction with the results. sources: the CCTV </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:276915:104218228</id><idPostId>104218228</idPostId><idBlogId>276915</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:276915</id><idBlogId>276915</idBlogId><link>http://www.cinefamily.org</link><displayName>The Cinefamily</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.cinefamily.org/blog/qa-archive-4-combat-shock/</link><displayName>Q&amp;A Archive #4: "Combat Shock"</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-01T21:16:42.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:276915:104218228:329500092</id><link>http://www.cinefamily.org/blog/qa-archive-4-combat-shock/#IDComment329500092</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T21:16:42.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Q&amp;A Archive #4: "Combat Shock" by 51tdg90ja7</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://sacslvfrance2.com</link><idEmailMd5>2ca80ea5c4826aa3ca09a2c16d264bfa</idEmailMd5><displayName>51tdg90ja7</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://sacslvfrance2.com"&gt;51tdg90ja7&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.cinefamily.org/blog/qa-archive-4-combat-shock/"&gt;Q&amp;A Archive #4: "Combat Shock"&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>