<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3wwqg/update/2012-03-30T02:31:58/95d9522811c685886e1bf051a4d9491bab58dc2298031bdef5f57a9455b18ce1</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>2 truckloads of arms seized in Bekaa
Posted on March 29, 2012 by M-BZ12



By: Rakan al-Fakih

MASHARIH Al-QAA, Lebanon – The Lebanese Army seized two truckloads of weapons late Wednesday night in the Bekaa border village of Joura, the latest in a series of  that have caused panic in the region.


Most Masharih al-Qaa residents, fearing Syrian incursions, have fled their homes.

A security source, speaking on condition of anonymity, told The Daily Star that the weapons were concealed in two Cold-storage trucks parked on a back road in Masharih al-Qaa.

No arrests were made during the Lebanese Army , the second since a clash between Syrian government troops and the Free Syrian Army which damaged several Lebanese houses on the border Tuesday.


The  have caused panic in the region, and many residents have fled to settle in calmer areas. According to Saleh Amer, a 50-year-old Joura resident, Masharih al-Qaa had been sheltering around 500 Syrian refugee families until this week’s .

“Following the  in the past two days by the Lebanese Army, dozens of those [Syrian] families have [also] fled the area to look for safe neighborhoods in Arsal and in the southern and western Bekaa and Zahle,” Amer told The Daily Star.

The Masharih al-Qaa villages of Joura and Daura are only 1 km from the Syrian-Lebanese border.

Amer said most of the area’s Syrian and Lebanese residents have decided to abandon their homes, believing that the Lebanese Army cannot protect them from Syrian gunfire.

“We are Lebanese and we have served in the Lebanese Army, but they did not protect us when the [Syrians] fired on our homes,” said 35-year-old Omar al-Radi, whose house was burgled and damaged.

Although officials have denied a Syrian military incursion into Lebanese territory, Radi said Syrian troops entered Lebanon and stole at least $6,000 in cash and equipment from his house. “All we need is safety and we don’t have that here,” he said.

At least five families from Joura, whose homes were hit by Syrian fire in recent days, were seen Thursday packing up their personal belongings and preparing to flee. Earlier this week, Zahra Mohammad Hamid, a 50-year-old Lebanese woman, was hospitalized due to Breathing problems she suffered when a mortar round landed next to her house.

As the number of Syrians fleeing the ongoing unrest has risen in the past few months, there has also been an upswing in security incidents and arrests.

Also Thursday, Military Prosecutor Judge Sakr Sakr accused 21 people of trading arms and smuggling weapons from Lebanon into Syria.

Six of the accused are already in custody, the rest are at large.

Earlier this week, the army arrested 10 armed Lebanese and Syrian men in Joura. They were driving vehicles loaded with weapons including mortar shells, rocket-Propelled grenades and military uniforms. The arrested were interrogated by army intelligence in Ablah in the Bekaa, and the security source said they were referred to the Army’s Beirut headquarters Thursday.

Four injured Syrians crossed into Lebanon Thursday. According to the National News Agency, the Lebanese Red Cross immediately transferred them to Tripoli’s Government Hospital.

The injured were only identified by their initials: M.E., M.A., H.L., W.A, the NNA said.

Although the United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees has reported a total of 8,148 registered Syrian refugees in Lebanon, there are likely many more refugees in the country.

According to a recent report by Lebanon’s Higher Relief Committee, there are some 6,200 unregistered Syrians in various parts Lebanon, putting the total number of refugees at over 14,000.

Source: The Daily Star</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ylh931</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cjnq</id></website><link>http://blogs.aljazeera.com/middle-east/2012/02/05/fighting-back-against-assads-forces</link><postedTime>2012-02-05T09:27:20+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T06:31:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3wwqg</id><link>http://blogs.aljazeera.com/middle-east/2012/02/05/fighting-back-against-assads-forces#comment-480321617</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zlwz2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-05</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>