<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m33gnd/update/2012-03-30T00:20:18/995ac027f376e7012f37c71db67dd6cc4acf950d0566379708ec38347844059d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Pitts is almost Always Spot on, but the essential truth in the Trayvon Martin case is that we don't know yet what the central truth is. An important truth seems to be that Zimmerman followed Martin, at least in part, because he was a black stranger  in a hoodie. Another is that, predictably and knowably, Zimmerman will not be charged, tried or convicted for murder. Another is that even if he was, the real and most devastating and intractable problems of the black community will not even be touched. Young blacks by the hundreds will again die violently in the next year. The  vast majority murdered by other young blacks carrying guns, some wearing hoodies. Neither Sharpton nor Jackson nor the NAACP will have much to say. Black schools serving failed, black families will inevitably  continue to fail. The devastating disaster of unwed pregnancies and single-parent, underclass families will continue unchanged.

As much as anything, the Trayvon tragedy is a diversion from our most substantial and disastrous failures. That may be the essential truth about Trayvon Martin.

RIP Trayvon.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z5r9w</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6rx1</id></website><link>http://www.sltrib.com/sltrib/opinion/53808843-82/martin-trayvon-zimmerman-black.html.csp</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T07:02:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T04:20:18+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m33gnd</id><link>http://www.sltrib.com/sltrib/opinion/53808843-82/martin-trayvon-zimmerman-black.html.csp#comment-480237416</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c82gz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>