<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/es7ou9/update/2012-01-21T01:54:08/5a4326c63ec01386c35cc3007e02d1a39722c37a37e442ce4684a5eab76c7893</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Michael, as a worship pastor in Chicago, my heart resonates with those incredible "we-moments" you describe.  You're exactly right - I  imagine this spiraling column, upward rising, faces of people I know and some I don't yet, but all uniting in truth and love and worship.  My hope is that I can support you in some way to achieve this goal. My wife and I (with our newborn son) don't have much $$ but we'll support you with what we have.  You two are our brother and sister - that's what family is for.

In particular, I'll be proud to be a part of showing of Her beauty and unity in diversity, instead of her flaws.  One reason you're songs feel so familiar to my heart is because of the transparency with which you write about your disappointments with Her.  I've been Burned before, as many people who dig-in to the work of the Church have. And yet there is still that glimmer of hope.  "His bride is STILL alive" and more viral than any YouTube vid.

The body of Christ has this humble way of taking Her lashes and rising from ashes, it's really quite beautiful.  Show Her Off for us, man.  I trust you'll do it very very well.  PS. We'll see you in Wheaton soon! </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yapune</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/bltc</id></website><link>http://gungormusic.com/2012/01/gungor-live-cddvd/</link><postedTime>2012-01-21T01:22:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-01-21T06:54:08+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/es7ou9</id><link>http://gungormusic.com/2012/01/gungor-live-cddvd/#comment-417281750</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-01-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>