<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwl724/update/2012-03-30T12:57:13/0841e2755c5713980daf26fe5dfd665afc2170c8f058fc0a41d9d4a09969fc02</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Last night you had a father on your show that was telling a horror tale of a hospital charging $5,000 for an emergency room visit for a sick child with a Stomach ache. He was condemning the hospital for charging him for tests that he felt was needless (metabolic panel and CBC) and IV fluids that he refused. Why did he bring his child into the emergency room if he didn't want anything done? Why couldn't he have gone to a minor emergency room? The blood work was necessary. The metabolic panel tells the story of what is going on inside the body without having to use radiology or more invasive means. The CBC will show any infection or internal Bleeding. All of this is necessary to rule out serious causes. If he just wanted a doctor to examine her, he should have gone to a non-emergency facility. The father said they brought an IV bag to hang but he refused it because it was a needless expense. Even though it was not hung, there were still the costs of putting in the IV line, the cost of the pump and pole that had to be brought to her room by a staff member and then had to be sterilized for the next patient, the cost of the tubing that had been set up and the cost of the IV bag that had probably been opened.  When it comes to high cost of health care I Always hear about the greedy hospital or the evil insurance co. I never hear any media suggesting that maybe the patients are partly responsible for the problem. Possibly you and your team could do something to bring this into the public's focus. 

I worked in the hospital setting for many years and one of the biggest problems we had were the enormous amounts of patients that come to the emergency room, not because it was an emergency, not because they didn't have insurance, but because insurance would pay better at the emergency room rather than minor emergency clinic or private office. Not only did they swarm in every week-end and holiday, but the other members of the family wanted to be seen also since they were there anyhow. Friday and Saturday nights were quite the social place. Not only did this disrupt the ability to provide immediate care for emergencies, but also effected every department within the system. Every department had to add staff to handle the extra workload which of coarse effects the budget. New facilities had to be constructed to provide services for the non-emergency, emergency room patients. All of this add to the costs of a emergency room trip.
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67dex7</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t33k</id></website><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/2012/03/30/viewer-comment-to-last-nights-on-the-record-at-10pm/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:26:09+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:57:13+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwl724</id><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/2012/03/30/viewer-comment-to-last-nights-on-the-record-at-10pm/#comment-480949506</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>