<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mprr7h/update/2012-03-21T12:31:10/31cc2fc39535a7483e5f613c86361312f2729635c3c193eee1db36d97df29c24</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>So i watched episode 11 even though i said i wouldnt but with me being a huge fan i watched and i must say i am upset with Abby and all the mother including Jill and cathy.

Abby is wrong for just taking melissa's side and not getting all the details from both all the mothers then she goes and yells in the kids faces if she is mad at there mothers you dont take it out on the kids they dont know whats going on or maybe they do because this is reality tv.

Then Holly, Christi and kelly made me upset too because they let Abby get away with it i know they want to keep the peace but as the kids mothers they should have pulled her aside and explained instead of going  making the situtation worst then what is was.

melissa i could go all day on her i am just shocked at her and i know the show made it look worst them what is was but come on now she stop wearing the ring and she didnt think they were going to say anything at all plus she gets mad when they ask about her engagement but she goes and talks with Jill and everything is ok she been knowing the other moms for years and talks to them about everything else but her engagement if Off limits then to have her man send them letters and then pretend like she didnt know about it is just over the top.

cathy is pushing thoses kids to hard to beat Abby and look what happen to one of her dancers she is too much she has some great dancer and maybe if she wasnt so determind to beat abby they would win first place and i blame there mothers to because they are letting her do this.

Jill iis just two faced and will do anything to get Kendall to the top i know she was happy as can be when cathy said she would have to take the other girls Spot n the dance group she could careless that the girl was injured.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dxxmg</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/4cck</id></website><link>http://www.mylifetime.com/movies/node/62760</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T09:03:31+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-21T16:31:10+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mprr7h</id><link>http://www.mylifetime.com/movies/node/62760#comment-472500121</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z2zqa</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>