<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mfvv3c/update/2012-03-15T10:44:34/50de8aaca60552cb05da0f347039c399361f60975e8276dbdd33afc650d88a6e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I'd like to double-down on my nerdiness for a moment and talk about The Simpsons.



In the episode 'The Prince and the Pauper', the citizens of 
Springfield-- and the audience-- learn that the man known as Principal 
Seymour Skinner is, in fact, an imposter.  The real Seymour Skinner 
returns to reclaim his identity, but eventually the town decides they 
like the old Seymour better and run the real Seymour out of town.  At 
the end of the episode the townspeople agree to pretend the events of 
that story never happened, effectively retconning that episode (other 
than one callback, seasons later).



It was a hated episode for many people who watched the earlier seasons 
of The Simpsons.  Matt Groening himself disliked it, and still does.  
The more direct creators of the episode, the writer and showrunners, 
defend it.  They say it was meant as a commentary on how people dislike 
change and react violently to disruptions to the status-quo, and that 
the feelings of the audience were meant to mirror the feelings of the 
characters in the show.  It sounds rather clever at first Blush, but it 
fails to encompass what that episode did to the universe of the show. 



'The Principal and the Pauper' called into question all the previous 
actions of 'Principal Skinner', given the context that he was a man 
 a role he felt obligated to play.  His willingness to surrender 
his life to the 'original Skinner' calls into question his motivations 
and true feelings.  To the audience, a character who has been molded 
over nine seasons has just become strange and suspect.  The audience 
reacts not just to the change contained in the episode, but also the 
effect the episode has on what came before.  To point at the audience 
and say 'Hah, I'm lampooning your fear of change!' comes across as a 
shifting of criticism that doesn't fully address what has actually 
happened.  However good your intentions, you're striking a blow against your audience and your fictional universe.



To point at Mass Effect 3 and describe it as a clever commentary on the  nature of human life puts me in mind of the reaction to episode.  Even if this game was marketed as a jumping-in point for new players, its core audience is people who have played the previous games.  Time has been taken to commit the player to the characters, the concepts, and feel of the Mass Effect universe.  Throughout the series, emphasis has been put on player control.  'Look,' says the marketing team, 'your choices are persistent between games through save files!'  References are put in to acknowledge the player's agency and will: 'Hey, remember the time you blew up X instead of Y?'  Even if many of the choices in the third game are fairly shallow (will you get +5 Krogan Power or +5 Salarian Power?) they still play into that concept.  

Ultimately, none of it matters.  Press a button, get an ending.  If life is Fleeting but decisions meaningful, then why are decisions not reflected in the finale?  What effect did the past two games really have?  Why must the galactic community we've come to know and love make nearly the same sacrifice as the Protheans before?  Are we expected to believe that not just individual lives are futile, but all life?  If that truly is the final message of the game, it's a payoff far outweighed by the cost.  It's not commentary on human existence; it's a sucker-punch 5 years in the making.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/65yi4q</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/j0bv</id></website><link>http://killscreendaily.com/articles/reviews/mass-effect-not-what-you-thought/</link><postedTime>2012-03-15T09:40:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-15T14:44:34+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mfvv3c</id><link>http://killscreendaily.com/articles/reviews/mass-effect-not-what-you-thought/#comment-466022055</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zaki7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-15</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>