<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mshavz/update/2012-03-27T14:13:16/a638a2f54389328d04d1091be99d2b45c4cb652afaaefd9fd5dfc54f7580a1b6</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mslt9f</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/htr93</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I think Brainwashed people like you are the one to sociopathic are unable to see the reality beyond their Noses. No civilized  country in the world dude..will allow Armed Gangs/Terrorist to run freely on cities with machine guns ,Bombs and rocket grenades. NO ONE..Not even if their intention is to defend anything!!!  NO coutnry in the world will allow armed terrorist to kidnap civilians. if they were really Noble in their actions they will NOT take their fight to cities risking the lives of civilians.. even less plant Bombs to the infrasestructure ,Railroads or Oil Pipelines ,Burning schools ,churches and kidnapping and killing Businessmen..This that greatly affect the quality of life of civilians. So you YES YOU.. pay attention carefully at the video link provided . So you can see Terrorist in action kidnapping civilians.. so later ASSAD army is blamed for it.. thats because EVERY CIVILIAN DEATH IS ALWAYS BLAMED ON ASSAD.. by the Human Rights terrorist and people like you..So  US and NATO have civilians blood in their hands with the weapons ,money and intelligence they supply to terrorist.. to destroy the country and blame government for the kills . Not all the opposition is like you. some have chosen to drop the weapons and join the government reforms and create political parties. but unfortunately there are still terrorist like you. that do not care for innocent lives..  google or yutube for..

-
FSA Terrorists Commit Massacres in Homs/ZghiMccnM28
-



</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l7ouz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/27/world/meast/syria-unrest/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T07:30:20+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-27T18:13:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mshavz</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/27/world/meast/syria-unrest/index.html#comment-477619358</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zcuv3</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>