<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw1w81/post/2012-03-31T00:36:41</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Well, here’s the thing. People say that green house gases, specifically
carbon dioxide, causes global warming. They claim that we put that carbon
dioxide in the air solely by Burning carbon based fuels.



Well, I have another theory. Our cities have food shipped to
them from the farms. The people eat the food and a great deal of the waste goes
into the river, estuaries, and the ocean. Now the ocean is the greatest
sequester to carbon dioxide on the planet. Most of this carbon dioxide is
captured by the ocean in the form of calcium carbonate. We see this in the huge
deposits of sedimentary rock we call, lime stone, made by little sea creatures
over the ages. However, our oceans have been effected by the huge discharge of
sewage into the oceans.



We can see this by looking at the large areas of anoxic
zones found around populated area. These zones are also call dead zones. These
dead zones are cause by chemicals run  from the where algal blooms deplete
the oxygen causing hypoxic zones. Within the hypoxic zones anaerobic
bacteria changes the water to a stew of acidic sulfides solutions which changes
the basic chemistry of the oceans. These changes inhibit the growth of the
little critters that sequester the carbon dioxide. We can see this by the
general decline in the coral reefs around the world. The oceans aren’t sucking
up the carbon dioxide like they should.



And so, the farmers fertilize their farms and it runs into
the oceans; the produce is shipped to the cities where people change it to
sewage and the rich organic discharge goes into the oceans. Thus we create dead
zones killing Off the creatures that sequester the carbon dioxide; the un-sequestered
carbon dioxide is then released into the atmosphere causing at least some part
of the increase of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere.



There have been huge volcanic eruptions in the past that
show healthy oceans can absorb more carbon dioxide than we even put into the
atmosphere today through the Burning of carbon based fuels. Unfortunately, we
no longer have healthy oceans. I believe the problem is more than just Burning
carbon based fuels. If we stop all Burning of fossil fuels today, we’d find that
our atmosphere would still have increasing carbon dioxide levels.



Today's air has a higher carbon 14 factor than it should have; fossil fuels should have a low carbon 14 content. This factor may have been cause by other pollution sources or it may be the carbon dioxide in the air is newer than many think.

Whatever you might think, we’re just going to have to find a better way of taking care of our planet.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hold1</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/b703</id></website><link>http://www.bigthink.com/dr-kakus-universe/welcome-to-the-solar-era-followed-by-the-fusion-era</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T19:41:25+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:36:41+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw1w81</id><link>http://www.bigthink.com/dr-kakus-universe/welcome-to-the-solar-era-followed-by-the-fusion-era#comment-481534080</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>