<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msw59l/update/2012-03-28T14:03:00/6090cf1200d649d000c36221882e7f7780e8d0ce73187b1663e3468c8c33840f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Why tear down existing mansion? It smacks of Romney's mindset of buying factories to demolish 'em
In the 1980s a friend of mine sold his house in LaJolla, CA- MOVED IT  the lot, bought a custom home blocking a freeway and MOVED IT onto the lot- It cost more to move it ($27K) than the 10cents on the dollar he paid to buy it ($17.5K) Now he has a 3 level home w/a rear garage (had to split it into 3 pieces to move it- part of cost was to clear the way of overhead power lines in addition to modified lot foundation for split levels)

Knowing this- why would Romney tear down a perfectly good mansion when it could be moved? 
Says a lot about how Romney- NO CLUE that the watchword for 21st century will be EFFICIENCY
just a "slash and Burn" mentality of corporate  for profit that he did for BAINE Capital-
Google "When Mitt Romney came to town" to see his track record, understand how he operates
He'll make sure the "Game is Rigged" when it comes to spreading the wealth among the wealthy

Mitt Romney is what I'd call a "Pump and Dump" Capitalist Corporate Raider
Happens in the stk mkt again and again- a stk is promoted until it  a peak then its dumped.
Baine Capital went one step further- buy a company, saddle it with debt, then sell it into bankruptcy
In short, Mitt Romney is just a typical god-damned Wall Street CROOK who's MadOff w/$$

On the other hand since it takes one to know one, its better to have a Wall Street Crook in the W.H.
than a community organizer who just thinks in terms of "spread the wealth" and non-consequential thinking- Ex- Solandra went bankrupt, no one is buying Electric cars weighed down by  and no one is promoting abundant natural gas to fuel autos, nor has anyone done a hybrid deisel/electric
Using corn to fuel cars with ethanol has our cars competing with us for foodstuffs, driving up food cost

Finally, N0 ONE even mentions reinstating the 1937 Uptick Rule that Bush SEC removed on 7/7/7
Why it that important? It was the LYNCH-PIN holding up the housing bubble- As soon as it was gone
Wall Street Banksters shorted the housing mkt into the ditch, transferring wealth of 90% of middle class to top 10% wealthy Americans by Raiding US treasury to cover "Toxic Assets" created by shorts</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l9jkw</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gblz</id></website><link>http://www.newser.com/story/comments/142793/romneys-mansion-to-have-elevator-for-cars.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T16:58:16+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T18:03:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msw59l</id><link>http://www.newser.com/story/comments/142793/romneys-mansion-to-have-elevator-for-cars.html#comment-478603380</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/aybni</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>