<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkdxyj/update/2012-03-25T05:41:50/05bbe97f4dedc602684c035445ab964cfc6833aa6f0fa095eadf2ce7d400783e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Sounds good for somebody that "hardly ever" makes an out. It also makes me happy that he (apparently, judging by the Rangers hat he was Spotted wearing) likes the Rangers as opposed to, say, NYY, which for some reason seems to be far and away the "favorite" MLB team of people outside the U.S.

I really hope the deal goes through on this. It'll probably be one of the last times (unless the CBA is changed again) the Rangers will be able to utilize the competitive advantage they've worked hard on for several years now. They &lt;em&gt;could&lt;/em&gt; be spending the money on the best free agent(s) available, as the Yankees have done often in the past and the Angels did this year, but instead they've chosen the long-term productive investment, and it's paid Off handsomely so far. It still irks me that they're going to effectively neuter that. It sounds like they want to encourage teams to either go for the money dump truck (a la NYY, LA) or the Moneyball approach (several teams now). And I like the Rangers' M.O. and I'll be a bit miffed when that strategy becomes a fringe source of talent. Grrr.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66pm8o</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zrdy</id></website><link>http://www.bbtia.com/home/2012/3/24/the-jairo-beras-plot-thickens.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-24T14:36:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-25T09:41:50+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkdxyj</id><link>http://www.bbtia.com/home/2012/3/24/the-jairo-beras-plot-thickens.html#comment-475732143</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>