<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mse4a9/update/2012-03-27T06:39:10/f320f6af921f089df2da7791a02a67bc535ad02d38f02b81f65ba8b6525742dd</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkju7q</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/r71bq</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>
I mean kvips once  "Nyongtory" and all the members reacted negatively. And this is just an example. There're tons of cases similar to this.  


Noy only "Nyongtory", there existed "TopNyong" "TopTory" "TopSung" "SunSung(=SungBae)" "SunTory" "NyongSung" "NyongSun" "SungTory" "TopSun"... 


And they caused many problems and tons of troubles between kvips, it's impossible for me to explain every case and give u all the proofs here. I can say there'a long history about this and kvips learned from experience and agreed to stop using them. 


(But few ppl're using them in the shade, in the fanpic sites) 


And I didn't mean to change the culture of ivips. I was just embarassed to see those names here and I was curious if it came from the korean fanpic culture. It's up to you whatever you do, but I wanted to tell you the experiences of korean BB fandom. 


But I apologize if I was rude to you... frankly I was too upset, I was upset because of those words, not because of you Ivips. We were repulsed by the words... It's hard to explain but most of kvips would feel the same... we had a bad history about those words but  I didn't consider how you would feel... SORRY. I needed to be more careful and considerate... 


 


kvips used those couple names in both way. Only a few ppl used it for "Yaoi" fantasies, most of us used it for describe ''bromance'' too. 


But it cause many troubles between the kvips. Even a few wicked used it for bashing other members they don't like... producinging hurting fanpics, etc. Many kvips're hurt sometimes because they didn't like dividing the members itself, sometimes because they support other combinations of couple shipping different from the combination  that others/majorities support. Tons of problems existed above this... Plz don't ask me more... I have a Headache :'( 


It was an obstacle for the vips' unity.  


Both GD x Seungri, TOP x Daesung have been Spotted holding like hands while walking at the airport? I'm sure they're  to show they're so much familiar to the individual fandoms. For example GD fandom and Seungri fandom're not on terms of harmony. Actually all the 5 fandoms're not in good relationships.. it's really sad. 


Of course most of vips support them all but there's  a bit troubles between the fandoms by a few ppl. Don't ask me more.. it also has a long history.. I have a Headache XD 


Q: 


k-netizens ever accused the boys of being like actually gay or just shippers did who want them together? Is that why they reacted like that? 


&gt;&gt; 


I think BB members're aware of the problems and they hate it because they're not. They wanted to be mischievous randomly like by kissing other members, but they didn't want to be treated as a gay by others.  


Q: 


When did we stop it? It's hard to say exactly when. There's Always been self-reflections about it since their debut... and kvips agreed gradually from one fansite to the whole sites in public.  


Now I regret to comment about it here. It's really hard-working to reply one by one. I didn't expect so many ivips would show interest 
"CRY CRY* Thanks :) 



 



</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rkgpf</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/g1xx</id></website><link>http://www.bigbangupdates.com/2012/03/daesung-said-physical-appearance-is-not.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T12:22:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-27T10:39:10+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mse4a9</id><link>http://www.bigbangupdates.com/2012/03/daesung-said-physical-appearance-is-not.html#comment-477314270</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>