<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3f9h4/post/2012-03-29T17:03:26</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3uypv</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h4iry</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Willie's link isn't to a 'news article', but a blog post from the Charleston WV Daily News from last October by Don Surber who, to put it mildly, has a political agenda. That political motivation becomes clear beginning with the headline,  "GAO: 42% of temperature gauges in U.S. are wrong".  My first reaction was "Uh oh, that's bad", which was probably the intended reaction.  But after reading the article, I realized that the GAO report says nothing of the sort. The GAO did not question the temperatures recorded by the gauges. What the report noted was that NOAA had established standards for what it considered ideal siting for the gauges - away from buildings, air conditioning vents, water tanks, etc. But, "in part because NOAA 
officials considered other factors, such as geographic distribution and a
 long history of records, to be more important", not all stations met all of the siting standards.  Welcome to research in the real world - you can't Always get the test conditions you want, but if you design your study right, you might get the data you need.

There is nothing I can find in the article that says the stations are not accurately recording the actual temperature of the air around them, just that some of them, roughly 42%, are not ideally placed.  Using some advanced mathematical calculations, I conclude that nearly 2/3 (58%) fully met the ideal siting standards NOAA established. It might be quite possible to run statistics on just that group to see what those results look like compared to the full sample.

But it really doesn't matter, because the research topic is climate, not weather. NOAA is not researching if it is advisable or not to wear a sweater today, but whether there are changes in average temperature over time. I presume this is done by comparing the data produced by the temperature gauges (what ever happened to 'thermometers'?) at specific intervals in time.  So if a particular gauge, because it is situated close to a building that reflects Heat, registers an average for 2005 of 23c instead of the 'actual' temperature of 22c a few feet away, it has no impact on the research question being explored. If it then shows an average temperature of 24c five years later, while the 'actual' temperature is now around 23c (ish), that would be one data point in support of the warming hypothesis. Spread this out over hundreds of gauges, 58% of which don't have any siting issues, and you start to have enough data to test hypotheses

Personally, I am very skeptical about any particular scientific study.  That's kind of required in science, and is what distinguishes the scientific method. I'm pretty sure that's why climate researchers shifted from 'global warming' to 'climate change' to describe their long-term data, because the data showed warming trends in some places, cooling trends in others, and not-yet-evident patterns in others. For some reason, stubbornness of opinion in the face of contradictory data has become considered a virtue in some circles recently. But that isn't skepticism, it's fantasy.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hsnsf</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/b0vv</id></website><link>http://www.insidehighered.com/node/36769</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T22:50:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T21:03:26+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3f9h4</id><link>http://www.insidehighered.com/node/36769#comment-479891142</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/82odv</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>