<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3frp6/post/2012-03-29T16:44:38</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31otp</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hu9u5</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>"BS. It's just personal opinion."

When you say that Austin wasn't as over it's not "personal opinion" it's wrong. 

"Rock was booed at Wrestlemania 17 cause it was Stone Colds back yard, but he wasn't in the build up to the match."

Uh, there was a build up to the match, and a good one at that. The Raw before it with their brawl as well as the "you can't touch each other" rule was great. And you missed the point of what I said.

If Rock was REALLY as over as you say he'd have been  at the event, regardless of where it was. Even if the  were only small in comparison. He wasn't.

"The majority of fans liked them both cause they were both great, it's hard to tell by crowd reaction cause Rock was a heel in the early fueds and then later on Ausin was in the alliance and they didn't cross that often really."

Yes, I liked both as well, but Austin was  more over. And it's not hard to tell. Rock was turned from a Heel to Face by the fans who  his persona, yet he was  booed against Austin. Austin  had the biggest  and chants, compare them with Rock's and you can tell who was more over.

"When Austin became the main man he was very popular, he got the big fued with Mcmahon and probably 99% of the audience liked him but when Rock comes in and they are against each other it's impossible for either to get 99% support cause they are both super popular."

Austin did at 17. Austin when he faced Rock, no matter the circumstances was  more over. When he tagged with him, he got more . Whenever the two were together Austin was  more over than Rock. Austin was the face of the , it only makes sense. Austin was the better one, or Rock would have taken his place.

 "But there's no doubt Rock was mostly the main man as soon as he peeked and since 2002 to this day Rock can probably draw more in my oppinion"

Well you'd be wrong. Rock peaked in 99-2000, Austin wasn't around for one of those years and Rock got booed out of the building at WM17, that should show who was more over. Austin was THE MAN until he had to stop wrestling due to injuries and passed the torch to Rock at Mania. Yet during the years Rock was on top, which wasn't very long as he left for  soon after he was never the draw Austin was. He was certainly not as over either.

While a lot of it has to do with the Fad ending when Austin left the title scene Ratings went down. Rock couldn't keep them up.

And still, Austin Always outsold(for the vast majority of the time) and outdrew Rock. You can't have an opinion with numbers, there are only facts.

"that's why it was Hogan vs Rock that doesn't make him better it just comes down to who appeals to you more. Just be grateful we had both of these guys, they made each other better. "

I am grateful. I happen to think Austin vs Hogan would be better. Sure, that part is opinion, but look at it this way:

The two greatest wrestlers and biggest draws ever in the same ring together. The two icons of the sport and leaders of their generation in one match. Who is the REAL best?

I think that would have sold a lot better than Rock vs Hogan, especially when Austin Vs Hogan was initially built up first, and some of the build for Rock Vs Hogan was ridiculous, like the part with the Semi Truck and the ambulance. That wouldn't have gone down on Austin's watch, he would have taken on the NWO by himself and then had an epic brawl and match at Mania.

But we'll never really know.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z4pf5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cq26</id></website><link>http://www.wrestlezone.com/news/252207-jerry-lawler-reveals-his-favorite-wm-match-to-call</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:24:00+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:44:38+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3frp6</id><link>http://www.wrestlezone.com/news/252207-jerry-lawler-reveals-his-favorite-wm-match-to-call#comment-479872270</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lqpgm</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>