<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi8rtf/update/2012-03-22T13:11:18/989bb30695e0cb88e41c02ccbf37f4e385a5f28018f9fbb08ffd395573e30c81</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This is So Sad in Everyway of the word SAD. I turned on my computer the other day and seen this on it. So I looked and heard the 911 dispatcher clearly state to Zimmerman "Are you FOLLOWING the Suspect"  Zimmerman " YES" Dispatcher " Ok, I dont need you to do that, DON'T FOLLOW THE SUSPECT" Never at anytime did you hear Zimmerman say I am or I think I am or anything such as Im in danger.. This was a clear case of: I have a permit for a gum anything that moves Black Im shooting but let me call and cover myself first. His friends and family said " He (zimmerman) is not a bad person he must have been scared" Of what I ask?? Trayvon was half his size Dry. The dispatcher said on the tape "Stay in your Car" Where was he so scared at?? Zimmerman got out of his car an confronted Trayvon in which Trayvon Started running away from Zimmerman, Zimmerman then followed him running around screaming "Help Me" from the top of his lungs,(Im still waiting to see or hear where was Zimmerman in Fear if he chased Trayvon) which can be heard on the 911 tape As Well. Only Good thing about this whole thing is that even though No One went out to help him (Which Is Totallly Sad) they called at the right Moment when Trayvon was screaming out for "Help Me" and when Zimmerman shot him. I'm totally Upset at the fact that if it was a White Young Man we would not be signing this petiton. Because they would of arrested the Balck Man on the Spot No QUESTIONS ASKED he would of been Guilty.. No Jugde, No Jury, Just Guilty Fare Trial MyBehind..I have one more thing to say to the family and friends of Zimmerman the legal term for self defense is as followed:
THE RIGHTTO PROTECT ONE'S PERSON, OR MEMBER OF ONE'S FAMILY, AND, TO LESSER EXTENT, ONE'S PROPERTY, FROM HARM BY AN AGGRESSOR. THE ESSENTIAL ELEMENT OF SELF-DEFENSE MUST BE FREE FROM FAULT, MUST "NOT" SAY OR DO ANYTHING FOR THE PURPOSE OF PROVOKING A DIFFICULTY, NOR BE UNMINDFUL OF THE CONSEQUENCES IN THIS RESPECT OF ANY WRONGFUL WORD OR ACT. LAW DICTIONARY SIXTH EDITION BY STEVEN H. GIFIS, PG. 490
Now Please let me know where was he in DANGER as you would state.. DONT WORRY I'LL WAIT...
FROM A GRADUATE FROM T.C.I COLLEGE (NYC) IN PARALEGAL STUDIES.. IF THE LAWYERS NEED HELP IN THIS CASE PLEASE CONTACT ME @ MS.SUNDAYJ.SMITH@HOTMAIL.COM I AM WILLING TO TRAVEL TO HELP WITH THIS CASE....</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dw4sw</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rpuk</id></website><link>http://www.colorofchange.org//blog/2012/mar/21/colorofchange-members-share-comments-trayvon-marti/</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T18:33:30+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T17:11:18+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi8rtf</id><link>http://www.colorofchange.org//blog/2012/mar/21/colorofchange-members-share-comments-trayvon-marti/#comment-473759917</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>