<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms95q8/update/2012-03-28T06:14:38/e1f0e42879e6543a2cd4eea0eb7ef04066e2cd01169d0be8180601a06873bd51</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms72k8</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8m5ma</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> I am offended every day by reality shows reminding me of primates and "Lord of the Flies," people driving cars with boom boxes so loud the paint is peeling  the car, and people yammering on endlessly about a fictional spook in the sky controlling their every move that, for some reason, I will Burn in Hell for all eternity if I do not agree with them.  I am offended by the way most people dress in public - the average American dresses like he Raided the rag bin.  I wouldn't attend a dog fight dressed the way some people show up in public.  I am offended by rap music when classical is available.  I am offended by the schlocky .mp3 music quality when people no longer know of the concept of music fidelity.  I am offended that Americans will buy quantity over quality every time.  I am offended people won't spend 5 minutes considering the other side of an opinion.  I am offended most people are mindless sheep.  I am offended by many things.

That said, I do not in any way deny people their civil rights to be who they are, dress the way they will, listen to whatever they call music, or practice whatever religion they so choose.  If they find that slop served at an Americanized Chinese buffet palatable instead of real Chinese food - have at it.

So, amconservative, I would say "get over it."  Unless they are scaring the horses, this is a free country.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lp3qj</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dngw</id></website><link>http://bangordailynews.com/2012/03/27/opinion/wednesday-march-28-2012-gay-marriage-the-labor-mural-and-cremation/</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T19:22:40+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T10:14:38+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms95q8</id><link>http://bangordailynews.com/2012/03/27/opinion/wednesday-march-28-2012-gay-marriage-the-labor-mural-and-cremation/#comment-478229870</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/u6nm</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>