<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/meoxwi/update/2012-02-09T21:42:02/348093059ff8135e2a4d5e841ad0081f45c8f76a695e73bbdafa0ae51f834fc3</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>good they are fu*ing disgusting.    in front are all chemically treated toxic lawns. there are no plantings. nothing is natural..they are an eyesore....and they are same looking in any city in the US like walmart....they are basically screaming out we hate nature and hate everything...also typically out front are also so the ubiquitous hummer etc..or some other pretentious human hating garbage, at least in my giant neighborhood next door screaming out we dont want to be a part of your neighborhood so it is blocked  in giant unconnected roundabout/cul-de-sac which the town tried to not even have to plow because it is so poorly built and disconnected from rest of neighborhood and built on a swamp and just paved over......and now all homes in it are for sale and half lots not even developed they were so poorly built and every home looks identical to picture above down to chem treated lawn....

I do know people who live in these horrible blighted 'developments' who were foolish and state they wish they had not fallen for scam of being like the joneses and are trying to move. I know others who sold at a huge loss as in half the price they paid just to get the he!! out of there.

mcmansion neighborhoods in deep south from which I got the hell out of have these things everywhere like mushrooms and all have fake name like something something 'farms since they are all built on top of farmland.

friends who live there dont even know the name of their neighbors. they are built in such a Cold unfriendly fashion to even make you not know your own neighbor like mini walled Off castles.

in short these things are a disgusting blight on our civilization and a mistake during housing boom once again directly related to greed and short term profit of flip it developers.....now YOU'RE stuck with it and need to learn your lesson not have all taxpayers bail you out...which is the other boondoggle....prolonging and exacerbating our decline. and preventing any lessons from being learned by anybody....apparently the moral of modern amerika...get bailed out learn nothing and blame everybody else for your mistakes while denying reality of climate change peak oil food scarcity and lack of water....for as long as you poss. can!!!!!!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/y7vq68</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/thxi</id></website><link>http://grist.org/list/america-has-40-million-big-houses-that-no-one-wants/?postpost=v2</link><postedTime>2012-02-09T16:12:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-10T02:42:02+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/meoxwi</id><link>http://grist.org/list/america-has-40-million-big-houses-that-no-one-wants/?postpost=v2#comment-434675766</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rfe4y</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-09</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>