<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/e6v7ui/update/2011-12-06T10:56:04/4419d0bf5a7273bee9ec98599837b19277f9cde06d87334f4b24bca7e133c991</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Unbelievable,I do most of these signs, when you smile at the communication of simple conversation and you giggle or grin, that is what happens to your face .Try it giggle right now you ears go back your eye brows rise and your corner of your mouth rises and extends. And of course your eyes light up it puts a twinkle in your eye because you are happy or laughing at the comment or situation! Then it drops immediately! Are you guys nuts?Inconsistent talking, I am ADHD according to some i can go from being very precise and detail, to stuttering a word that wont come out quick enough ! you guys are hilarious..Coughing covering my mouth when i cover my face ? I have asthma, and this time of the year with the Cold triggers and the allergy's it happens very quickly, i Cough and cover my face as soon as i can and try not to Cough on you, while i am Wheezing or clearing my throat.I am also a very intelligent person as are most people. In my instance when i do depositions to help people on the stand, we are told to look the judge in the eye and stay focused, for me that is so uncomfortable its not funny and it triggers i am either not telling the truth or i am a liar and i will be discredited because of my actions..I look away because I focus on the detail of what had happened in the question being addressed to answer to the courts as to get it right and truthful in detail? If I am talking to you and I multi task as many people do. If you look around at everyone in the court room after you answer the question you are putting up a red flag to determine whether or not they believe in what you just said..what the heck , it goes for the same you tell a story to a few friends in a bar or at a dinner meeting and you lok around to see if they believe you or not? If you constantly look in there eyes as you are telling it , that is distrust or a red flag because i need your trust.. really ... look away no stare no look away no don't stare you are insane..how did this get printed? This is like Saturday morning cartoons.. The bugs bunny ,Road runner hour, remember ! Beep Beep My A.. Just be your self every one has gut instincts and people are usually really good judgments of character and when they doubt themselves as we all do at times its ok we txt our friends or call our buddy's and say can  what did you think of the story at the dinner table.. Always fun conversation and pleasant even if the speaker is not Albert Einstein, just be your self and enjoy the people around you even with our faults thank goodness we have them to make it real..S</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/dahuvb</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/vkyn</id></website><link>http://news.menshealth.com/spot-insincerity/2011/11/28/</link><postedTime>2011-11-28T07:39:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-12-06T15:56:04+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/e6v7ui</id><link>http://news.menshealth.com/spot-insincerity/2011/11/28/#comment-380360010</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rpoa6</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-11-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>