<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nnuo/update/2012-03-29T12:58:09/51fa05e308d68df2e7e58db5eebe281113c61ff0f185f23096b6a94fa0f01f78</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>It's the leftwing activism parading as science that is the problem.

They shut down the North Western National Forests to logging in order to protect the Spotted Owl back in the early 1990s. It turns out that the Spotted Owls real problem is the Barred Owl, which is killing them  by displacement. It turns out that logging had little impact, because the Spotted Owls would just move if their homes got logged. Now, in defiance of natural selection and in the cause of misplaced preservationism, they are going to shoot the Barred Owls. Maybe they could hire some of those laid  loggers and mill workers to shoot the Barred Owls.OOPS! That screw up was led by The Audobon Society. Lots of science guy in there I bet.

Attempts to "cook" environmental stdies in order to use the EPA to shut  access to land use. "The fraud was discovered when a U.S. Forest Service employee informed supervisors that five federal and two Washington State researchers had planted endangered lynx hairs in areas where the animals did not exist... After learning of the allegations, the Forest Service conducted tests of the allegedly planted hairs and determined the hairs matched those of a lynx living in an animal preserve and of a pet lynx belonging to a federal employee...Had the fraud not been exposed, the planted lynx hairs could have led to sweeping land restrictions against property owners, recreationists, and workers in the affected regions. Among the potential restrictions are  on skiing, snowmobiling, driving, logging, and livestock grazing." 

There have also been attempt to transplant endangered plants into areas where they never were in order to invoke the Endanger Species Act to halt development. Or how about when they declare a mud puddle after it rains a "wetland" to shut down land use? Environmental science is allegedly involved in decisions like that too.

See also: Anthropogenic Global Warming Hypothesis and climate alarmism in general that procedes from argument by authority, rather than studying all the evidence.

Environmental scientists are their own worst enemy as alot of them are into the field to push agendas, rather than do science. They abuse their authority and credibility and then wonder why conservatives, who are inherently distrustful of rule by technocrats and the self appointed, don't trust them.

</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hsnsf</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/b0vv</id></website><link>http://www.insidehighered.com/node/36769</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T22:50:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:58:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nnuo</id><link>http://www.insidehighered.com/node/36769#comment-479650456</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gl0hf</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>