<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjg25/update/2012-03-26T14:14:32/18d904842e7fe29f5bd82638056fd67dce85e5ea08a738a23295a65e6890b032</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The owners are but business men who treasure success in the field as it shows that they are getting a return for their money, but KD had to have conditions when he decided not to guide the ship but run it aground.
1-He was set the same requirements as any manager who was likely to takeover, CL, one or two cups [tbh I do not think we will even win the FA]
2-He got the finances to facilitate the objectives laid out by the owners, and went on shopping spree for dross
3-His excuses about our loses have become even more bizzare as each game passes-by, kits, Tiredness, injuries, the ex-players who were quick to nail Hodgie and Rafa, are suddenly quite timid, cannot criticise KD
4-His lack of game flow-awareness is bizzare for a player who was well above most for the Reds, team selection is another Headache, 
5-Sending some of our accomplished players to the bench or out on loan is amazingly stupid after buying squad &amp; future players and completely rejecting our youth reserves
6-His brutal defence of his failure sends Shivers down all true Reds, jornos and the owners, they will make a decision to let him go soon, with all our blessings.
As one of us pointed out we really need a replacement, we all experienced the murmuring after the game, with supporters walking Off, after KD insulted some of us supporters for being brain-dead.
Enough is enough, he should go just like any other manager who has failed to attain basic managerial targets, we should be looking for another  manager, the process has already started if the owners mean business.
LETS STOP KIDDING OURSELVES - NO MAN IS BIGGER THAN LFC - EVEN KENNY.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rprgd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gfg</id></website><link>http://www.liverpool-kop.com/2012/03/arsenal-legend-insists-two-cups-is-not.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T10:36:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:14:32+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjg25</id><link>http://www.liverpool-kop.com/2012/03/arsenal-legend-insists-two-cups-is-not.html#comment-476597524</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>