<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m354ks/update/2012-03-28T19:46:29/6daf54b3cc9a4faa8ba85ec31d95e52a3e566731439bf0d6c2a61090b7683888</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkq50m</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dobch</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>When I first started watching MM, I didn't know who Jones was, but thought, "Wow, she really sucks." As the season went on, I thought that hte sucky stiltedness was part of Betty's character. She has a husband who cheats, treats her poorly (to say the least), and essentially ignores her except when he needs arm candy. He and the shitty psychiatrist created a profile for her and then seemed to force it onto her. Her life was an  and she was  just on the cusp of a catastrophic collapse. 

Now, though, I think it's just an amazing piece of synergy where Jone's particular style of bad  works extraordinarily well. It feels like if the facade were to fully crack and fall away, all that would be left was a raw, Bleeding, raging id that would destroy everything in  just to watch it shatter. I don't think that January could actually  that, but it's just the qualities of her  that make it appear that there are steel belts barely keeping her sanity intact (and the metal is fatiguing). HOwever, if given that direction, she would probably end up Acting like a normal human. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rbpb3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/a-little-kiss,71049/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T03:05:20+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T23:46:29+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m354ks</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/a-little-kiss,71049/#comment-478901660</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/do65w</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>