<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4abs/post/2012-03-30T17:19:33</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>So in the end the General Assembly proponents (on behalf of the Governor's aspirations) would have Maryland's already suffering hard-working tax, ratepaying residents who would use electric energy ... at a minimum pay:

1. Rate increases at $1.50 a month for electricity an average household for 20 years (assuming the public service commission doesn't authorize additional increases in the future)

2. 1.5 percent for commercial properties (and government properties?). A cost which will of necessity be passed along to renters and each businesses customers.

3. An unreported amount for standby backup energies at the ready to handle the load when the "Off Shore Wind Farm" experiences periods without wind, periods of light winds, periods of winds too heavy for safe operations, periods when it is Too hot or too Cold to operation and/or periods to service the turbines.

4. An unreported amount for electricity transmission and switching costs.

5. An unreported amount of federal taxation to provide moneys for federal tax treatments, grants and other subsidies.

This on top of the reprehensible new and additional taxations to address the Billion dollar shortfall on Maryland's existing budget and the Billion plus in new spending the General Assembly reportedly is generating for going forward.

In the end, the little guy ends up holding the empty bag....</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67riat</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zmzu</id></website><link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2012/mar/30/md-house-approves-omalleys-offshore-wind-energy-bi/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:19:37+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:19:33+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4abs</id><link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2012/mar/30/md-house-approves-omalleys-offshore-wind-energy-bi/#comment-481212104</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/djjwo</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>