<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwqfpg/post/2012-03-30T18:52:20</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzv5j</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I certainly did not mean to get you THAT worked up, especially since I've respected most of your old post.

To summarize my initial article, I was simply stating that the strong yen is hurting Japanese car manufacturers.(30 mins ago I read another article on Mazda and their hard times right now due to the yen, despite great products from them)  If your making less profit  each car, it will take it's toll on a company and it's products in the long run.  That was all I was saying!!!

As for reliability, quoting Consumer Reports(think what you will of them but no one else has a 10 year reliability survey) a 10 year old Toyota have the same amount of problems as a 5 year old GM, and after 10 years Honda and Toyota have about half as many problems as a 10 year old Chrysler, Hyundai, VW, or GM.  Yes, I know they are all more reliable today, I'm just saying no one has had proven reliability like Honda and Toyota.

As far as all Hyundai's being better then all Toyota's and Honda's, maybe on paper their MPG,HP and warranty are better, but the reviews I've read (I know what you read may be different) but most Honda's and Toyota's still do well.  Yes the Accent, Elantra and Sonata are GREAT, but there are still publication that respect the Fit, Accord, Camary, Rav4, highlander and CR-V.  Honda is coming out with new versions of some aging platforms, they have  stuck to their 5 to 7 year product cycle.  But my guess is that Hyundai will probably stick with the same 5-7 year product cycle, it's just Hyundai has just come out with their new lineup in the last 2 years, while Honda and Toyota was getting old.  I'm also  to see Hyundai providing such great competition, it's better for all consumers, maybe some got comfortable being in the top Spot for so long, now they have to buckle down and try harder.  We can only expect to see better products from them.

As for the Chinese Auto industry, YES their cars suck, A LOT of stuff from China SUCKS!!!  But people still buy it because it's cheap!!!  I'm hope we never see them here.  China has been hoping to  entry into our markets for years now, but yes, they still are not up to our standard yet.  They know that.  But you still see them at North American car shows each year.  They would not be there if they had no interest of joining us.  I'm not saying we will see Chinese brand cars in 5 years or ever down here, but they would like to.  And from what I've read they are hoping to do that with vehicles that cost $10,000 or less.  I  shop for quality, from cars to yard tools to appliances to cloths.  I try to buy local when I can and avoid Chinese(except their food, that's awesome) as much as possible.  But a lot of my friends and acquaintances don't, and only look at the price tag.  And if they can buy a  car for under $10,000 SOME will.  And your right, people do remember awful quality.  Remember those old 1980's Hyundai's.  Lot's of people do and is one reason why Hyundai's warranty is better, because the avg. car buyer USED to see Hyundai as inferior quality/reliability(again, I've read about this somewhere, this is not my opinion).
I do agree that Hyundai's reliability is on a great track, and I hope they continue.  I really do like a lot of their cars, and have been holding Off on them until they can prove they are good in the long run, i.e. 10 years or more.  

And I didn't say the automakers got a bailout, I simply stated that in the future they may not get one if needed.

Again, I apologize for getting you so angry.  I was simply stating my opinion based on things I've read and how I understood them.  Obviously you have had different experience and base your opinions on that knowledge.  I would have expected that response with name calling from a few others on this forum, but never from you, and hope that we can continue to exchange opinions and ideas in a respectable manner.  If you like I can try and find some articles to back up my claims if that would help but you don't have to look far to find the financial difficulty most of Japans industry is in now due to their Yen.
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zfngs</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gbur</id></website><link>http://www.thetorquereport.com/2012/03/hyundai_expects_to_beat_its_al.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T23:48:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T22:52:20+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwqfpg</id><link>http://www.thetorquereport.com/2012/03/hyundai_expects_to_beat_its_al.html#comment-481290089</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>