<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3bf6d/post/2012-03-29T14:46:19</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Well, yes and no.  We have the power to take our money elsewhere when we buy electricity,  petrol and food for example, but this does not do us much  good when the big battalions get together and form an unofficial cartel.  We started  with many power providers, but now have just six major ones - mostly foreign owned. The result is poor service and high prices. This will Always happen in business.  The famous John Lewis 'Never Knowingly Undersold' statement is, in my view a very clever marketing tool, which does not actually produce the lowest price - it simply makes all of them charge more or less the same regardless of their costs and becomes  the highest the market will bear instead of the lowest possible.

If we choose which services we take,  some might see, for instance, education as not being relevant to them if they have no children, or their children have grown up, and can save some money therefore, but won't that service then run out of money quickly?  What if we make a wrong choice? People do not all insure their houses (stupid, yes, but it happens)  and when they Burn down they are on the street. Suppose someone says they do not want to pay for the police or the fire brigade. What happens then?Can you really have a mutiplicity of suppliers in, say the health service or the police, or defence?   I cannot see how it could work. True, we have private health insurance and private hospitals, but they do not provide the things that are not profitable, such as emergency ambulances or A &amp; E.   You could do it with fairly minor services like Job Centres, but surely, only government is big enough to provide the big things?  I can see a two tier level of service, with the rich getting the Hilton Hotel and the poor getting the Travelodge in service provision.  It must be possible to give private management style service within government surely?  I know traditionally, public services usually are inefficient, but is this a law of nature, or just poor management from the politicians downwards?

There is no doubt we need to tax less, but surely the way to do that is to take the inefficiencies out of the services, abolish all the quangos as promised etc.

I think my old brain is not up to thinking what you have in mind, so no doubt someone will chip in with some ideas of how this would all work.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zrszh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/jolo</id></website><link>http://talkcarswell.com/disqus.aspx?id=2311</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:13:53+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:46:19+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3bf6d</id><link>http://talkcarswell.com/disqus.aspx?id=2311#comment-479749760</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>