<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miei5i/update/2012-03-22T17:22:56/ba7a73810896e5dc1129fbf3894b273d6ee3a7bcd18ccdba2924eb264e1f471a</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Why one RACE group has to be more special than others. The federal agency has launched a civil rights investigation into the case that has riveted the nation. Martin's family asserts that race was a factor in the black teenager's death". Really!!, all of this is sickening. Latino people are being treatened like garbage and sometimes killed by black and white racist  people, just because they assume that all Latinos are illegal Mexicans and nobody, says anything. I do not see any outraged people protesting. Why  is not  a crime (Federal and State) to attack a Latino person based on her/his color ,nationality an If you take the public transportation bus in cities such as Chicago, New York, Miami, Minneapolis, Los Angeles, Atlanta, to name a few, black people do not like seen a Latino there, I was called names, I was told to go back to Mexico and I was splashed water on my face by a black woman just because I was Coughing and she assumed I had Tuberculosis. That’s a hate crime based on race. I have seen  other Latinos being insulted and hit by blacks and whites because they just hated us. They call us little Mexicans, and Act very condescending toward us, the same happens at the work place. That's a hate crime based on the Latino race. I am a Democratic voter, however, my Latino friends and I will not vote this coming Presidential elections, and I hope other Latinos  do the same. 
 </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yrsqd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/22/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T06:52:55+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T21:22:56+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miei5i</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/22/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html#comment-473970702</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lzmpx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>