<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m7fnuo/update/2012-02-26T22:02:53/29a97ed79ba6ca790bcdea03d5cc7ddfcbb7932b5f275d5ef950ead997ebf7fa</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Written by a housewife in New Brunswick , to her local newspaper. This is one ticked  lady..."Are we fighting a war on terror or aren't we? Was it or was it not, started by Islamic people who brought it to our shores on September 11, 2001 and have continually threatened to do so since?Were people from all over the world, not brutally murdered that day, in downtown Manhattan , across the Potomac from
the capitol of the USA and in a field in Pennsylvania ?Did nearly three thousand men, women and children die a horrible, Burning or crushing death that day, or didn't they?Do you think I care about four U. S. Marines urinating on some dead Taliban insurgents?And I'm supposed to care that a few Taliban wereclaiming to be tortured by a justice system of anation they are fighting against in a brutal Insurgency.I'll care about the Koran when the fanatics in the MiddleEast, start caring about the Holy Bible, the mere beliefof which, is a crime punishable by beheading in Afghanistan .I'll care when these thugs tell the world they aresorry for hacking Off Nick Berg's head, while Bergscreamed through his gurgling slashed throat.I'll care when the cowardly so-called insurgentsin Afghanistan , come out and fight like men,instead of disrespecting their own religion byhiding in Mosques and behind women and children.I'll care when the mindless zealots who blowthemselves up in search of Nirvana, care about theinnocent children within range of their suicide Bombs.I'll care when the Canadian media stops pretending thattheir freedom of Speech on stories, is more important thanthe lives of the soldiers on the ground or their families waitingat home, to hear about them when something happens.In the meantime, when I hear a story about aCANADIAN soldier roughing up an Insurgentterrorist to obtain information, know this:I don't care.When I see a wounded terrorist get shot in thehead when he is told not to move because hemight be booby-trapped, you can take it to the bank:I don't care. Shoot him again.When I hear that a prisoner, who was issued a Koran and a prayer mat, and fed 'special' food, that is paid for by my tax dollars, is complaining that his holy book is being 'mishandled,' you can absolutely believe, in your heart of hearts:I don't care.And oh, by the way, I've noticed that sometimesit's spelled 'Koran' and other times 'Quran.'Well, Jimmy Crack Corn you guessed it.I don't care!!If you agree with this viewpoint, pass this on toall your E-mail Friends. Sooner or later, it'll get tothe people responsible for this ridiculous behavior!If you don't agree, then by all means hit the deletebutton. Should you choose the latter, then please don'tcomplain when more atrocities committed by radicalMuslims happen here in our great Country! And may I add:Some people spend an entire lifetime wondering, ifduring their life on earth, they made a difference inthe world. But, the Soldiers don't have that problem.I have another quote that I would like toshare AND...I hope you forward All this.One last thought for the day:Only five defining forces have ever offered to die for you:1. Jesus Christ2. The British Soldier.3. The Canadian Soldier.4. The US Soldier, and5. The Australian SoldierOne died for your soul,the other four, for you and your children's Freedom.YOU MIGHT WANT TO PASS THIS ON,AS MANY SEEM TO FORGET!AMEN! GOD BLESS CANADA AND AMERICA .</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/y93rba</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f7e3</id></website><link>http://www.wnd.com/2012/02/planning-for-islamic-caliphate-to-begin/</link><postedTime>2012-02-26T02:04:19+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-27T03:02:53+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m7fnuo</id><link>http://www.wnd.com/2012/02/planning-for-islamic-caliphate-to-begin/#comment-449650648</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hb43s</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>