<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/e77dw8/update/2011-12-17T08:13:12/9574453dabe9f03a28d04b86c676a417b979be6e620af5d65be9df2033bc41a7</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ey1rao</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cjcbl</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Nonsense in your last paragraph.

Of course there are things beyond our perception!

We can not perceive ultra-violet radiation directly, for example (although a sun tan or sun Burn is noticeable as indirect results - and these phenomena can be created by other means).

Do you really mean to say there are not phenomena which are beyond the  of all instruments which can be built by humans? This is a rather arrogant claim. If scientists really believed this, they might as well close shop and go home.
Various instruments have been developed precisely to make up for the shortcomings in our perceptions, but as they are inevitably translations into phenomena which we can perceive - there is potential for information (or quality) to be lost in that interpretive process. "The map is not the territory". Indeed, all perception is a matter of *excluding* information from the universe to a more or less narrow bandwidth, The organs we use to perceive visual light do not also perceive sound waves, pressure, gravity, temperature etc.

And here's another one. Do you perceive your own thoughts? How do you know whether you are 'really' thinking? Is it a perceptual phenomenon to be aware of your thoughts? If you dream about the appearance of something - i.e. a synthesis of visual phenomena - how is that different from the synthesis made by our visual cortex when we 'see'? Consider that we have two eyes - two seperate images must be merged together! What you think you 'see' is actually constructed by a learned process. Babies, for example, can not do this because they have not learned to synthesise the seperate images from both eyes into a unified experience of vision.

Consider "dark matter". We don't know whether it exists, but the current astrophysical models suggest its existence, although only as a vague hypothesis - however, we have no instruments to 'perceive' it, therefore (according to your postulate) we must conclude that dark matter does not exist. That is absurd.

Even those who believe themselves to be logically minded, critical thinkers, non-supersitious etc. are liable to fall for one or more of dozens of common cognitive biases. A little humility is goes a long way to Safeguarding against such misjudgements.

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_cognitive_biases</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ch50jz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6tdd</id></website><link>http://www.csmonitor.com/USA/2011/0105/Are-you-smarter-than-an-atheist-A-religious-quiz/Results</link><postedTime>2011-01-05T19:13:58+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-12-17T13:13:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/e77dw8</id><link>http://www.csmonitor.com/USA/2011/0105/Are-you-smarter-than-an-atheist-A-religious-quiz/Results#comment-388702730</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/duy0m</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-01-05</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>