<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwii07/post/2012-03-31T08:58:53</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>What people aren't realizing here is that this case has more to do with class than race.  Remember back a few years when Bill Cosby's son was found shot dead by the side of the road?  The L.A. Chief of Police gets on television and says that finding the killer of Ennis Cosby is the #1 priority of the LAPD.  Since when is finding the killer of a young black man the top priority of the LAPD?  Answer: When you're a Ph.D candidate from a wealthy family with a famous father.  

Let's say Travon's dad was a Harvard Law School graduate and a partner in one of the most prestigious law firms in Florida.  Travon, an honor student who is due to graduate this spring and matriculate to Yale University in the fall, is driving home one night when his car breaks down.  His cell phone is out so he is walking to the nearest gas station.  He takes a shortcut through the neighborhood of one George Zimmerman, an unemployed truck driver who lost his commercial drivers license after receiving yet another DUI.  George has a G.E.D., a mullet-cut, and does not own a shirt with sleeves.  He shoots Travon.  Result:   George would have been arrested on the Spot and would reside beneath the jail today.  

Reality:  George's dad is a retired judge in that county.  I'm not sure on the background of Travon's family, but my bet is that George will get Off.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67zt7h</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ewhe</id></website><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/trayvon-martin/trayvon-martin-grieving-a-tragic-death-in-the-spotlight.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:24:41+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T12:58:53+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwii07</id><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/trayvon-martin/trayvon-martin-grieving-a-tragic-death-in-the-spotlight.php#comment-481810011</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/r3tn0</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>