<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mbbcvk/update/2012-03-10T02:32:59/535173748be571f130b17cfb95180e86109afe74ecdfab6d4f318f8882aad3d9</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>First they were saying it was another abduction in Indiana of a young woman whos car and all were found in the same way as this young woman, now they are saying its an accident. I have a couple of questions: who is going to leave their fully functional car with all of your belongings as well as phone and money and ID and take a walk in the woods for weeks wedge yourself between a tree and hope someone finds you? Who does that? and this is the first they are saying that she was Mentally unstable. I just dont get the connection.  a good job, a loving family, and all of her family said this missing was out of her charter espically since she actually spoke to her father on Christmas and her mother kept calling her over and over the day after Chritmas. she put a male friend out of her house then she is missing. They find her car on the 27th but they forget to log it into the computer as an impounded car? but they find her fully intact car still running and they find her car 12 miles away from her house! but what really has me confused, if this is an accident, how do you accidently leave your car in a place that is out in the open and wander around for weeks and do so that NO one sees you until you turn up wedged aganist a tree and died from what the medical examiner says is hyperthermia and mental confusion and thats an accident. I live in GA and although we have had some low temps this winter it was not as bad as last year with the ice storms that had people stuck and sleeping at their jobs and trying to get to work by any means necessary, Now last year Stacey didnt get so Cold that she parked her car walked into the woods and and wedged herself aganist a tree why would she do it this time? and what happened to the other young woman that was missing in the same manner as Stacy?
To the Family, May God Bless you all With Comfort and Peace at this time I am so sorry for your loss. But please Fight for Stacey, If this is sounding in ANY way unlike Stacy Fight to bring WHOEVER did this to her to Justice. Make the GBI and the FBI and All earn their Checks they recieve. Make sure they Give Stacey just as much time as they give all of their other LIGHTER-skinned Cases. My Family will keep you all up in Prayer. God Bless you ALL...</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yqch5h</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t26w</id></website><link>http://newsone.com/nation/find-our-missing/afisher/stacey-english-hypothermia/</link><postedTime>2012-02-14T22:04:51+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-10T07:32:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mbbcvk</id><link>http://newsone.com/nation/find-our-missing/afisher/stacey-english-hypothermia/#comment-461245711</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h3xuj</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-14</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>