<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/c7ouq0/update/2011-05-20T12:11:46/8e7f3f5d1fee309a16a3e7a298cc9ec8ea027e6cea83a90cdd38f6b7158d10b6</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/c7xtb3</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Pray what is the universal "caste" of a chaiwala ?  Or for that matter that of a software engineer ? Caste today is purely a tool for political mobilization as the Indian Constitution provides for special benefits for "socially and educationally" backward classes in addition to Scheduled Castes and Tribes.  It is this vague formulation that politicians have exploited to the hilt. Unfortunately, the better Off OBS have cornered most of these benefits and in rural areas are the main oppressors of the SC/STs who out of frustration become easy targets for Christian missionaries. But the converted SC/STs soon realize that their  social status does not rise one bit even after conversion !! "Upper caste" Christians routinely harass these SC/ST converts. They attend different Churches and there is no inter marriage among them. Even at death they are buried in separate cemeteries !  Just read the matrimonial column in the Mid Day newspaper in Mumbai. Here "Brahmin" Goan Christians seek alliances only from other "Brahmin" Christians !!! The same is the story in "The Hindu" newspaper where "Nadar" Christians seek alliances only from other "Nadar" Christians !! Hindus regardless of caste go to the same temples and are cremated in the same Burning ghats !!! It is these hypocrisies that are pointed out by Hindu groups and has the effect of blunting the nefarious activities of Christian missionaries. Hindus have to be eternally vigilant to protect their religion and its believers. Thanks to rising education (particularly among girls), incomes and urbanization, the pernicious aspects of the old caste system are already on the wane. Inter caste marriages are no longer an exception. This trend too will put an end to the false propaganda of the Christian missionaries and Hindus will resonate to the clarion call "Garv se kaho hum Hindu hain" !  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/g82fd9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/776o</id></website><link>http://www.firstpost.com/economy/hindu-population-set-to-fall-below-80-in-census-2011-10765.html</link><postedTime>2011-05-17T03:49:15+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-05-20T16:11:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/c7ouq0</id><link>http://www.firstpost.com/economy/hindu-population-set-to-fall-below-80-in-census-2011-10765.html#comment-207929663</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/d9skd</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-05-17</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>