<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qs0b/post/2012-03-29T12:19:59</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3q937</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/akimk</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Hospitals have been offering huge buyouts for practices.  Plus, our overhead is getting silly.  Seriously, the hospital can outfit a clinic with something like GE Centricity EMR that they maintain, the hospital absorbs the billing and coding, and possibly they even take care of scheduling.  It looks good on paper - get rid of the overhead Headache, however, most of the docs I know that have sold out their practices end up quitting within a year once the hospital takes control.

Liability is also an increasing problem - as you mentioned, defensive medicine is a very real one (I do a lot of tests that I don't feel necessary just to appease the patient).  Having the hospital deal with the liability issues is a bonus.

Another issue is referral base - specialists Depend on primaries to refer patients.  As more and more primaries are absorbed into hospital systems, they tend to refer internally - if you're not part of the system, you're locked out.  As a general rule, hospitals loose money on general practitioners, and make it back on the specialists.

If ObamaCare stands, I think ACOs will be a serious issue, and will force almost all docs away from truly private practices.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zdeq3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rvx5</id></website><link>http://money.cnn.com/2012/03/29/pf/healthcare-costs/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T09:47:53+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:19:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qs0b</id><link>http://money.cnn.com/2012/03/29/pf/healthcare-costs/#comment-479619778</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ms0gg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>