<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gqd6g0/update/2011-10-14T09:59:13/cdb596250065fb0206e8f6a169e3fff5845569fd2d0077c77627f59be805e176</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gqg55c</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g19bi</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I never expected to find someone else buying the same three games as me this year. Despite what others say, MW3 will be a fun game. It's just like you said...fast, instant action. I can pick it up and play a game or two when I only have a little while to game. I also don't buy a CoD game every year, though it's nice to have that option, but as a result I didn't get Burned out on it like everyone else that is complaining.

As for the other games mentioned I agree. Rage is just a generic shooter that doesn't even have a decent MP. Dark Souls, if it's anything like its predecessor, is a terribly boring game. I kept hearing positive things about Demon's Souls so I decided to pick it up. I got through the first area and was completely bored with it. If you like it, great. Enjoy. I'll stick with Skyrim. As for Ace Combat? I'm sure I've read about the game but I really can't place it  the top of my head.

I'd also like to address Diernes and his quote: "You sir are completely bent over by the mainstream video game industry." I bet for every person reading this, I could replace "video game" with something else. The fact is, we all have tastes that  with the mainstream in some form. If you don't, it's likely you are one of those people that doesn't like the mainstream simply because it's the mainstream.

When it comes to certain things, my tastes don't Align with the mainstream. For example, beer. I tend to prefer beers that most people haven't heard of, until recently anyway. Craft brews have become increasingly popular. I see this as a good thing, even if the beer I enjoy eventually becomes mainstream. Incidentally, the games I enjoy have become mainstream, but I won't stop playing them just because they are mainstream. I've been playing CoD since the first one. I've been playing the Elder Scrolls since Daggerfall.

At any rate, the games I play don't say anything about who I am personally. I take my work seriously, and when I get home at the end of the day, I don't want to play a game that feels like work. I'll wind down with a couple games of MW3, or maybe some BF3. I'll fill my longer gaming sessions wandering through the latest corner of Tamriel that Bethesda has made available to me. If you do want to judge me based on the games I play, that's your prerogative. I'll still buy whatever games I want, and enjoy them, rather than come here and sling negativity at everyone with preferences different than my own.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/mrjs20</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7d9s</id></website><link>http://xbox360.ign.com/articles/120/1200215p1.html</link><postedTime>2011-10-14T10:11:27+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-10-14T13:59:13+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gqd6g0</id><link>http://xbox360.ign.com/articles/120/1200215p1.html#comment-334630007</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6bhj6</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-10-14</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>