<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3vi6l/update/2012-03-29T09:10:13/a6fb3ec06c7616505e8c2fa6af8c150e431ca19b6f832091b7185f9d3e15f477</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3v7ac</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8h6nm</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>And, I would say "rightly so."  There is a big difference between being open and accepting of others versus excluding others and promoting bullying.  I don't know why the promotion of positive messages are equated with being unfair to negative messages.

If we do a fair comparison using an example:  "World Peace is Possible."  What's wrong with that?  Contrast that with "Jews should stay in Israel."   Is  the anti-Jewish T-shirt "trampling on the sensitivity of others?"

They removed the teaching of specific religious tenets from our schools because public schools need to teach all of the public, not just a specific religious dogma shared by a few.  Additionally, religion should be taught by religious organizations and not by public schools as we have a separation of church and state, clear as a bell, and any selection of any one religion would be the government endorsing one religion over another - simply unconstitutional to do so.  Kids still can pray, or not, in school.  It's up to them.  It will not be held over the PUBLIC address system, nor endorsed by the public school because of the First Amendment.  This is plain as day simple.  That said, the history of all religions may be taught in school as religion is an essential part of history in that it was a major factor in wars, migration of peoples, the rise and fall of various civilizations and so forth.  We cannot exclude religion from history, thus it is taught in the context of how it affected history without teaching or endorsing specific tenets of any given religion.

I disagree on core subjects only idea and thus also on the homeschooling which I feel is a great disservice to children.  School is all about the core subjects but also about socialization and interaction with others in our society.  We need to have kids learn about all different forms of government, people, societal views, current events, and varying opinions.  Slapping blinders on them and having them see a sterilized, limited, protected, and unrealistic view of the real world, in my opinion, does little to prepare them for the real world.  It's like the old Catholic school deal - once those kids got out from under the thumb of oppression from those schools, it was like they were shot out of a cannon.  They got a great "book" education but quite a few had a difficult time interacting with others from different cultures and differing religious backgrounds.  I have gay friends, raised in strict Catholic schools.  They had a heck of a time adjusting to the real world.  They claim to be ex-Catholic but now in their 60's, I see their ex-Catholic status as much like being an ex-Burn Victim.  You may be out of the fire but the scars are still there.

You may raise your children however you see fit.  I just hope they are prepared for the real world and realize that gay people  have been here and Always will be.  That is just another fact of life you may not find in religious school teachings or in the home-schooling planner.
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hs9qw</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dngw</id></website><link>http://bangordailynews.com/2012/03/28/news/gay-tolerance-t-shirt-on-brunswick-classroom-wall-triggers-wider-conversation/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T22:59:29+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:10:13+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3vi6l</id><link>http://bangordailynews.com/2012/03/28/news/gay-tolerance-t-shirt-on-brunswick-classroom-wall-triggers-wider-conversation/#comment-479476308</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/u6nm</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>