<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmg9c/post/2012-03-30T08:50:55</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>It is certainly good to be optimistic.  It makes you wonder if people were optimistic about the future of race relations after the Civil War or if they foresaw the century of prejudice that would continue to characterize them.
The strategy for change has been wrong.  Maybe the leopard can change his Spots, but not if he wishes to continue to look like a leopard.  The natural realm from which we obtain resources is not a matter of a simple choice  to disregard them in favor of more costly man-made options.  This is what the left has been trying to do since they discovered that the sex drive was often not an exercise of choice.  Based on that premise, we have liberated women from the traditional role of housewife, homemaker and mother.  We have allowed contraception and abortion as options to correct the unexercised right of a woman to choose regarding the sex drive.  We have sanctioned so-called "same sex"  civil unions and "marriages' because some people have been found to be "orientated" differently than most, (approximately 3 out of 100).  
With regard to natural resources, environmentalists have made equations between the length of life and the factors thought to shorten it and, as a consequence, we have now decided that coal, one of the most abundant of natural resources in the U.S., will not be an option as a fuel.  Oil has the potential to be spilled and so its production (here in the U.S.) must be curtailed.  (The Arabs are a backward, lesser species, so they can continue to pollute their atmospheres, hopefully shortening their life spans, and sell their oil to us. I wonder if they have figured this out yet?  Does this qualify as hypocrisy on our part?)  
The aforementioned solutions to the problems of the natural realm have so increased the cost of living over the last several years that the budgets are not paid for.  The debt has increased and the promise of the future is that it will only get worse.  This is real change!  This is undeniable change!  To some, this offers hope.  To some, this is the American Dream.  
We will see in November just how many actually think that a reduction in the purposes enumerated in the preamble to the Constitution of the United States, 
to include a right to breathe clean air and not to have to reproduce, are viable alternatives to "a more perfect union, establish justice, Ensure domestic tranquility, provide for the common defense and promote the general welfare and to secure the blessings of life, liberty and the pursuit of happiness for ourselves and our posterity."  
If not, democrats and liberals will discover that they have been seriously mistaken.  If or since there is a God.....
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zwo40</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/4lgx</id></website><link>http://www.arcamax.com/politics/ariannahuffington/s-1118982-126348</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T08:26:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T12:50:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmg9c</id><link>http://www.arcamax.com/politics/ariannahuffington/s-1118982-126348#comment-480704187</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6qz16</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>