<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk1uml/post/2012-03-26T11:43:28</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mium0c</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8nur8</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I would like to think you are joking but I know you are not. The sad part is that free thinking was not involved in your analysis. If it was you would ask yourself two things when this man expressed this story to you... why didnt he open his business in a different neighborhood and why was it easier to move back to India then moving to a different area, state, neighborhood of this huge US. I moved to europe once for work and it was hard enough moving there, I wouldve have moved back without the help of job. I know plenti of Indians and they still live in the States in very nice areas and enjoy a great US experience. Dont be sucked into the case by case ideology. You can Always find a convenient situation for every argument. The real issue is about how this case was handled by the police. Because once again al sharpton is involved it distracts people from the greater point. A thorough investigation which includes cross examining the only real witness, the shooter, was not performed and police did not perform Standard Operating Procedure as in any other shooting and took this mans word and decided the case on the Spot.  This is not their job. Florida law (You should read it) clearly states that guilt or the lack thereof will be decided by the court. We can spew racial comments all day but that doesnt change the fact tthat we citizens should be concerned about this process and how it was handled. Also read florida law section 776.041. You will find it very amusing. Eventually, this could affect you or someone you care about. Please be concerned</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66hwvz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dndh</id></website><link>http://www.myrtlebeachonline.com/2012/03/23/2734569/self-defense-laws-questioned-after.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T19:26:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T15:43:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk1uml</id><link>http://www.myrtlebeachonline.com/2012/03/23/2734569/self-defense-laws-questioned-after.html#comment-476481144</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zr8ib</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>