<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m09l0k/update/2012-04-02T00:18:01/baa3592b0e8df8ae201126a3c1f6eb4ffee2540a40132297729a02e6f31464c2</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>

Bible Prophecy

“Evil Men (and Women) Will Wax Worse and Worse”

Deceiving . . . (Lying)

and BEING Deceived”

Jesus (Yeshua) called Satan the “father of all lies.” The Bible warns “in the last days” evil men (and women) will be prevalent. Lying and deception (which are now called “spin”) will characterize the generation (and the leaders) who will pull the world down into the dark abyss and terrors of the coming “Apocalypse” . . .

“But KNOW this,

that in the last days

perilous times will come . . .

Evil men and impostors will grow worse and worse,

deceiving (lying) and being deceived.”

(2 Timothy 3:1, 13)

The Scriptures tell us God cannot lie and He h ates all lies. God says truth is non-negotiable and is fundamental to His law. In the past, liars and perjurers were held accountable and dealt with harshly and severely. Today we see lying casually accepted in the news, in the movies, and on television. Lying is now being presented as funny and harmless. This generation is unique in its reaction to liars and perjurers. This nation even lifted up and still glorifies a recent President whose most notable characteristics were flagrantly staring into a TV camera lying and deceiving … and then later being convicted of criminal perjury. This generation mocks our rules of law. This generation mocks God’s Law. As noted, telling the truth is fundamental to God’s law. In the Bible we find when a nation and its leader(s) defiantly mock, ignore, and turn their backs on God’s law, God will turn His back on that nation and will remove His protection and blessings from that people. God help us. The future of that nation and people is Always very, very grim …

A stark warning . . .

“Knowing this:

that the Law is not made for a righteous person,

but for the lawless and insubordinate,

for the ungodly and for sinners,

for the unholy and profane,

for murderers of fathers and murderers of mothers,

for manslayers,

for $exually immoral (fornicators),

for homosexuals (sodomites),

for kidnappers,

for liars,

for perjurers,

and if there is any other thing that is contrary to sound doctrine”

(1 Timothy 1:8-10)

“But the cowardly, unbelieving,

abominable, murderers,

$exually immoral,

sorcerers, (drugs … “pharmakeus”)

idolaters,


and all liars

shall have their part in the lake which Burns with fire and brimstone,

which is the second death .” (The darkness, aloneness, and torments of  HeII

(Revelation 21:8)

Sorry if I'm not politcally correct but I don't have to be.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6vbi9z</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yjmx</id></website><link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2012/04/01/dismembered-ohio-woman-was-stabbed-suffocated-police-say/</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T17:26:01+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T04:18:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m09l0k</id><link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2012/04/01/dismembered-ohio-woman-was-stabbed-suffocated-police-say/#comment-483279691</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8pox8</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>