<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34ary/post/2012-03-29T10:32:29</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>hi, i found this link a few weeks ago before surgery and was happy to find some pro's &amp; con's, and up's and down's in the comments. that's life. i fell almost 11 months ago, the surgery was recommended 7 1/2 months ago and thanks to our workers comp system it was finally performed 2 days ago.  the discs between C5,6,&amp;7 were removed, bone blocks inserted, and titanium plates screwed into place.  pretty normal procedure.  i'm 59, holding up well for the age, hike extensively with a 30 lb backpack, run half-marathons now &amp; then, and jog the 5 miles home from work once in a while.  of course a haven't done much of that since i was injured and i have  20 lbs. but i continued to work every day in an active outdoor job and maintained a positive outlook.  i came to after surgery and immediately noticed my wife smiling and the lack of pain in my left arm.  i had one instance of Numbness in my right hand and  forearm that 1st evening but no extreme pain from the surgery which may have been residual effects of the general anethesia.  the first night was fitful in and outs of conciousness due to weirdly sore trapezoids and a chatterring ward-mate on a morphine induced rant.  day 1, post surgery, i met all the requirements to be released early in the A.M. and left the hospital without having any post surgery pain meds.  i spent the day e-mailing friends and relatives and walking around the back yard wondering what projects i would be able to finish in my time Off.  day 2, post surgery, TODAY! slept pretty good with no need for pain meds, up early as usual and ready to go for a short walk around the block.  it seems that i am well on my way to recovery.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/mdz3gz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/bkyf</id></website><link>http://acdf-surgery.com/stories/scott/five-months-after-acdf-surgery/</link><postedTime>2011-05-19T01:29:25+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:32:29+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34ary</id><link>http://acdf-surgery.com/stories/scott/five-months-after-acdf-surgery/#comment-479532069</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zz8il</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-05-19</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>