<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3u23v/post/2012-03-29T15:00:21</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The health care issue has nothing to do with how, where, when and on what the government spends our tax dollars. War is an obvious easy target but it doesn’t have anything to do with spending money. If we didn’t have wars ongoing would we still be 15 trillion dollars in debt? You bet we would. In reality the health care issue is one of entitlement and learned entitlement. Allow me to explain anecdotally; when I was young my father worked for a multination corporation at Oak Ridge, Tennessee. The company offered what was called MAJOR MEDICAL and EMERGENCY CARE INSURANCE. Dental and vision were not a part of the package. If I had the Flu and went to the doctor my family paid the entire bill and if medicine was prescribed my family paid for that also. If I crashed my bicycle (and I did it a lot with no body armor or helmet, yet here I am) and cut my leg the insurance paid for the doctor visit, stitches, tetanus shot and the prescription for the antibiotics. My father paid something monthly for the insurance but the company paid the lion’s share of the monthly costs. The company did that not because they felt that everyone in the country deserved to have cheap health care insurance rather as one of the gimmicks to help attract and keep valued employees. What I just described happened in the 1950’s. While I don’t have any evidence to validate it, I’m betting that perhaps only 30% of Americans were covered by such insurance. 

Now, let’s look at “health care insurance” from that time until today. What has happened is for many reasons most of which were still aimed at keeping or attracting valued employees, the things that were covered by the 1950’s insurance started to increase. Dental and vision care was added. Drug and alcohol rehabilitation was added. All manner of mental health therapy was added.  From the ‘50’s through the mid ‘80’s the economy of the USA grew exponentially. Paying for increases in coverage was very easy for the companies. But that of course changed and companies started cutting back on coverage and their subsidies they paid in the employee’s name. Also health care costs increased at a rate much higher than wages. But that isn’t the problem. That’s call living on the economy. The problem is we thought we were entitled to all this cheap health care.

I am 68 years of old age. I have worked for 46 years and today I work very hard (10 hrs a day 5 and 6 days a week) for a corporation that offers a reasonable health care insurance plan. I choose to have health care insurance therefore I choose to work. When I choose to quit work or my health fails to the point that I cannot work I will have no insurance. I will live Off my retirement saving (what little is left from all the bursting bobbles) and social security. I have planned for this; it was my responsibility to plan for this. It isn’t anyone else’s responsibility but mine. 

Here’s the juice, people get sick from time to time; they need to visit a doctor from time to time; they need prescription drugs from time to time. It’s called LIVING. It is an expanse that each of us should bear as a part of our day-to-day earning and spending. My father told me that it isn’t how little money you make that gets you in trouble, it’s how much you spend.

I have represented a very, very complicated multiplicity of issues in a very two dimensional manner to illustrate the point that WE are responsible and accountable for ourselves and our lives and WE cannot leave such an important task to the government. Jonathan Edwards said in Sunshine, “...He can't even run his own life, I'll be damned if he'll run mine…”

Have a really super day and remember it is neither the round nor the square but the spiral that leads to the top of the stairs.
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zdeq3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rvx5</id></website><link>http://money.cnn.com/2012/03/29/pf/healthcare-costs/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T09:47:53+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:00:21+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3u23v</id><link>http://money.cnn.com/2012/03/29/pf/healthcare-costs/#comment-479764852</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hkviy</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>