<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/312236/post/127937196/comment/328559357</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Here is an excellent red enchilada sauce recipe:

Enchilada Sauce

2-tablespoons vegetable oil
3-tablespoons flour
2-tablespoons red chili powder
1-teaspoon cumin
1-teaspoon garlic powder
2-cups chicken or beef broth
½ teaspoon salt (or to taste)
1-8 ounce can tomato sauce

1. Heat oil in large 2-quart saucepan; stir in flour—make a roux – stir constantly until light brown-about a minute 

2. Add remaining ingredients bring to a boil and simmer until thick – stirring constantly 

I flash fry my corn tortillas and use a sillicone pastry brush to coat each one with sauce (one at a time then fill with grated cheese, chopped onions, or cooked shredded chicken). Spread a little sauce in a 9x13 baking pan and place rolled enchiladas side by side. You can put a little sauce on top if there is any leftover; but be careful--too much sauce makes the enchiladas mushy. Top with grated cheese. I cover with foil and put in a 325 degree oven for 10-15 minutes (just until cheese is melted and the enchiladas are hot).

Here's a recipe for Spanish Rice:

Heat about a tablespoon of cooking oil in a skillet (one that has a lid). 

Then add a cup of uncooked rice (not instant) and cook over medium Heat until it just starts to turn a very light gold color (if you cook it too long, it will Burn and taste bad). Keep stirring the rice and moving it all over the pan to prevent Burning.

Add a can of chicken broth and about three fourths of a small can of tomato sauce (you can also use the Knorrs tomato bullion if you choose--I break it up into crumbs so it's incorporated into the rice). I also add dried/minced garlic and dehydrated onions (they come in a shaker)--add enough to suit your taste.

Cover and simmer over low Heat for 20 minutes--if the rice is still too liquidy, cook a little longer with the lid Off.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:312236:127937196</id><idPostId>127937196</idPostId><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:312236</id><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><link>http://www.denpdf.com</link><displayName>denpdf.com</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.denpdf.com/enchilada-recipe-enchilada-recipe/</link><displayName>enchilada recipe- Enchilada Recipe?</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T15:01:57.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:312236:127937196:328559357</id><link>http://www.denpdf.com/enchilada-recipe-enchilada-recipe/#IDComment328559357</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T15:01:57.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on enchilada recipe- Enchilada Recipe? by lpar161</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>5529399ec0ffe6218f32dca2420b11e5</idEmailMd5><displayName>lpar161</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>lpar161 commented on &lt;a href="http://www.denpdf.com/enchilada-recipe-enchilada-recipe/"&gt;enchilada recipe- Enchilada Recipe?&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>