<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3p1yv/update/2012-03-29T20:37:15/ad8701d6449c599f4f3f1583b2a2d733c792493f9b4c6d3e55f58aad9aca805d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I am Glad Chantelle is fine and the moose was well behaved. 

I wish people would film ADF&amp;G when they are snaring bears, aerial wolf and bear hunting, bear baiting and the use of carbon monoxide to kill wolf pups in their dens. These savage, barbaric and cruel atrocities on wildlife should be exposed where the whole world can watch how these Cold blooded people torture and kill wolves and bears with no compassion or mercy on God's creation.

The animals are very intelligent and they know who will or will not hurt them. These crooked, abusers, manipulators and exploiters from the moose Federation, Advisories and ADF&amp;G are just waiting for any opportunity to go after the moose because the moose is a profitable business for them.

Recently its more acceptable to live among wild animals than some human criminals. Why do they not bring up about issues from these criminals such as Alaska wildlife conservation director who is charged with helping illegaly kill bears. Corey Rossi, BOG Cliff Judkins,current Chair and Bob Bell scamed themselves an illegal trophy hunt for musk ox in a susbsistence-hunting area. When they came back, they changed the law to cover themselves up. Corey Rossi didn't show up in court, and through his lawyer Rossi pleaded not guilty. There is also an article about Rossi.

Rossi has also been active with the organization Sportsmen for Fish and Wildlife, a somewhat controversial hunter advocacy group. Guide AARON BLOOMQUIST, who has a business relationship with Rossi, was recently handed coveted, SPECIAL PERMITS FROM THE WILDLIFE DIVISION for bison, Dall sheep and musk ox. Bloomquist is to take to the Western Hunting and Conservation Expo in Salt Lake in February hwere they are to be actioned to raise funds for the organization.

These Outdoor Sportsmen (trophy) hunters and Fur trappers organizations and whoever have business with Alaska's wildlife are taking any opportunity to go after the wildlife and exploit them for profits, for themselves. They are the ones who are running the hunting industry which only benefit and enrich themselves.

Our system of wildlife management is corrupted.

For example how many people had died by wild animals?

How many people had died by some human criminals and by drunk-drivers?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z2km8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dneq</id></website><link>http://community.adn.com/?q=adn/node/160533</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T03:26:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:37:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3p1yv</id><link>http://community.adn.com/?q=adn/node/160533#comment-480075028</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zglg0</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>