<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mqvpx8/update/2012-03-04T10:37:27/22e47bbd71d112a2ac9a61e976d55bc6d496e7313edd64c01fad9e50d4642856</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mqlkgd</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ac6uo</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>"I had seen news of that poll in the last day or so ... it does concern me."
It shouldn't.

We go through this every election. The memory hole thing kicks in  between, now, once again, like Always, even that part of the public that actually pays attention to polling at this time of year has to go through a refresher.

Rule of Thumb: If if really WAS any sort of a concern, we'd expect to see a work-up by Nate Silver at NYT online - but we don't. Silver hasn't posted anything at all on that poll. Neither has another leading poll aggregator, Pollster.com at HuffPo online. Even the last of the Big 3 poll aggregators, Real Clear Politics/National Journal, isn't having kittens on this poll. 

General principles: Quite apart from other considerations, March is simply way. too. early. to be polling head-to-head for a November general. If you're desperate for some reason to track a general right now, go start tracking Wisconsin - where it's also too early but not nearly so wildly so.
Why? That response to the question of what drives politics when it was asked of U.K. P.M. Harold MacMillan: "Events, dear boy; events." We don't know - as a matter of physical reality, we CAN NOT know - what's going to happen in the world between now &amp; November; but we do know this: stuff WILL happen, &amp; that such stuff will impact the election. Right now, there's 8 months of room for that stuff; there was a time when countries could start &amp; end entire wars inside 8 months.

Next we have to consider whether one of the parties is running an incumbent while the other is still embroiled in it's primaries; &amp; yes, indeedy, that the situation right now. IOW, there's a big oranges-to-orangutans comparison problem. 

Now to the pollster: this is Gallup poll conducted for USAToday. Gallup has a large number of posts &amp; analyses on it's website, but it's not featuring this particular poll. Why not? Wild guesses to start: too early &amp; one party hasn't got its nominee yet ...

But add to that purpose of the poll, i.e. gotta keep the customer satisfied. 
A little context: Gallup is not PPP, which has proved quite reliable but is still regarded as slightly Dem-sympathetic; &amp; it's not Rasmussen either, which has proved only intermittently reliable (It's fine once it gets within a few weeks of election day), but otherwise provides a lot of ammo that suggests it polls through deeply rose-colored glasses. But Gallup does have it's, uh, oddities. For one, it has a GOP bias - not a big obvious one, like Rasmussen has, but still. Next, there's its Gallup's "Daily Tracker" poll, which is unavoidably quite erratic over shorter periods &amp; close to useles compared to polls which try to dig down into the voter base. For another, check this out: every presidential election cycle, Gallup catches Heat for a handful or more of odd, superficially misleading polls; as Gallup then explains (when it gets challenged by the aggregators) some of these come from customer directions, which can/do affect the nature of the questioning of those polled, &amp; can/does limit what raw data Gallup is allowed by its customer to release. This came up multiple times in 2008. 

Is USAToday one of 'those' customers? No &amp; yes. USAT doesn't have a CHRONIC history of withholding permission from Gallup to release raw data - but it has done just that in past elections. Also, USAT tends to be subject to instances of where how &amp; what the questions asked being subject to criticism, some fairly serious. There's a tendency to put that down entirely to USAT's ownership (beyond R leaning), but I think this gets conflated with USAT's business model. Like all large MSM, USAT wants a horse race, thus more ad sales. Where we see a counterintuitive poll result coming from USAT, we have to be alert to this mixing of streams. The horse race desire is obviously applicable to some degree or other right across the MSM, so the 3 other national papers plus the 5 major screen news channels are all also subject to this bias - but historically, it doesn't show up nearly as much with any of them (not even with Fox, surprising to some mabye).

Another factor, which goes in particular to that 'way too early' issue. This poll is focused on "registered voters". But polling registered American voters this far in advance is also a poor predictor because of the difference in character between the two national parties. The GOP vote base tends more strongly - FAR more strongly - to register early &amp; stay current. That should come as no suprise: the GOP vote base tends to be older, more sedentary (in every way, including less likely to move to another state to obtain work), more work-oriented through the male, most likely to own rather than be an employee of a business, more likely to own their residence, less likely to have changed home address in the previous 4 years, more rural, etc.  In contrast, a substantial portion of the Dem vote typically comes from younger voters, first time voters, or first time voters i that locale, &amp; urban, so tend to register relatively closer to the given election, far more often than Rs in the context of voter registration drive. 

Finally, in any election involving an incumbent as one of the contestants, a far more reliable co-relate, at this stage at least, comes from the favorable-unfavorable ratings of the incumbent, without regard to opponent - that is, against a "generic" candidate from the opposing party. But even just that measure, absent any other factor (IOW 'all other things being equal' - which they of course never are in the real world, so instead, 'all other things being equal' pretty much comes down to averaging out historical polling experience since WWII, which itself skews to GOP nominees by 5:3), operates somewhat differently when the incumbent is a Democrat versus when the incumbent is a Republican. That's because, absent consideration of the favorable-unfavorable ratings that SPECIFICALLY apply to who in particular actually ends up contesting the general, the GOP has done a far more effective job of selling it's brand, historically to older land-line voters. 

There's lots of other reasons that suggest this poll is pretty much useless in terms of have any PREDICTIVE value (tho it may have OTHER value), but that's more than enough for now.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ykw5zl</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tz1k</id></website><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/shep-smith-talks-to-the-romneys-and-their-sons-on-saturday-night-live/</link><postedTime>2012-03-04T04:43:35+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-04T15:37:27+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mqvpx8</id><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/shep-smith-talks-to-the-romneys-and-their-sons-on-saturday-night-live/#comment-455960774</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7zl7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-04</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>