<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwdd0e/update/2012-03-30T09:46:27/f19b8e972cbd5dd05e4779632a85ec5bc7018c030f56a25ff58bdab978d37265</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Just like here, Elfo appointed by Kremen, and as shown in those Federal District Courts, with that Ku Klux  of 1871, 42 USC 1983?

What's the difference in Idaho or the 4th Corner?

Deputies Jeremy Freeman and Trevor Vander Veen should be in hot water.  Their actions in tasering, arresting, and charging Brian Wiederspohn with assault have gotten their employer, the Whatcom County, Washington Sheriff's Department, socked with a $500,000 judgment for false arrest and malicious prosecution.  But that's no skin  the deputies' noses.  The judgment will be satisfied by taxpayers, and neither deputy has been charged with a crime, lost his job, or even been disciplined.

Despite attempting to frame an innocent man.

Despite tasering an an innocent man.

And despite lying about their actions in court.


On December 28, 2004 Freeman and Vander Veen paid a visit to Brian Wiederspohn's home to arrest Wiederspohn's daughter's boyfriend.  They had an arrest warrant, but not a search warrant, which the law required in order for the deputies to enter Wiederspohn's house without the owner's permission.  Confronting Wiederspohn at the door, they asked to enter anyway, and were refused.

Stories differ at that point on what happened next.  Freeman claims that he put his foot in Wiederspohn's doorway (to balance on a "rickety, wooden stairway" outside the door) and Wiederspohn slammed the door on Freeman's foot.  (Wiederspohn claims Freeman just Cold-cocked him, Vander Veen tasered him, and the two arrested him.)  In any case, Freeman and Vander Veen tasered and beat up Wiederspohn, hauled him to jail, and had him charged with assaulting an officer.  Both filed incident reports, specifically mentioning the "rickety, wooden stairway," and claiming that Wiederspohn made the first move.

Both were lying?

The Northern Border Counties Always require a Klansmen for Sheriff!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ztwzv</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dne9</id></website><link>http://www.bellinghamherald.com/2012/03/29/2459143/white-supremacist-running-for.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:45:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:46:27+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwdd0e</id><link>http://www.bellinghamherald.com/2012/03/29/2459143/white-supremacist-running-for.html#comment-480755058</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8qeaq</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>