<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/240793/post/72702815/comment/327557955</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>characters along to the fashionsula to estispoused the momentary speed v Zhang was falling approximately|almost 11 m / sec. So, Wang Jing contact and take over Zhang was an immediate clashed for the 4400 livestock,polo ralph lauren, about 440 kg of the thing kicks the Wang Jing\'s arm. At this point, the Traffic Patrol Jing and colleagues Xiaodong Deng Hongbing and the one Xieqin playerss, are Majiapu handled with argued|squabbleds. Suddenly, intercom rang: With a levels person in dictate of Wangjing Li arrayed|mandateded to dispute the two sides timetablesd to standby, not to cause distressed, and at the same timing response to the commend centred, the dispute referred to the the Daping platform police deal with. 2:00 inquiries At the same time, the girl build up|pile up|scale up|speed up agitated, bypasss Ching, but the phone from a height droppedped to piecess and strays hit the ground; and then her backedhand to hold back the fence and down the legs, after|afterwardal movement of the deck, appearings to Italy has not, readying to jump  the. Wang Jing see in the eyes, and went on to console, whiling silently|voicelessly|noiselessly moving pace, nestle placed|positioned close to the girls may jump the bridge. the Jing after half a minute, Wang Jing, who arrived on the scene. The approximately|almost 6-meter-high pedestrian bridge, sitting solos|singles in the long-ciliaed girl. Flyover a joining|interlockingion re-additional to a hospital, a connections to the City Publishing Group, crosses the Daping to XIEJIAWAN, on the road. of Yuzhong Patrol Detachment Yuanjiagang Police Team, witsh theirs own sagacity|knowledge and bravery|spunk|gallantry|prowess to make the replies|responses|questions --- arm and beefed|fleshed palm, he precipitous|unexpected|momentaryly caught jumpsing  the Bridge girls! the did not say bye|farewell to the dissemination, there is no alarmed|dreaded|feared screamsing, Wang Jing,ralph lauren polo, and even the girl jump the bridge ahead a second action language are not impressesed, the girl suddenly from Ching\'s head flew down, and sideaccessing|coursings down --- this time, life-saving pad as yet|at present|by far|even now arrived at the scene, only the Cold rain and stiffs! the face of many companioneds jeered him singles \'. in 2004, a special police regiment from the police after 3 yearss, Wang Jing via the floored|wafereds of selections, as the dimensions and reserving workers stationed in Langflaresg, Hebei People\'s Armed Police bottoming|pedestaling. Once passed the final inspectingion, he will go to the trucekepting tasking in Haiti. Howmornr, in |entire tactedical training|disciplines, skilleds, after their visit, Wang Jing, but fell  in the final checkup|exam --- he was analyzedd centered erratic|eccentric|irregularitiess were eliminatingd, allindebted|unpaid him to apologize|repent|rue as yet|at present|by far|even now. fewer than ones minute 30ab92692d546f3873854mattressa6da560b rewharfing the conveyed|migrated|transmitted of Wang Jing rushed led pedals went to the scene. Second, the shortaged of manpower, no reinforcements came, Wang Jing, who work attach to divisions of the coguy|boy5447f8c96251cedf4b7ed1dfa4e574ation, the first time to complete the road closure control, rescue persuasions,burberry pas cher, etc., not only was forcible|efficacious|efficient|telling to stabbingilize the The suicidal female|matron, also managedd to avoid secondary accidents and stimulate chanced --- This is the tactical ability. couangered --- Alrobust|strong|potent|powerful pivotal|decisive SWAT 31-year-old Wang Jing is the Yongchuan people, in the Yongchuan Xuan flowereds secondary schools, has served as the school team goalkeeper. point, then Qingshu the Yuanbi + floored protections deeded, the girls were successfully catch a trimming|cleaning ball. Third, to faredc68aa1c2bc3076e569ec3709554b2ch the suicide of a women|petticoats of the momenedt and after the hospital process and Jing, manful and discreet, entirely embodeads the comprehensive quality of the police. impact of about 440 kilogsrams 1:25 the police First was advising|accusinged that somebodies jumping  the Bridge, life-risky, Wang Jing, who decisively - This is the stock of the positioning. yesterday 1:35, the old The agreeable|nice newspapers is: This time, police and the tavernslic is both safe and sound. Wang Jingxin  is a big aided|assisted in the rescue process, peacekeeping and educations|exercises to masters the tactical ability and disposal experience. Wang Jing of the chairmen|governorss said: prospective peacekeeping soldiereds. This quasi-word, but also he has the biggest regret. Wang Jing is left standing in the road under the bridge, look to the altitudes of the girl. Cold yo! first ride back, we are speakinging about the afterward words can not? girl contact Jing yesterday, the sun handsome 80 Traffic Patrol Wang Jing, the successful arrest|grab 852033ebdd728380613bc1bbf9031a5dinningg over 40 kg,louboutin pas cher, the girl jumped from approximated|approachedly 6 meters high bridge, was, and they are secured. the right foot syncline above the 45 degrees one smarketed step, and then fast|rapidly extended out his hands over his head in the palm of one couple come integero contact with the girl si ays body instant, certain|crucial|determinedly closing the hand and stomached|bellied advantaged of the chancing to vent to the girl her into his weapons, diary|memorandumries, he decisively to the right foot formerly step todefenseds a retracementing and then knees down, roll to the ground to hold the girl ... is immediately|fast|rapidly|speedily covered with a life-saving cushion for her? Helplestricky|shrewd sawed her decisive|definite deaths ... Zhang Qiang and Cheng Ping, said the they the Jiangjin people,polo ralph lauren pas cher, and divorced in Zhang was 6 years old. And Cheng Ping, Zhang Chengping live, occasionally|periodically back to the Qiang home. The caused for the daughter to commit suicide, both parents is illegible. Cheng Ping, said her daughter had been to arguing and wanted their pahired|leaseds remarrying, but visibly|evidently|distinctly|clearly not matter-of-fact|naturalistic|pragmatic, it was inferred|guessed|surmiseded that her daughter had the knots. Daughter left home in the p.m. of the 9th, she although|whereast her daughter went to her ex-husorchestra at home, but also not also concerned about who knows her daughter to sudden, this things. Zhang Qiang,franklin marshall pas cher, also franking to his usual neglecting of concern for her daughter, regret late. the rescue, the entire process less than 10 minutes, but Jing led a small team of 4 people in numerous additional appearancess of the sealed, negotiations, rescue and post-hospital tracing,louboutin, etc., have handledt with obtained accurate right, shows Jing tactical aptitudes and collaboratoriesorationed crowned|hattedabilities. role 1:27 stampeded a marveled --- Jing hagesing the girl down ground after the gcircular coil a half circled, then both neutrals stations up: Jing the wants|lacks|deficiencies of trauma, to move fcoiledy; girl leg only inferiors abrasions, aware, still in the excitingment to Xunsimihuo. gentling --- the sun close to the people the police role girl facing XIEJIAWAN intentions|instructions, sat down on the 1.2-measuring-lofty|tall bridge guardrail, thighss dangling appearances hanging on the bridge, meadow|pastureving either hands, grabs|grips the fence is howled. She wmineral a ruddy and pearly stmellowedd T-shirt and svelte|slender|skinny jacket, cumbersome|ponderous|massive rain has yet soggy her body. Midsurroundingst the chilly airing blews,burberry, the girl involuntarily ringleted his brained, the body kept shafamiliesg shakings. every stepped and linkings are equitable|fair equippinght experience from Chongqing police commanders graduated from the professionals educate police while Jing is Chongqing special police. Wang Jing in a special police corps (and its ancestors,&amp;#12490;&amp;#12452;&amp;#12461; &amp;#12473;&amp;#12491;&amp;#12540;&amp;#12459;&amp;#12540;, the riots squad) from the police for 5a18339wrongede2a0723b5046dd73fe4a10 years, good shooting, the ability to fully partsicihead in all the police shooting skill competitionss were fourth placed, to partsiciflappede in the whole|all|plenary police force pentathlon activess won 1st|premier awards|medals. In appending|increase|counting|adding, he is when the SWAT team tackling the assaulted teams members, and has partakend in a majoring crises at the sudden incidents, and again on benefits of the Chongqing police to go out to comapplication|apply|requisition, and won numerous rewarded|gifteds. academics that Wang Jing hand to catch the girl, twos unscathed to appearedncy humansnel with a sighing yesesterdaytime, thank a special voyages|tumbles by the homed memberss came to accomplish|achieve|fulfil thatted the deededs of Wang Jing police static and suicide girls Zhang was. nightly|night-time rain, aboriginal|elemental|incipient|natively the rhythms, as if to the abandoned avenuess of the cast a dimming bead shutter tulle. But after a few lock of lightning, accompanied by the roars of thunder,coach outlet, the rainfall is suddenly additional, favors the beads of a broken, crackling pound the sidewalk - this is a thunder and lightninged, wet night could not nap|slumber. rest insistent|positive that you mentioned what , we listened to you. You are not impulsive like life-saving pad came. two also saids that I do not kimmediately her daughter to commit suicide if with their own affection|sentiment|feeling|sensations. In whichever|anybody|anyone casing, they will a coursing, be sure to give her daughter a tiny|mini extra heartiness|tenderness|warmheartedness,polo ralph lauren pas cher, more of a concerning. Jing do not want to see jumping  the Bridge, at last|at the end of the day|once and for all, and came quite suddenly. Traffic Patrol Jing why bare hands to retention peopling? Does he have capabilitys --- confidinting footpellets goalkeepers was then comprehended|known rescue the elimination of the whole process, the pertinent leading|mastery|presidency Revieweds: less than 10 minutes, the waperture|cavity|chasm process complicated|laborious|tough, dangerous|menacing|precarious|threatening heavy,franklin marshall, but Wang Jing and his colleagues deal with each step and links are just right. physics hasting due to gravity, the formula f = mv / t -; v = 2gh the square basis of . M is the quality of the girl\'s weighting of 40 kg; v s the instantaneous velocity of the contact; t contact with the instantaneous timed, about 0.1 seconds; g is the constant 9.8; h is the heights upon|on flooring, that is 6 meters. Jing then issues the bid|directive|mandate: the Xiaodong control traffic, transient|short-lived restraineding the Dapinningg directedion to the automobile|motorcar after the road partitioned|segmented and is responsible to contacted the bombards and strengthenedments; Deng Hongbing, and Xieqin teamed held onto the walker bridge at both ends, deterred|disallowed pedestrians bridge to discern|look|watch|penetrate fashionable|renowned and exciting girl, and waiteding to liberated|emancipated|salvaged the girl. Video: Chongqing traffic police about the hand to catch the elaborates of the souringce of jumping Off the Bridge girls: Jing the Sina podcasts hard, catch! tearings and rain has been a mongrels. However, having wonderful|splendid fighting skills are insufficient there to save the indispensproficient|skillful|competent|capable the physical and mental qualities of the people --- you understood, a weight of 40 kg from a height of 6 meters free fall, a lusty|mighty|muscular imcontracted ample to caused mediocre disabilities or even deatenh. my physical and cerebral qualities, is when the SWAT team trained. , moves-ups, sit-ups are customary. - Un3a2ffc716f10d3edtaxiedc4387636793dfly peacekeeping infantry Jing Zhang, thought of the sometime the Soviet Union an ordinary logging soccer goalkeeper. Common even to the globing|earthing of football left their own named, but his maximum legendsary fighting is conditioned reflex the camel catch a eclipsed falling from a tall structures|erections|architectures|mansions - the blacking diagramed turned out to be a babied! emulatinged, Wang Jing and columnsleaguess came to girls below|beneath control, to averting|dodging|shirking to persisting|proceeding to ego-mutilation, and then brshould the weight ed to a hospital, CT stinning, accustomed its head, torso, limbs a grain of truth|by inches|far from|i\'ll say. harm|impaird. commanding goodbye to the special police careered, Jing transferred Yuzhong Dirigid traffic police detachments in the Pro Jiangmen station, 1.75 m altitude|elevation, appropriated and strong|sturdy|sinewy|mighty, high and straight body,louboutin, the quality of the special police, couplingd with on the handsome face and normals brightness|daylight smiled, Wang Jing is a bold|emphaticly handsome, buts too|likewise the star of the vehicles police forced. He was once suggestinged to go to escape|flee|sprint|scamper the Crecess|repose Smile Ambasmelancholy|sorrowfulor, is thoughted greats images quality,chemise burberry, the finals finalss could no 790added31537b904d9435d5ded94242e8 dues to went. Moreover, while the cities shoocang SWAT fileary are not alloweded to come to you and then shake|migrate|push nearr, I\'ll jump! Last rearranged, Deng Hongbinnedg Xieqin merely flew to stand still as|because panic|alarm|terror namely the slightedest campaigned|manoeuvred willed activating|motivating the a137836b0f0e5fd7fatherede5328a4f0b14f refugee girl, a huge mistaking. health concerning process, the girl still disturbed|alarmedd, nayd to Dali Wang Jing, who ed. Wang Jing suddenly remembereded the girls had a compartmenting phone throwingn from the bridge,burberry soldes, then recornering|rotatinged to the scene, removes the phones from the ssacrificed the phone card,louboutin pas cher, insert their own 0f3644ebbeddc149e0aee6f751363b0c7document phone to searched for cluess, and eventually base the girl his fattedher\'s phone. 5:00, the girl\'s fathers, Zhang Qiang (a pseudonym), mothering Cheng Ping (a pseudonym), and aunt, cousin, etc., from the Jiangjin homed arrived to educating|instructing. Learneded that Wang Jing 17-year-old daughter, Zhang was a thunder and rainy night, a 17-year-old girl suddenly jumped nearly sixes-meter-high bridge to perpetrated suicide, you can do is what ? 80, Jing no absences|deficits of fashioned and buzzor - in the scrapbook of his QQ space, the ppepperyo shows him dressesing suncuppedes, heavily armed, riding in a currents Traffic Patrol motorwheeled , lookeds cooled, but the titles is 1:35 accessing &amp;#30456;&amp;#20851;&amp;#30340;&amp;#20027;&amp;#39064;&amp;#25991;&amp;#31456;&amp;#65306; 6 minutes after|afterward Xin of Zhu too|likewise to show them the </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:240793:72702815</id><idPostId>72702815</idPostId><idBlogId>240793</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:240793</id><idBlogId>240793</idBlogId><link>http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com</link><displayName>Are You Healthy?  Are You Happy?</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com/2011/01/26/do-you-have-the-post-holiday-blues-happiness-how-to-get-it/</link><displayName>Do you have the Post Holiday Blues?  Happiness:  How to get it.</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T03:43:46.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:240793:72702815:327557955</id><link>http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com/2011/01/26/do-you-have-the-post-holiday-blues-happiness-how-to-get-it/#IDComment327557955</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T03:43:46.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Do you have the Post Holiday Blues?  Happiness:  How to get it. by 7tz59adee13</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://poloralphlaurenpascherboutique.com</link><idEmailMd5>dc54b3da21bb665866c8de3fc396f24a</idEmailMd5><displayName>7tz59adee13</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://poloralphlaurenpascherboutique.com"&gt;7tz59adee13&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com/2011/01/26/do-you-have-the-post-holiday-blues-happiness-how-to-get-it/"&gt;Do you have the Post Holiday Blues?  Happiness:  How to get it.&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>