<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjn4x/update/2012-03-26T14:38:27/acacd287b605053f2e1f55caaceba66e18de4cfb1132ca2ffd144560de46de63</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk9zsl</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hynpt</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I hear you man. I don't have a problem giving a pat on the back to G-Mac. G-Mac was in the final group and did not get it done. I  like to hear from the players that did not get it done, I learn a lot about them. In G-Mac's case, his post interviews were in keeping with the highest standards of Golf and the spirit and intention of golf. I like that, it's a learning moment for young people .

As far as  goes, I heard a number of times on the TV  complementing Mac on a good shot, I saw them speaking with each other, I saw them enjoying the Heat of competition and the  of the sport. True sportsmanship. Tiger put himself in a very dark place and a burden he alone will have to carry. He or I or anyone of us can not change the past, we live in the present to shape the future. In his post interview he gave thanks to the people that have been helping him, his friends and the fans. He has a hard road ahead of him, for there are many that live in the past, for me, I'll enjoy the present and look forward to the future. 

Ya, I'm on that gravy train.
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rnqzm</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/9dd2</id></website><link>http://www.golfchannel.com/news/golftalkcentral/what-we-learned-arnold-palmer-invitational-2012/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T00:02:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:38:27+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjn4x</id><link>http://www.golfchannel.com/news/golftalkcentral/what-we-learned-arnold-palmer-invitational-2012/#comment-476617629</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h82xx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>