<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi6od7/post/2012-03-22T22:31:57</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mjebbl</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rk8cg</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> 3 - Certainly you don't want to claim that what is moral is whatever increases your own power. Such an elitism may be attractive to a young adult trying to make his way in the world - just think how popular Nietzsche is among college students - but it doesn't scale.

I started to write a refutation of Rand's ethics, but then I remembered that Pigliucci did that already. Really well. Read it here: http://rationallyspeaking.blogspot.com/2010/11/about-objectivism-part-iii-ethics.html

Here's the beginnings of my refutation: https://gist.github.com/2166198

There is a reason Rand is rarely taught in philosophy classes; and there is *so* much more philosophical work out there, I find it very difficult to sympathize with your (and others' *Cough* Dream and James Steele *Cough*) enthusiasm for Rand's work. Certainly, her books are inspiring, but don't for a minute think that they are the end-all-be-all of philosophy.

8 - You can't know that "it will be because we continued to use reason." The point is this: Why did the Greeks need Apollo to pull the sun across the sky? Because it helped to explain the world around them.

Why do we need science, and logic, and reason? Because it helps to explain the world around us.

Logic and science is inadequate though; Cornel West and others explain this. If my close friend dies, I can learn about the biochemical reactions that cause me to feel sad. But knowing that information won't make it any easier for me; I won't be satisfied with that answer. But if I read Seneca and realize that "the reaper doesn't discriminate" or I read Camus and contemplate the absurdity of life or I turn to poetry or fiction or jazz or even theology or whatever, these things I can find  in. And it's different for everyone. Rorty, I've been told, turned to poetry when on his deathbed. These things are outside of the realm of science: they are creative, artistic, and appeal to the powerful emotions within us. And who's to say that it's *wrong* for me to find Comfort in jazz music? If Coltrane's smooth sax helps me understand and make it through a life-crisis, is it really less important than logic and reason?

That's just one facet of the argument. Think how math, physics, chemistry all explain basically the same phenomenon, but they do it in very different ways. Even within math you have geometry, calculus, statistics. Newton (and Leibniz) invented calculus; who will invent the next language that we use to explain the world around us?</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6a3nek</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/1046</id></website><link>http://www.joaoeira.com/post/19122706398</link><postedTime>2012-03-12T09:11:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T02:31:57+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi6od7</id><link>http://www.joaoeira.com/post/19122706398#comment-474154863</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hcgv</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-12</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>