<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msdrr9/update/2012-03-27T09:28:41/5a0c92678ffc2b89ed50f2fe4532abbbe0bc3f4757d94dbb1e4c1ffff3744865</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I have run into two curmudgeonly "difficult" writers in my career: Jacques Barzan and Thomas Sowell. It is well known that Barzun had little use for copyeditors, and it was my misfortune as a young copyeditor to be assigned the task of editing a volume of essays that included one by Barzun. I do not recall having done very heavy copyediting, but I do recall to this day the ferocity with which Barzun objected to just about everything I had suggested. By the time I encountered Sowell I was an acquiring editor, and I handled two of his early books at Princeton University Press, the first being his revised dissertation on Say's Law. I don't recall having had any trouble with Sowell over copyediting at PUP, but when I was later director at Penn State University Press and we had agreed to publish his book titled "Race and Culture,"  I soon learned that he had become resistant to copyediting, so much so that he refused to accept any changes recommended by one of our top free-lance editors. In response, I said we would publish the book only if he agreed to allow us to include on the copyright page a notice to the effect that the publisher assumes no responsibility for errors in the book attributable to the author's refusal to accept copyediting. Sowell refused, and we mutually agreed to cancel the contract. That action also required us to return to the NEH the subvention it had awarded us for the book, though the NEH, as I recall, kindly allowed us to deduct the cost of copyediting, which was over $2,000. In trying to find a reference to Barzan's jaundiced view of copyediting via a Googlke search in writing this comment, I came across this essay by Sowell in which he refers to Barzan's view but also recounts his own experiences with copyeditors, whom he considers the "bureaucrats of the publishing industry": http://www.tsowell.com/About_Writing.html. Without naming names, Sowell refers to his experience with us at PSUP thus: "Fighting back Always entails the possibility of losing. But, with intrusive editors, not fighting back guarantees that you will lose. After engaging in a tug-of-war with one publisher over their editorial fetishes, I simply offered to return the royalty advance and cancel our contract. He accepted. Months went by before I found another publisher—but it was one offering a larger advance and less copy-editing. It didn’t have to turn out that way, of course, but Faint heart ne’er won fair lady." He went on to publish this book with Basic Books, and it did very well in both sales and critical reception: http://www.amazon.com/Race-And-Culture-World-View/dp/0465067972. Some day I'll have to go back and compare the copyedited MS (which I still have) with the published version to find out just how much less copyediting was done by Basic Books.---Sandy Thatcher</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y943f</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/l7r5</id></website><link>http://chronicle.com/blogs/linguafranca/2012/03/23/are-you-a-difficult-writer/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T19:52:57+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-27T13:28:41+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msdrr9</id><link>http://chronicle.com/blogs/linguafranca/2012/03/23/are-you-a-difficult-writer/#comment-477398870</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5z4kh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>