<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/8k9a6j/update/2011-03-29T14:24:33/705895bdfe5eb82885a1fb7b3600777e3478865a716a945229263028e0e1110e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This is worth repeating in my humble opinion...

Civilain use, military use and govt agency use are all different. Civilians have no need to check on anyones condition etc. I did not say they(bad guy) were not a potential threat when down...I said "finishing" them  is unacceptable. If you hit properly...like all these would be experts would have you believe...then you have no problems..but we know it is bull...so the individual goes down...do you know many people hit with a shotgun? Do you know many people that function well wounded, Bleeding out? If you are in a 'safe" position, with proper tactics, light and shotgun...you can readily see wether or not follow up action is necessary...you do not need to expose yourself, risk life or limb..you stay put, you watch..and if it appears the threat is still relevant...you shoot. 

Important lesson for all...

Then when you are explaining to the authorities what you did, there will be no question that you were in a defensive mode, took defensive actions and at no time unwittingly or willingly exposed yourself to possible harm, you did not advance, you did nothing overly agressive..get it. You did everything you could to avoid the situation. The end result of which was unfortunate and ended in a possible loss of life which you tried to avoid. You were justified in your use of deadly force to stop an "imminent" threat to your/families life. Killing should Always be a last resort...</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/5hoerc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry2d</id></website><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=42558</link><postedTime>2011-03-28T14:06:51+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-03-29T18:24:33+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/8k9a6j</id><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=42558#comment-174215187</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c7ft3</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>