<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwf09n/post/2012-03-31T02:02:43</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Subscription models for content are not a stable form of revenue and you'll constantly be chasing new subscribers to replace those who fall to the side over time.  You're essentially fighting for the traffic and then trying to convince that traffic to pay for what most people feel should be 'free'.  Subscription models also struggle with SEO unless you're doing some kind of IP delivery.  My experience has been that it's an unnecessary Headache.

The traditional CPM or CPC models, when handled correctly, do not interfere with the content and if targeted by the visitors prior activity, can result in meaningful ads to that individual.  It's attractive to most people because it's easy to implement and often yields a smaller but consistent stream of income.  

I'm on the other side of Jim's argument.  Unless a site is so narrowly focused around a product, I don't care if the ads relate to the content of my sites.  I want the ads to be meaningful to the visitor.  If the company serving the ad understands that you recently searched for a Nikon camera, then my all means show something photography related for ad content.  You might not buy a camera, but you sure might check out an ad for scan cafe and that's good for the advertiser and me because I'm sending them targeted traffic.

As for sponsored posts, I  wonder if the advertiser had any input or creative control of the content, so I find them a little questionable.  I love Legos and my kids love Legos, but I'm here for your voice and not that if the Lego people.  I don't like feeling that it's been compromised.

It's easy to test various models and see which offers the best balance of maintaining readers and an acceptable income each month.  I'll let you in on a .  I almost Always choose the higher revenue model because there are mouths to feed....and we really like Legos.

Good luck Jon~!
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67lm6i</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/h5i3</id></website><link>http://blurbomat.com/2012/03/30/online-advertising-for-indie-publishers-banners-alone-wont-pay-the-bills/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:37:27+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T06:02:43+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwf09n</id><link>http://blurbomat.com/2012/03/30/online-advertising-for-indie-publishers-banners-alone-wont-pay-the-bills/#comment-481582892</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7x4r</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>