<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/a77z09/update/2010-10-12T17:20:05/b836bc4ca4b01743c52b02f92d703710bc0b70c89a3949ffe408b2674fcaba82</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Anecdote: Valerian root (which can also be readily found in capsules) did nothing more than kick  a bad bout of Anxiety when I tried it. Melatonin, on the other hand, works wonders. It is a hormone, so very specific reactions can occur  on what other medical conditions you have, but a broad-based statement of safety can easily be made on this one.  on the person, you'll want to look in the range of 1-5mg. Personally I take 3mg, though I can get by on less, it just takes a little longer. Keep in mind that melatonin will basically reinforce a specific sleep cycle, so if you take it at 8:00 P.M., expect to be up at around 4:30 in the morning. Personally I take it around 10:00 which gets me up in plenty of time for work... If the 5mg dose still isn't phasing you, shoot for a complex with vitamin B, or just take a small B complex with it, as that tends to help people who have issues taking it alone.

Seriously, I cannot stress this enough: Try it. It's cheap, and worth a shot for the vast majority of people in whom it is perfectly safe. I wish I had discovered it years earlier than I did, as I'd have been much better ...

Additionally, caffeine intake is something that I think plagues American society in this arena. I don't think it's inherently bad, and it can in fact be quite beneficial to some, but people need to understand the chemical, rather than going by rules of thumb... The half-life of caffeine is 4 hours, so you'll need at least that much time before you can expect a decent night's sleep, but the other half is still there, so in general you are better Off limiting your overall intake throughout the day to see how that affects your quality of sleep.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/8nrc7j</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2010/HEALTH/10/12/rs.sleep.aids/index.html</link><postedTime>2010-10-12T12:34:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2010-10-12T21:20:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/a77z09</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2010/HEALTH/10/12/rs.sleep.aids/index.html#comment-86379686</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/huw4u</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2010-10-12</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>