<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3x1zq/update/2012-03-29T14:00:52/237262ba53f3e245c8a3e185f9545cd0cdef5615d1663cebf19bcfe29ef39567</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Harvey, causality is intertwined with time. If there was no space-time at the Big Bang then there was no Cause. This is why I'm leaning in the direction of there being a universe prior to ours that gave birth to our universe. And perhaps a universe prior to that one that gave birth to it and so on. Why am I saying this instead of saying God did it? Well God is suppose to be love.  The Christian counselor, Gary Chapman, lists five primary ways we express love. Gifts, physical touch,  of service, quality time, and words of affirmation. God doesn't do any of those things. He doesn't help around the house, compliment me or give me hugs, neither does He talk back when I talk to Him. He doesn't say thank you or I love you. How does God express His love to you? If it's only platonic then why are Christians called the Bride Of Christ? Have you ever heard of the doctine of union? Again, we all have insecurities. Religious believers or God(dess) believers fill the need or void with Gods and Goddesses. If I was ever to believe in a God again it would have to be a Goddess. I'm not attracted to the masculine. I'm not gay, you see. If I'm going to entwine my soul or come into a love union with another soul (filling the void or insecurites) I would prefer a female. Let me put it to you this way. When you worship someone they are at the center of your life. Why would I place a man (Christ) at the center of my life unless I was attracted to the masculine? I'm not enthralled or stricken with awe and wonder at the masculine. I am with the feminine because I'm not gay. If it's going to be a soul union between two people then I prefer a woman. I don't want to be the Bride Of Christ in other words. If I'm going to find wholeness and completion by filling the void (insecurities) then I would rather bond with a woman and fall in love with her rather than with a man and be His Bride. Or I can simply love-and take care of myself, Gain a true perspective of my value and worth and love others from a secure position. Embrace death as part of life. If I'm afraid of death then I'm afraid of life. By embracing death I embrace life and everything about it. It is from here one is transformed and they see things differently. What matters now is to live your life well and to the fullest. The fear of death is removed as Anxieties and fears are released.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l5xdh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry26</id></website><link>http://debunkingchristianity.blogspot.com/2012/03/more-criticisms-from-dr-reppert-on-otf.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T19:51:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:00:52+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3x1zq</id><link>http://debunkingchristianity.blogspot.com/2012/03/more-criticisms-from-dr-reppert-on-otf.html#comment-479701963</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/59byr</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>