<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkpwds/update/2012-03-26T16:43:03/f5d1564308e2039f12b5aaa2a6e89d1857afec7466fa4650f04267a80807bc98</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I actually went and did some research because in no story about "pink slime" was there any mention of what was actually harmful about it.  In fact, I learned some interesting things about ammonium hydroxide (ammonia and water) from Wikipedia and other sources, including the fact that it occurs naturally in our stomachs.

What I could not find, anywhere, were what health risks pink slime actually posed in and of itself.  The whistle-blower at the FDA blew the whistle not because of health risks but because we're being ripped Off into thinking we're buying higher quality meat.  The trick of pink slime is that it is very lean, so it gets added to fattier ground meat to bring the percentage of fat content down.  It also doesn't taste good, making for mealier, drier burgers ("So that's what's been going on!" I exclaimed).

But as far as I can tell, the cries of "OMG ammonium hydroxide" are Overheated nonsense.

If you really do want to avoid pink slime, buy meat labelled "Organic" as that term is regulated and may not include things like "lean finely-textured beef".  Or, if you remember the good old days, don't buy "ground beef" buy "ground chuck" or "ground round" which is a specific named cut of meat (and have the butcher grind it for you).</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lauw1</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gblz</id></website><link>http://www.newser.com/story/comments/142718/work-halted-at-75-of-pink-slime-makers-plants.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:40:46+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T20:43:03+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkpwds</id><link>http://www.newser.com/story/comments/142718/work-halted-at-75-of-pink-slime-makers-plants.html#comment-476728736</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hcmsz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>