<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mido61/post/2012-03-22T19:37:23</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>well i have 4 weapon classes you could use.... i dont like using smgs but i still think some people have good results with them..
 
PRIMARY- ACR- 2 attachments, silencer, extender mag (to keep on spraying and spraying)
                 -Type 95 (if used correctly)- 2 attachments, rapid fire(it kills in an instant!!!), silencer
                 -L86 LSW(it kills with three bullets at close, mid and semi-long range even with
                                  silencer :o)- kick,silencer
                 -MK14- i love this weapon for medium and large maps- 2 attachments,silencer, 
                              rapid fire.(if you have fast fingers youll love this weapon!!!! 2 bullets
                              and its lights out for your enemy. if headshot you only need 1 bullet :D)
SECONDARY- stinger (take out any good killstreaks like ac130 :p or any annoying helicopter 
                          or pavelow :s)
LETHAL-semtex 
 
TACTICAL- Depends on your choice.... i use flash bangs
 
BLUE PERK- sleight of hand (if you like to be where the action is and need to keep shooting and shooting)
 
RED PERK- hardline (sucks when they kill you and u were  just 1 kill away from your killstreak... use this for a change.. if u use hardline pro  2 ASSIST KILLS COUNT AS ONE KILL FOR YOU!!! :D)
 
YELLOW PERK- marksmen (sucks when you all you see before dying is the bullets coming from a far away enemy. use this too see them from far away. TIP-if you cant see your oponent eventhough you see their name try shooting at the middle or their name and half a centimeter beneath it too. if u have the pro version and you like sniping it will let you hold your breath for double the amount of time)
 
KILLSTREAK- 1) sentry gun- if placed correctly u might get yourself a few kills. i usually get 3 
                            to 6 kills.
                        2) care pakage- u might get yourself a pavelow, juggernut,AC130 and 
                            more. usually u´ll get a sentry gun. but with this second sentry you
                            can cover the blind Spot of your first sentry. AWESOME FOR 
                            OBJECTIVE GAMES!!!!)
                        3) helicopter- if u use hardline like i do u´ll get it every death or 2.
 
DEATHSTREAK- second chance (kill the guy who put you on the floor. and to top it all kill yourself a guy or 2 before recovering hahahahaha)</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/m1orlg</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/m59</id></website><link>http://www.product-reviews.net/2011/11/08/best-gun-in-mw3-your-weapons-list-and-perks-setup/</link><postedTime>2011-11-08T06:13:28+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T23:37:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mido61</id><link>http://www.product-reviews.net/2011/11/08/best-gun-in-mw3-your-weapons-list-and-perks-setup/#comment-474061632</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-11-08</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>