<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw0wja/post/2012-03-31T13:58:18</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw0fmg</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a53fb</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Sadly being over weight CAN be genetic BUT it can also be due to a low self esteem, instead of popping "happy pills" to feel better they overeat. There is a reason some food is called " food".....supposedly it makes someone feel better after eating it. Also, back in "those days" children were told by their parents to "clean your plate, there are starving children in the world". 
Yes, being over weight is very unhealthy, and it does cost $$$ in medical bills, BUT on the other hand, so does someone who is anorexic or has bulemia and Vomits after eating to "stay thin" because they think they are fat or will get fat is just as serious a problem. These people DIE as often as someone who is over weight. Think about singer Karen Carpenter, she was very very thin &amp; it cost her life. Marie Osmond also had issues with fear of weight Gain, going up and down the weight scale puts health in danger as well.

No, I am NOT overweight, I am 5 ft tall &amp; weigh 112 lbs.....and YES, there are and have been over weight people in my family. 

Think before you make comments that really hurt, we ALL have issues with things WE may not want to admit....i.e. smoking or drinking too much, racking up credit cad bills by spending money we don't have etc.

 No one is perfect, we all have issues take a good long look at yourself before making horrific hurtful comments. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67xhtd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/31/living/fatshion-beauty-bloggers/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:07:43+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T17:58:18+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw0wja</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/31/living/fatshion-beauty-bloggers/index.html#comment-482048173</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ahhl5</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>