<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m1sc7x/update/2012-03-14T09:26:55/e7ef35cf75bb7e97dddb3cc01a2907d9becd9a50a266f9db220ee8c37eb95e81</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m1ima9</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g14do</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>His statement is pretty good.  It's not exactly what I would have wanted, which is more of an apology.  I didn't honestly expect they would apologize though, they want to save face.  If he thinks he's getting any brownie points for promising DLC though, he's dead wrong.  I don't want to pay money to get the ending which should have been included in the first place.  He's also still wrong on they Day One DLC, the game could have been delayed.  
Great games like Zelda and Super Smash Bros. do this all the time and the fans don't gripe because they know it will be worth it.  I just imagine that in the days before DLC a character like Javik would have been a great  to hide in the game, but now, who needs that when you can give Bioware/EA more money?  


Overall, I give him points for not being condescending towards gamers like a certain unnamed person from IGN was *Cough Colin Cough*.  

I have to say in response to cheezzhead that his point is ridiculous.  If you bought a car, it worked great, beautiful interior, extra options like satellite radio and you were loving it.  However, if there was some kind of flaw and the paint start to peel Off when it rained, wouldn't that ruin the purchase for you?  I mean, yeah, everything else is great and the car runs and does what it is supposed to, but the fact that it looks terrible because all the paint is peeling would really sour the whole thing for you.  This is a similar situation.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6cqa7s</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7d9s</id></website><link>http://xbox360.ign.com/articles/122/1220712p1.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-14T10:38:42+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-14T13:26:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m1sc7x</id><link>http://xbox360.ign.com/articles/122/1220712p1.html#comment-465071457</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/m1er1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-14</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>