<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9wbp7/update/2012-03-18T17:02:23/f965661a476afeaaffd7443353b0a068443fcd9abc3f2a47ade80c072b2a46e3</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9i75y</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rfrdc</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>It is your same attitude that is used against you and your people.  That narrow minded rhetoric based only on rage and emotion is simply that ... hate filed and narrow minded.  The only thing that can come from that attitude is ultimately war, murder, death and more of tragedy like this.  Senseless terrible horrifying.  Your people have butchered, murdered, raped ... as have SOME of all the people of the world.  So you are saying 300,000,000 people are evil barbarians because of the  of soldiers?   How many people did the soviets murder and kill how many people did the Khans of old murder?  How many died in the Iran-Iraq war?  How many have died in the fighting between India and Pakistan?  War produces senseless violence, killing and destruction.  The image of an innocent family brutally murdered should be forever seared into the minds of the entire planet ... this occurrence was one of supreme brutality and barbarity and can never be understood nor forgotten. 

Until the average citizens of the world stop hating each other this sort of senseless horror will continue.  If it isn't the Americans it will be the Chinese if it isn't the Chinese it will be the Indians or Brazilians or whatever powers arise in the future.  Don't you understand that?

The average American is outraged by this, they hate that our soldiers are overseas they hate that their fathers, brothers, cousins, sons and daughters were deployed to places they'd never heard of.  Almost all of the soldiers are from the poorest families in America, they are enticed to military service by military recruiters offering to pay for university education, etc.  They are told they'll never see service, they sign up to learn trades so they can earn a living, etc. and then they end up deployed for years on end learning little and being forced to be away from their wives, children, and families.  It clearly has driven some of them insane. Some of them were insane before they entered the military.  And clearly the training of the troops isn't adequate if things like this can occur and they have time and time again haven't they!  They have.  For years and nothing has been done to change things??  WHY!!!  People in America are outraged by that!! 

The vast majority, hundreds of millions in fact, of Americans oppose the war now they oppose having troops overseas.  But our government doesn't listen and when they do they are slow to .  Look at the occupy movement there are people in our streets camping out being tear gassed, pepper sprayed by our own authorities.  Some are there out of anger with the global economy, some are there out of anger over the environmental destruction occurring around the globe.  But if you walk those streets and ask those protesters to name a single thing they are angry about 99% of them would say the wars. 

You want to feel hate and blame ... blame Exxon ... blame Walmart ... blame British Petroleum ... blame the banks of Europe blame the billionaire oil princes of Saudi Arabia ... blame the international arms dealing companies.  Blame the generals of the world .. blame the Cold war Era military industrial complex that has desperately tried to justify its continued existence.  I believe in large part these wars were created, manufactured in order to keep those interests profitable after the end of the Cold war what were all those business interests that had spent the past 60 years engaged in the business of war to do?  Peace doesn't make profits for those companies.  These forces have done as much or more to perpetuate the wars than any nation.  Certainly those groups have been pushing for these wars and they have profited handsomely from the wars.  The rest of humanity has been robbed.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6erf6j</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/h8a5</id></website><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2012/03/201231862852921747.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-18T12:30:57+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-18T21:02:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9wbp7</id><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2012/03/201231862852921747.html#comment-468549123</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/m91bw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-18</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>