<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/234352/post/86320894/comment/329347172</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>,Sac Hermes 2011 NewGame notes ,lisser ghd, competing with and Duke for a Spot in the Houston rotation,Burberry Donne, struck out seven in five shutout innings in a Triple-A game at the Astros\' training complex. The 21-year-old Lyles is breaking in a curveball as his fourth pitch . . . The Astros signed former Oakland A\'s catcher . Blue Jays manager John Farrell said as long as McGowan\'s name stays  the medical reports,louis vuitton outlet, he will have a Spot in the rotation. Schafer learned a lot about leading  from the Braves. KISSIMMEE,Anna Segal wins WX Tignes Ski Slopestyle silver - ESPN Vide, Fla. -- The Astros are a long way from being a potent offensive team,nike pas cher, but it has to start somewhere,Nike Mercurial Victory Tf, and Houston is starting at the top of its batting order. \"I feel comfortable leading ,\" he said. \"A good leadoff guy can change a lot of outcomes. You set the tone for the whole game right away, and that\'s something that I enjoy doing.\" McGowan, bidding for a Spot in Toronto\'s rotation after three years of arm and knee problems, gave up one unearned run in his second spring start. Drabek followed and also allowed an unearned run. \"In eight years in St. Louis, I don\'t think we ever had a true leadoff hitter there,\" he said. \"A lot of teams don\'t,louis vuitton damier, and I think it can be a true advantage. I think Jordan and (Jason) Bourgeois both have a chance to do it.\" Jake Marisnick homered for the Blue Jays in the ninth inning. \"There\'s a lot of experience there. They helped me understand that you don\'t just go up there and hack away. There\'s a lot more to it than that,\" he said. \"You\'re setting the tone, you\'re taking pitches. Leading  is not so much about yourself. It\'s letting the guys behind you see pitches, working pitchers, giving your pitcher a break when he grounds out ... it\'s a complicated role. It\'s not just go up there and swing.\" hit a two-run double against Houston starter ,burberry borse, who gave up four runs and eight hits in four innings. \"He\'s been doing it all spring,\" Astros manager said. \"He\'s grown up and he\'s come to camp with a mission.\" \"It\'s even more  when he\'s throwing 92 to 95 (mph) with the sink that he\'s shown,\" Farrell said. \"He\'s passing every plateau,Burberry Uomini, and that constant buildup and endurance is where he\'s at.\" Blue Jays 6, Astros 3 Schafer joined the Astros in a trade last summer with Atlanta,More Sean Adams, where he was long regarded as a top prospect but rarely had a Spot open for him. He has a slot with the Astros, primarily because he embraces the leadoff role. New Astros general manager Jeff Luhnow is not about to take a legitimate leadoff man for granted. is batting .350 after seven games this spring,burberry borse outlet,Seattle Seahawks Football Clubhouse - ESPN, and the 25-year-old center fielder has been doing everything a leadoff man should do. He Reached base in all three plate appearances and scored twice in Thursday\'s 6-3 loss to the . and each pitched three solid innings for the Blue Jays. 
 
[WORDPRESS HASHCASH] The poster sent us \'0 which is not a hashcash value. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:234352:86320894</id><idPostId>86320894</idPostId><idBlogId>234352</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:234352</id><idBlogId>234352</idBlogId><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog</link><displayName>Wanton Wordsmith</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/</link><displayName>The day he went away</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-01T16:46:33.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:234352:86320894:329347172</id><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/#IDComment329347172</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T16:46:33.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The day he went away by hljfeos1625p</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://borselouisvuittonvendita1.com/</link><idEmailMd5>eb7d26f3a1645b277d8eba3638244b0c</idEmailMd5><displayName>hljfeos1625p</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://borselouisvuittonvendita1.com/"&gt;hljfeos1625p&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/"&gt;The day he went away&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>