<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/169114/post/71678645/comment/328173474</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>It&amp;#039;s probably obnoxious that I share my FaceBook conversations here.  But, you guys are family, so I just like sharing some of my thoughts.  If it gets annoying, PLEASE let me know. 
 
In the aftermath of a pretty passionate/ intense debate on the Trayvon Martin/ Zimmerman issue, yesterday.  One of my FB friends expressed appreciation and respect, though not in complete agreement.  So, I took the moment to explain my ardor or fervor, as it were, in making my points or driving them home, I added this. 
 
One of, if not my biggest issue with civil rights groups and advocates, is that most often, they center on ONE group - ONE particular &amp;#039;minority&amp;#039;. I have very little tolerance for Black rights issues, as well as Gay rights issues. These groups aren&amp;#039;t demanding equal rights, they are demanding SPECIAL rights. If everyone is so concerned about EQUAL rights, they should be JUST as passionate and zealous in defending the rights of everyone else, there should BE no splinter groups. Gays should stand for Women&amp;#039;s rights, Women should stand for Muslim rights, Muslims should stand for Hispanic rights, Hispanics should stand for Black rights, Blacks should stand for Gays&amp;#039; rights, etc.. There should only be ONE group, one LABEL - HUMAN. If you are human, you are entitled to the exact same rights EVERY other human - no exceptions. It&amp;#039;s really hard to respect the plight of the splinter groups, because the sentiment becomes, &amp;#039;why should your concerns take precedence over mine?&amp;#039; Why are you more important than me? However, if all of these groups came together, in solidarity, united, no one could question it - there would be communication between peoples, and IMAGINE the force they would be represent. Anytime people protest, advocate, speak out about injustice or the civil rights or an issue that hits home for them, with which they identify, it rings of self-involvement. It feels, to me at least, that they are only speaking out because it affects them personally, or someone they love. It&amp;#039;s selfish, self-serving, I cannot, in good conscience, get behind that or even have much respect for it. When we decide to grow up and fight for everyone, rather than just ourselves, our families, and our friends, we will understand the concepts of community - unity, and HUMANITY. Until then, we are spinning wheels. Paulus, I respect you, too - as well as your opinions. Please don&amp;#039;t mistake my passion for anger, disrespect, or judgment. I do get pretty passionate, sometimes - and I can definitely be a bit forceful, if not illustrative in the way I phrase my arguments. It&amp;#039;s just that I have spent my entire life feeling like an alien. Since I can remember, I have ALWAYS looked around at the world with puzzlement. It never made sense to me why we live the way we do, why we treat one another the way we do, why we relate to one another the way we do. Life is not meant to be easy, I know. But, it doesn&amp;#039;t have to be like this. The hatred, the rage, the fear, the Anxiety, the madness - they are ALL completely unnecessary. WE make it this hard. Yes, something are unavoidable. Yes, life is harsh. So, then, why make it worse. Why not try to make it easier for ourselves and everyone else by at least attempting to show some compassion, humanity, grace? No, we would much rather erupt in fury, it&amp;#039;s absurd - and it only adds to the madness. I have spent my entire life waiting for people to snap out of it and come to the realization that we are the same. We are all facets on the same diamond - we have different perspectives, but are connected to the same source, the same light sparkle within each of us. The ONLY things that separate us are TIME and SPACE. Had you been born Aug 22, 1973 at ORMC at 3:45 pm, to my parents, you would BE me. I would be someone else. There might be some variation, because our souls are unique, but our life experiences are a major factor in what shapes us. So what gives any of us the right to judge? Who are we to hate - we are only hating ourselves, because we ARE one another, just from different perspectives. This, all of this diminishes us all. We are SO much more than this. I&amp;#039;m just waiting for everyone else to figure that out. So, that&amp;#039;s a big part of why I get so passionate. I am SO tired of disappointment. Yes, I know. This is the world, deal with it. I HAVE been. I&amp;#039;m waiting for the world and humanity to change, to grow, to realize its own beauty, and to shed the shackles of despair and degradation and rise to meet and embrace its TRUE potential.  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:169114:71678645</id><idPostId>71678645</idPostId><idBlogId>169114</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:169114</id><idBlogId>169114</idBlogId><link>http://912wolverines.com</link><displayName>http://912wolverines.com/</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://912wolverines.com/code/</link><displayName>growl</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T01:14:45.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:169114:71678645:328173474</id><link>http://912wolverines.com/code/#IDComment328173474</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T01:14:45.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on growl by loca73</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://intensedebate.com/people/loca73</link><idEmailMd5>284fd5d8f892bb87048ccc4c2ff0f0d2</idEmailMd5><displayName>loca73</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://intensedebate.com/people/loca73"&gt;loca73&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://912wolverines.com/code/"&gt;growl&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>