<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jfek/post/2012-04-02T04:16:55</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwu783</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lbsqh</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>@avclub-88a202ed3e8edffaa7d5530011934ee2:disqus : Basically everything @avclub-3bca94e353e508c1a49bf984fc5c346d:disqus  said was true. To quote Pitchfork (I'm not usually one to quote Pitchfork because often their ideas about music are too out there for me, but this one was Spot-on): "'We Found Love' ranks among Ri's best singles because it recognizes that there's not much more that needs to be said: in three and a half minutes, the line moves from being a great pop lyric to a triumphant mantra to something suggestive of a whole spectrum of unspoken emotion. The best pop music transports you to somewhere beyond words, and Rihanna's strongest singles all seem to be in on this Secret. Need I remind you of some of her most powerful hooks: Ella-ella-ella-ay. Oh-na-na. Ay-ayy-ay-ayy-ay-ayy."
Umbrella was, hands down, my favorite pop song of the '00s because it had the perfect combination of a clever concept, great lyrics with a nice hook, warm-but-not-overly-warm vocals, and great production. We Found Love is quite similar, though without any cutesy concept behind it. I feel like maybe it could have had a bit more lyrical depth, but it still packed an emotional punch while being incredibly catchy. I think your problem with We Found Love and Umbrella is the same as my problem with Since U Been Gone and Toxic: personal taste.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zijro</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/march-31-2012,71681/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T05:02:41+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T08:16:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jfek</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/march-31-2012,71681/#comment-483342151</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lbsqh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>