<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3q3jz/update/2012-03-29T12:21:12/7054c464c7dd524f3376b7c66b5455fe0fc159cdbee52f85b294a48a5196146e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3d8zr</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/51o1w</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>A.Palmer, unfortunately you are incorrect.  The natural gas coming into your home is at ounces of pressure and LNG take hundreds of pounds of pressure.  OK, so you buy a pump, but now you are dodging the road taxes on the fuel (remember that the federal government charges over 50 cents per gallon in taxes on gasoline), so you go to jail.  We converted a lot of our corporate vehicles to LPG (propane) and had to pony up taxes to the state and feds.  By the time we hired all of the accountants required to track the usage, it was almost a wash in cost.  The only problem with LNG is that you have to contain the boil  when not running, so you either need to continue to idle your engine 24/7, or hook up to a vent line when you shut down.
I need to explain that  LPG (Liquified Petroleum Gas) is propane and or butane both of which can be kept in liquid state by pressurization.  NG (natural gas) is basically methane and is used as a pressurized gas.  Methane cannot be kept in liquid form (LNG) except by keeping it extremely Cold (-256F).  It will boil  and the boil  is what is used as fuel.  The boil Off will continue and if not vented either as fuel or to a vent line, the pressure will climb until it ruptures the tank or fuel lines.  But I have touted it for years for use on over the road truckers and for rail road trains that keep their engines running almost 24/7.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lsewc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry2d</id></website><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50486</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T21:03:27+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:21:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3q3jz</id><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50486#comment-479620778</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ypeut</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>