<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m37hw8/update/2012-03-29T06:59:36/90ad50d622927f3afd1342163c45e12a5d9b456b94bf69def29da2a688ecd46d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m37gi7</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c10i1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Let's start at the beginning...

Money *should* represent trust or faith between people.

After all, if I do something for you or give you something, I expect you to do something back. Money formalises that exchange. Means that we don't need to barter directly or  have goods on hand to trade.

Of course, finding something universally exchangable to represent 'money' which can't be faked is very hard. Human beings like to be lazy so the desire to cheat the system is overwhelming.

Gold doesn't work because it is limited. Is human ability to trust limited by the availability of shiny metal? I'm not a gold bug.

But we haven't found anything since which can work in this way. Paper money created by central banks worked for a long time. But now those who understand this and have set the system up in their favour with first access to the money  stand to  from it. Unfortunately power  does corrupt.

In the current world, money is created by central banks. The 'other side' of that equasion are paper / electronic IOUs ('assets') which will supposedly get paid back. But when and by whom? Or is the game just to devalue those by printing even more money and creating more IOUs?

You think the US will pay back it's trillions of dollars in debt?

That has what has happened for the last 40 years. And in this world of inflationary money, he who gets the most debt fastest will  win. Does that lead to a fair, honest, productive and efficient society?

I don't personally think so. Look around you... definitely not!

In reality, money should be able to be created as we exchange goods and services with each other. There on the Spot.

It may just be that with a network of connections Reaching out to everyone's pocket on earth (mobile / internet) that we can find a way to create an honest monetary system based on faith...</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z515f</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/finance/economics/houseprices/9172925/House-prices-fall-as-stamp-duty-holiday-ends.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T07:18:30+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T10:59:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m37hw8</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/finance/economics/houseprices/9172925/House-prices-fall-as-stamp-duty-holiday-ends.html#comment-479408474</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cu9hl</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>