<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi6f3u/post/2012-03-22T22:26:06</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miy6ug</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lwzl4</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>To prey? in context of the loneliness, despair, fear,  and materialism of our culture, I suppose you might think His words are "preying". His words were as  radical and courageous as He was. He doesn't care about the Pew survey. He doesn't care about the score and arguments.He cares about our hearts. I am sure you are a good person. But please--let go of the stereotypes.  Many Christians like myself feel embattled.  Do you know any Christians? You might  be very surprised that they are human beings who have hard lives, who cry, but and find grace and  and meaning in community and God. Christian or not, these are words we need. 

Blessed are the poor in spirit: for theirs is the kingdom of heaven. Blessed are the meek: for they shall possess the land.  Blessed are they who mourn: for they shall be Comforted.  Blessed are they that hunger and Thirst after justice: for they shall have their fill.  Blessed are the merciful: for they shall obtain mercy.  Blessed are the clean of heart: for they shall see God.  Blessed are the peacemakers: for they shall be called the children of God.  Blessed are they that suffer persecution for justice' sake, for theirs is the kingdom of heaven.  


</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yqp7q</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q0fi</id></website><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/22/jeff-foxworthy-to-host-bible-trivia-game-show/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T14:34:27+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T02:26:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi6f3u</id><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/22/jeff-foxworthy-to-host-bible-trivia-game-show/#comment-474151883</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/czfhj</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>