<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jetd/post/2012-04-02T02:41:25</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0f45g</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cdzr</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>The report has many interesting facts.  One being that Zimmerman was booked under the offense "Homicide Negligent, Manslaughter- Unnecessary Killing to Prevent Unlawful ".  It seems to me that even at the time of booking the police had a good understanding of what happened.  They could have booked him for multiple things, but instead booked him for negligent homicide and an unnecessary killing.  Just a thought, I know that they had to book him for something in order to take him in, it's just extremely interesting that this is what they chose, and believe me when this goes to trial, a question about this will come up.  

The other interesting thing to me is that the second officer states the SFD treated Zimmerman for his wounds, on the scene, in the back of the cruiser, before he was taken downtown.  Everyone is saying that there is no blood on the video, ok, maybe they cleaned him up when they treated him.  Other people are stating that you can see a gash on the back of his head in the videos.  My question is, if he was treated on scene for his wounds, I would think their would be at least cotton in his Bleeding nostrils, at least some form of bandage or tape on a "gash" on the back of his head.  Yes, there are ways to treat wounds without using a bandage, but gash implies a serious wound, they didn't say abrasion, or cut, they have repeatedly said gash.  Also, if he had a gash due to his head being pounded into the ground, a concern would be infection, the area would be cleaned, and bandaged with some sort of anti-bacterial ointment.  I can't imagine a paramedic not bandaging a person with a Bleeding gash on the back of their head.  A slight cut, or abrasion, ok, but not a gash.  I might be way  base here, maybe they don't bandage murder suspects to preserve evidence or something, but this guy does not look as though he's been treated for any sort of serious injury when he arrives at the station.  Any white bandage or cotton would show up on those videos clear as day.

My point is, there are a lot of things that can be extrapolated from the evidence in this case, just because you have an opinion doesn't mean other people's opinion's are way Off base, or that they aren't stating facts.  We don't know the facts, and police reports aren't bible by the way, they are simply witness accounts, same as if you were a witness making a statement, and are subject to scrutiny in a court of law.-  It's not up to you or anyone else to determine what the facts are, it's a judge and jury's job to do that.  Clearly the police did not do their due diligence in this case.  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67uto8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q0fi</id></website><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/31/public-opinion-shifts-on-trayvon-martin-case/</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T06:29:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T06:41:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jetd</id><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/31/public-opinion-shifts-on-trayvon-martin-case/#comment-483317900</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z5p36</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>