<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mieb38/post/2012-03-22T17:13:12</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I have treated 2 cats with SQ fluids.  One cat we caught the disease late and though she only lived one more year, her quality of life was really good until about the last week or two.  I ended up putting her to sleep @ age 16.5 b/c she was in congestive heart failure, which is often a related issue to kidney disease.  I had another cat at the same time who was actually older but had Always been healthier .  About a year after I lost Mouse, I started seeing symptoms in Doodle.  We got right on it.  I treated. Doodle for over two years before her age (20.6!) got to a point she was ready to go.  I put her to sleep but I knew that she had enjoyed a good life and she knew beyond measure that she was loved.  Her profile is still up on Catster b/c I don't know how to move it to the other side.  What I would say is don't be afraid of sticking your cat with a needle.  Be patient with yourself.  It doesn't hurt the cat.  It's hard at first but it will get easier.  I used to give fluids to Doodle while I was on the phone!  Second, it is the greatest gift you can offer...you take on the stress and the Anxiety so your baby can have an easier life.  With both Mouse and Doodle, the time they had left became very special and we bonded on a new and deeper level.  I know the knew I was doing what I could to take care of them.  As Nike would say, Just Do It!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ynu3f</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/u683</id></website><link>http://www.catster.com/lifestyle/ask-a-vet-can-you-save-a-cat-with-kidney-disease</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T15:13:26+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T21:13:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mieb38</id><link>http://www.catster.com/lifestyle/ask-a-vet-can-you-save-a-cat-with-kidney-disease#comment-473961350</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>