<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tg2y/update/2012-03-29T09:32:04/eeda61b115a4522cf60968c3e269b7647294a41a7824b5dddb928a6c77ce0c20</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Obama is determined to show that he is a strong leader capable of making tough decisions.  HE got Bin Laden.  HE got Gaddahfi.   HE helped overthrow Mubarak.  HE got the troops out of Iraq.  HE is withdrawing troops from Afghanistan.  Now, HE is telling the North Koreans, no more food aid until you cancel that missile launch.  

Obama, you are indeed, a exaulted leader who has transformed American Foreign Policy.   Let us recount your wonderous deeds:

He has apologized for the misdeeds of this country to the countries of the world, when such an apology is not needed nor desired by the American people.  The fact that he would so abase the actions of his predecessors, or of this country, is the height of arrogance and an affront to the American people.



He strongly supports the United Nations, an institution, which is incapable of keeping the peace among nations and is so corrupt that, despite massive funding by this country, works against our national interest at many turns and those of our allies.



He has, due to his naïve understand and gross mismanagement of relations among countries, appeased the enemies of this nation, thinking that, he could change the course of their actions, yet, at the same time, he has alienated our friends and allies.  His policy toward Egypt illustrates the recklessness of this administration:


--His withdrawal of support from President Mubarak of Egypt, an American ally for thirty years, helped lead to his ouster and the rise of militant anti-American Islamic parties; 


--With the rise of the Muslim Brotherhood and other militant Islamic parties, the 1979 peace treaty which Egypt made with the country of Israel, is now threatened.; 


--With the demand by militant Islamic parties for strict Shariah Law throughout the country, the very survival of Coptic Christian Church in Egypt is in question;


 --Due to the overthrow of President Mubarak, other militant Islamic parties in other countries have been encouraged to rise up against their current leadership; 


--With this administration’s gross mismanagement of its policies in Egypt, it has caused other countries to give pause when considering the value of an alliance with the United States, when on a whim of this administration, such an alliance can be terminated immediately.


      


He has, by his diplomacy of appeasement, allowed the Theocratic Islamic leaders of Iran to pursue their ambition to possess nuclear weapons, despite repeated threats by this Islamic regime to use such weapons against ourselves, our friends and allies.  When presented with an opportunity to support national opposition to this regime, this administration chose to be silent, allowing the opposition forces to be crushed.  Despite the past history of Iran’s support for terrorist organizations that have killed American Service men and women, he has done nothing to redress such aggressions and has allowed the prestige of this rogue state to increase, while allowing our own to diminish.



He has, due to his unrealistic and delusional policies, encouraged the enemies of our ally, Israel, to hold fast to their stated objective: the destruction of said state.  He has insisted that Israel negotiate away defensible borders and territory, won in numerous wars since 1948, stop building settlements in those territories, yet demanding nothing of the Palestinian authorities.  He has restrained Israel in its determination to eliminate the nuclear threat posed by Iran.  When his Secretary of Defense discovered that Israel was planning to attack Iran, the administration exposed it to the world.  In so doing, his diplomacy, rather than secure peace for Israel, has increased the likelihood of war.


  


He has refused to seek Congressional authorization for his military actions against the dictatorship of Muammar Gaddafi of Libya, contributing American military assets for said purpose.  While regime change was affected, the administration’s failure to secure Libyan shoulder launched anti-aircraft weaponry has placed the security and wellbeing of many around the world at risk. 


 


He has thrown away the fruits of victory in one war, in which our brave men and women of our armed forces, who have risked all to reestablish order and labored to transform Iraq into a civil and democratic society.  He has ignored the advice of his military commanders to retain a residual force of 20,000 troops after 2011 to stabilize Iraq.  His diplomacy failed to win the necessary immunity deal needed to protect any of these 20,000 troops from being subject to Iraqi law.  As a result, this President withdrew all the forces.  In so doing, he has handed this country over to those who would promote civil unrest and Iranian hegemony over the different peoples of Iraq.



He has mismanaged his “good” war in Afghanistan to the point that American citizens question the wisdom of keeping United States military personnel in that country.    



He committed additional forces to action, only to announce a withdrawal timetable, which is geared more to his reelection bid, than to the concept of victory in the field.  Once again, in the commitment of forces and their withdrawal, this President ignored the advice of his military commanders.  



He has shown his distain for the military by instituting new criteria to determine combat pay for our armed forces.  This new policy requires soldiers to be shot at first.  Once again such action begs an answer, why now?  Does not firefights, ambushes, improvised explosive devices or suicide bombings meet this requirement?  Is the President claiming that Afghanistan is pacified; that it is no longer a combat zone?   Recent incidents would put the lie to that statement.  With the accidental Burning of copies of the Koran by United States personnel, the Afghan people took to the streets demanding death to those who desecrated  their holy book.  Within days, two innocent American soldiers paid with their lives in retaliation for this “insult.”  While the President apologized, no such apology was demanded from the Afghan Leader.  Another incident, involving the murder by a United States soldier of Afghan civilians, has further endangered all military personnel within that country.  Yet, the President is determined to stick with the mission of training the Afghan army to take over the security role within their country.      


  


He has begun to negotiate with the Taliban to affect our withdrawal from Afghanistan.   To spur the interest of the Taliban, he has releasing certain murderous Taliban thugs held in Guantanamo Bay. However, the Taliban have since refused to negotiate with the representatives of the United States.  The fact that negotiations would be made with those who were allied with the terrorist organization, who on September 11, 2001 attacked the United States homeland, is a gross insult, not only to the citizens of this country, but to the memory of the victims of those attacks and our dead and wounded heroes of Iraq and Afghanistan.



 He has, as Commander-in-Chief, endangered the security of the American people by his policies of appeasement and weakening of the offensive and defensive military capacities of the United States:


--To that end, the President has changed the rules of engagement placing the lives of American service men and women at risk on the battlefield;  


--To that end, the President has developed military strategy based upon ideological and erroneous assumptions about the world and the military challenges this country faces. 


This President seeks a world without nuclear weapons, a noteworthy goal.  But to disarm unilaterally in the hope that other nations will follow one’s example is madness and invites destruction.  


--To that end, the President has suspended the building of the missile defense shield in the countries of Poland and the Czech Republic without informing their governments of his decision to curry favor with the Russian government;


--To that end, the President has negotiated the Strategic Arms Reduction Treaty with the Russian government, that fails to address the protection  and defense of the citizens of the United States and its allies, putting limitations on the United States defensive capabilities without the necessary limitations on the Russian offensive capabilities in order to achieve Russian support to force Iran to stop the development of nuclear program.  Such concessions to the Russian government have achieved nothing;


--To that end, the President has not funded the modernization of the American strategic arsenal despite that fact that the Russians and Chinese are carrying out such programs;


--To the end, the President has said he will share defense  with the Russians, which could counter our missile defensive interceptors.  There is no guarantee that such Secrets could find their way into the hands of the Chinese, Iranians, or the North Koreans;


--To that end, the President has surrendered the high ground of space to countries such as Russia and China.  He choose to eliminate the Space Shuttle program before the United States had a capacity to send astronauts to the International Space Station, or to send astronauts on repair and replacement missions for our numerous satellites.  Instead, he has allowed the United States astronauts to pay for passenger seats aboard Russian rockets.  For the nation that put a man on the moon, this is a humiliation of the highest order. 


 While he believes in the national government assuming the major roles in most endeavors, with regard to space exploration, he has left this to private investment, further illustrating his hypocrisy.  


--To that end, the President has attempted to socially reengineer the culture of armed forces of the United States.  Such actions as his ending of the policy of “Don’t Ask, Don’t Tell,“ while it ends discrimination against those of different sexual orientation, has had a negative impact on the morale of our forces, forces which are currently engaged on battlefields around the world;  


--To that end, the President has decided that our national defense shall suffer the brunt of the proposed massive cuts in the federal budget.  He is determined to reduce the size and force of our military personnel, eliminate such programs as the F-35 and the littoral combat ship, delay the next-generation ballistic missile submarine, terminate the next-generation bomber, and eliminate the entire ICBM leg of our nuclear triad, in order to protect entitlement spending.

INDEED, O WONDEROUS AND SUPERIOR ONE, YOUR RECORD IS ONE TO BEHOLD!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z2xjm</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ju4p</id></website><link>http://www.breitbart.com/Big-Government/2012/03/28/US-suspends-plans-for-food-aid-to-NKorea</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T03:10:15+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:32:04+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tg2y</id><link>http://www.breitbart.com/Big-Government/2012/03/28/US-suspends-plans-for-food-aid-to-NKorea#comment-479490201</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/7dzw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>