<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw9g6c/post/2012-03-31T02:24:54</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>IMO the worst thing is the trash that passes for children's movies today - adults can figure out what's right and what's wrong when they see a movie; what they agree with and believe in and what they don't.  But when you have environmentalist/socialist tripe all wrapped up in cute little movies that kids want to see like the Lorax (and Cars2 which had all the fossil fuel Burning vehicles as the bad guys), that begins an early indoctrination of children.  Whatever happened to leaving politics out of kids' movies?  Adults have their minds set for the most part when watching a film,  but children, especially young children, don't.  

This is libtard 's real crime - brainwashing kids with evil ideas.  I hate to say it but it makes me Glad that I don't have any children of my own because I'd have a heck of a time trying to undo all the liberal trash that would be poured into their brains not only in "innocent" G-rated movies but also in public school. 

There are a few minor exceptions to Christian films not doing well - I think the Naria films have done fairly well for the sci-fi/fantasy genre; at least they seem to do as well as secular-themed fantasy films and were shown pretty much everywhere. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zkoj2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ogrn</id></website><link>http://godfatherpolitics.com/4448/theaters-continue-to-shun-christian-movies-while-catering-to-moral-decadence/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T06:03:48+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T06:24:54+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw9g6c</id><link>http://godfatherpolitics.com/4448/theaters-continue-to-shun-christian-movies-while-catering-to-moral-decadence/#comment-481590075</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>