<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkoftp/post/2012-03-26T15:37:48</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Saw it this weekend too.  And I agree, while the actress who played Katniss was brilliant it is very disappointing (though unsurprising) that they didn't even look for a POC to play her.  I have read the books and loved them, such a realistic portrayal of a girl teenager in that situation.  And I love that she starts out as such and ordinary person in the way that she is so busy hunting/working/etc. to keep her family alive that she doesn't have much time/energy to think about the oppressive government, the unfairness of her situation, even romance with boys.  At the start, she doesn't feel she even has a teaspoon to raise and that even if she did it isn't worth worrying about as what would it change?  Just such a true place that many people are in or have been in.

Things I loved:
1. The way everything looked, I think they captured the feel of the districts, the capitol and the games very well.

2. Ditto on how the people looked (except for the whitewashing of so many of the characters).

3. The way they used the announcers to explain things that Katniss explained in the book with internal monologue and same with the way they used the notes in the parachutes to explain what Haymitch was thinking.  Very smart conversion from book to movie in those instances.

4. I liked that we got to see what the President and such were up to, you don't see that in the book since it is completely from Katniss' perspective

5. I agree Cinna was great, I was so worried he would come  wrong in the movie, but he didn't.

A few complaints about the movie:
1. Handheld cameras were overused to the point of annoyance and taking me out of the movie.  Sometimes they were appropriate, others not so much.

2. Katniss was softened too much in the movie, not as much as I expected granted, but still I was not happy.  The three times that stand out to me are:

a. After the announcement that only 1 victor from a district is made, in the book Katniss immediately levels her bow on Peeta, though when she realizes he was not even thinking of attacking her she puts it down.  They skipped this in the movie which is unfortunate since her rashness and focus on surviving is such a huge part of her character.  They showed these character traits elsewhere, but this scene is important and I didn't like how they changed it.

b. It wasn't conveyed how she starts out 100%  then it gets somewhat muddled to mostly  the romance with Peeta, the confrontation with them towards the end of the book was erased from the movie as Peeta does not know she is Acting at all until the train ride back to the district after they win. 

c. The long crying scene well after Rue's death.  Unnecessary and not per the book, she felt like doing that, but toughened up so that she wouldn't seem weak to the sponsors.

3. I don't understand why the mockingjays weren't better explained.

4. I didn't like that the Peeta giving Katniss the Burned bread was portrayed somewhat differently, the guilt/shame/obligation wasn't fully fleshed out regarding Katniss to Peeta and they missed out on showing how Peeta doesn't get just how important it was to Katniss, partly because of his privledge.  To him it wasn't a big deal and there is no reason for her to feel any obligation, to her it was a pivotal moment.  Her obligation to Peeta for it is a big motivator for her in the book.

5. I agree that Haymitch was also softened was too much, he was an asshole in the books especially the first one, much meaner to Katniss especially

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lc6kr</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ync</id></website><link>http://shakespearessister.blogspot.com/2012/03/hunger-games-thread.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:53:01+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T19:37:48+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkoftp</id><link>http://shakespearessister.blogspot.com/2012/03/hunger-games-thread.html#comment-476670737</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dfint</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>