<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkpzms/update/2012-03-26T16:13:37/09e0cb9731049c20bf53efa85a681fb35e03fd3689732d865bdfbe0b46a5f55f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mjc7vk</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lazol</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I'd agree with Samuelson that  there may be more than one significant contributing factor. The primary cause was actually an Overheated housing market, where everyone, regardless of their means, was being encouraged to buy one or more houses, not to live in, but to use as a virtual piggy bank to get rich (see David Bach's &lt;i&gt;The Automatic Millionaire&lt;/i&gt; for an example). The fundamental flaw is that such a plan  heavily on a rising market, where property can be sold Off  fairly quickly at a profit, and leaves the practicioner at a loss when no one wants to buy. Others who encouraged people to buy or refinance a home, at 125% financing, just get the tax writeoff, without explaining the reprecussions, are similarly to blame.

Whether monetary policy was the &lt;i&gt;root cause&lt;/i&gt; of that market bubble, or was merely one of the factors making it easier, I'm not sure. In any case, with a backlog of foreclosures, short sales, and deeds-in-lieu in the pipeline, it may still take quite a while for the market correction to finish, and we all need to be sure that the people taking advantage of the "buyer's market" don't make the same mistakes all over again, and get stuck when the balance shifts again, and sellers once again command the stronger position.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ejudi</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/egg0</id></website><link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2012/03/19/causes_of_the_crisis_113521-comments.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-19T04:10:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T20:13:37+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkpzms</id><link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2012/03/19/causes_of_the_crisis_113521-comments.html#comment-476702780</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gbra</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-19</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>