<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwh1rb/update/2012-03-30T13:53:55/40b07b23b5e075802216f05405b4e2d90d2a63d397399e1822b5fc5b27df342d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw2n66</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rrw86</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>As a father of young children I find it disturbing that we have people willing to profit from the addiction of others and kill anyone who stands in their way. But, as long as addicts and drug dealers are only killing eachother or themselves and not me or my family, I gotta say OH WELL. Why? Total prohibition does not work. The "war on drugs" is a lame attempt to meddle with the supply of something for which there is an incredible demand so THAT does not work. My concept of "making addiction illegal" works in theory, but is about as fascist as Hitlers "final solution", so that won't fly. (My example is the extreme opposite of total prohibition aka trying to affect supply, where mine example is to try and affect only the demand, and is used moreso for philosophical debate. But it drives right-wingers here  their computer chairs, and I love it.)

 SO what do we do Shadowgirl?

We keep our friends and loved ones close, our enemies closer, work hard, stay Off the crack pipe and avoid criminals and addicts like the plague.

What else CAN you do?

But don't Bleed for people who WILLINGLY get into the drug trade, or jam that first rig of drugs into their arm. Well, how about you Bleed enough for the both of us then...</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zp0px</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7maa</id></website><link>http://www.edmontonsun.com/2012/03/30/case-considered-suspicious</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T04:16:59+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:53:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwh1rb</id><link>http://www.edmontonsun.com/2012/03/30/case-considered-suspicious#comment-481008226</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h2m8h</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>