<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkombp/update/2012-03-26T15:11:57/6d93c75756657c4ac292bc9cebdaf30167b0d04993a90e3c76b33235e50b7602</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>While I think I appreciate being lumped into the category of women who are "decent looking enough" and not morbidly obese.. I would have you know that I have worn a size 14 most of my adult life. By any calculation, I am overweight. I have a DDD chest, and an ass that needs constant work to prevent it from expanding it's boundaries. By all accounts, I don't meet your "criteria" either. And yet, somehow, I have  managed to date (and love) tremendously fantastic men. Smart, gorgeous, affectionate, succesful men who make me laugh and bring something interesting to the table. Why? Because I bring just as much into a relationship, and a good percentage of men are able to see that. Thank Goodness your hypocrisy is limited to members of the cast of Jersey Shore, men under 25 and you.

Because everyone else is on the cuddle-Tony bandwagon, and I've  tried to be honest and direct.. I'll explain why YOU don't meet MY criteria, and why I couldn't date you, be affectionate with you or ever look at you as more than a friend.

1. Your life is without soul. You have no appreciation for anything other than gambling and dollar bills. You have no culture, insight, taste or discernable quality that makes you remotely interesting.. outside of the poker room and your hotel room. Develop some. 

2. You have no long term plan. I've dated plenty of men who are professional gamblers. All of them have enough common sense to save, reinvest and not squander their money away in stupid machines.

3. Your hygeine is deplorable. No shot am I sticking ANY part of my body in a mouth rife with bacteria and mashed potatoes. Least of all, my tongue.

4. You judge EVERYONE and say horrible things about entire classes and groups of people, and almost never go out of your way to show kindness, love or generosity in any capacity. I don't mean sending your Mother $50 on Farmtown, either. When was the last time you showed another human genuine kindness without them first doing something for you, or you expecting something in return? 

5. Possibly, the most important. You have no concept of being a man. I am a straight woman.. I want to date a MAN. You blame everyone else for everything, you accept no responsibility for your actions, and everything is EXCUSE, EXCUSE, EXCUSE. You talk about gender roles? You can't take care of yourself, much less a woman. I'd be perfectly content to let a man take the reigns and make decisions for our well being, from time to time. I have no problem with masculinity or dominance, or even authority when properly applied. I'm no women's libb-er. But why, under any circumstance, would a woman even let you walk her across the street with you leading.. when basic, common sense seems to elude you at every opportunity? 

Man up, Tony. Get honest with yourself. Do something good and right and forward thinking. Then maybe, just maybe, someday you'll be lucky enough to have a real relationship with one of us who "Aren't too fat to date, and passable enough in the looks department."

P.S. And stop saying you're a republican and a Christian. This Burns me up above all else. That's like claiming Diet Coke is healthy, or that cocaine is only dangerous in excess. You have no idea what you're talking about. 

That is all. Back to lurking. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ro1w1</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/bpiv</id></website><link>http://sevencard2003.blogspot.com/2012/03/well-heres-bad-news-uve-all-been.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T09:59:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T19:11:57+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkombp</id><link>http://sevencard2003.blogspot.com/2012/03/well-heres-bad-news-uve-all-been.html#comment-476647589</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>