<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5du5cd/update/2011-07-18T16:33:38/ee6bbfef8262b8b0951aed7361e7e000664883c8da7c88d5211e1cf53ded385f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5dxkth</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Sfeted, thank you for your comments. That's the first time I've heard ultralight or lighter weight backpacking referred to as a "craze" :-)

Firstly, this is not meant as a replacement for a professional and "safe", as you put it, first aid kit. If that's a priority for you then by all means buy the  the shelf pre-packaged products and use them instead, there are lots of great options available.

This is simply what I do to carry less weight with me on the trail. It's for my own personal use. It's not for a group or for any SAR mission where I would be applying first aid to someone else.

Is there a risk of contamination or cross-contamination? Sure, a miniscule one IMHO. How is using a small home-packaged amount of ointment in a sealed straw any worse than handing over a pre-opened tube of the same ointment? In fact I would think the tiny package is preferable to the tube which after use could continued to be carried and re-used for a long time and by multiple people.

As for the risk of inhaling the fumes of the cooking straws, well I'm melting them slightly and not Burning them - there is a considerable difference. I doubt that the risk of inhaling fumes from less than 20 seconds of a melting (not Burning) straw is even as bad as crossing a busy road and inhaling all the exhaust fumes.

Bottom line: If using this solution is of any concern, don't do it. Go and buy the little Neosporin packets and be happy. It won't hurt my feelings at all. But, if you think that this is a useful way to take only what you need in a sealed one-time-use packet and it will work for you - feel free to use it.

I appreciate your feedback and understand your concerns, that's why I approved your comment so that everyone else can read it and make their own determination on the associated risks.

Thanks again!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/go43jj</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/vf9h</id></website><link>http://www.briangreen.net/2011/07/diy-single-use-antibiotic-packs.html</link><postedTime>2011-07-05T17:06:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-07-18T20:33:38+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5du5cd</id><link>http://www.briangreen.net/2011/07/diy-single-use-antibiotic-packs.html#comment-256380020</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g9i95</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-07-05</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>