<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mild4f/update/2012-03-23T01:08:36/8438b1ea6b8d8522e55a097419fbbe01417524922906c26acac471ed70f08ae7</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miy6o4</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/at3g4</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>The NDAA has some very good things in it, like economic sanctions against Iran, health care costs for the DoD, military modernization, and energy security goals of NATO. The one thing that has been criticized is the indefinite detention of suspected terrorists, which may include US citizens. I disagree with this completely, but it is not new, and has  been the prerogative of the president. The NDAA is not new either. Basically it has been used to fund the military, and as such, must be passed each fiscal year. While Senator Feinstein and others have argued that current law does not
 allow the indefinite detention of American citizens, the Obama 
Administration, Senators Carl Levin and John McCain have argued that it may still allow it.[10] In his Signing Statement,
 President Obama explained: “"I have signed the  chiefly because it 
authorizes funding for the defense of the United States and its 
interests abroad, crucial services for service members and their 
families, and vital national security programs that must be renewed . . .
 I have signed this bill despite having serious reservations with 
certain provisions that regulate the detention, interrogation, and 
prosecution of suspected terrorists." [31]
On December 31 and after signing the National Defense Authorization  
for Fiscal Year 2012 into law, President Obama issued a statement on it 
addressing "certain provisions that regulate the detention, 
interrogation, and prosecution of terrorism suspects". In the statement 
Obama maintains that "the legislation does nothing more than confirm 
authorities that the Federal courts have recognized as lawful under the 
2001 AUMF". The statement also maintains that the "Administration will 
not authorize the indefinite military detention without trial of 
American citizens", and that it "will interpret section 1021 in a manner
 that Ensures that any detention it authorizes complies with the 
Constitution, the laws of war, and all other applicable law". 

As to "Obamacare" , which is a derrogatory term used by so many who do not understand just what the provisions for the proposed heath care reform really are, the main purpose of the bill was to make sure all Americans can get medical insurance, whereby receiving adequate medical care. 40 million Americans have never had or currently do not have medical insurance. That's a travesty. The Republicans, thanks to the Tea party have made sure the bill got weaker and weaker as it went through the House, then the Senate, then back to the House, then finally passed by the Senate. Some good things came out of it. You cannot be denied coverage for pre-existing conditions; you cannot be dropped after having a serious illness; your children, especially those still in college, can remain on your policy until age 26. It used to be age 17. President Obama believed that all people should be able to receive quality health care, and as a result, should be able to get insured, even going so far as to suggest all persons should be insured. Well, yes, all people should be insured. His goal was to make it affordable by offering a public option, along with private co-ops. It was such a win-win. But you should know by now that anything our president succeeds at gives him credit for re-election, and the Republicans just won't stand for that - the rest of the country be damned.

Draconian is hardly the word I would use for what Obama has been accomplishing. Is your life any worse since he became president? If you lost your job, I certainly understand that, but this was not Obama's doing, not in the least. And tell me, what civil liberties have been taken away from you. NONE, absolutely none. If you are really Itching for draconian legislation, just put one of the Republican candidates in office, and you will see just how bad things can really get. You have no idea.

You are speaking with sound bites with no substance. Don't believe everything you hear without questioning why it was said, who said it, what is their connection, what is their intention. You really need to find these things out.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6d4ghc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ant8</id></website><link>http://www.alternet.org/story/154622/conservative_bullying_has_made_america_into_a_broken%2C_dysfunctional_family%3A_but_there_are_ways_to_regain_our_wellbeing_/comments/</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T07:08:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T05:08:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mild4f</id><link>http://www.alternet.org/story/154622/conservative_bullying_has_made_america_into_a_broken%2C_dysfunctional_family%3A_but_there_are_ways_to_regain_our_wellbeing_/comments/#comment-474222625</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dvq5n</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>