<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mio0ty/update/2012-03-23T23:07:19/a39d6509141ac69346194b1b183fd48065594beff2ca2bdcc449140903a70e8c</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This movie seemed to take all the heart and passion that makes you care about Katniss' survival in the Hunger Games and sucks it right out. 


Jennifer Lawerence, Elizabeth Banks, Stanley Tucci, etc were wonderful. But even they couldn't make up for a hacked up script.

********* SPOILERS BELOW *************





First of all, where is the hunger? Food which is such a HUGE part of the book is basically gone entirely from the movie. It is never clear that Katniss is driven out to the woods to hunt by a need for survival. Gale scares away a deer because it's the day of the reaping, as if he would ever turn down a kill like that. What? In the Capital Katniss and Peeta both leave the table without being finished, rather than attempting to fatten themselves up before the game. They never even comment on the food now available to them. Katniss easily finds food and water the first day in the arena and never mentions being hungry once in the games. No bread from District 11. The careers supplies are blown up without there ever being an explanation of what that would mean for them, and their inability to feed themselves. And no lamb stew either in the Capital or the cave. That was such a great little detail, and even carried through to Catching Fire and Mockingjay.

Second, Haymitch is one of the best characters in the book and he is completely misused here. No quarrels with Woody Harrelson, but one minute he is a drunk and the next he has stone Cold sober with no inbetween?? The Haymitch in the books was an alcoholic.. he became functional but he was still struggling. 

Third, it felt like they were just Burning through scenes to get through them. They added a ton of behind the scene stuff to fill in more background info, but in return we got a very abbreviated chariot scene (that could/should have been much more powerful). The training went on quite awhile but no discussion of Peeta and Katniss training together, only them suddenly training separately, even though what we saw of training prior to that was mostly them separate anyways, so without the book, I'm not sure I would have followed. The entire alliance with Rue from beginning to end lasted what five minutes? Barely even enough time to show it, definitely not enough to make the audience feel what it felt in the book. The killings happened so quickly and with so little emotion that it removed the horror that one feels in reading them and instead felt very desensitized. Not saying I wanted more violence... but maybe more aftermath. The book dealt with a lot of the fear before, and the feelings that game afterwards. This movie didn't have that. Were was the mockingjay? Seriously very little mentioned in regards to that for the amount of significance it will have later. I didn't find a girl that would rally a rebellion in this movie. Even the berries it seemed more like she was actually giving up rather than playing the Capitol. They could have done it much better.

Fourth, camera work was jerky and awful. The green screen on the chariot scene is terrible, as is the CGI on the tracker jacker attack. The muttations look like regular mutts not evil Capital creations representing each district.

And the biggest disappointment Katniss and Peeta's relationship! Seriously?? Of all the things to mess with!! Peeta sleeping under the tree, when in the book he stayed awake all night to protect Katniss. When Katniss found him, he didn't say "remember we are supposed to be in love, so feel free to kiss me anytime you want." Instead the kissing is Katniss' idea. It just doesn't make sense for her emotionally closed Off character. Peeta questions Katniss' motives for the kissing the whole time rather than appearing to believe she is in love with him. The whole cave scene is incredibly short, very little bonding time for the two characters and Katniss doesn't have to drug Peeta to go to the feast. It just doesn't seem like a very convincing love story that would garner the kind of attention we see later in Catching Fire, etc. It honestly seemed (apart from the 2 kisses) like a brother/sister relationship. Her and Gale had a lot more onscreen chemistry.

Overall, just a lot lost in translation. I enjoyed seeing the behind the scenes stuff with the Gamemakers and Snow, but the movie never "caught fire" for me. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66h4rg</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/51bc</id></website><link>http://www.relevantmagazine.com/culture/film/reviews/28692-review-the-hunger-games</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T19:04:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-24T03:07:19+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mio0ty</id><link>http://www.relevantmagazine.com/culture/film/reviews/28692-review-the-hunger-games#comment-475004061</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>