<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwkafm/post/2012-03-31T09:12:34</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Praise God!  I live in the U.S. There will be intense hardships here in the coming years.  Nevertheless I am EXTREMELY happy for the South!!  And I hope this continues.

Russia and China have resumed their prior Cold-War roles as "big brothers" to the South.  Of course, India is rising very fast and it will soon emerge as another big brother.

The moral ethic of SHARE-AND-CARE is the ethic that is guiding all of those countries.  I've read something about the focus of all of them.  Their desire is to elevate their people.  The desire of the U.S. is to CRUSH its own citizes as well as the people of the world.

Well, I should not say "the U.S."  I should say, rather, the banking families,  societies, "royal" families, Zionist entities and all such demon groups that, for some reason, are motivated by evil.  

I never believed that those people were involved in "satanism," as I felt that that was just some bullshit idea created by people like David Icke.  But, I think I've changed my mind.  Because you have to ask yourself: What could motivate a person to get up in the morning, plan and practice evil ALL DAY, and then repeat that shit over and over again?  ONLY RELIGION.  Not "greed."  Not "power."  There has to be something deeper motivating these demons, other than greed and power.

And it doesn't matter whether or not a pitch-fork "satan" exists [Personally, I don't believe in such a being].  What matters is that THEY believe it exists.  And even if they don't believe that a "satan" exists, they find it a very useful tool.

I can imagine them, in double-file line, dressed in long robs with hoods, carrying candles.  And each one has a knife in his or her hand].  And they're walking, solemnly, towards an altar.  On that alter is a baby--crying.  Thei first hooded demon [probably Obama] finally  the altar.  He stabs the infant in the heart, killing it.  And the next, and so on.

Why not?  That's what David Icke's been telling people for a couple of decades, and that's what I've been rejecting for a couple of decades.  But, why not?  Again I ask: What could motivate an entire hidden class of people to destroy Libya the way they did, with such Cold brutality that cannot be explained?

Oh, it's "religious," yes.  These people are SICK, satanic ritualists

Now, let us all hope that these demons won't start World War III as a result of these new intended moves by the BRICS nations.  They've started wars for much less.  They know nothing else but violence, intimidation, blood and death.  They create bloodshed for the purpose of appeasing their god, "satan."  This must be the case.  This is their sick belief.

None of us have drones.  But we have our good thoughts, 

We also might have a friend that history might record as the surprise of this : Benjamin Fulford.  Mr. Fulford has been calling this stuff well in advance, and making "wild" claims that can no longer be considered wild.  He had been stating, at his blog and in video interviews from Japan, that Secret meetings had been held that involved a total, global restructuring of the world's economy.  He's been talking about this for years.  

There are forces behind these moves.  One is called The White Drago Society, and the other forces, believe it or not, are "white hats" in the Pentagon that are sick to their stomach with regards to the way the demons are leading the U.S.  There might be a coup in the U.S., and that's my prediction, not Benjamin's.  But a coup from the white hats, not the bad guys.

This all sounds wild.  Wilder still, though, is the fact that Fulford was ahead of everybody on this stuff.

May The Universe, God, Allah, WHOEVER continue to bless the BRICS countries with success, and may we all be protected from the intense hatred that is now boiling up inside the demons of the North.  May their hands be tied, and global war be prevented.

Let us pray that these demons do not launch a false flag operation such as never been seen before.  They are up against the ropes.  They want to stay in power.  

Benjamin, if you're reading this, don't you think that it's about time to send the 10,000?  If such N forces exist?</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/671n72</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6ae6</id></website><link>http://mathaba.net/news/?x=630133?disqus</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T07:44:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T13:12:34+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwkafm</id><link>http://mathaba.net/news/?x=630133?disqus#comment-481818715</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>