<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkldgo/delete/2012-03-25T13:07:11</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi0mf5</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> Granted, I am extrapolating from your responses, Jm. You should extrapolate from the known facts about Terrilyn.
- she confessed to microwaving the family pet "to hear it scream"; she confessed to hiding it from her own family for -- what -- 15 years?? All the while, she went to the same damn microwave oven 5 times a week to Heat up pizza, without remorse or needing to tell anyone about her crime. Without even sensing the horror of it.
- we know she bought the murder weapons; she's confessed twice to using them. 
- we know she's committed sadistic  against grown women.
- psychologically, a family pet is the mamalian equivalent of a small child; no normal human is capable of microwaving a pet, to say nothing of doing horrific things to a child, which is analogous but worse.
- we know she has drooled over the thrill of committing sadistic Acts and "committing mayhem."
- she's confessed twice now doing all the killing.
Ms Terrilyn is Hanibal Lector and Jack the Ripper all rolled up into a ball.  This makes the Rafferty defense theory CREDIBLE -- which is all I claimed. 
If you really think she "only did it to please her man," I'll let you share a hut with her in the woods for the next 5 years, both of you together, locked from the outside. </body><verb>delete</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ynxte</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/r11g</id></website><link>http://www2.macleans.ca/2012/03/22/mcclintics-letters-filled-with-rage-and-violence-shown-to-jury-in-stafford-case/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T15:10:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-25T17:07:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkldgo</id><link>http://www2.macleans.ca/2012/03/22/mcclintics-letters-filled-with-rage-and-violence-shown-to-jury-in-stafford-case/#comment-475901776</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>killed</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>