<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3t8jp/post/2012-03-29T09:27:47</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3vu1b</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/65z4s</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>sjw This is Spot on.

It is not a lack of PR or presentational skills: this was the excuse trotted out for the Major government. As a donor and activist I was forever being told that it was a matter of presentation and that so-and-so was really very good on the quiet. 

What was really wrong was sleeze: to be sure not as bad as Labour made out, but enough in reality to cause a problem. Moreover, the Willie Whitelaws and John Biffen types were sorely missed.

Now we have a group who, it turns out, squandered their time in opposition. There is a lack of solid policies, that is the real problem.
There was a very good phase I learned at business school: 

"having lost sight of our objectives we redoubled our efforts in every direction."

There are far too many ministers and MPs who lack expereince: many have done no real jobs at all. There is too much grandstanding,  and too many  comments which are blatantly untrue. Nobody believes the statements about how we are "winning" in Afghanistan, and have achieved our goals in Iraq. The rush t celebrate the Arab spring was absurd. Moreover nobody takes much notice of the UK politicans on the international stage: we have not one operational aircraft carrier.

However, they had the opportunity to learn while in opposition: they should have done mock cabinet exercises, drawn up contingency plans, and done mock interviews of presenting bad news.

I and others continually warned of the dangers of sleeze, and, of course, we were reassured. So much for that. After all the lessons of how not to do things from the Major Era they fall into trap after trap, hoist by their own petards. The one area in the UK economy in which productivity has gone up is in petard manufacture.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zytj2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ms5i</id></website><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/benedictbrogan/100148041/david-cameron-needs-more-ministers-who-speak-like-everyday-britain/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T11:01:49+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:27:47+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3t8jp</id><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/benedictbrogan/100148041/david-cameron-needs-more-ministers-who-speak-like-everyday-britain/#comment-479487305</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/85vxl</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>