<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmpdl/post/2012-03-30T09:24:39</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>" despite a wide scientific consensus that climate change is real"

As a conservative I do not distrust Science, I distrust consensus. 

“I want to pause here and talk about this notion of consensus, and the 
rise of what has been called consensus science. I regard consensus 
science as an extremely pernicious development that ought to be stopped 
Cold in its tracks. Historically, the claim of consensus has been the 
first refuge of scoundrels; it is a way to avoid debate by claiming that
 the matter is already settled. Whenever you hear the consensus of 
scientists agrees on something or other, Reach for your wallet, because 
you're being had.



Let's be clear: the work of science has nothing whatever to do with 
consensus. Consensus is the business of politics. Science, on the 
contrary, requires only one investigator who happens to be right, which 
means that he or she has results that are verifiable by reference to the
 real world. In science consensus is irrelevant. What is relevant is 
reproducible results. The greatest scientists in history are great 
precisely because they broke with the consensus.



There is no such thing as consensus science. If it's consensus, it isn't science. If it's science, it isn't consensus. Period.” 
    ― Michael Crichton</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hsnsf</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/b0vv</id></website><link>http://www.insidehighered.com/node/36769</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T22:50:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:24:39+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmpdl</id><link>http://www.insidehighered.com/node/36769#comment-480734652</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>