<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fpwb/post/2012-03-29T17:08:00</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This spring really helped Oliver.  He's close, and he's seen the things he has to work on now.  This year could see a lot of movement of pitchers back, and forth from Toledo.  We have who is arguably the best pitcher in baseball on our Team.  He should be their role model.  Oliver is close, it just seemed as if he was focused to much on his mechanics to worry about the men on base, or what the game situation was.  Of course he was not the only one doing that. 

Below didn't look too bad, but he does not have that killer fastball to blow by anyone, so his game is really dependant on the umpire calls to the corners of the plate.  A rookie pitcher is never going to get a close call versus the Yankee's, so it is hard to judge his last start base on the stats because of that.  He does have a great breaking ball so he's close.  

Smyly looks like a real ace.  Young future ace, with a presence.  If he's picked he'll be on a strict pitch count, and the bullpen will have to be used, but they are going to used a lot with any of our 5th starters that we have this year.  If Smyly is the one, well that could free up assets to use in a trade down the road with Oakland for Cespedas.  

The lack of sharpness from the lower portions of the bullpen lately is more troubling than the 5 th starter.  I would like to see the Tigers carry 12 pitchers so they can get enough quality innings from them till we get to the final 3.  That would give us 4 guys to use between the starters, and the final 3.  I assume there will probably a lot of movement between those 4, and Toledo if guys don't step up hard when brought in.  

I don't even what to think about picking the hitting bench, it gives me a Headache.  If we take 12 pitchers, and say Raburn has won the 2b position, then Santiago, Laird, and Kelly puts us at 11 there.  The rest I don't want to think about.  I want Dirks up with the Team all year, but that is from my fan perspective.  Management has a lot of other things too consider, and they've done a great job so far, and I'll understand whatever they do. decide.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z4qaa</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lz6q</id></website><link>http://detroit.tigers.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120329%26content_id=27731360%26vkey=news_det%26c_id=det</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:10:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T21:08:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fpwb</id><link>http://detroit.tigers.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120329%26content_id=27731360%26vkey=news_det%26c_id=det#comment-479895790</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5aidg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>