<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mtng7o/update/2012-02-29T17:44:02/968c5397d3fe07a8ff11c9a8fb3be0d6fdf49ad09fe63d7aa35747d2ff311179</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mttws0</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yf9bn</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I "liked" your post because you just handed over Exhibit #24,987 of what a scientologist actually practices when it comes to human rights and yes, such "spiritual" philosophy. 
Also,  you don't know who you are talking to, here, do you?  I could run little PR rings around your head so fast you would come out the other end saying, thank you, ma'am!

I also know a bit about ethics and more from previous jobs and there are so many points above that are wrong, Off source, etc etc  in your post above that you would spend about 3 lifetimes clay demo'ing and wordclearing (every Method, too) from my chits.

You people today who call yourselves scientologists are just pitiful.  How many years now have you fools not only subjected yourselves to 24/7 sec checks, you're actually paying for them! Are you friggin' kidding me?  And you allow someone to tell you what you can read, who you can like, talk to, and when you can fart.  Then you expect adults to listen to you 4 year olds on important matters?

All the real scientologists left decades ago to find other ways to help themselves As Well As help others, but for real this time, once we Looked and Listened and realized sci was not for real.  We stopped pretending.  You guys can't even fake being good little fakers.

And Your OT's (I feel so calm)  are wimps compared to Our OT's (We flew through galaxies and found parking spaces when we landed).  Pfffft....   there's not enough oxygen left in your brain cell to even have a meaningful debate.

Someone who commits crimes or fraud or violates human rights is called a criminal, no matter what flavor the koolaid he or she drinks.  Out here in the real world there are literally thousands of people formerly involved in scientology and that involves those all the way up the lines, my dear.  We recognize  every turd of bullshit by heart, but hey, you go ahead. Add one more lump in the pile of scientolgists' shit confront when faced with Cold hard facts and (hold your bladder) peer reviews  and (cross your legs)  Human Courts of Law.

</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yp605z</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rpyi</id></website><link>http://blogs.villagevoice.com/runninscared/2012/02/debbie_cook_countersues_scientology.php</link><postedTime>2012-02-29T11:04:09+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-29T22:44:02+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mtng7o</id><link>http://blogs.villagevoice.com/runninscared/2012/02/debbie_cook_countersues_scientology.php#comment-452756872</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hy6ie</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>