<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m02br9/post/2012-03-31T14:34:10</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The whole mentality around Earth Hour demonizes electricity.
Every material social advance in the 20th century dependedon the proliferation of inexpensive and reliable electricity. Giving women the freedom to work outside the home  on the availability of electrical appliances that free up time from domestic chores. Getting children out of menial labour and into schools  on the same thing, as well as the ability to provide safe indoor lighting for reading. 

Development and provision of modern health care without electricity is absolutely impossible. The expansion of our food supply, and the promotion of hygiene and nutrition, Depended on being able to irrigate fields, cook and refrigerate foods, and have a steady indoor supply of hot water. Many of the world's poor suffer brutal environmental conditions in their own homes because of the necessity of cooking over indoor fires that Burn twigs and dung. This causes local deforestation and the proliferation of smoke- and parasite-related lung diseases. 

Anyone who wants to see local conditions improve in the third world should realize the importance of access to cheap electricity from fossil-fuel based power generating stations. After all, that's how the west developed.

http://www.rossmckitrick.com/uploads/4/8/0/8/4808045/earthhour.pdf</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67jj28</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ms5i</id></website><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/jamesdelingpole/100148381/global-weirding-the-new-big-lie/</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T11:15:07+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T18:34:10+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m02br9</id><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/jamesdelingpole/100148381/global-weirding-the-new-big-lie/#comment-482078726</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8kdpp</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>