<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/234352/post/86320894/comment/329787747</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Zheng Lixia told reporters, handling the beverage process have a lot of things so she was moved to: selling breakfast initiative with the traffic police to maintain traffic order; the public to get up early in morning exercises to help care drinks to prevent people from looting; them in a single bottle of drink throwing on the car, only to fall to bash in the passers-by. passers-by to laugh it  ... in the handling process, the driver told them that the thirsty drink a quick drink. Zheng Lixia told reporters that they do not know how,louboutin, was really thirsty,f50 adizero, it touches Tanghan covered, then they simply took  his jacket removal drinks. After all the drinks loading, the driver to bring money to thank them, and was turned down, the driver said the sentence: until 11:00,scarpe louboutin, they will all drinks in the road the car, and then the road clean. They are too busy to even breakfast to eat, returned home at noon after lunch,jordan, 13:00 sharp, 10 of them appeared on the road to carry out normal cleaning operations. Effort 10 sanitation workers Games Tug of War thought to allow foreign drivers to minimize losses District project every time to confide in the first On the road filled with a box full of drinks. Meng Chao Zhu Dingzhao the photo 35 boxes, an average of more than 350 cases, the strength of the 10 sanitation workers come from? Qingpu District Sanitation Department cleaning brigade Zhu captain with a smile to face the questions of reporters, told reporters that the strength of the 10 lesbian is really a great Games, Tug of War project the district each year, as long as they participate in to confide in the first, the project has become a sanitation traditional projects in the district to participate in sports competitions. microblogging Recommend | hot microblogging today (edit: SN017) correspondent Meng Chao Pu Jia-you share: Welcome to the comment I want to comment the pavement of the accident as soon as possible restitution Zhong Weiping,louboutin pas cher, Chen Guiqin,ralph lauren pas cher, Wang Qiaoling ...... reporters yesterday afternoon in the West Yan\'an Road Bridge cleaning squad leader Zheng Lixia find are jobs, she casually reported the same day early morning the names of the other sisters involved in the handling of beverages. Although things every few days, but she told reporters, when she and her sisters want is to make foreign drivers to minimize losses, so that the pavement of the accident as soon as possible restitution. The past four days, they are 10 sisters have such a feeling: two arm pain, making legs like filling a lead in the same, even the toilet squatting down. a semi-trailer equipped with more than 3500 cases Jinmailang drinks morning line to the Qingpu District, Huai\'an City, Yan\'an West Road and Huaihai South Road intersection when turning, overloading combined with excessive speed,tn requin, the carriage baffle and the hook , over 3500 boxes of drinks spilled the road. The time of the accident,burberry soldes, 10 sanitation workers in Qingpu District, the Sanitation Department,nike air jordan, Bridge cleaning  on the road just clean,christian louboutin, they braved the Cold relay handling more than 6 hours, more than 3500 cases of drinks eventually onto the car. Their legs after the pain even on the toilet squatting is not down, but they do not charge a truck driver remuneration, and even spilled drinks on the ground, they did not drink a bottle. Zheng Lixia told reporters foot compartment them both,polo ralph lauren, they are simply out of , so they are spontaneous division of labor, and some on the ground passing drinks, and some received in the compartment,ralph lauren, and some are responsible for placing the car. Zheng Lixia said in the transfer process, their waist curved hands lifting a box of drinks,tn pas cher, then toss, drinks will be soon delivered to the hands of sisters standing beside the carriage. If the small box drinks,nike tn, sisters, one person can be flung standing and sisters in the hands of the compartments inside. If it is equipped with a large box of orange juice drinks,sac burberry, you need two people can be thrown up. The mobility of the drinks on the road end up with ice,chaussures louboutin pas cher, they stood on the ice ballast to pass. When after FCL drinks are loaded on the train, they found that the bulk of the single-bottle beverage can not re-installed,burberry pas cher, so they recommended the driver to buy some snakeskin pocket, drink into a pocket and then loading. But unfamiliar with the driver in Huai\'an, so commissioned to give them money to buy their pockets, and ultimately 300 snakeskin bag failed to hold these scattered single-bottle beverage. driver stood helpless. Taking into account the pedestrians and vehicles on the road will be gradually increased, the road so much drink will certainly affect the traffic in the event of looting, will increase the driver\'s loss. Zheng Lixia a gesture as a squad leader, the other sister cried: more, only then FCL and bulk beverage onto all accident vehicles and the traffic police transferred to another four truck. According to its introduction in the early morning of the 7th, in accordance with the provisions of the Sanitation Department, they bridge cleaning classes, 10 people arrived at work at 3:30 Lot of road sweeping, when they arrived in Yan\'an West Road and Huaihai Road South, cross port traffic light, filled a box full of drinks on the road,air jordan, some scattered single bottles of drinks have been smashes, the road was icy ballast. 300 snakeskin pocket to fit the bulk single-bottle beverage the reporter the Zhu Dingzhao tired sitting on beverage containers pass the FCL drinks Related articles&amp;#65306; the early morning of August 13, at half past the the Shengzhou Onchidium town, Chen Laotai the middle of the night to wake up  the air conditioner, suddenly, I heard the downstairs window at a slight cry for help, they open the windows and doors viewing. In the night Chen Laotai the found the door neighbors relative to Granny lay a shadow, and issued a very Faint cries for help. nike tn Men\'s pursuit of the beautiful singer is not disfigured after chaussures louboutin pas cher &amp;#31119;&amp;#24314;&amp;#23588;&amp;#28330;&amp;#21457;&amp;#29616;&amp;#28165;&amp;#20195;&amp;#28857;&amp;#38046;&amp;#26426;&amp;#27599;&amp;#27425;&amp;#21487;&amp;#28857;&amp;#21315;&amp;#26522;&amp;#38108;&amp;#26495;(&amp;#22270;) ralph lauren &amp;#26032;&amp;#35199;&amp;#20848;&amp;#30007;&amp;#23376;&amp;#21019;&amp;#28508;&amp;#27700;&amp;#19990;&amp;#30028;&amp;#32426;&amp;#24405; &amp;#23631;&amp;#24687;4&amp;#20998;&amp;#38047;&amp;#28508; the makeup teacher named operation , claiming to be in high Admissions acquaintances, just to spend some human costs, to  high candidates to do so on a regular undergraduate . Operation of a score on will certainly be admitted , to Ensure that does not crash ; paying more money only if the score can be admitted to a regular university . In this way, the operation of a continuous two cheated seven parents ranging from 2,000 yuan to 18,000 yuan , a total of 51,000 yuan . 
 
[WORDPRESS HASHCASH] The poster sent us \'0 which is not a hashcash value. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:234352:86320894</id><idPostId>86320894</idPostId><idBlogId>234352</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:234352</id><idBlogId>234352</idBlogId><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog</link><displayName>Wanton Wordsmith</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/</link><displayName>The day he went away</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T07:07:11.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:234352:86320894:329787747</id><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/#IDComment329787747</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T07:07:11.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The day he went away by helen0391</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://www.chaussuredefootfrshop.com</link><idEmailMd5>2ea40f49db0e9d50a1a5b2ba6554f366</idEmailMd5><displayName>helen0391</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://www.chaussuredefootfrshop.com"&gt;helen0391&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/"&gt;The day he went away&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>