<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msvd8x/update/2012-03-27T16:55:20/84802b1c571e5f20b3b8653d646347d26c357674cb8ecc518877e9d04d14a8ed</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mslb64</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lc2sx</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>In the entire history of the world there is perhaps only one society that did not use recreational drugs. That was the Eskimos and the only reason was that they couldn't make drugs in that climate. Once outsiders brought drugs in, they used them like everyone else.

The reason is simple. Higher nervous systems require constant stimulation to survive. If you deprive young children of stimulation, they will be damaged all their lives. If your nervous system stops firing constantly, you die. If you turn the TV Off for too long and don't go near the internet, you get bored and want some entertainment. Think it over while you have a piece of chocolate and a cup of coffee with your friends.

For drug abuse (as opposed to use), the problem is often Anxiety-related disorders. Like, for instance, large numbers of female heroin addicts report that they were sexually abused as children. They are trying to self-medicate the long-term trauma. As you might expect, treating them as criminals doesn't do anything to reduce the long-term trauma at the root of the problem.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lfmzz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/v3kr</id></website><link>http://healthland.time.com/2012/03/27/did-marijuana-use-sentence-trayvon-martin-to-death/</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T15:45:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-27T20:55:20+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msvd8x</id><link>http://healthland.time.com/2012/03/27/did-marijuana-use-sentence-trayvon-martin-to-death/#comment-477767901</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8t18</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>