<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwcxqt/post/2012-03-30T05:01:51</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>How can "its understanding of the fundamentals of capitalist accumulation" be "strong," if, as the author contends, the innovation of Keynesianism means a complete severance between the results and prospects of the real economy and the value-relations defined by Marx and subsequently developed by Marxist economists, including Mattick (Jr. and Sr.)? 


To illustrate my point, the author gives completely vague and qualitative appreciation of Mattick's book, then descends into complete rejection: as the author would have it, there are no practical limits to the US ability to print money in order to cover the author (and Jacobin mag's) geriatric 1970s-Era policy hobbyhorses, like the guaranteed minimum income (which Jmag can't go more than a week without mentioning). 

What disturbs me most about this point of view, beyond its incoherence (simultaneously endorsing Mattick's book and completely repudiating its argumentative and substantive core), is the political naivete. The lurking presumption behind the theoretical limitlessness the author assigns to Keynesian reformism, is the idea that the only reason the 1970s soc-dem and reformist hobbyhorses have not been implemented is the fact that they were inadequately politically marketed to the public. The idea there were real material barriers to a continuation of the pre-existing consensus, and that there is no way (as is fashionable in the academy) to neatly clade this into "political" and "economic" obstructions (why are these in principle separated for "Marxists"?) It is as if the author remembers nothing of the summer-long political brinkmanship over the US credit rating downgrade, a year ago. Creating a political platform which could plausibly implement some fossilized reform like the guaranteed minimum income (I should add the idea among jmaggers that this is somehow less 'beyond the pale' of mainstream politics or more 'realistic' than wishful thinking spontaneism only underscores the political naivete and insularity of its contributors; neither thing is anywhere near public discourse where it stands) would require politically overthrowing capital in the U.S. today, anyway. In which case, why would we just pass something Richard Nixon came up with as a social-patriotic palliative in a period of world social rupture? No faction of capital is in any mood to entertain Keynesian Utopian (in Marx's sense) reforms, today. So one wonders where the author is going with his excited and Fevered exclamations of the general lack of practical limits to Keynesian policy. Does he believe the task of the Left is to advise Capital as to its own better interests, whereby a DSAified Democrats might pass all the shit your guys' dissertation advisers thought-up in 1975?It doesn't make sense.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r32py</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yqz1</id></website><link>http://jacobinmag.com/blog/2012/03/goodbye-mr-keynes/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T13:57:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T09:01:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwcxqt</id><link>http://jacobinmag.com/blog/2012/03/goodbye-mr-keynes/#comment-480538061</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>