<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34old/post/2012-03-29T11:15:29</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mbl032</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6t2yu</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> Hey Peter,

In the spirit of discourse, I agree that our lives are filled with 
healthy forms of bacteria and fungi that enrich our lives, but I have to
 hold firm on my opinion of xanthan gum, because at the end of the day, 
that’s all it is, really, a silly little opinion of mine.   Opinions are
 like onions, when we cut into them, they might cause our eyes to run a 
bit, but once we try them on, or in this case, taste them, we find that 
we actually like them.  I have severe mold allergies and xanthan gum 
happens to be derived from one that my body doesn’t agree with, so 
biology led me down a different gluten free path, if you will. Guar gum 
can’t be had by all, either, especially those that have sever legume 
allergies, so the debate is divided, to be sure. Xanthan gum is three 
times as expensive as guar gum, however, so there is that to take into 
consideration.  I hadn’t noticed guar gum not being able to tolerate 
high Heats as well as xanthan gum, though.  Do you mean for frying in a 
pan?  I’ve had great success using guar gum for everything from fried 
chicken and donuts. 

Can’t wait to meet you in Chicago!!!
Cheers!
Karen</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/mb65qc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/uo8o</id></website><link>http://www.blackbird-bakery.com/living/the-main-reason-xanthan-gum-is-a-no-no-and-guar-gum-is-a-yes-yes/</link><postedTime>2011-11-03T07:17:42+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:15:29+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34old</id><link>http://www.blackbird-bakery.com/living/the-main-reason-xanthan-gum-is-a-no-no-and-guar-gum-is-a-yes-yes/#comment-479567096</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-11-03</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>