<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjhqk/post/2012-03-26T14:28:27</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mbisjm</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l55s6</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>"But 1999 had Austin and he captured peoples' attention in a way only Hogan ever did (sorry Rock)."

I think you mean "1998", since that was the true year of Austinmania with the Vince McMahon rivalry. Austin may have still been there in '99, he was arguably not the most popular guy in wrestling that year. Watching from August-November 1999 when Austin didn't have Vince to feed Off anymore, his character started to lose steam and you could tell he was gonna turn heel soon, as a matter of fact even in the middle of the year when Austin still had the belt and he was still feuding with the McMahons his #1 Spot was being threatened. You know what, what about September-November '98, his Spot was already being threatened then! Sorry, but without the Mr. McMahon character Austin wouldn't have drawn as well as he did in 1998 or 1999. In '97 Austin was already getting a main event push, yet he couldn't beat WCW. It's no coincidence WWF started overtaking WCW in the ratings once the Mr. McMahon character was on TV every week.

Also Austin in '99 pretty much feuded with same guys he was feuding with in '98, it wasn't like Austin was feuding with &lt;B&gt;anyone&lt;/B&gt; and it drew money, all of Austin's opponents in '99 were established main eventers by '98, mainly because Austin didn't wanna feud or even wrestle midcarders that year. The only exception being HHH, but Austin dominated the feud and HHH was probably the least over of all the main eventers that year. HHH/Austin wasn't even the most interesting program in the WWF at the time. 

Also Austin and Hogan were pushed similar as they only wrestled main eventers on TV, rarely lost and they had "superman" characteristics.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/629xs2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/u1wu</id></website><link>http://www.rspwfaq.com/2012/03/10/hhh-v-the-world/</link><postedTime>2012-03-10T16:41:24+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:28:27+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjhqk</id><link>http://www.rspwfaq.com/2012/03/10/hhh-v-the-world/#comment-476608603</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zrh3b</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-10</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>