<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpwecv/update/2012-03-22T09:16:53/2fa4c01225aa589babd3e3aa83e1e24cfb0af0179a9076c0ce084c566d75976d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mbo5pm</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rgki5</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> Wade
I beg to differ, Apparently you ARE a NIMBY guy, and obviously could care less about what goes on inside your neighborhood's property, even when it directly adversely affects you.. Shamefully you exist believing that what happens inside China does get to stay or remained left as contained only inside China and has no ill effects on yourself nor the world, in reality is your own myopic selfish viewpoint cleverly being camoflauged, yet it is a myth it being a FICTION, GET IT ?  Your advocating that we all as a society or nation justifiably continue burying our heads in the sand only to look the other way on a global environmental issue like this, is a disgrace to mankind and demonstrates your own lack of commitment to preserving life as we know it on planet earth already is in trouble,  so that it becomes your own selfish way and manner of living are what is wrong with the world . YOU most probably exist as the neighbor who throws his own raw garbage out over the fence into a neighbors back yard, you being too lazy to first bring it to the dump yourself,  conveniently dump it over the fence just so you don't have to look at your own filth, but on the other hand ferociously believe it is OK for someone else to have to deal with cleaning at your own scummy filth even when you won't.  You need to change both your environmental manner and way of thinking and doing life! We are all in this together (WAAITT). Earth is OUR ark/ space ship. Both you and I exist as the passengers situated on board seated side by side.  What happens next door, or around the world, does matter!!!  effects all of us... regardless of where you first presently live or remain seated. Killing sharks for fin soup  adversely effects even your unborn grandkids, should you be so fortunate to have kids of your own. Extinction of any species is tragic incident enough and  final. When mankind  knowingly causes it to happen, makes it only that much worse. Why would you knowingly selfishly deny your own great grandkids from something that exist important to sustaining their own life balance on the planet as well as the entire global eco system? Hey Pal, you need to rethink your own miasma, otherwise leave and get Off of my ark, since your stench is making me sick so that I now want to Vomit.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ywmyf4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/amtr</id></website><link>http://www.treehugger.com/green-food/thousands-shark-fins-found-hong-kong-sidewalk.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-07T06:38:19+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T13:16:53+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpwecv</id><link>http://www.treehugger.com/green-food/thousands-shark-fins-found-hong-kong-sidewalk.html#comment-473566300</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zdmcg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-07</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>