<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mphtxs/update/2012-03-21T14:09:44/4800b05fe5b56f02eb410c4fffe4124ee4003f7444122d8de76624f748cb521e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpl6ts</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8gsiu</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Regarding the CRX from '82 that got 52 mpg, on one hand it's sad that 20 years later we are still 10 mpg below that mark but on the other hand there are a lot of technical and not so technical issues going on here. From an engine standpoint, those old Hondas ran extremely lean while cruising, and thus got very good gas mileage at the expense of much higher NOx emissions than running stoichiometrically. Our current emissions requirements preclude the application of such a lean Burn, thus mpg has decreased. We have at the same time added a massive amount of weight to the vehicle (mostly in the name of safety, but also Comfort, convenience, etc) and made car engines larger and more powerful, which both decrease mpg as well.

It may seem counterintuitive that in the name of environmental stewardship (decreasing emissions) we decrease mpg, but that's just how it works given that NOx is regulated but CO2 isn't. In the magic ICE triangle, you have emissions, efficiency and power, and while bettering 2 is easy at the expense of the third, bettering all 3 is very tricky (although we are getting much better at making powerful, efficient engines with direct injection and turbocharging. It's tough to make a large engine that is efficient across all output levels).

Turbo diesels are another story, and arguably their prevalence in the US compared to Europe is driven mostly by emissions regulations as well. The EU regulates emissions with a different priority than the US, one that favors the diesel emissions more (they allow more NOx and are looking at CO2 I believe, although I could be wrong about that).</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dik0t</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/y2ru</id></website><link>http://www.engadget.com/2012/03/21/nissan-leaf-upgrade-2013/</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T15:45:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-21T18:09:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mphtxs</id><link>http://www.engadget.com/2012/03/21/nissan-leaf-upgrade-2013/#comment-472601444</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lqvlq</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>