<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ngye/post/2012-03-29T12:33:28</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m348pp</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l16n4</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Just because people see an "injustice" does not mean it's there, or that it is in fact an injustice.  Calling something an "injustice" is quite often a judgement and rarely a fact.

Very often people would be entirely unaware that an "injustice"( whether "real" or otherwise) even exists, and upon learning about it become concerned and need to take action, which very often leads to a bigger "injustice".

For many people experiencing "concern" is a step to experiencing "Anxiety" which inevitably leads to to suffering.  We live in the "information age". We have acsess to unprecidentade amounts of information, yet in this country  the amount of drugs (legal and otherwise), alcohol, and garbage "foods" consumed are staggering. Perhaps gathering information is not the key so much as learning to quite the mind and become a skilled observer.

"You obviously never....."  How You would know what i have considered is an assumption on Your part, although i do concur, there are many things i have not considered.  My examples where just an attempt to show that we are all a bundle of inconsistencies and if any of our lives where put under close observation we would all  reconsider our positions on calling people "dolts" or anything else for that matter.  

Everyone is  in accordance with the programming of their own DNA and life experiences, combined with the knowledge they have Gained from other sources in their lives, and the circumstances in which they live those lives.

Perhaps the lesson is to quiet the mind, become the observer, release judgement, embrace humility and expand the parameters of our original programming.

Or not, either way i am going to have a tit's day, and i hope You do too :)

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hhsdx</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/amtr</id></website><link>http://www.treehugger.com/fossil-fuels/demand-cheap-energy-entitlement-culture-gone-mad.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T13:43:56+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:33:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ngye</id><link>http://www.treehugger.com/fossil-fuels/demand-cheap-energy-entitlement-culture-gone-mad.html#comment-479630490</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/r5464</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>