<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3hnr9/delete/2012-03-29T04:20:33</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Hey Prop 5 foes and friends, guess what? discrimination exist in alaska. Even if its against the law and unconstitutional, its practice is in the economic, judicial, social, political, educational...the list is much. But for this native alaskan, There is no avenue of recourse, no mediation, no legal protection afforded to Alaska Natives.

We have gotten very used and accustomed to not having any rights or voice in correction to the abuse, we would rather you left our lands that we existed upon for thousands of years. We would love to enjoy the standard of living that the average caucasian enjoys on the resources and richness of alaskans lands and waters.

We would love to be able to get about our state upon modern roads and highways that every other state in this united states enjoys and takes for granted everyday of their lives, to be able to travel from one north area of alaska all the way to the south east or points beyond, and be able to have supplies and fuel driven up to the northern parts of alaska instead of relying upon russian tankers and coast guard ships.

But since statehood, its been: "No Dogs &amp; No Eskimos ALLOWED!"

1 Maccabees Chapter 1:
41 Moreover king Antiochus wrote to his whole kingdom, that all should be one people, 
42 And every one should leave his laws: so all the heathen agreed according to the commandment of the king. 
43 Yea, many also of the Israelites consented to his religion, and sacrificed unto idols, and profaned the sabbath. 
44 For the king had sent letters by messengers unto Jerusalem an...d the cities of Juda that they should follow the strange laws of the land, 
45 And forbid Burnt offerings, and sacrifice, and drink offerings, in the temple; and that they should profane the sabbaths and festival days: 
46 And pollute the sanctuary and holy people: 
47 Set up altars, and groves, and chapels of idols, and sacrifice swine's flesh, and unclean beasts: 
48 That they should also leave their children uncircumcised, and make their souls abominable with all manner of uncleanness and profanation: 
49 To the end they might forget the law, and change all the ordinances. 
50 And whosoever would not do according to the commandment of the king, he said, he should die. 
51 In the selfsame manner wrote he to his whole kingdom, and appointed overseers over all the people, commanding the cities of Juda to sacrifice, city by city. 
52 Then many of the people were gathered unto them, to wit every one that forsook the law; and so they committed evils in the land; 
53 And drove the Israelites into Secret places, even wheresoever they could flee for succour. 
54 Now the fifteenth day of the month Casleu, in the hundred forty and fifth year, they set up the abomination of desolation upon the altar, and builded idol altars throughout the cities of Juda on every side; 
55 And Burnt incense at the doors of their houses, and in the streets. 
56 And when they had rent in pieces the books of the law which they found, they Burnt them with fire. 
57 And whosoever was found with any the book of the testament, or if any committed to the law, the king's commandment was, that they should put him to death.</body><verb>delete</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h3ze8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dneq</id></website><link>http://community.adn.com/?q=adn/node/160531</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T23:37:34+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T08:20:33+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3hnr9</id><link>http://community.adn.com/?q=adn/node/160531#comment-479323430</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8j14r</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>killed</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>