<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m1u3b2/update/2012-03-13T20:43:12/b2dbf305a1c1c275be9e769cba2733f9318c7cdbe98d2c3353ae2817f657f111</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I've been on 1 mg of Xanax for almost five years a daily dose, and although the drug saved me from a very painful and disturbing panic attack (one in which I collapsed in a movie theater bathroom, and crawled out for help, in a shake for the rest of the night a good 14 hours until I got some Xanax in my system), I was young and not really worried about system addiction or even what Xanax was, it was my saving grace. I am now 23 and have been doing research for over a year on Xanax, and while I am thankful for the drug I am ready to cut it . I have realized most notably it makes me tired, yes school has been much less of a worry and while I graduate in May and am thankful for Xanax helping me get through school I want to be free of it come May. I am a evangelical christian and decided I don't want drugs running my life but Christ, just trying to give everything to him. I am a motivated person so it was not hard for me to go Off Xanax... it's been two days and while I am happy I am not taking the drug I do notice a cloudiness to my days a slowness, and every once in a while Dizziness. I understand it's part of the withdrawal process, but I am happy to know I am not the only one dealing with this. I would also like to let you all know that this is beatable, as it seems many of you are taking lower doses than me and suffering for harsher withdrawals, but I KNOW I will beat it so know that YOU can too! Have faith!

"He said to me," 'My grace is sufficient for you, for My strength is made perfect in weakness.' "Therefore most gladly I will rather boast in my infirmities, that the power of Christ may rest upon me. Therefore I take pleasure in infirmities, in reproaches, in needs, in persecutions, in distresses, for Christ’s sake. For when I am weak, then I am strong. - 2nd Corinthians 12:9-10</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/goty2d</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/qmjk</id></website><link>http://www.choosehelp.com/detox/xanax-withdrawal-symptoms-how-to-get-off-xanax.html</link><postedTime>2011-07-05T15:25:18+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-14T00:43:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m1u3b2</id><link>http://www.choosehelp.com/detox/xanax-withdrawal-symptoms-how-to-get-off-xanax.html#comment-464690664</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-07-05</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>