<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0u3dl/post/2012-04-01T18:53:25</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Technostress: a response

Being able to have a conversation about technostress is a great idea, as
 I'm quite sure many of us experience some of the same issues I 
mentioned.


I built my own website in 1998 because I wanted to find a way to have a 
voice online and share my ideas and creativity. Using Geocities on 
-up was... interesting. In 2004 I left "work" for the last time due 
to overstress (I was working full-time in a music store selling 
instruments). Now home, I started doing more online for myself, and soon
 was designing a site for free for someone who had miles and miles of 
content. 

I've been doing this ever since. Finding WordPress helped quite a bit too. The main source of stress for me :

- bend a theme to do what needs to be done (gazillion of hours changing CSS and HMTL values) 

- realizing I've spent a dozen hours working with a theme that's flawed (what theme isn't?)

- finding out the hard way that themes look beautiful on the seller's 
page, but to make it show the same upon purchase requires a whole more 
work and usually multiple back and forth with the designer or other 
users on so-called "support" forums.

- e-commerce (need I say more?)

Basically, the learning curve is Always steep, the "help" very costly, 
either the designers want to be paid extra to "look into it," or I waste
 long hours massively Googling through a jungle of poorly written 
documentation - documentation written by coders from a coder's 
perspective and presenting things in a way a coder may understand - but 
guess who buys those themes?... not usually coders because they can make
 their own!

So now I'm going for "responsive" themes, and find out many don't work properly in IE,
 most designers sell you the theme when in fact you're actually paying 
him/her/them to be a beta-tester and iron out the issues.

My stress could be lowered if I shut down shop, yes. But I'm passionate 
about what I do and aim at providing a fluid product. Clients don't know
 that since they know even less that I do. So I feel even more stressed 
and even guilty for not being able to do the work quicker and more 
efficiently.

So I'm stressed out, having Heartburns and Headaches, even depression 
when I waste a day or two on ONE issue that ends up being very 
complicated due to the fact that the problem is on the coder's side.

Today I am finding out about Initializr, and wondering if I could find a
 template creation tool (non-WordPress) or a theme creation tool 
(WordPress) that could become part of my designer's toolbox. 

Any help would be much appreciated! 

Regards,

André Lefebvre
Creative Forge
www.creativeforge.org

 
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ev72ux</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/645a</id></website><link>http://speckyboy.com/2011/08/18/technostress-the-freelancers-disease/</link><postedTime>2011-08-19T07:52:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-01T22:53:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0u3dl</id><link>http://speckyboy.com/2011/08/18/technostress-the-freelancers-disease/#comment-483165948</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lv3uf</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-08-19</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>