<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjn29/update/2012-03-26T14:37:43/f50e0f5be4a2c7e3b8ff3ccf295d9b730ec90f21d21b5cdd9571dbb80a7c6736</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>"My focus is going to be on building the city, but if someone comes and they want a property in the country, or not around people, then why wouldn't I want that?" Keyserling said. 

These are code words for screw you Steve Tully.  I want this deal so I can get paid for my efforts at developing with taxpayer money.

Same crowd with the same on tired rhetoric which amounts to nothing more that wasting our hard earned money.  This scheme is being engineered by one who lied about ending his real estate profession, represented the Chamber on the Bellamy curve deal and has failed on at least two occassions to pay his real estate taxes to the point where they were advertised for sell in the latest sale.  This guy will say anything to get what he wants.  There is something lurking in the woodpile if he and Dadson are involved. One can rest assured we will never know the truth of any of it, but will learn about slush funds that are hidden away only to be available to fund the next great idea.  The beautiful people in Beaufort can keep on playing footsy with Keyserling and will surly learn that there are three things that will Burn ya - gasoline, kerosene and a Keyserling.  He will tell you he cares about his hometown but will stop at nothing to transform it into a vision only his and his cronies can envision. Look at his tranformation to date and one can see he says one thing but does something entirely different.  Sutton his major rival in the last Mayoral election has, after opposing him vehemently, gotten in bed with him and follows his every move with total support lending merit to the adage that "politics makes strange  bed fellows".  If you want to change direction do not reelect Keyserling, McFee and O'Kelley to office this fall.  They keep coming up with money for this deal, found $9,000,000 for the Boundary Street  scheme; yet we get taxed for a half empty Town  to the tune of millions and had our taxes raised 16% to do it.  We are getting riped Off to no end as this train of fools will surly leads us down a road we don't need to go down.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r1ecg</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnmq</id></website><link>http://www.islandpacket.com/2012/03/26/2013607/developer-citys-commerce-park.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T04:52:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:37:43+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjn29</id><link>http://www.islandpacket.com/2012/03/26/2013607/developer-citys-commerce-park.html#comment-476616986</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/84aqn</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>