<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/migccl/post/2012-03-22T15:54:38</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>For all of you who said Trayvon assaulted Zimmerman; How do you know that Zimmerman didn't grab Martin ( maybe he was trying to make a citizen's arrest) and Martin trying to defend himself attempted  to get  Zimmerman  of him which then led to a scuffle and because Zimmerman was overzealous and apparently thought he was police officer pulled out his gun, in panic, and shot him?  That could explain the blood and busted nose, it also fits the girlfriend's statement and goes along with the 911 recordings and witnesses.

[Aside] I think we sometimes get sick of hearing about things concerning racial injustice that we search and  defend events to make the ringing of injustice untrue. And thats understandable because if  we admit that racial injustice does occur, we have to examine why it happens   and thus examine ourselves, which is very hard to do. What we must understand is that all racial injustice doesn't occur out of the evil and terrible racism.  Injustices occur from misunderstanding and misinformation. Our attitudes and opinions of each other are based on facts-- loosely. The facts tainted by generalizations, stereotypes and personal experiences create our prejudices, create our injustices. A typical police officer deals with a lot crooked black people, so naturally he would think most blacks are crooks( crooks in the making or potential crooks) therefore, when a "concerned" citizen shoots a 17 year old black male that looks the same as all the crooks he works with everyday it is easy to believe the guy Acted out of self defense because his story lines up with his perception of black males. Thats not to say he hates all black people or thinks all black people are crooks, just those that line up with his image of a crook-- and those who don't tend to  have earned their Spot of "good black person"or the "but you're different"  and are perceived as exceptions- not the standard. White people do this to blacks, blacks to do it to whites, hispanics to blacks and blacks to hispanics; its done to Asians and they do it to others too. But whites tend to take all the heat because they are the majority; essentially have most of the power in this country and historically their prejudices wreak havoc on minority populations.  Well you say there are white crooks, and he doesn't think all white people are bad. Well he knows he is not bad, his mother and father and wife and children aren't bad, so therefore in his mind most white people can't be bad. Or you might say well where's the outrage when a black person kills another black person. Well, most go to prison when this occurs and again self preservation steps in  and  the "we can't make a big deal out of this because they will use this further their assumptions and stereotypes about me and my people"- you usually try not to draw attention to the bad done by your own because of its mis-reflection of yourself. Anyway, an injustice occurred in Sanford, lets stop bickering and right the wrong.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ycbvl</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yzhx</id></website><link>http://www.miamiherald.com/2012/03/21/2706562/rally-in-support-of-trayvon-martin.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T22:47:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T19:54:38+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/migccl</id><link>http://www.miamiherald.com/2012/03/21/2706562/rally-in-support-of-trayvon-martin.html#comment-473889000</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zdrcx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>