<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mz51wt/update/2012-02-23T11:07:28/a08b58c7f20e9358346dedd331c7c971620bea56b2939bc9d9e332510c06b153</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>New definitions for 2012 politics
Santorumonious – The conviction that a holier than thou belief system qualifies one to dictate to everyone else how to live their private lives.  Similar to being sanctimonious, except that it contains an extra layer of hypocrisy in which the believer decries governmental intrusion, while at the same time demanding everyone else live according to their standards.  Subject uses a sense of victimization to justify all of their most outlandish expression of ideals (see Gingrichamania).

Romnebotism – Possession of a near human like appearance, but lacking the ability to completely emulate human qualities so that real people can perceive the difference.   This condition renders the afflicted incapable of human emotions or empathy, instead causing subject to equate self-interest, greed and Thirst for power with having had true human experiences.  In more extreme cases the subject is known to confuse businesses for people, lack understanding of others not being incredibly wealthy and thinking their love of cars means caring about other people.  This condition is considered incurable and only kept in check by returning to private industry and being allowed to fire other people at will.

Gingrichamania – A highly dangerous mental condition characterized by unrealistic self aggrandizement, bizarre planning and frequent angry outbursts against anyone unfortunate enough to question such behavior.  This condition is not dangerous to the subject themselves, only to supporters, reporters, former colleagues and any seducible women unable to hide quickly enough.  The subject uses a cloak of victimization to excuse all such behavior and to draw other unsuspecting listeners into its web of rhetoric, by convincing them they are also victims of liberal bias and elitism (see Santorumonious).  Ignoring the subject is the only known method of defense.

Paulookaville – A non-existent place in a non-exist time that hearkens back to a bygone Era of self-reliance, golden standards and freely available drugs.  This time and space is thought to be a crime and worry free utopia, but has never existed in human history, except in John Wayne movies directed by Frank Capra.

Bachmanaracts – The blurry vision that all people that oppose your beliefs are gay, yet the inability to recognize one’s own spouse as being gay.  This condition is characterized by the firm belief that God commands the subject to seek public recognition and their leadership (see Santorumonious).

Perrywinkle – A hybrid growth of every negative stereotype of Texans rolled into one.  It looks impressive in its native environment but is incapable of survival outside of the Lone Star State.

Christietosis – A continuous angry and belligerent response to all outside stimulus.  Caused by the resentment that no matter what, they are destine to be the governor of New Jersey as their life’s greatest accomplishment, while feeling they could do better, but knowing they aren’t qualified for even that.

Palinatude – Hey, pay attention to me.  I’m still out here.  I’m still relevant.  Really, I am.  You know you still want to hear what I’ll say next.  Listen, come on, listen to me.  Ya-betch-ya.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/y106hh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/eyjq</id></website><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2012/02/that-was-not-the-gop-debate-rick-santorum-needed/253474/</link><postedTime>2012-02-23T04:36:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-23T16:07:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mz51wt</id><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2012/02/that-was-not-the-gop-debate-rick-santorum-needed/253474/#comment-446996825</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8805r</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>