<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3sddc/post/2012-03-29T23:19:06</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>In respect to the rules I'll use "BS" to describe in less than accurate lingo what this really is.    At the end of my paragraph I'm going to tell you the Secret that proves it's just a trick on the American People. 

The Federal Government could just as easily made a mandate that Pre-Existing Conditions are covered without all this BS that we see before the Supreme court. 

Insurance companies have a price chart and they pay less than you're charged.   Then at times let that pile up and pay a settlement on many outstanding balances. 

Money is spent on celebrities, PR, TV ads, bonuses to reps who find reasons not to pay.    

This bill is the most wrong of all the wrongs that keep the prices high for the end user.   If we could pay the actual cost of medical care many folks wouldn't need insurance for Colds or vaccines or checkups.  They'd pay out of pocket.  

So when we see all this BS designed to make us think we need insurance instead of a greater need to put some controls on insurance just remember the control is being placed on the wrong end of the relationship.  

Let's get rid of Mandatory insurance and require insurance companies 

So how do I know we're all being tricked?   Because the insurance companies can LOWER the cost if more people are forced to pay for it? 

This means if they lower the prices, more people would.  And it would offset on it's own.  So why aren't they doing that?   After all, the fact remains is their own admission that it could be priced at an affordable price if more people paid into it. 

Ponder that and realize they already have the power to lower the prices without the mandate and in turn they'll get more people insured by CHOICE. 
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lx0lv</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zmtw</id></website><link>http://front.moveon.org/why-doctors-are-cheering-obamacare/</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T13:15:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T03:19:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3sddc</id><link>http://front.moveon.org/why-doctors-are-cheering-obamacare/#comment-480194211</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6ams1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>