<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwvfcc/update/2012-03-30T16:13:50/1dd6b19eb7dce810392527de92b693e87a14636755638bf53d495d10b95aa9f2</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwv4m9</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7r5m</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> Hey Michael,

My home language is Afrikaans, I was educated in English up to my engineering degree and I lived in Germany for a year. Although my German is incredibly rusty, I do dream in all three languages and it is entirely situation dependent. Even my conscience is multilingual  on the situation. For example, there are certain phone numbers I can only recite in Afrikaans, others in English and a select few in German. It's messed up, but that's just how it is. 

The fascinating part is that you Reach a point where you no longer translate the language into your own, you simply understand it. For example: writing this paragraph is simply me writing it as I think it, I haven't even thought of what it would sound like in my home language. 

If you want to learn a language, learn the humour that goes with it. It will give you a perception of the language which you simply cannot learn from books.

I wouldn't consider myself more intelligent than others, it's simply ONE of many areas where people's brains can excel/fall behind. Don't ask me to cook or draw. I'll Burn water and I almost flunk elementary school because I kept colouring in over the lines. :/ </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dspvs</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dhmp</id></website><link>http://www.omg-facts.com/view/Facts/50075</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T17:12:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T20:13:50+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwvfcc</id><link>http://www.omg-facts.com/view/Facts/50075#comment-481149183</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lcf4v</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>