<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwi5i0/update/2012-03-31T08:06:20/82be97287bb2a902b1c536b582777ba8aa33d2f63de2b91e25a99fa392492d87</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwf3o4</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Anonymous guest wrote:&lt;blockquote&gt;A good definition of a troll is someone who tries to hijack a real or serious issue or topic and make himself the center of attention.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
Then put your money where your mouth is, let's take the attention Off me, and refocus on my ideas, shall we?

Do you disagree with my thesis that you can expect the same, tired scapegoats every time there is a tragedy in Berkeley, even though there is no evidence for them? Because the poll was an accurate predictor of such responses.

Here's the formula:

IF the tragedy takes place within a few blocks of a medical cannabis clinic (or even in the Berkeley Hills), THEN people will &lt;a href="http://www.berkeleyside.com/2012/02/21/alleged-killer-had-been-in-and-out-of-mental-institutions/#comment-444937682"&gt;blame the cannabis clinic.&lt;/a&gt;

IF the tragedy happens the same night as an Occupy Oakland protest, THEN people will blame Occupy Oakland.

IF the tragedy happens to an unnamed Berkeley High student, THEN people will &lt;a href="http://www.berkeleyside.com/2012/02/23/breaking-berkeley-high-student-shot-in-oakland/#comment-447402714"&gt;blame illegally registered students from outside Berkeley&lt;/a&gt;.

And now, of course, my guess is that in &lt;i&gt;any&lt;/i&gt; tragedy, people will &lt;a href="http://www.berkeleyside.com/2012/03/30/sacramento-street-shooting-victim-dies-arrest-made/#comment-480826883"&gt;blame Chief Meehan&lt;/a&gt;.

Do you disagree with this thesis? Because so far the evidence supports it.

Anonymous Guest wrote: &lt;blockquote&gt;it's a bit farfetched to presume that the 34 people who supposedly participated in your so-called "poll" were necessarily taking it or you "seriously"...&lt;/blockquote&gt;

34 people took it seriously enough to vote in it, rather than complain about it. Were they all Cold and caloused, or did they also understand that the poll was simply a device to illustrate the points above? There are other commenters who &lt;a href="http://www.berkeleyside.com/2012/03/30/sacramento-street-shooting-victim-dies-arrest-made/#comment-480987714"&gt;who seemed to get the point.&lt;/a&gt;

What do you think? Or, were you just trolling?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67gita</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7btb</id></website><link>http://www.berkeleyside.com/2012/03/30/sacramento-street-shooting-victim-dies-arrest-made/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T14:40:00+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T12:06:20+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwi5i0</id><link>http://www.berkeleyside.com/2012/03/30/sacramento-street-shooting-victim-dies-arrest-made/#comment-481776155</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/3qr</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>