<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/319679/post/127957277/comment/328729801</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Coming this fall... the terrifying sequel to the most horrifying, depraved and mind-scarring of all My Little Pony Fanfictions ever to  Equestria Daily. 
 
&lt;u&gt;TACOS&lt;/u&gt; 
 
- 
&amp;quot;Trixie? What are you doing in my house?&amp;quot; Twilight said, her voice trembling as the blue mare slowly shambled towards her, a meat grinder floating gently in her magical blue aura. 
&amp;quot;Oh, Sparkle&amp;quot; The great and powerful mare crooned softly, drawing herself up close to the shaking purple filly. &amp;quot;Don&amp;#039;t you know?&amp;quot; Twilight suddenly gagged as she felt Trixie&amp;#039;s magic aura wrapping around her throat, all oxygen being cut ... 
&amp;quot;...Nobody neighsays the great and powerful Trixie... and lives...&amp;quot; 
 
- 
Spike slowly pushed open the cracked door to Carousel Boutique. &amp;quot;R-Rarity?&amp;quot; he stammered.  
Something was very wrong. Rarity&amp;#039;s fabric was strewn all over the place. Curtains were torn down Off the walls and Rarity&amp;#039;s ponyquins were knocked over. If Spike didn&amp;#039;t know better, he&amp;#039;d say there had been a struggle. But who would attack Rarity? 
&amp;quot;Rarity?&amp;quot; He tried to call out for his beloved mare again when he suddenly stopped, a &amp;#039;squeltch&amp;#039; sound echoing through the room and a soggy feeling permeating through his footclaw. Spike jumped back to see what he had stepped in... 
...A pool of blood. 
 
- 
&amp;quot;Y&amp;#039;all will never get away with this, Trixie?! Ya hear?!&amp;quot; Applejack yelled as she dangled in Trixie&amp;#039;s magical aura, held aloft over the spinning blades of the grinder. 
&amp;quot;Oh little Hayseed... So blind to the truth. Why don&amp;#039;t you know?&amp;quot; Trixie chuckled, switching on a light, only to reveal two horns and a pair of wings, displayed neatly on a mantlepiece. Applejack nearly Vomited at the sight of them. 
&amp;quot;I already have... Mwahaha... MWAHAHAHAHAHA!!!&amp;quot; 
 
- 
The pink pony&amp;#039;s mouth cracked into a twisted grin, her teeth stained with blood... &amp;quot;I have taught you well... my faithful student...&amp;quot; 
 
- 
&lt;i&gt;All you have to do is take a ripe tomato dice it up like this... 
Now just take a taco shell, some cheese and onion, some sour cream just a titch...&lt;/i&gt; 
 
 
 
&lt;u&gt;TACOS&lt;/u&gt; 
Coming soon to a fanfiction near you... 
 </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:319679:127957277</id><idPostId>127957277</idPostId><idBlogId>319679</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:319679</id><idBlogId>319679</idBlogId><link>http://www.equestriadaily.com</link><displayName>http://www.equestriadaily.com/</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.equestriadaily.com/2012/03/comic-trixies-secret-revealed.html</link><displayName>Comic: Trixie\'s Secret Revealed</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T19:58:46.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:319679:127957277:328729801</id><inReplyTo><link>http://www.equestriadaily.com/2012/03/comic-trixies-secret-revealed.html#IDComment328721126</link></inReplyTo><link>http://www.equestriadaily.com/2012/03/comic-trixies-secret-revealed.html#IDComment328729801</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T19:58:46.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Comic: Trixie\'s Secret Revealed by @DustyTheJanitor</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://twitter.com/DustyTheJanitor</link><idEmailMd5>d41d8cd98f00b204e9800998ecf8427e</idEmailMd5><displayName>@DustyTheJanitor</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/DustyTheJanitor"&gt;@DustyTheJanitor&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.equestriadaily.com/2012/03/comic-trixies-secret-revealed.html"&gt;Comic: Trixie\'s Secret Revealed&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>