<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3id1u/post/2012-03-29T21:11:17</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mst1b2</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g3jej</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> Good lord indeed, you can't compare  with dissimilar devices and ignore what makes them different.

No one would ever confuse a  with a laptop, it was a ridiculous comparison that did nothing but confuse people as to whether the increased Heat generation is a issue or not.

The  is a sealed device, it's completely reliant on passive cooling and has no way to vent excess Heat if it builds up too fast.  So it takes less Heat for it to start feeling too warm.

Never mind you were  on stereotype because not all laptops get Too hot to the touch.  A ARM based laptop especially would run cool to the touch.  Along with the fact most people just use a cooling pad with a laptop but they can't do that with a tablet!

While also you ignored the difference in how the two type of devices are used.  What's too warm for the lap is quite a bit warmer than what's too warm to hold in your hands constantly!

Then on to web browsing, problem is not all browsing requires the same amount of computing power.  Higher resolution graphics and images do take more work and nothing is going to change that the back light requires 30% more power for the same amount of brightness as the iPad2.

So guess what, specs matter!  You want to ignore them then do so at your own risk but stop pretending there was nothing wrong with what you tried to state!  If anything you should have compared the new IPad to the iPad2, at least then it would have been relevant!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l8xwp</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/hb4c</id></website><link>http://www.slashgear.com/why-the-ipad-heat-is-linked-to-hot-sales-26220049/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:22:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:11:17+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3id1u</id><link>http://www.slashgear.com/why-the-ipad-heat-is-linked-to-hot-sales-26220049/#comment-480101495</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/jo27</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>