<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwcv2t/post/2012-03-30T04:51:13</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Well, I do know that I have had a similar encounter. Long ago when i lived in another city, a LARPing session I was invited to was for oWoD with rules for Masquerade and rules for Apocalypse had just come out. I decided to be a werewolf. Needless to say things were going well and interesting, then of course the clique group decided they were going to screw with me since I was the newbie. The werewolf ST was a complete idiot and didn't even know the rules of werewolf (I had been playing the game and even looked over the LARP book) and such. Needless to say my character got ambushed and skewered and they intended to turn me into an abomination right there on the Spot, of course in full view of pack members who did nothing.

After that I was pretty pissed , and didn't bother going back for a long while because I had been there for one whole session and my character was pretty much ripped out of my hands before I even had an idea of what I should be doing.

Several months passed, the group got kicked Off the campus because of complaints, and a new GM took over and such. I decided to try again. This time I decided to be a Mage, but the group was still being pretty dickish over all. End result I ended up turning a few of their players into walking freak shows before dying in a paradox explosion myself and never returned. GM of course, retconned that whole event out, of course.

I've learned to stay away from anyone claiming to be apart of Camarilla sanctioned events now. Pretentious dickery does not begin to describe my experiences with them.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/mup0dq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gd1l</id></website><link>http://spoonyexperiment.com/2011/11/06/counter-monkey-vampire-spoonys-jyhad/</link><postedTime>2011-11-06T11:39:33+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T08:51:13+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwcv2t</id><link>http://spoonyexperiment.com/2011/11/06/counter-monkey-vampire-spoonys-jyhad/#comment-480530897</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzkal</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-11-06</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>