<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31pxn/update/2012-03-29T16:21:03/a79fd038755024314d6efdb2493ab80af6de2f4c76b53c5f224a190175802f36</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I'm on here every single day, but don't post regularly because I get so much  just from reading everyone else's comments.  I have to say that today's comments by the trolling "Christian lady" (emphasis on the quotation marks, please) have had me in absolute hysterics.  She's like so many "righteous" people I know: so wrapped up in her own piety she has no patience for pleasure (her own or anyone else's).  She doesn't realize she's the kind of "Christian" who keeps people OUT of church due to her uber-judgmental attitude.  Who wants to go to church with someone like her?  Only other people like her, not people like us. 
     
By "us" I mean you splendid, magnificent, generous DR devotees and me.  I know many of you are deeply spiritual women and even those who may not be have hearts overflowing with kindness and acceptance.  I have seen you  out to each other with concern and compassion on more occasions than I can count on topics that range from a sick spouse to a traveling child to the births of grandchildren.  The sense of true friendship that bursts  the pages on this site is the reason it's the only Rob-site I ever, ever visit.  I often see more evidence of Christian (Jesus, not Grey) love here than anywhere else on any given day.  (I also can't help wondering if "Christian lady" might just be someone messing with us for fun because we're such a rapidly Rob-fensive lot.)I turned this over to my hubs to read because if there's any man on earth who has benefitted from my love affair with "Fifty" it's been my husband.  Since I found MY favorite Christian (Grey, that is), hubs has been getting laid with Christian Grey/Ana Steele-regularity and enthusiasm and you can trust me:  he is DEFINITELY NOT complaining about the new, improved "kinky fuckery" OR accusing me of reading porn.  (Although, so what if it is porn?  I'm very much an adult.  I can read whatever - or kinkily fuck my DH - whenever and however and as many times as I want!)  DH got such a kick out of her comments, but says he sure feels sorry for whoever is stuck with her because she's guaranteed to only tolerate "plain, old, CHEAP vanilla, not even Ben &amp; Jerry's Finest".  Now for the funny stuff - I was sitting in church this past Sunday morning (yes, horrible, sinful, Burning, going-to-hell-for-loving-"Fifty" me) and I had been fidgeting in my purse for a couple of minutes when my DH suddenly leaned over and whispered "You need to learn to be still.  We'll have to work on your control, pretty girl" in his faux-Dom voice and I nearly fell out of the pew from instant horniness.  A few minutes later I got the giggles thinking about his comment and he leaned back over and said "This is not the appropriate place for misbehaving, Mrs. _______ .  You're making my palm twitch," which left me squirming (throbbing delightfully, actually) and giggling like a nervous virgin throughout the rest of the sermon.   When church was over I asked if we were going out to eat and he replied "No.  You deserve a spanking for disobeying me and I'm an 'in-the-moment' kind of guy", then drove all the way home without speaking or touching me.  Sweet Lord!!  Well, girlfriends, that was all she wrote!  We were home in less than ten minutes and he was indulging his twitching palm and I was enduring my "punishment" with a big, fat, happy, I've-been-married-27-years-and-never-had-this-much-fun-in-my-life grin plastered on my face from ear-to-ear, calling for God like a Pentecostal.  (Spent a good bit of time on my knees offering...ahem...supplications to "atone" for my sins.  I think when he yelled "FUCK!" it meant I had been forgiven.)  I love you ladies and count you as friends.  (I truly, truly do!)  If they were selling condos in the DR my wonderful, sexy, playful, loving, fun, fun, fun husband would ante up the money to buy me a penthouse there and move in with me.  (And if you girls are there it's gonna be a rocking' place anyway, but you'll have to keep your twitchy palms Off my man or I'll go all Ana-on-Gia-and-Mrs. Robinson on you.)Maybe now "Christian lady" can tell me how badly my DH and I are going to Burn for experiencing explosive marital lust in church.Funny, funny, uptight people make me laugh.  The obvious question to me is:  Why would you be on such a sinful site as "Robsessed" if you feel you should only be obsessed with God?  (I know it's sometimes difficult to make a distinction between the two.  Hint to "Christian lady":  Rob is the one who looks hotter in a beard.)P.S. If by some terrible twist of fate she and I end up being the last two women on earth with Rob you ladies better pray for his sake he ends up with me.  I may be twice his age, but I can promise I won't serve up any plain, old vanilla.  Christian Grey has opened up a "Ben &amp; Jerry's 500-flavors-and-still-counting" in my brain (and panties) and I'm not repenting.  Quite the contrary - I'm thanking God for inspiration!P.P.S.  I am making my first-ever visit in England at the end of June and would love to arrange to meet some of my fellow hell-bent friends for lunch,tea or dinner (or all three if we get on a roll) one day.  Anyone up for meeting this lusty old lady?  I'm making a list of all you willing to Burn in the Grey fire with me!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z8ull</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/djgv</id></website><link>http://www.robsessedpattinson.com/2012/03/kristen-stewart-mentions-robert.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T05:17:08+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:21:03+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31pxn</id><link>http://www.robsessedpattinson.com/2012/03/kristen-stewart-mentions-robert.html#comment-479848664</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>