<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31ow8/update/2012-03-29T16:20:16/d7d44f5f9486da2147fa79d551c1b61fa4a8042d96b1b372fe557116192bef44</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Some Police Need to Go to Jail 

by BooMan

Thu Mar 29th, 2012 at 10:37:48 AM EST


Pretty much everything George Zimmerman's father says in this interview is demonstrable bullshit. All you need to do to prove this to yourself is to read the 911 call, look at Google Maps, and look at the video of Zimmerman arriving at the police station on the night of the incident. Here is Dad's account:



&lt;b&gt;
Because there has been a lot of break-ins in the area, Robert said George thought it suspicious that someone would not be walking on the street or the sidewalk on a rainy night -- that Martin would be walking between the town homes. He said after making those observations, his son decided to call the police. "He called the non-emergency number first, and they asked him where he was, because he was at the rear of the town houses and there was no street sign," said Robert.


Even though a dispatcher told George Zimmerman not to follow Martin, his father said his son continued his pursuit to locate an address to give to police.


"He lost sight of the individual, he continued to walk down the same sidewalk to the next street, so he could get an address for the police," he said.


"He went to the next street, realized where he was and was walking to his vehicle. It's my understanding, at that point, Trayvon Martin walked up to him and asked him, 'Do you have a [expletive] problem?' George said, 'No, I don't have a problem,' and started to  for his cell phone... at that point, he (Martin) was punching him in the nose, his nose was broken and he was knocked to the concrete."



Robert said Trayvon, "continued to beat George, and at some point, George pulled his pistol and did what he did."



&lt;/b&gt;
The only time that Trayvon Martin was walking between the homes was when he took the sidewalk  of Twin Trees Road. And Zimmerman called 911 well before he ever got to that sidewalk. Prior to that, Martin was seeking shelter from the rain at the Clubhouse (which we know from his girlfriend who was talking to him on the phone). Zimmerman initially gave the Clubhouse as an address, but he made clear that Trayvon Martin was no longer at the Clubhouse:




............................


It's easy to pinpoint Zimmerman and Martin's location from this conversation. They are on Twin Trees Road which basically connects the front entrance to the rear entrance of the gated community. There is no place to be walking in between homes on Twin Trees Road because all the homes are connected. When you come to the bend in the road, however, there is a sidewalk that leads around to the backyards of the homes, and that is where Trayvon Martin ran. And that is where he died. So, Zimmerman's father is wrong. His son did not observe Trayvon Martin walking between homes before he called 911. He also was not near the rear of the townhouses. He was either in or near to his SUV which was located on Twin Trees Road. 


He didn't pursue Trayvon Martin in order to obtain an address to give to the police. He had already provided an address and specific details about the location. He had also arranged for the police to call him when they arrived. He didn't go to the next street because there is no next street. There is a bend in the road, and he didn't go down the bend in the road but onto the sidewalk. He wasn't coming back to his vehicle either. He went down the sidewalk, around the back of the houses, and confronted Trayvon Martin who asked him why he was following him. 


The next part of Zimmerman's dad's account is now in severe doubt because, despite the initial police report (pdf), the video of Zimmerman's arrival at the police station shows that he has no visible wounds, no bandages, no cut on the back of his head, no swelling around the nose, no visible discomfort, and no grass or wetness apparent on his back. He doesn't look like he was attacked at all. 


This does not square at all with Officer Timothy Smith's report that: "While I was in such close contact with Zimmerman, I could observe that his back appeared to be wet and was covered with grass, as if he had been laying on his back on the ground. He also was Bleeding from his nose and back of his head...Zimmerman was placed in the rear of my police vehicle and given first aid by the SFD. "



While Zimmerman's back could have dried  on the ride to the police station and someone could have brushed the grass Off his jacket, the lack of any wounds or bandages calls Officer Smith's entire report into question. 



The fact that his father's explanation doesn't square with any of the known facts in the least is another damning blow. It now appears that the police covered up this incident and filed false police reports. A lot more people than Zimmerman could be going to jail.



http://www.boomantribune.com/story/2012/3/29/103748/031#21</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z4qe1</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/v1i</id></website><link>http://www.jackandjillpolitics.com/2012/03/afternoon-open-thread-803/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:11:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:20:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31ow8</id><link>http://www.jackandjillpolitics.com/2012/03/afternoon-open-thread-803/#comment-479847818</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/agfa</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>