<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwka2q/update/2012-03-31T09:11:15/ab2a648520d85b7647d836cb659c003809f3a6267a72e95f5526f37738fd255c</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>It was white guilt that got Obama elected. 45% of whites voted for him; 96% of blacks voted for Obama. Whites who put a black in the White House have no one to blame but themselves. 
Pat is entirely right in quoting official stats showing black-on-white crime is many times the rate of white-on-black. Pat's great book, Suicide of a Superpower, lays out a forceful argument of why we white Christian Americans are losing and eventually will lose this country. It ought to be read by every critical-thinking America. 
Besides the race issue, this is also a generational problem. I am nearly 70, grew up in the 1950's when Ike was President and the nation was firmly united following the horrors and finally the victory of World War II. Back then, negroes were largely law-biding and hard-working. The biggest problem among youth was "juvenile delinquency" and the threat of Communism. Watch some of the old Bishop Sheen programs to get a flavor for the times. 
I grew up in big cities (NYC, where I was born), once the greatest city in the world, now a cesspool. I am thankful my life is drawing to a close because this is not the country I grew up in nor is it the country in which I want to spend what little time I have left. If I had the resources I would move to Rome to be near the Vatican to continue my Catholic journey and find peace. 
It saddens me to see the decline of America in all aspects -- culture, atheism, sexual depravity, vulgarity, etc. The youth of today, black, white or whatever, generally do not know what hard times really are. They are spoon-fed lies and propaganda every day that tout the merits of materialism and have no sense of spiritual enrichment, they lack respect for traditions that can be traced back thousands of years and to the Ten Commandments. 

Everything today is upside down in terms of values. Public education has largely failed and private education is not much better. The universities are filled with liberals who indoctrinate students in alternate histories that have no basis in fact but are born of prejudice. The politicians, no matter the party, are generally venal, self-serving and cowardly. There are no statesmen any more to tell the truth; they merely spout cliches aimed at soothing the ignorant masses. Bread and circuses, as held sway in Ancient Rome, are what matter. Fear and greed- the twin emotions that drive Wall Street and much of America - rule the day.

The Catholic Church is the last truth-telling institution on earth, finding itself increasingly isolated in a secular godless world -- just as Jesus and St. Paul predicted would happen in the Last Days. We enter heaven through the "narrow gate," as our Lord said, and few will find it. The love of most has grown Cold. It is a cynical age and I want no part of it. 

I look forward to going a "far, far better place," as Dickens put it in Tale of Two Cities. I pity this generation and those to follow who will witness the demise of America as we have known her, loved her and Always wished her to be.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z1tbk</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry2d</id></website><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50546</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:44:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T13:11:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwka2q</id><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50546#comment-481817827</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hp7ft</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>