<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/eowed4/update/2012-01-15T02:29:07/db04810eaa752c5b4ec00c7f57f81f0509f431abd77c80cd70aa6d3d08c9d473</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>God Bless Taylor, you did the right thing and a good deed of honoring the Girl Scouts. 
 Thank you.

Returning U-TUBES feces.
I visited the Leftist Socialist U-TUBE site once, what a cesspool of low class sub human printed Vomit of hot air idiotology screeching hate, bias and prejudice supporting sin and corruption. 
Experiencing U-TUBE was a A Sick Physical Feeling similar to turning on the lights in a dark room and witness a million cockroaches running and dropping from everywhere. 

At U-TUBE any moral person would swear they have stumbled into hells vile abyss of post Sodom and Gomorrah's ghosts Era. 

U-TUBES Liberal site is a sure sign of human decay and failure as the Radical Liberal Socialist Left destroys everything within sight then they turn upon themselves devouring their own in an insane uncontrolled animalistic cannibalistic state.
 
Thus proving very concerning as to further regressing sub-human behavior rather than the advancement of our caring, moral civilization. This also proves the absolute failure of our Government and NEA's run american public school system along with the Progressive Socialist run colleges of teaching higher socialist propaganda.

Allow U-TUBE to decay and self destruct on their own by Not patronizing their site, as the far east Muslim sect systematically kills their own on a daily basis.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ds7l09</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f7e3</id></website><link>http://www.wnd.com/2012/01/youtubers-punish-girl-scout-for-her-beliefs/</link><postedTime>2012-01-14T01:41:24+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-01-15T07:29:07+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/eowed4</id><link>http://www.wnd.com/2012/01/youtubers-punish-girl-scout-for-her-beliefs/#comment-411420690</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-01-14</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>