<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk1ets/post/2012-03-26T11:12:40</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkbojd</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a9kkg</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>They didnt do an investigation. In the amount of time spent on this case to when they let George Zimmerman go, no real investigation was done. There werent even sample taken to see if ZImmerman was drunk or stoned, they did that on the kids body. I know it is just the same old racist, rightwing way, what you are saying. You just want to let Zimmerman Off. Due to a real investigation, that means real forensics, which was not done, is going to be hard to do. Zimmermans friend who backs up his story was not an eyewitness. This is basically a case of where a 17 year old kid who had a right to be where he was. walking home in a gated community, was stalked, forced into  a confrontation (in reality it was Traevon Martin who had the right to defend himself from assault) and then he was coldbloodedly killed. YOu and all the other racist rightwingers defending this killer from any justice are making the situation worse. I do believe there will be a lot more people going to the pollls in NOvember because of this case. I think George Zimmerman needs to be in fear of his life. He is a stone Cold killer.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66ebyx</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cusm</id></website><link>http://www.rawstory.com/rs/2012/03/23/geraldo-rivera-hoodie-allowed-zimmerman-to-kill-martin/</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T13:21:29+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T15:12:40+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk1ets</id><link>http://www.rawstory.com/rs/2012/03/23/geraldo-rivera-hoodie-allowed-zimmerman-to-kill-martin/#comment-476459492</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/64mjb</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>