<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkeygb/update/2012-03-24T22:57:00/efb93a4648ce42fcf6b3016c7f9883e099443f2caa83ff409095883176d9d972</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi1ga0</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>For what it's worth, liberals think that it's impossible to engage conservatives in civil, rational conversation, as well.

I'm a Catholic pro-life moderate, but I talk about politics with my friends all the time, and most of them are liberals, and against my point of view. Granted, the "gay marriage" topic Always gets extremely Heated, but that's because a number of them are gay, and think that it's discrimination, and another way for religions to make them seem like less than people. Then again, I only reject it because it steps on my religious rights, otherwise I would be fine with it - but, to quote author Michael Ende, that's another story, which shall be told at another time. However, most debates really only become fights when I start getting angry and don't talk about the subject with compassion. 

We, as pro-lifers, need to engage liberals in compassionate debate, not with anger. We need to lay everything out on the table to look at, and respect one another and allow them to explain their side, and then speak with love when it is our turn. We cannot let ourselves become angry or violent, because then we run the risk of looking like the bad guys.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6681pi</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/j4xz</id></website><link>http://liveactionnews.org/opinion/dear-lawmakers-please-dont-make-a-mockery-of-the-pro-life-movement/</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T09:21:58+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-25T02:57:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkeygb</id><link>http://liveactionnews.org/opinion/dear-lawmakers-please-dont-make-a-mockery-of-the-pro-life-movement/#comment-475623130</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mxoi</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>