<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw42sw/post/2012-03-30T17:18:34</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The media outlets are using the narrative of Martin and
Zimmerman to boil the tragedy down to a simple matter of race, forgetting that
racists come in all colors. That was immediately evident when I saw the photo
of Trayvon in his football uniform—obviously younger than 17. 



He did not deserve to be murdered, but perhaps attitude
(something more evident in the photos of him a little closer to his age when he
died) may have contributed SOMEWHAT to this tragedy. He may have been 
(in some of the reporting) like a " NO_LIMIT_N***A"—Trayvon's
OWN Twitter handle. 



Every photo of Trayvon in the majority of news accounts
shows him as an "angelic" thirteen (or so)-year-old. That is FRAMING,
pure and simple.



What we do not see was someone who wears a grill, Twittering
about Glocks and "dabbled" in pot... the subsequent facts of his life
that have come out (thank you, Daily Mail). Is it possible he that look the
part—in attitude AND dress.



Let me be clear, this is NO REASON TO GET SHOT! 



Consider this scenario... Trayvon is walking around alone, certainly
not wearing the football uniform presented in the media. 


The media outlets are using the narrative of Martin and
Zimmerman to boil the tragedy down to a simple matter of race, forgetting that
racists come in all colors. That was immediately evident when I saw the photo
of Trayvon in his football uniform—obviously younger than 17. 

He did not deserve to be murdered, but perhaps attitude
(something more evident in the photos of him a little closer to his age when he
died) may have contributed SOMEWHAT to this tragedy. He may have been Acting
(in some of the reporting) like someone who sees himself as a  "NO_LIMIT_N***A"—Trayvon's
OWN Twitter handle.

Every photo of Trayvon in the majority of news accounts
shows him as an "angelic" thirteen (or so)-year-old. That is FRAMING,
pure and simple.

What we do not see was an older teenager who wears a "grill," Twittering
about Glocks and "dabbled" in pot... the subsequent details of his life
that have come out (thank you, Daily Mail). Is it possible he that looked the
part—in dress AND attitude.

Let me be clear, this is NO REASON TO GET SHOT! 

Consider this scenario... Trayvon is walking around alone, certainly
not wearing the football uniform presented in the media. 

A "neighborhood watch" volunteer confronts him—rightfully
or not. Trayvon becomes confrontational (again rightly or not), angered that
someone would even question his place in the neighborhood—an attitude that is prevalent
in current youth culture, worshiping the "thug" life. It is how some young people self-identify, and the anger that comes with living the (real or imagined)
"thug life."

It CERTAINLY could happen; there are many people that would
respond with anger after asked what they are doing in an area—regardless of
skin color—especially by someone who is NOT a police officer. 

Wouldn't it be reasonable to say that Trayvon thought, "Who are YOU to
hassle me, is it because I am BLACK?"

The situation quickly gets Heated—Zimmerman justified (at
least to himself) in asking what this kid doing walking around the
neighborhood, alone at night. In response, Trayvon pushes back, thinking he
doesn't have to answer to this "cracker" (as in the t-shirts that
have been going around). 

What Trayvon PROBABLY DIDN'T KNOW prior to confronting Zimmerman,
was that he was carrying a gun.

 </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/672jyu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/618n</id></website><link>http://www.poynter.org/latest-news/top-stories/168391/the-iconic-photos-of-trayvon-martin-george-zimmerman-why-you-may-not-see-the-others/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T10:17:18+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:18:34+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw42sw</id><link>http://www.poynter.org/latest-news/top-stories/168391/the-iconic-photos-of-trayvon-martin-george-zimmerman-why-you-may-not-see-the-others/#comment-481211170</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lnv0q</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>