<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkxwxe/update/2012-03-26T08:19:18/d48e70fd3cc339eed6281d6a50f43015a5e993ce9e94827172ae796997d6a3c1</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>There is a big difference between the black bear and the brown bear (aka grizzly). Black bears are common across the entire US, but the grizzly bear is restricted to few points in the lower 48. 

Alaska, on the other hand, has everything. Perhaps the best brown bear viewing area is Katmai National Park during the Salmon runs in the summer. Another great place is Pack Creek in Tongass National Forest. Both are expensive places to get to.

In the lower 48, Yellowstone is way better than Jackson for bear viewing. Again, it is timing, but Pelican Creek, Hayden Valley, Fishing Bridge, Lamar Valley are hot Spots. Likewise, Glacier National Park also has a healthy bear population.

Anywhere along the high mountain range of California is prime black bear territory, but if you want to see bears, check out Yosemite valley where you can watch them break into cars at night. The problem is so bad that simply having a cooler visible in your car makes it a mark. 

Regarding Gatlinburg, Jeanne is right. It can compete for the tackiest place on earth. Unfortunately, parts of the Smoky Mountains cannot be easily  without going through Gatlinburg. Cades Cove is probably the best place for bear watching, if you can tolerate the incessant traffic. As a ranger buddy once said, when people see bears, their brains go out the window. 

In the Smokies, bear hot Spots seem to be Abrams Falls trail, Gregory Bald trail, Cades Cove loop road, Walnut Bottoms, but bears can be seen anywhere in the park. However, for the BEST bears in the Southeast, Martin is right. Eastern NC/SC bears statistically come in at 1 1/2 - 2X the weight of their mountainous counterparts. The reason is simple, better climate, better food supply. There are GREAT places to view bears in the coastal plain, but I will not divulge all my Secrets!

The above is my experience as a wildlife photographer!

</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rysly</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/vhd7</id></website><link>http://www.elliott.org/blog/where-are-americas-best-bears-2/</link><postedTime>2012-03-25T11:58:53+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T12:19:18+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkxwxe</id><link>http://www.elliott.org/blog/where-are-americas-best-bears-2/#comment-476355930</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l2af6</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>