<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi6ihx/post/2012-03-22T22:37:21</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ek4o5u</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l9dpo</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>What is amazing about Obama?  Despite the fact that the Republicans and the rest of the Right Wing Noise Machine rolled out the most racist, vile smear campaign in political history in an effort to derail his presidency, he still managed to save the U.S. economy from complete collapse. Anyone who doesn't realize just how serious things were when he assumed office is either not paying attention or is simply too stupid to understand.

I disagree with many of the things Obama has done. The fact that the right labels him a "socialist" is absolutely hilarious; he is, in fact, too far to the right on many issues. He is way too cozy with the financial sector, and he has given in way too easily and way too often to the ridiculous tax cuts the right demands for rich people.

The top tax rate is currently at one of the lowest points in U.S. history. There were periods in the 20th century when the top tax rate was 90%. And while many people did not like paying that tax rate, they also understood that running a government costs money. They also understood that an effective and powerful governmental structure provides the platform on which private sector interests make their fortunes. Imagine trying to publicly fund major infrastructure projects in this political climate. The Repubtards would have a collective aneurysm. Just think what would happen if we needed to build an interstate system. Or if we decided to mount a manned mission to Mars. Or any other public-works project that required spending tax money for the good of the entire nation.

Over the last few decades, the Republicans have made it possible for a very small percentage of people to amass a very large percentage of the nation's wealth. If you are unfamiliar with it, Google "U.S. Gini Coefficient." This is a formula used to measure income inequality, which is considered to be an fairly effective means of determining the overall health of a nation's economy, as well as a measure of social and cultural health. True PATRIOTISM is not a "me first" game. A TRUE Patriot recognizes that their country should serve the best interests of every citizen. A TRUE patriot recognizes that a country that crushes 90% of its population to serve the needs of the other 10% is not a great country.

The damage the Republicans and the Right Wing have done to this once-great nation is unforgivable.  The true downfall of America began the day the Republicans -finding themselves unable to get him any other way- attempted to remove a legitimately elected President from office because he got a BLOWJOB. In that moment they proved that NOTHING was too low, that there were no limits to how far they would go to undo the will of the voters.

They did it again -but even worse- with Obama. All of the things that have been said about him  (Born in Kenya, Socialist, Muslim, Terrorist Sympathizer, White People Hater, Radical, etc) are the result of paid propaganda campaigns. Any one of you who parrots any of those things because you think that you "know it to be true" are complete fools who are being used as useful idiots by your corporate overlords. NONE of those things are even close to being the truth, and you would simply be embarrassing if you weren't actually so dangerous.

Because yes, it is DANGEROUS for propagandists to go that far in trying to deligitimize a political opponent. It is designed to divide the nation so that compromise and mutual respect become impossible. The Right Wing Noise Machine promotes an agenda of ignorance and stupidity. They quite literally want people to be stupid, and to accept on faith things that simply are not true. As long as they can keep the rubes talking about Abortion and Contraception and Socialists and Birth Certificates and all of the other stupid s*** that passes for political discourse these days, they can distract them from thinking about things that are actually important, like the REAL "wealth redistribution" of the last 50 years that has created a permanent underclass in America that exists solely to serve the Mass-Consumption-Wealth-Generation Machine that has sent over 50% of the country's wealth into the hands of 10% of its people.

Do you ever wonder why the Right is so dead set against public education? It's because they don't want you to think. It really is that simple. Listening to Rick Santorum complain that college is for "elitists" was both hilarious and disgusting. Anti-intellectualism should not be a badge of honor. The "Founding Fathers" that the Right likes to blab about so often? They were all well-educated men who respected intellectual achievement. Do you think documents like the U.S. Constitution just write themselves? Do you think a random sampling of people in the crowd at a Sarah Palin rally could sit down together and use what they know of law, politics, government, and history and come up with a working constitution capable of serving as the political foundation of the most powerful nation on Earth? And craft it so well that it could last for 200+ years?

Every time one of you rubes posts something about "socialism" or "Obamacare" or any other inanity you are, in effect, saying "I don't  think for myself!" and "I'm too stupid to know any better!" To the poster who said something about how nobody wants Obamacare: just remember when the time comes that you get cancer and your insurance company is legally restricted from dropping your coverage, you will have "Obamacare" to thank for it. When your kids go  to college and you are able to keep them on your coverage for a few additional years you will have Obamacare to thank for it. When you are able to get coverage despite your preexisting condition, you will have Obamacare to thank for it.And when enough of you clueless rubes have died , and this nation FINALLY moves to single-payer health care, your kids and their kids will have Obamacare to thank for getting the ball rolling.

How anyone could not understand the absolute necessity of a single-payer system is beyond me. And the way people rail against it (it's SOSHULIZM!!!) clearly demonstrates their ignorance, and shows that the paid propaganda of the health insurance lobby is actually working.See, in reality, just about every single government agency or program is a form of socialism. It is a means by which the collective purchasing power of the people is used to do something that would cost a lot more if individuals had to do it for  themselves. Health care is a perfect example. The U.S. pays a larger percentage of its GDP on health care than does any other country in the world. And for that money it gets really good coverage and health care for some, while leaving about half the country with inadequate insurance and access to health care, and the remaining 30 million or so with no insurance and no health care at all. How can this be "the greatest country in the world" when tens of millions of its people cannot even get to see a doctor? And how can anyone call themselves a "patriot" and yet not support the idea that everyone in this country should be able to see a doctor? 

Single-payer is not about deciding what doctor you can go to or what procedures you can get, It's simply about using the collective purchasing power of 150 million taxpayers to buy a group policy. Just as it's less expensive on a per-person basis for your employer to provide you with an insurance policy, it's WAY less expensive on a per-person basis to fund single-payer health care. That's not "radical socialism," it's just math. The strain on the U.S. economy of the nation's health care costs is staggering. Those of you who oppose single-payer are already paying other people's costs. If you have insurance, some of your costs go to cover the costs to hospitals for all the people who go to Emergency Rooms when they get sick because they don't have insurance. It would be far less expensive, in terms of overall health care costs, to insure those people, thereby keeping them out of the ER. 

With the U.S. population getting older, the strain on the economy will only get worse. As health care costs continue to climb the pressure will eventually crack the economy. The rates at which costs are climbing is untenable. The only question is "when do we do it; now, while it's still relatively easy, or later, when it will be much more difficult and much more expensive?"

It really has been amazing to watch how both parties -though the Republicans are much worse about it- have dismantled the entire U.S. economic system in the space of one or two generations,  and replaced the entire manufacturing sector -the component of the economy that built this nation- and replaced it with a service economy, one where everyone pays everyone else to do  things for them. We no longer make things for a low cost and sell them for a higher costs -a system that creates wealth- we now just do things for each other, which does not create wealth. Underneath all of that is the finance/monetarist economy, which creates wealth out of nothing, and then buys and sells it back and forth while creating the illusion that each transaction is adding a layer of wealth. That's what happens in the so-called "bubbles" -the tech bubble, the housing bubble, etc. And it's great when you're on the bubble as it expands, but not so great when it pops. 

And all the while that the Republicans are dismantling the country and selling the parts overseas, they're rousing the rabble with talk of Birth Certificates and Socialism and...wait, what is it this week? Oh, yeah: "Critical  Race Theory." LOL!!! A bunch of stuffy old black dudes who examine the way the criminal justice system has, over the nation's history, favored stuffy old white dudes. Wow, that some really scary stuff. I hope those professors don't take  their tweed jackets, roll up their sleeves, and start doin' some terrorizin'!

Seriously, people: get a friggin' clue. Turn of FOX -and yes, FOX really is as bad as people say it is- and pick up a book. Learn some REAL history instead of the weird stuff that people like Sarah Palin and Michelle Bachmann just make up as they go along. Learn some political and economic theories so you can start to understand why stuff really happens, and who is it that profits from the stuff that happens? Because in the end, that is what it's all about: the desire for profit fuels the world. So when you hear someone tell you that single-payer health care is bad, ask yourself who profits from blocking it? When you start hearing that we're getting ready to go halfway around the world to blow up some more brown people and then take over their country for a decade or so (of course, they won't tell you that part. They'll tell you that "we will be greeted as liberators" and that the war "will take weeks, not months) ask yourself who profits from it? (hint: the answer is  Dick Cheney). When you hear a politician claiming he or she wants to do away with public education and give students "vouchers" that they can use at "any private school of their choice" (which of course means a religious school) ask yourself who profits? (That's a trick question: the answer is "the entire Republican party" because that means the religious school does a lot of the work of indoctrination and forcible-ignorance-insertion that the politicians would otherwise have to do).

Again: I am not an Obama-loving Lefty. What I am is someone who has taken some time to read about stuff,and who has taken some time to pay attention to stuff. That's really all there is to it. And I can tell you that, no matter what you think of Obama (or, for some of you: what you think you think of him because that's what you were told to think) the simple fact is that his administration truly did save this country -and possibly the entire world- from a complete collapse of the economic system. I don't think most people have any clue about how close we came to a financial Armageddon. As I said, there are a lot of things he has done that I do not like at all. My biggest concern for our country is how it is basically owned and operated by huge corporations, rather than by the people and their democratically-elected representatives. It  cracks me up to hear a right-winger complain about "big government" when it has been the Republicans who have been responsible for most of the spending growth and deficit expansion over the last 50 years. The most thrifty and fiscally responsible President in the last 50 years? Clinton. The least thrifty, most fiscally irresponsible President in the last 50 years? GWB. And that part is not even close; he spent money like a drunken sailor on shore leave. And he didn't even put the costs of his ridiculous wars on the books. First thing Obama did when he took over? He added them to the budget. In other words, he took responsibility for cleaning up a mess he didn't even make. Tell me the last time you saw a politician -or, really,  anyone at all- do something like that. 

And the next time you're complaining about Obama and spending, I suggest you don't get your facts from FOX. Try getting them from, oh, I don't know..how about a book? That should work! Get out a book, or even look this stuff up online, just not from a "news" channel like FOX (or MSNBC for that matter) and look at the facts: Clinton left Bush a budget surplus that was projected to be between 2 and 3 billion dollars, and would likely last a decade or more as long as spending remained at reasonable levels. Even without putting most of the costs of the war on the books, GW ran up deficits totaling about TEN BILLION DOLLARS. So much for the part of fiscal responsibility, huh? The exalted Saint Ronald of Reagan wasn't much better. Despite all his talk of "small government" and how "government is the problem" and how "taxes are too high" and so on, he immediately began running up deficit, he expanded the size and Scope of the federal government, and he raised taxes twice. His biggest use of deficit spending went to military spending. Ronnie may have had Alzheimer's even before he began his first term, but he was no dummy. It was clear to anyone who was paying attention that the Soviet Union was on the brink of collapse. Reagan kicked the arms race back into high gear, giving the world the impression that he was playing tough with the America's deadliest foe (when in truth they hadn't posed a real threat in years, and never really were as big a threat as they were made about to be). The military spending was an easy way to prime the pump of the U.S. economy, just as every president, democrat and republican, since the war of 1812. And when the Soviet Union did collapse, the republicans immediately made the claim that "Reagan won the Cold War." LOL. I love that kind of phony-baloney bulls***, and I love watching people lap it up like it's gourmet food and not the bulls*** it actually is.

So, um, yeah: read a f***ing book once in a while. Of course,  if you just read my entire post, you've probably done your reading for the day. But tomorrow, it's book-learnin' fer ya!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/d0isfo</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tz1k</id></website><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/jerry-springer-rips-into-fox-news-accuses-network-of-bashing-president-obama-every-day/</link><postedTime>2012-01-18T14:01:58+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T02:37:21+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi6ihx</id><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/jerry-springer-rips-into-fox-news-accuses-network-of-bashing-president-obama-every-day/#comment-474157641</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c9umy</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-01-18</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>