<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/cp6der/update/2011-06-20T18:56:32/0e02901baba9f95bb502f97ccea1c7d291382ef85b501bf8b829ed197591aff8</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Up until a couple of months ago I had 2006 les Paul gold top 1960 re-issue. Times were tough so I had to sell it and got exactly what I originally paid for it. Didn’t loose a penny. Couldn’t stop the calls from coming in at over $1,500. It gave me pause but I sold it anyway. I began to Regret it almost instantly. I was left with my strat and missing my Les Paul that I wanted since I was a kid. I'm 47 now. Those years with that gold top were some of  my favorite times. But, I had to change the pick-ups, get strap locks, upgrade the caps and constantly re intonate. Every time I changes the strings, the wheels would spin and saddles would just fall Off the guitar. All that said, I was still a proud owner of a gold top. 
I was able to get a beautiful custom one of a kind guitar from a local Luthier to replace it. It’s a gorgeous Les Paul copy.  $4,000 of a pure curly maple Beauty and brand name hardware. I got it on a trade deal so no cash out of pocket. Just last weekend I saw a post of someone with a 2008 gold top standard in perfect condition. The add said he didn’t like the gold and wanted something prettier. I couldn’t drive fast enough the 2 hours to meet him and traded on the Spot. 
This guitar is the most amazing Les Paul I have ever seen or played. Its perfection in every way. All complaints were taken care of. It was light yet solid, the action was perfect, the tone was amazing, the see though panel on the electronics is just cool (who doesn’t like to look in there) the strap locks were factory installed, the case was beautiful but my biggest surprise was yet to come. The first thing I did was change the strings. I was fully expecting the tail to slip out and the saddles to move. I took care to cover the guitar to avoid scratches from the tail sliding across the top and made a mark to get the bridge back in the right position after my aggressive cleaning rag turned the height screws. But wait; they were stuck? I pulled and pulled before I realized, they had set screws! I laughed out loud considering myself to be an advanced user, I felt tricked. They finally did it! Locked those baby's in place. My amazement continues as I put the chord though my strap so it didn’t fall out and plugged it in. I then realized, it was already upgraded. I let that chord hang as never again did I need to worry about it falling out in the middle of my solo. I laughed again. Then, I turned on my amp. Played through clean and dirty tones with each pick-up configuration. After 10 minutes, I hit the standby switch and once again laughed out loud! The tone was pro and perfect in every sense. I have been smiling and laughing ever since. If you’re a guitar player, you simply must own a 2008 les Paul Standard. It is a ton of fun and the STANDARD all guitars should live by. Get one, open the Beautiful case, look at it then play it. Let me know if you don’t laugh out loud at the experience. I'm certain you will smile. Thank you Gibson!
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/84pcn4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6yb5</id></website><link>http://www2.gibson.com/Products/Electric-Guitars/Les-Paul/Gibson-USA/2008-Les-Paul-Standard.aspx</link><postedTime>2010-10-07T07:06:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-06-20T22:56:32+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/cp6der</id><link>http://www2.gibson.com/Products/Electric-Guitars/Les-Paul/Gibson-USA/2008-Les-Paul-Standard.aspx#comment-230584547</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mbqxd</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2010-10-07</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>