<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m15g8n/update/2012-03-12T18:31:55/c062d3f894984277ccdb3d86570557f2b930b3f673e6332e99f652bb92297ab4</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Paul supporters were railroaded by entrenched leadership many large counties.  The powerless have no recourse but to appeal, which is exactly what they did. There were young folks at Polk County who are new to the system and passionate about being involved, and didn't know any better than to protest.  
As a Paul supporter and Polk County delegate, I can tell you that myself and many of us - including some that you libeled above as being instigators - were trying to calm those folks down and get them to surrender their cases and simply win the respect of an honest effort and a peaceful surrender.  
This article is straight-up hearsay and your "sources" have just as much ulterior motive as anyone else in that room.Most of us are not trying to be divisive or disruptive at all, we just want a voice within our own party.  Many chairs and party officials are openly hostile to Paul folks as well, the only difference is that it's acceptable when you're in power.  Check the facts on the Scott and Pottawattamie conventions and you'll see that the Paul element followed the rules and still got bulldozed by a mainstream republican element that would rather exclude them than involve them.  What you're encouraging in this article is basically for them to just shut up and take it.  Kevin, I bear you no ill-will or disrespect, but do try to lace in some objectivity.  The convention process is about passion and activism.  It's not supposed to be a comfy get-together for lifelong republicans who are used to their names being on the seats.  This country is Burning, and frankly, as much as you may not like rough-cut Paul supporters, you need us.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6aizvp</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/qla9</id></website><link>http://theiowarepublican.com/2012/ron-paul-supporters-cause-county-convention-chaos-threaten-lawsuit/</link><postedTime>2012-03-12T06:35:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-12T22:31:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m15g8n</id><link>http://theiowarepublican.com/2012/ron-paul-supporters-cause-county-convention-chaos-threaten-lawsuit/#comment-463767212</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-12</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>