<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp7uxf/update/2012-03-21T15:39:39/8dff61df89718654be7f92c656a69c6f8907777824d77e1b9c1ae0a59b6967fe</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpl4vo</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/r7i7y</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Knock it , Guy, if you you pretend your context is pretext.  Let those with eyes read and consider. 
Here are the remarks:

If they [a mixed race couple] were far away from the gentiles they would all [have] to be killed -- when they mingle seed it is death to all. If a black man &amp; white woman come to you &amp; demand baptism can you deny them? The law is their seed shall not be amalgamated. Mulattoes [are] like mules they can't have children, but if they will be eunuchs for the Kingdom of Heaven's sake, they may have a place in the temple. 
Shall I tell you the law of God in regard to the African race? If the white man who belongs to the chosen seed mixes his blood with the seed of Cain, the penalty, under the law of God, is death on the Spot. This will Always be so. The nations of the earth have transgressed every law that God has given, they have changed the ordinances and broken every covenant made with the fathers, and they are like a hungry man that dreameth that he eateth, and he awaketh and behold he is empty.[Prophet Brigham Young, Journal of Discourses, v. 10, p. 110] 

Brigham Young is quite clear that mixed couples would be killed if they were "away from the gentiles" [meaning the U.S. law enforcement agencies could not interfere with the operation of Young's priesthood killers.  Young et al were virulent in their race hatred, and the FLDS teachings of race hatred, subservient creations and ressurections come straight from Young's teachings. 
Guy, don't play games, guy.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/624q9r</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6rx1</id></website><link>http://www.sltrib.com/sltrib/opinion/53667380-82/church-doctrine-blacks-bott.html.csp</link><postedTime>2012-03-10T08:02:33+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-21T19:39:39+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp7uxf</id><link>http://www.sltrib.com/sltrib/opinion/53667380-82/church-doctrine-blacks-bott.html.csp#comment-472702525</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g2iwp</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-10</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>