<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kbf7/post/2012-03-29T22:40:04</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>What the Leafs are is a very mediocre collection of players. Nothing more - nothing less. Forget that "we were in a playoff Spot as recently as February" mantra - they quickly fell out of that Spot as soon as those around them started playing for real. The fault lies with the GM. He put this team together and there's no coach in the world that could turn that bunch into a competitive team. He then compounded his errors by handing Grabovski a sweetheart deal far beyond his capability as an 82-game C. He was - and is - a 3rd/4th line C at best, and if you start paying those kind of players the salary he just received then you're headed for disaster in a cap world. Phaneuf never was - is not now - and never will be a $6.6 million D. Better players were selected AFTER Kadri in his draft. The contract given to Komisarek was simply a joke. The thinking that Connolly could somehow become something he never could be in Buffalo over several years - and then pay him $4.5 million for two years - was a serious error in judgement that he's now stuck with. Starting a season with not one but two untried goaltenders was another serious error in judgement. Lupul, who has played just 48% of the games since the 2007-08 season, was a gamble that seemed to be paying Off, until he went down yet again at the most inopportune time. And giving up a Top 2 pick (Seguin), another first rounder (Hamilton) and a 2nd (Knight) for a pure sniper (Kessel) who desperately needs a Top C - and then failing to get him that C - was just plain dumb. And what made it even dumber was that he had to KNOW there was no way he was going to get that kind of C. Not from the UFA list and certainly not in trade as he had nothing with which to deal. So why waste that trade on Kessel? Keep the picks and build. Even if that process takes a couple of more years to bear fruit, they're no further ahead  with the approach he DID take. All of which points to a GM even more overrated than the players he signed. A  recipe for disaster. Just ask Montreal, who at least canned their mistake today.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zjfp5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zsj8</id></website><link>http://www.torontosun.com/2012/03/29/leafs-worse-than-bad-against-flyers</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:00:23+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:40:04+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kbf7</id><link>http://www.torontosun.com/2012/03/29/leafs-worse-than-bad-against-flyers#comment-480166323</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gfnyc</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>