<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msm6qz/update/2012-03-27T08:02:05/cf7295c190428885da81ce0b808150210cb871b8ebc9bb299c0b1a61375257bc</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Gary Weiss's AYN RAND NATION, from which this piece is excerpted, is an important book that shows just how much La Rand and her monomanias have become the new normal on the American Right.   

It used to be that Randianism was a crackpot, fringe phenomenon--as shown in Jeff Walker's THE AYN RAND CULT (1999). As Weiss demonstrates, however, this is no longer the case. There are now people in Congress and in the finance world who openly declare their dedication to Rand and her agenda. ATLAS SHRUGGED serves as their bible, their Utopian sourcebook. She is almost mainstream today.     

An experience of mine demonstrates just how far Rand has come to be at the center of right-wing discourse. In 1972, I was living in Binghamton, NY. Hurricane Agnes had just devastated the area. So, being at the time a budding satirist, I penned the following letter to the BINGHAMTON PRESS:    

"I'm sick and tired of reading all these Bleeding-heart reports about alleged flood victims. If these people's homes are in such bad shape, they can show some private initiative and fix them on their own."   

 "I made my money by my own efforts, and I don't like seeing my hard-earned salary go so some crybaby can mooch Off a government handout. All this flood-welfare is the first step toward socialism, and I want no part of it."   

 "Jonathan Swifte"   

Well, the letter elicited a flood (so to speak) of angry responses, even from avowed conservatives, who praised the help sent by government programs as well as by charities and individual groups.    

That was 1972. Today, by contrast, many a conservative would enthusiastically say "amen" to Mr. Swifte. Randian bloggers frankly say things like, "If someone is stupid enough to build his house in hurricane country, that's his problem! He shouldn't be robbing my pockets to rebuild it." The words "looters and moochers," taken right out of John Galt's speech, come up in their ravings. (One also encounters "blizzard country" and "earthquake country" in these sorts of heartless statements.)    

And of course, there's Ron Paul, who denies Federal aid to Katrina victims and calls for abolishing FEMA. Or Gov. Kasich of Ohio, who rejects Federal help for tornado victims. Those two are simply among the most audible voices out there. Their views are seen as respectable, not wacky.   

Randian dogmas have morphed into a standard component of GOP ideology. It's not a pretty picture. I recommend Gary Weiss's book for further enlightenment on the matter.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l6dl8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ant8</id></website><link>http://www.alternet.org/news/154700/the_horrors_of_an_ayn_rand_world%3A_why_we_must_fight_for_america%27s_soul/comments/</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T01:13:23+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-27T12:02:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msm6qz</id><link>http://www.alternet.org/news/154700/the_horrors_of_an_ayn_rand_world%3A_why_we_must_fight_for_america%27s_soul/comments/#comment-477351194</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/awnqd</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>