<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwqy30/post/2012-03-30T18:24:56</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw40i3</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zd1jb</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>oh I understand where Punk is coming from, but with Rock Cena it is different to a potential Lesnar Batista match. Cena has worked all year, I can't fault him on that, and with Rock coming back it is to boost WWE, whatever you want to say about him leaving the WWE he is still one of the most recognisable faces from Wrestling and in films and has helped bring alot of attention to this years mania, not to mention he was one of the defining faces in WWE during the attitude Era along with austin, taker, HHH, etc, him coming back is good business, him coming back is making me and lots of my friends want to order wrestlemania for the first time in years, not to mention this match has been waiting to happen for years with Cena and Rock taking occasional shots at each other.

Batista and Lesnar are different, while they were succesful in their own right they never really made the mark as the Rock did in his time, not to mention in their post wwe careers (yes Lesnar went on a succesful MMA career but he's not known much outside of it). With what I said about Rock Cena been waiting to happen, lesnar batista has no basis for a main event at mania with a year long build up, no legit Heat between them before, it makes no sense.

As for those who work all year round, thats exactly it, they have the whole year to get over and get a place on the card, and they have years to earn a Spot in a mania main event, which is what Cena has done, even though I hate him with a passion.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67zkmd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dhf8</id></website><link>http://www.ewrestlingnews.com/news/3961/wwe-to-announce-wrestlemania-29-main-event-on-raw</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:42:42+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T22:24:56+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwqy30</id><link>http://www.ewrestlingnews.com/news/3961/wwe-to-announce-wrestlemania-29-main-event-on-raw#comment-481269527</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/roe8p</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>