<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpqdzm/update/2012-03-21T18:35:35/c122bbb5539c3a251d81918969c488b2233438dfca60e623298fca1383ed2561</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mj4o5d</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cxr8f</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>It's hard for the average person that has Always trusted the media to believe that they are all on the worng side.  Actually, if this were really still America, we would have FCC void their licenses as they (most all ) have violated their oath by being extremely and openly biased.  People are like sheep, easily led by the sly and cunning deceivers onn both sides of the aisle.
You are correct, media, DemonRats and Republicans have made Ron Paul out to be a nut case because they fear anyone that will upset their GODD OL'BOY network!
     How many will ever vote for a black man now after this side show?  I supported cain but almost everyone universally said the saem thing, "I'll never make that mistake again"!  And that because of the way Obama has both played the race card and proven himslef to be an outright, undeniable RACIST himslef!
    I feel very sorry for the lemmings because they cannot discern right from worng and wouldn't be able to Spot a liar and deciever if they fell over one.  Jim Jones knew all about them!  Things went his way until one Congressman smelled a rat!
     America will never be the same, one way or the other!
     Obama and his gang behind him, the really BIGmoney people under cover, have played this well, they picked a time when Americans have been dumbed down and have become lethargic girly-men.  This nonsense could NEVER have happened even 40 years ago!~</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6595y8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lkcy</id></website><link>http://www.wired.com/threatlevel/2012/03/ff_nsadatacenter/</link><postedTime>2012-03-15T23:25:18+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-21T22:35:35+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpqdzm</id><link>http://www.wired.com/threatlevel/2012/03/ff_nsadatacenter/#comment-472869439</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zgyqj</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-15</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>