<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkfgga/update/2012-03-26T12:15:38/ca86db238e56fde294f7041279b8d6138223dcbf6d32f9a2a3658e1231c9f0c5</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Well, they sneaked this one in - it has the potential to create a lot of problems, for both listed building owners and the conservation bodies that keep telling them what they can do with their own property.

I can only be thankful that I have carried out a major refurbishment and repair programme of a grade II listed house  before the VAT exemption is removed. Getting any work done on a listed building is a nightmare.  It cost almost £1000 merely to obtain the necessary permission from my local council to repair the house - a protracted and costly process that meant the building was subject to continued weather and water damage while I waited for approval.  They threaten you with prosecution of you do anything without their approval.  

The cost of materials and labour has been considerable. I very much doubt I would have gone ahead with some of the work without the VAT exemption.

I had to replace all exterior woodwork on the property - windows/porches/doors - which were rotten, holed and letting water into the fabric of the building.  Even though I had no intention of doing anything other than a like-for-like replacement, a conservation officer made 3 visits to the property, demanded several sets of drawings and was very prescriptive and officious. 

The VAT exemption exists to encourage owners to maintain and repair the fabric of buildings that have costly problems because of their age.  Conservation legislation allows unelected officials the right to tell you exactly what you can and can't do with property you own and occupy, and they can even insist that you use very expensive materials and processes when much cheaper variants are available - most of which have no impact on the appearance of the property anyway.

If the VAT exemption is removed, it should be matched by a corresponding relaxation of the highly onerous conservation rules that are imposed on the owners of listed buildings, or the wholesale de-listing of most Grade II buildings, since the current rules are only tolerated because; a) you are heavily penalised if you break them; and b) the VAT exemption goes some way to mitigating the extra cost of work on listed buildings. 

Taking away the VAT exemption while maintaining rigorous (and in many cases, quite barmy) rules on what can or can't be done with a listed building is very unfair. If this fundamental imbalance is not addressed, it will lead to either widespread law breaking or the slow decline of much building stock which, if properly managed and renovated, could be used and occupied for a long time to come.

The problem is that in recent years English Heritage has enforced conservation rules on Grade II listed buildings that were meant to be applied only to outstanding historical buildings, with a resulting raft of people feeding Off the system and Bleeding the owner dry. The way they decide whether or not a building can be modernised is also haphazard across the country, to say the least.  Houses are meant to be lived in, not turned into museums of ancient crafts, and whether one sort of mortar or brick or another is used should be up to the owner (who's paying for it), not to conservation officers. 

There needs to be a wide-ranging consultation and, if the VAT exemption goes, a total rethink on the rules governing listed buildings, with much greater freedom allowed to make them fit for purpose in the 21st century.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yl2sd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/finance/budget/9158983/VAT-increase-on-listed-buildings-will-discourgage-improvements.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T07:01:40+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T16:15:38+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkfgga</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/finance/budget/9158983/VAT-increase-on-listed-buildings-will-discourgage-improvements.html#comment-476504389</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hahvk</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>