<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mid0ff/post/2012-03-22T19:54:05</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Whitney's Wife here on Thursday, 3/23/2012:

Happy Spring to all who are still hanging in with our infrequent postings on Whitney's progress.  It's been 11+ months since W called me while on an errand and said "I think I'm having a stroke!" and I replied "call 911, take an aspirin and I'll see you there."  Since that air lift to Harborview Hospital in Seattle to now, he has gone through a remarkable recovery and healing process.  He has gone from not knowing the year it was/is...2001? 2006? as days went by once out of his coma and spent a month there, then on to St. Joseph's in Tacoma for PT, OT, etc. for several weeks, then our 24/7 caregiver duties for months and months afterward to get him back on his feet.  He blanked several months including at least from April forward prior to the actual stroke, then having to learn who we were and our names and how we fit into his life.  The interesting thing was that being a complex puzzle person, as soon as he was in Neurosurgery learning to walk w/walker again, etc. he was able to do more complex puzzles as long as the print was large enough since he had and still has the (what I call Picasso vision) double/broken line sight and wears an eye patch for steadiness.  We created a family tree of family names and who fit where on posterboard that he could study when gaps popped up.  By the first of 2012, he was able to stay/live alone and book and catch the Access bus to his OT, routine appointments and be safe.  This gave me parts of each week to catch up on all the ignored projects needed on my place that suddenly halted once I went to Harborview with him last May.  Camping in the waiting room was how I spent my summer vacation.

Sometime in February, W casually noted that he was having head pain and odd symptoms and Headaches, etc. and then the truth came out that he'd been having such for over a month..so  we went to Harborview to do a consult with Dr. Rockhill, Head of GammaKnife Radiation Department.  We had seen him after his stroke last summer and W has had to get well again and then think about making decisions. That day came and W chose to have the gammaknife radiation surgery and underwent the procedure March 6th, for CT, MRI, Angiogram to brain, assessment, then 88 minutes in radiation machine.  He wasn't allowed to stay in hospital overnight so Off we went to a motel with instructions of what to do if Convulsions, groin hemmorage, or other scarey signs came up..all for me to solve as the only watchbird.  He was fine though slept roughly thru the night and we got up and he felt so good we went to the Seattle Art Museum's Paul Gauguin Show...it was fabulous and W did very well with his walker.  We had lunch out on the way home in Gig Harbor (long drive) and he went to bed.  A couple of days later, he walked out of the house for a trip to Costco and said he was going without his walker!  Now, we have advanced from walker and hunched over, to folding walker into a grocery cart and pushing it in a crowd, to holding my shoulder to walk to a building and carts inside, or to sit in church recently, but not totally on his own.  He is keeping a journal but he has made more progress every day since coming home and feels blessed to have undergone the surgery and feels he is on his way to being himself again.  Maybe we'll eventually get back to ballroom dancing again!  For now, we hope to take in seeing Lighthouses of Washington as we get the urge to travel.  He has been cutting limbs and twigs from last summer's hired help clearing out the back flower beds...quite a remarkable recovery! Prayer and protein and confidence in the "I can do it" attitude have brought W a long way.  We just want to thank you again for the prayers and good thoughts for Whitney.
Have a happy Spring! 
Phyllis (Polly) and Whitney</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ga32l2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tlm8</id></website><link>http://whitneysworldwideweb.yolasite.com/blog/well-wishes</link><postedTime>2011-05-16T22:26:40+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T23:54:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mid0ff</id><link>http://whitneysworldwideweb.yolasite.com/blog/well-wishes#comment-474071245</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-05-16</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>