<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwkpln/post/2012-03-31T10:05:17</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>It is difficult to read this and not be utterly sickened by the entire deviousness of the piece. 

No! these children were not "bystanders" i.e. no-ones, non-persons, not flesh and blood human beings of indeterminate age and gender, of no faith, no religion. These, indeed, were a Jewish teacher at the school with his own two, very young, children and a fourth victim was a little girl of eight, daughter of the head-master,caught by her hair, as she tried to escape, and who was murdered in Cold-blood, in the playground, by the killer, when he put his gun to her head. One's whole spirit rages at this writer's open contempt for the victims, at her utter lack of empathy or imagination. Not once does she mention the Jewish identity of Merah's victims. Instead, they are referred to as "five people outside a Jewish school".  the same formula, a former French Prime-Minister, Raymond Barre, used when referring to the victims of the bombing at the Liberal Jewish Synagogue in Paris in the "60's. He lost his job, rightly so.

 "Interned at the BBC and in the US Congress", has she? The British Bigotry Corporation - yes she would fit in easily, there. I note that she does not let us know which Congress-person she interned with. What a desperate lack of intellectual courage. Or - an after-thought - perhaps she did not intern at Congress?

In fact, when this story first broke, I though that the killer, yes, the"monster", was a Chechen, recruited by Al-Qaida, to carry out this horror, so much did it remind me of Beslan. But, there you go, it was a Frenchman, Puffed-up by Islamists, Muslim Extremists who will stop at nothing to impose their pathological view of the non-Muslim world.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67mo6y</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ref4</id></website><link>http://www.opendemocracy.net/node/65126</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:07:25+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T14:05:17+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwkpln</id><link>http://www.opendemocracy.net/node/65126#comment-481854548</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>