<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3j8yw/post/2012-03-29T18:08:09</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>MartinR I'm having a hard time with your comment...just like so many others that have already tried and convicted Zimmerman when none of us (you included) were there.  First, weight does not  dictate who wins or dominates a fight (someone's build and strength and ability to think quickly are strong factors when fighting)...especially when someone feels their life is in danger (which by the way...they both probably felt their life was in danger) and again we were not there and "we/you" are not qualified to make a factual statement either way.  Being narrow minded is when you are unable to see both sides of a situation.  I cannot make the call as to whether either of them was justified in their actions once the confrontation took place, neither can you nor can the rest of the nation who was not there.  However, 1) there were witnesses which say Trayvon was the one on top of Zimmerman and hitting him  so that tells me a fact therefore allowing me to form an opinion, 2) Zimmerman was told to stay in his vehicle and to not pursue which he ignored and again gives me a fact and allows me to form an opinion, 3) Zimmerman has a history with violence which does not look good for him but does not automatically make him guilty (which makes you narrow minded if that is what you or anyone else is basing their conclusion and verdict of guilty on) but it is a fact that allows me to form an opinion of him,  4) Trayvon has a history as well and was suspended from his school as well as some items found in his backpack that also don’t appear to be on the up and up but don’t make him guilty of anything but gives me a fact and allows me to form an opinion.  My point being for those of us who were not there, we can only form an opinion and we all have a right to our opinion but what we don’t have a right to is convicting and punishing without the courts involved and unfortunately there are also many who are taking it to the next level and using this incident to advance their own agenda.  So many are so quick to automatically determine this was murder and it was racially motivated and a hate crime and those very same people are allowing themselves to appear racist and from some of their actions are appearing to be driven by hate.  
It's scary to read some of what I have read over the last couple of days and it's scary to me that we as a nation feel that we are justified to react with anger and qualified to make a determination as to what this was, what happened, and what the punishment should be and it is scary to me that without being there and without having all of the facts there are so many who feel qualified to determine that just because there may not be medical records or someone’s physical appearance that satisfy what you deem appropriate in your mind to justify murder that it was just Cold blooded murder plain and simple.  Logic tells me nothing about this situation as a whole is plain, simple or obvious.  Quite honestly I go back and forth because it does confuse as to me why a neighborhood watchman was carrying a gun and it is an extremely sad event with a horrible outcome.  It is a tragedy that should have never happened.  There were poor choices made by both that evening. Just because someone chooses to believe or look at the situation differently than you doesn't make them narrow minded.
I feel for Trayvon's family and I truly hope that if Zimmerman is guilty that he is punished to the fullest extent of the law.  However, my biggest concern at this point is that there are so many out for blood and so ready to serve their own punishment that it may set  a chain of events that could set  an explosion like none other we have ever witnessed in our time.  I mean…doesn’t it concern you in the least that an organization like Black Panthers has put out a Bounty on Zimmerman’s head?  Do you think if that comes to pass that it will stop there?  I don’t think its narrow mindedness you need to concern yourself with…it’s the vigilante attitude that is spreading quickly. Just because someone is not agree</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z2k9c</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/mchl</id></website><link>http://www.myfoxdfw.com/dpp/news/national/video-shows-george-zimmerman-after-shooting-032812</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T03:27:21+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:08:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3j8yw</id><link>http://www.myfoxdfw.com/dpp/news/national/video-shows-george-zimmerman-after-shooting-032812#comment-479953222</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l4w8k</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>