<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mim160/update/2012-03-22T18:14:54/bc2ed67de17db20bb63645f556182c82b0f1f41addcf8800d2f16cfc81f10f82</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp3ago</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cd8w</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>If we think about it, only a few groups are really successful in making good sales and not very many are marketable Acts outside the music show format. And also remember that Korea's market isn't exactly huge to begin with. Most of these groups can't even get lucky with at least one number one track a year.  

However, most of their companies keep them in the hope that these groups will hit gold and deliver.  In between activities, the idols work hard for the investment spent on them prior to debut plus the cost of maintaining them after... meaning the daily living expenses, clothing and transportation allowance, fees of their managers, trainers and stylists, as well as looking for good materials for their next release.

That is why the idols are encouraged to work hard and find schedules on their free time to compensate for the expenses and add to whatever little is left of their fees.  Variety show Spots are the most accessible to them as there  many regular youth oriented shows in different stations.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yhvb1</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/nou3</id></website><link>http://seoulbeats.com/2012/03/the-variety-image/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T08:42:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T22:14:54+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mim160</id><link>http://seoulbeats.com/2012/03/the-variety-image/#comment-474009803</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6tom5</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>