<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw0jgi/post/2012-03-31T13:47:04</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwqocx</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cr295</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Another thing you need to take backis your accusation that I bashed Romney for being a Mormon; the post you refered to was posted by someone else and my connection to that post was to tell that poster not to write anti-mormon stuff as mormons (except Mitt and Dingy) are good people as I have  said in all my posts.

I know the Romney Camp are a bunch of alinskis so I am very careful not to let them get that to be the story like they did against Huckabee;

There is plenty of low-hanging fruit to throw at Romney growing on trees he planted himself, and I want to keep the focus there.

I did make a joke about Ann Coulter, and I said Romney could be caught comiting an abortion himself and Coulter said well at least he did it privately and not with federal money so its a states rights issue ....or something like that, the joke being about Romney supporters backing him no matter what is found out which at a certain point makes you wonder what they are fighting FOR

And also I was thinking of using the traditional "picture with a goat or small child" line, but decided to avoid confusing by using abortion instead because everyone would know that was a joke as well and Mitt has a pro-abortion track record. 

It is telling that you were horrified at the idea of Mitt comiting an abortion himself, but Acted like his pro-abortion record is somehow so removed from aborting babies, when the real difference is that Pro-abortion people who don't kill the baby themselves but have funded it themselves, and mandate funding for it just didn't get their hands dirty visibly, but their hands have a "damn Spot" on them ("out out Damn Spot")</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67c0oh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry2d</id></website><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50549</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:12:59+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T17:47:04+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw0jgi</id><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50549#comment-482038338</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/crqzj</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>