<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkfw4m/post/2012-03-26T13:04:15</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>There is an excellent big centre available at the # 5 Spot in the draft.  Keep drafting and things will be fine.  NO more trading of first round picks. They will be fine if keep drafting and developing players in the minors.
Schenn was rushed and shouldnt have been exposed like he has.  Thank Cliff Fletcher and Wilson for that.  At least they are developing Kadri who is a future star the right way.  Waiting for him to mature properly under Eakins
Their is nothing wrong with players like Lupol Phenuef Kessel Gardiner Gunnarson Liles Grabowski.Franson.

Young guys that will be with the big club eventually.
McKegg, Ross, Colburne Blacker, Holzer, Biggs, Percy Kadri.Carter D'amigo.  All these guys can play.  But they still need development, and Burke is not rushing them.

In my mind they need to draft their future star and number 1 centre, and bring a proven vetren like Roberts and Neuwendyk to lead.  That accompanied by a top five NHL goalie.  

Until such time that they add these pieces they will lack the leadership on and Off the ice.

This team will flounder until more skill size and leadership is added and nothing more should be expected.

Problem is that Burke raised the bar too high when the team wasnt ready</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rsool</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zsj8</id></website><link>http://www.torontosun.com/2012/03/26/burke-has-leafs-on-wrong-track</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T13:46:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:04:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkfw4m</id><link>http://www.torontosun.com/2012/03/26/burke-has-leafs-on-wrong-track#comment-476542447</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lndwz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>