<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34278/update/2012-03-29T10:30:50/d2e5880cd9a176f545e19f8fe0151fb46b95420bb17f136d9fa71c2f7fa165a4</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m37geg</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l1o7t</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I think Matt was good as well on this but his best moment ( and I can't find the dingalink ) was when he said that it was the people who cared about Trayvon who actually made this a story.  Most people would have heard just that neighborhood watch guy shoots black guy in Florida and that would have been that.  I think the 911 calls helped Propel the story.  Anything that treated Trayvon as a human being helped.  

Matt's analysis of why the Right dumped on the dead kid was ok but needs to fleshed out.  He won't say it but obviously there is a chunk of the conservative demographic that believes there is something dysfunctional about African Americans either genetically or something problematic about them being in groups that drives lots of the Trayvon hating.  It's addictive like some sort of racially stoked game/porn.  

On Roe v Wade backlash stoking up the religious right, I think his point is a bit less salient.  Backlashes to modernity started before Roe and the religious right  would have found something to be upset about.  

Props to Bill on the Kennedy breakdown.  I think he is pretty Spot on with how Kennedy is thinking and probably Roberts as well.  If it is 7-2 I bet you could see some language that strives to narrow the commerce clause.  Too bad that probably won't affect the drug war :-(</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zaiz6</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/l8nm</id></website><link>http://bloggingheads.tv/videos/9368</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T04:26:37+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:30:50+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34278</id><link>http://bloggingheads.tv/videos/9368#comment-479530910</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ljbe1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>