<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0l24s/update/2012-04-01T03:29:50/7e0d98249b6827e8e532e387210056008c8ba2ca1634ccf41a327f0fc8a7b5c7</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m06h62</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a56lq</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>@thing55: "We've gone from a country that combined elements of rugged individualism with elements of striving for the common good to a country that scorns the latter to a shocking degree.  We don't have the luxury of starting a new country with the kind of visionary minds that set the U.S. on the right path in the late 18th century.

I know. It's pretty bad. They're one step away from being the "Burn the poor for fuel" party.

"Everybody Acts like we're stuck with what we've got and there appears to be little appetite for the kind of bold rethinking that is required.  We need to revise our economic and political systems, not spend decades on timid reforms.  As long as the right thinks that all we need to do is go back to a 225 year-old document, we won't have true progress."

I agree. Poor things, they're paralyzed by fear of change. For example, how many of them oppose the insurance mandate because it would be the first time government ever required people to buy something. Well, okay, it would be the first time, but why is that a problem?

"As for the Supreme Court, I'm not optimistic.  I've followed it and found it interesting, but unless Roberts or Kennedy or somebody has the cajones to browbeat the others into some reasonable way forward without completely striking down the whole thing, hundreds of thousands, perhaps millions of Americans, will needlessly suffer.  The status quo is completely unacceptable."

The reality is that even if they uphold it all as constitutional the result is still completely unacceptable.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67cc84</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/opinion/dorf-supreme-court-health/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T12:27:37+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-01T07:29:50+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0l24s</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/opinion/dorf-supreme-court-health/index.html#comment-482610344</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a56lq</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>