<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mj0tlf/update/2012-03-20T11:14:42/20331686a31648beb0f5c7edd37016331bb4b5db26d17d40d3dc2eedfa4e9485</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mjrisn</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/y3zaz</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>My daughter (18) was in another town about 40 miles away one night about a month ago playing pool and took  walking because her boyfriend insulted and humiliated her in front of a bunch of people. She asked him to take her home, he refused, so she left. Now, it just so happens that for the first time in her life she accidentally left her life support device (cell phone) in her own car back in our town, so there she was afoot, on a dark two lane county road, in a strange town. On her way to a convenience store a couple of miles away to call her dad and I, two guys in a truck pulled over and asked if she needed help, so she hopped in. SHE FREAKING GOT INTO THE VEHICLE WITH THEM!!! I almost died when she told me the next day. Needless to say, they were very kind, let her use one of their cell phones to contact a few friends (who she sent the guys' names and a description of the truck she was in) and dropped her  at her car. One of them kicked her boyfriend's ass (3 times) when he came out of the shadows Acting like a prick and wouldn't stop, then they had her call them when she made it home. The also talked to her about what she deserved and didn't and to put herself first and drop the scum she was dating. Lo and behold, she listened to them when she would listen to none of the rest of us! The now ex-BF was no problem as he couldn't walk, let alone drive and follow her. So yes, they were angels in disguise and I am thankful to them for my daughter's safety and well being. As a female I want to say, please don't let a couple of people keep you from being the kind gentleman you seem to be. I shudder to think who might have come in contact with my daughter had these guys not been there. As mom, the whole situation she put herself in makes want to Vomit, but I realize there are still really great people out there. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6m8s99</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gvlu</id></website><link>http://www.dreamindemon.com/2012/03/19/rodney-peterson-charged-disorderly-conduct-offering-girls-ride/</link><postedTime>2012-03-19T13:18:46+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-20T15:14:42+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mj0tlf</id><link>http://www.dreamindemon.com/2012/03/19/rodney-peterson-charged-disorderly-conduct-offering-girls-ride/#comment-470268313</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/alt62</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-19</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>