<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwfwwq/update/2012-03-31T02:00:47/288bbed3ba917eb786be99b3f5a9ff025df2549f92b26c74b3e10472dd90149f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwuhgk</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Honestly Larry, I feel like your comment is a bit of a cop-out. Your basic complaint is that my theology is too refined. I suppose I should just say, "Thanks," and move on. A man once approached the Puritan preacher Richard Rogers and said, "Mr. Rogers, I like you and your company very well, only you are too precise." "Oh Sir," Rogers replied, "I serve a precise God." 

I believe God has spoken clearly, and in many areas has been very precise. I want to know my God. And I don't want a merely approximate picture of Him, with blurred edges and fuzzy splotches. I want to know precisely who He is, so that I can see the full beauty of His glory, with clarity and contours and definition. And insofar as He's revealed Himself and made that possible, I want to pursue that with all my might.

&lt;i&gt;...Paul mentions, he prefers not to know anything among us other than Jesus Christ and him crucified.&lt;/i&gt;

I don't think that means quite what you seem to imply it means. Paul made that statement in chapter 2 of 1 Corinthians. 1 Corinthians has 16 chapters. And that's to say nothing of the 12 &lt;i&gt;other&lt;/i&gt; letters he wrote, making up half of the New Testament, containing doctrines that span bibliology, theology proper, Christology, pneumatology, anthropology, hamartiology, soteriology, ecclesiology, eschatology, and more.

&lt;i&gt;I wonder if we were all in one room, would be on one accord, or would our refined theology get in the way of us loving Christ and each-other.&lt;/i&gt;

It's likely that we would not all be of one accord. But unity is not achieved by sweeping our doctrinal differences under the rug. Unity is achieved by hashing out our disagreements over Scripture, imitating the noble Bereans, and pursuing &lt;i&gt;true&lt;/i&gt; unity based on &lt;i&gt;truth&lt;/i&gt;, not a superficial concession to agree to disagree.

&lt;i&gt;Could it be that we are speaking the tongues of men and of angels and have not love?&lt;/i&gt;

I've re-read my post, and I can't quite see anything that comes Off as unloving. Unless you define "unloving" as disagreeing with a doctrinal position, and seeking to set forth what I see is the biblical alternative. In which case, your disagreement with me makes you unloving as well.

&lt;i&gt;I think of the woman at the well, whom, after she encountered Jesus, went back to her village and shared what she experienced, and many passed from death to life. I doubt very seriously if she had a refined methodology, relative to sharing Christ with an unbeliever.&lt;/i&gt;

Again, I'm sorry, but I want to know more of Christ than the basics. I find Him so compelling, so glorious, so lovely, that I want to know Him as He is. I don't want to conceive of Him in any way other than He is. By God's grace, Christ's loveliness does not allow me to be satisfied with a merely surface-level understanding of my Savior and His Word.

&lt;i&gt;Sharing Christ out of a pure heart based on a pure and authentic encounter with Jesus is what attracts sinners and seeing/sensing a lifestyle that is Christ centered is what convicts.&lt;/i&gt;

I have to disagree with you here. Our sincerity--or anything else about our presentation--doesn't attract sinners. We can be sincere, and be sincerely wrong. Only the Word of God, preached faithfully and accurately, convicts of sin and regenerates the sinner (Rom 10:17; 1Pet 1:23-25; Jas 1:18). And because of that I want to make sure that I'm representing the Word accurately.

&lt;i&gt;Paul gave King Agrippa his personal testimony, which brought Agrippa to the crossroads of salvation, so much so, Agrippa said, "You almost persuaded me to become "one of those" Christians" Perhaps Agrippa would have "bowed the knee" had Paul's presentation been more "Spot on" (oooops! Sorry Paul).&lt;/i&gt;

I think Agrippa would have responded if Paul used the Ten Commandments. Someone should have told him about the Law and evangelism.

:-)</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zw4n0</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tit5</id></website><link>http://thecripplegate.com/schreiner-the-threefold-division-and-the-law-of-god/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T08:10:25+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T06:00:47+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwfwwq</id><link>http://thecripplegate.com/schreiner-the-threefold-division-and-the-law-of-god/#comment-481581883</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/memwr</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>