<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwnr0f/post/2012-03-30T19:31:03</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Hey, OP. That's actually pretty sweet, but you really shouldn't rely on something external to stop your Suicidal thoughts, at least, not exclusively.

You see, things can go wrong when you rely on external sources to make you feel better. You won't  be able to see your niece/nephew, most likely. And besides, it's a just a train wreck waiting to happen to rely on a small child to "fix" your Suicidal thoughts. Kids aren't  nice to be around, honestly. Some people are more tolerant of kids and how they  than others, but I believe everyone can agree that they are 100% capable of driving someone up a wall.

So, with that, I would recommend you get some sort of help with your Suicidal thoughts. Maybe use your future niece/nephew as motivation? If you get help, you'll be a better role model, not to mention. I'm not saying people with Suicidal thoughts can't be good role models, but struggling with them can really affect your relationship with others. And also, Depending on how severe they get, you may actually try something. You wouldn't want to do that. If your niece/nephew found out that their aunt tried to (or God forbid, actually did) commit suicide, that would be pretty horrible for them, especially if you were close.

Maybe try counseling. It's not an easy thing to completely get over, so don't feel bad if you occasionally feel those thoughts again. Relapse happens.

Good luck with everything, OP, and try to be the best aunt you can be. &lt;3</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67vmpl</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dypr</id></website><link>http://www.sixbillionsecrets.com/view/Hope/1605000</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T23:00:31+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T23:31:03+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwnr0f</id><link>http://www.sixbillionsecrets.com/view/Hope/1605000#comment-481318837</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ydkjg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>