<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tog9/post/2012-03-29T10:15:59</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3vi5g</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gkjgb</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Maybe Joseph Smith has only been vilified by those who feel misled by him. Also, it was very much to his benefit to found Mormonism. By the time he and his church had relocated to Nauvoo IL, he was the not only the "prophet" living Off the tithes and offerings of his fairly large church but was also able to start businesses from this income (like a fancy hotel). In addition to being the prophet, he was also the mayor, and had his own armed militia to command, you know the one he used to destroy the printing press and Burn down the offices of the newspaper that was exposing his publicly denied but very real and secretly practiced polygamy. To try and claim that it was not to Joseph's material benefit to have founded Mormonism is to be truly blinded by your biases and your cognitive dissonance.

Also, fairlds.org is hardly unbiased and "fair." The most balanced site egarding matters of Mormon theology and history that I'm aware of is mormonthink.com. They present not only the concepts that most Mormons are taught and believe, but then the point of view of the critics as well as those of the apologists.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hcpj2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ant8</id></website><link>http://www.alternet.org/story/154710/former_mormon_what_americans_need_to_know_about_mormonism/comments/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T04:55:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:15:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tog9</id><link>http://www.alternet.org/story/154710/former_mormon_what_americans_need_to_know_about_mormonism/comments/#comment-479520206</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/govfy</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>