<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/323728/post/127798188/comment/327570368</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I thought your first article about the podcast was Spot on and I felt EXACTLY the same way after watching it. I have enjoyed Redeye for about a year now after discovering it one night when I had fallen asleep with the TV on and woke up at 2 AM and it was on. And being relatively new to Twitter, I have been on the hashtag rarely, but mostly because the people I follow or followers are on it. And even before the podcast, I have seen growing arrogance and comments towards people that don&amp;#039;t live in New York City, but not enough to piss me  that bad. Just an underlying tone. &#13; 
I was not one that called her anything, but might have if she continued to lean forward and talk over everyone to make some ignorant point. And watching the replay of it, she pissed Off Andy too. But watching the podcast, i do feel it was directed at all the fans. And as I said...if you spend half the podcast ragging on your fans, and the other half saying you weren&amp;#039;t.....you were. And what I found equally odd..is they finished the podcast bragging about their ratings. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:323728:127798188</id><idPostId>127798188</idPostId><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:323728</id><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><link>http://www.chrisisright.net</link><displayName>Chris Is RIGHT</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/06/29/red-eye-in-which-i-get-off-the-short-bus/</link><displayName>Red Eye: In Which I Get Off The Short Bus</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-06-29T13:44:42.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:323728:127798188:327570368</id><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/06/29/red-eye-in-which-i-get-off-the-short-bus/#IDComment327570368</link><postedTime>2011-06-29T13:44:42.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Red Eye: In Which I Get Off The Short Bus by BarryNMooch</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>17a4a8bbf297b410695dd3fa62e73f1a</idEmailMd5><displayName>BarryNMooch</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>BarryNMooch commented on &lt;a href="http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/06/29/red-eye-in-which-i-get-off-the-short-bus/"&gt;Red Eye: In Which I Get Off The Short Bus&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2011-06-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>