<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk7wvr/update/2012-03-25T18:40:50/6b348ac109c32d7f2a497701204ceecce9d5428428b70d5365b380b255b9923d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>What is ignored here, and it is a very critical point, is the effects of lead bullets on the meat consumed by humans. Most bullets used for hunting "mushroom" on impact, scattering lead fragments in the animal. Inexperienced hunters, sadly the majority, generally require more than one shot to kill a game animal, increasing the problem. It is difficult to remove every bit of lead from a carcass, and the end result is frequently human consumption of these lead fragments, with proven negative health effects.

As an avid hunter that has killed thousands of game animals, I see absolutely no reason why toxic lead ammunition shouldn't be . The cost of alternatives is minute in comparison to what the average hunter spends per hunt- less, for example, than the cost of driving a few more miles to a better Spot. And there is absolutely no question that many animals that are shot run Off to die, and these animals are consumed by predators, vultures, and all manner of small creatures that make up the base of the food chain. 

Six million pounds of lead scattered into prime hunting grounds every year is indeed a problem, and every hunter should consider the consequences of their collective actions. If the industry is successful at lobbying and prevents a law protecting our environment, then we as hunters can boycott the lead bullets ourselves. Switching to lead-free ammunition will not harm the sport in any way, and will make obtaining food from the wild much more healthy for us all- not just for the birds.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r7koz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yzhq</id></website><link>http://www.mcclatchydc.com/2012/03/25/143034/environmentalists-take-aim-at.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-25T18:45:24+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-25T22:40:50+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk7wvr</id><link>http://www.mcclatchydc.com/2012/03/25/143034/environmentalists-take-aim-at.html#comment-476075819</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/89mde</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>