<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw5lhd/update/2012-03-30T05:52:55/e3bf686d5b4bb7c3aac1d0b2ee3239281a158fa05b8551b60d83e61ebc47af17</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m30544</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8e9st</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Without a long term policy the lights will indeed go Off diminishing our business competitiveness even more. In the short term the government should:
Stop all foreign aid, this will cover the costs of two power stations per year = affordable and not reliant on companies from economically dodgy countries.
Decide on one proven design that already has regulatory approval (e.g. the US AP1000) stick to that design. Place a fixed price contract to build as many as required stations in the next few years. We currently have 19.  A new station can be built in three years so surely it is possible to start say three this year, three next year, three the following year...
Don't forget to contract for the fuel, wouldn't want to find it is unobtanium.
Seriously expand research into thorium, it was proven in the 60s but discarded as not suitable for making bombs, should be able to Burn up existing waste, safe as self limiting can't go critical. It would possibly only take a £200m to do the research and produce a good design that in a few years we could sell to the the Germans. We probably don't have any private companies that are prepared to invest this money for a long term return so would have to be done by the government as was done in the 50s/60s.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zn6ca</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/finance/comment/damianreece/9174656/Did-our-Government-know-RWE-and-E.ONs-interest-in-nuclear-power-had-cooled.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:26:27+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T09:52:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw5lhd</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/finance/comment/damianreece/9174656/Did-our-Government-know-RWE-and-E.ONs-interest-in-nuclear-power-had-cooled.html#comment-480572828</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a3zzo</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>