<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/er1bjv/update/2011-12-08T16:41:20/1d74fb18b9f3c37fc5301d90f43a6332b8524217191eac62cc3b0c69f79e7640</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Photo's 39 &amp; 40 bring back vivid memories of how desolate Attu was but after being held on a troop ship in the Bering sea for several days on the WW 1 vintage President Filmore it was good to land just about anywhere.  I landed at Massacre Bay mid morning May 11, 43 and for the first few days hand carried clusters of 105MM shells to the guns just  the beach they were heavy and that tundra was tough walking.  The only vehicles that could move were tracked caterpillars that pulled a tracked Athy trailor, wheeled vehicles were useless. Next I drove a D6 Cat fitted with an A Frame for unloading heavy supplies from landing craft, we used the small streams for a road or the beach as there was no tundra and when you went any distance you went in pairs so when one got stuck the other could winch it out. I saw most all of the island on the Massacre Bay side and hundreds of dead Japs and the medics area where the Japs bayneted our wounded casualties.
I was with the 707 Ord Co and we had it tough but nothing like the Inf line companys who really had it bad because of the awful weather and poor Cold weather gear such as leather boots and field jackets.  The best piece of gear was the two piece down sleeping bag, the inside one a mummy type that guys would cut Off the bottom and cut arm holes to wear like an overcoat.  
The cemetery near the bay with all of the white crosses was a grim reminder of just how costly regaining Attu really was, I lost a few friends there.

Ken Clegg</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ex2vx8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/h7jj</id></website><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/infocus/2011/08/world-war-ii-battle-of-midway-and-the-aleutian-campaign/100137/</link><postedTime>2011-08-28T11:06:24+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-12-08T21:41:20+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/er1bjv</id><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/infocus/2011/08/world-war-ii-battle-of-midway-and-the-aleutian-campaign/100137/#comment-382422076</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-08-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>