<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/276915/post/104218228/comment/329600288</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Follow Jerry Crasnick on Twitter . Holland ranks among a select group of lefties with the ability to blow the ball past hitters. His average fastball radar gun reading of 94.2 mph was sixth-highest among starters behind Ogando, Verlander, Price,borse burberry, and . When the St. Louis hitters weren\'t griping about the wide strike zone after Game 4, they were gushing over his velocity. Calling all aces \"They have plenty of arms,\'\' a National League general manager said. \"If you play them in a four-game series, there\'s not one game where you say, \'We\'re facing one guy we can tee  on.\' Given their offense, that\'s pretty important. Sure, you wish you had a Verlander, but there aren\'t many guys like that out there. I think the balance of that rotation is really good.\'\' Is there a legitimate top-of-the-rotation presence in that group? More important, does it matter? Holland attracted quite a following in October for his sprig of a mustache and entertaining dugout impersonations of Harry Caray and Arnold Schwarzenegger. But he wants to dispel the notion that he\'s some sort of happy-go-lucky cutup. Holland grew his hair into a shaggy, disheveled mop in the offseason and spent the winter in a quest for self-improvement. After concluding that inconsistency with his breaking ball was his biggest obstacle to  the next level, he made that a major point of emphasis over the winter. Which brings us, finally, to , whose talent and stuff prompted the Rangers to shell out almost $112 million between the posting fee and the contract. Like Dice-K, Darvish reportedly throws seven or eight pitches, and might be wise to shelve a couple for the sake of efficiency. But he\'s not ready to give away any trade . During his introductory news conference last week he declined to even acknowledge how many pitches are in his repertoire, much less outline his plans. When asked whether he\'s interested in getting guidance from the great Nolan Ryan and Greg Maddux during his voyage of self-discovery this season, Darvish demurred. The international star whose every move is chronicled by dozens of media members each day gave the same flustered response that might come from an American high school kid who followed the illustrious careers of Big Tex and Mad Dog. \"I\'m having fun,\'\' Holland said, \"but I also want people to get the message that I work my tail . I know a lot of people were concerned with me doing my impersonations and the other stuff and saying, \'Is he really going to be focused?\' Trust me -- my mind is on baseball.\'\' Jerry Crasnick is a senior writer for ESPN. to purchase a copy of his book,Five options for Denver Broncos quarterback Tim Tebow - NFL - ESPN, \"License to Deal,\" published by Rodale. Crasnick can be  . Darvish, by all accounts, is supremely confident in his ability and driven to be great. But he\'ll have to make numerous adjustments to the American culture and baseball in the U.S. Japanese starters from Hideo Nomo to Hideki Irabu to have grappled with the transition with varying degrees of success. SURPRISE, Ariz. -- The prototypical Major League Baseball ace is consistent, reliable and capable of giving his team a lift every time he takes the mound. He either has overpowering stuff, &amp;agrave; la and , or the intensity, focus and command to take very good stuff to another level. That means you, . In some respects, the whole \"Who\'s No. 1?\'\' debate is a trick question. All 30 big league teams have de facto top-of-the-rotation starters. But Minnesota\'s , Kansas City\'s and Baltimore\'s are atop their teams\' depth charts essentially by default. \"It\'s not complicated,sac hermes,\'\' said. \"He\'s throwing 95-97 miles an hour from the left side. How many guys in the game do that? There\'s a handful, and they\'re all studs. Jon Lester. CC Sabathia. David Price.\'\' As the Rangers pursue a third straight World Series appearance,louis vuitton, pitching remains a focal point and a source of pride for the organization. Two years ago, Texas\' staff ranked second in the American League in innings pitched and fourth in . Last year the Rangers  the staff  from 3.93 to 3.79, fifth-best in the league. Despite playing half their games in a charitable offensive park, they\'ve shed their reputation as an organization that bashes first and asks questions later. Holland went 16-5 with a 3.95  last season and saved his best performance for Game 4 of the World Series. A day after hit three home runs to lead St. Louis to a 16-7 blowout, Holland took the mound with skeptics in abundance. He threw 8 1/3 innings of shutout ball in a 4-0 victory, and nobody doubted him anymore. , , , and slot in right behind them. , , ,burberry borse outlet, and are accomplished pitchers in their mid-20s, and and ranked high in Cy Young balloting last year. A year or two from now, and could be automatic mentions in this group. With seven legitimate starters, the Rangers are better equipped to survive the oppressive Texas Heat. Washington also has the luxury of monitoring the workload for Feliz as he prepares to shift from closer to the rotation. Despite the absence of Rangers from the list, two big league front-office people said Texas\' rotation is worthy of a pennant contender, particularly because it\'s supported by such a formidable lineup. But they\'ve also become adept at saying goodbye and retooling on the fly. In December 2010, spurned a nine-figure offer from the Rangers to sign a five-year, $120 million deal with Philadelphia. Last season, stepped forward to embrace the role of staff leader, finished sixth in American League Cy Young Award balloting and parlayed it into a five-year, $77.5 million free agent deal with the AL West rival . So where do the Rangers go from here? So here\'s the salient question in Surprise: Do the Rangers have a new staff leader in residence who was born more recently than the Lyndon Baines Johnson administration? We\'ll find out soon enough. \"A lot of times you\'re not defined by who starts Game 1 of the postseason,\'\' an NL executive said. \"You\'re defined by who starts that game in August when you have two starters on the DL and you\'ve taxed your bullpen and need someone to step up. That\'s what gets you there in the first place.\'\' Leaders-in-waiting \"I feel hesitant to approach them,\'\' Darvish said through an interpreter. \"If they come to me with advice,ghd purple, I would be very grateful. I don\'t know if I\'m ready for that.\'\' Darvish had better be ready and take advantage of every resource at his disposal. Life in the big leagues awaits, and aspiring aces need to grow up in a hurry. Depending on how finicky you are, 10 to 20 pitchers embody the characteristics of a true No. 1. Halladay, Lee, Verlander, ,Sac Birkin Hermes, , and are no-brainers. and qualify if healthy, and still exudes that ace cachet at age 36. \"You move on,\'\' Washington said. \"Of course you\'re going to miss a pitcher the quality of a Cliff Lee or a C.J., but the guys here have proved they can handle the job. We\'re very confident and comfortable.\'\' Among Texas\' seven potential starters,burberry sito ufficiale, Holland and Darvish are generally regarded as the best bets to join the elite group of pitchers with the \"ace\'\' designation. \"What I said last year is pretty much how I feel now,\'\' Rangers pitching coach Mike Maddux said. \"We don\'t have a No. 1, but we have the same chance to win every night, so there\'s no letdown. If we don\'t have a No. 1, we\'re stacked with 2s. And that\'s OK.\'\' The have two pitchers who fit the description. Unfortunately,nike air jordan, club president Nolan Ryan is 65 years old and special assistant Greg Maddux is 45. They would be challenged to cover first base at this point, never mind take the mound and give manager Ron Washington a quality start. \"We watched this guy go from an older boy to a young man,ghd site officiel,\'\' Mike Maddux said. \"Just to see him mature before us is pretty impressive -- not just as a baseball player but as a person. That equates to success on the field.\'\' The Texas rotation,hermes site officiel, as currently constructed, is long on talent and relatively short on experience. , the elder statesman of the group at 32, has 631 big league innings if you exclude his time in Japan. Lefties , 25,Kitchen Window No Wheat Doesnt Mean No Noodles NPR, and ,Bobby Brown Comments On Ski Slopestyle Win - ESPN Video - ES, 26, continue to grow and evolve. is transitioning from closer, and could land in the rotation or the bullpen. The Rangers also have , who was a postseason savior as the team\'s long man in October. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:276915:104218228</id><idPostId>104218228</idPostId><idBlogId>276915</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:276915</id><idBlogId>276915</idBlogId><link>http://www.cinefamily.org</link><displayName>The Cinefamily</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.cinefamily.org/blog/qa-archive-4-combat-shock/</link><displayName>Q&amp;A Archive #4: "Combat Shock"</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T00:41:30.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:276915:104218228:329600288</id><link>http://www.cinefamily.org/blog/qa-archive-4-combat-shock/#IDComment329600288</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T00:41:30.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Q&amp;A Archive #4: "Combat Shock" by hljfeos4501x</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://www.borselouisvuittonvendita1.com/</link><idEmailMd5>3978ef7b5a15d74b4867f1633813e002</idEmailMd5><displayName>hljfeos4501x</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://www.borselouisvuittonvendita1.com/"&gt;hljfeos4501x&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.cinefamily.org/blog/qa-archive-4-combat-shock/"&gt;Q&amp;A Archive #4: "Combat Shock"&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>