<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3jx7e/update/2012-03-29T18:37:55/5b566336c169366c050ca4cc4c0ed2ab83f6f9175b779da4f2d95ecf63fd96c1</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39ju1</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ykgq9</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I agree with Sammy....Glenn is starting to wear on me and I find he talks out of both sides of his mouth sometimes and I didn't used to think he ever did.  If some non-Santorum supporter or opposing view person calls to challenge him, it's pretty much pointless, typically, you get about 20 seconds to make your case then the person gets stopped and then the Stu, Pat and Glenn sophomoric sarcasm downpour starts and the caller doesn't get to rebut.  I'm not saying this happens all the time, but it seems to happen more than it used to.  I find it sort of rude, but hey, it's his show, and but hey, that's when I sometimes stop listening or do something else.   Still, I listen to the show pretty much every day for some of the time, but somehow, I don't believe Glenn as much as I used to do.  Now I do what he's  said, check things for myself and don't blindly follow, cause, guess what, he's only human, not perfect, no smarter than most of the rest of us.  One thing more that bugs me, Goldline is still a sponsor even though they really do rip people  on gold coins with 50% markups over Spot price.  Check Santa Monica news and legal questions raised in the courts there.  Back to Santorum, really, this big government creepy republican is the answer to Obama?  Only if Divine Providence does intervene could he win, cause he'll need a miracle.  I've Always voted Republican, but I'm sick of their pathetic, warmed over status quo candidates-really, think about it -- Nixon, Ford (one bright candle - Reagan) then GHW Bush, Bob Dole, G W Bush, McInsane, and now Romney or Santorum!!  I'm giong to throw up.  Aren't we sick of choosing the lessor of two evils the establishment constantly allows us to pick from??   Stop falling for this insider, status quo crap, people!!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6znloz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rb19</id></website><link>/2012/03/29/mitt-romney-make-another-elitist-faux-pas/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:29:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:37:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3jx7e</id><link>/2012/03/29/mitt-romney-make-another-elitist-faux-pas/#comment-479978034</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzq0q</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>