<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwk78n/update/2012-03-31T09:38:46/79424a0ea3f0417bd2deac3ed7bba6dbb82fb1b5b01bd953b512363d26023111</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwiigu</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8gltt</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Incorrect. What he did was to misinterpret 'vernalisation' a genuinely observable effect whereby if you chilled grains, they germinated better in Cold soil.

His mistake was to claim for political purposes that the change in the grain biochemistry was genetic, when it wasn't. This meant that Soviet geneticists who opposed this nonsense were attacked by the regime.

The last time we had an outbreak of Lysenkoism before this present climate pseudo-science was in the mid 1980s when a group of Marxists in the Natural History Museum tried to claim something like Lysenko, which was that you could get highly accelerated genetic change [evolution] at times of societal stress.

That was headed Off by the scientific establishment which at that time had not been so corrupted by the Marxists. Luckily, enough of us grey heads not controlled by our present Marxists like Nurse have now turned up to tell the politicians that there is no 'back radiation' capable of doing thermodynamic work and the pyrgeometer measurements supposed to prove it are nothing of the kind.

Hence we're into global weirding scares etc. as the alarmists flounder. I hope you will read the textbooks because I suspect you know I'm telling the truth.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67jj28</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ms5i</id></website><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/jamesdelingpole/100148381/global-weirding-the-new-big-lie/</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T11:15:07+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T13:38:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwk78n</id><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/jamesdelingpole/100148381/global-weirding-the-new-big-lie/#comment-481836044</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ma9h9</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>