<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mm3ezz/update/2012-02-11T23:58:45/90da6c1fbe7e8fe4b422dbe8dea008f68179097b7bbb9c852bc61c2bd3303dff</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mmfitx</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>1. Not all dogs are drooly. It's usually just the big ones like St. Bernards.
2. The smell of letterboxes is disgusting. I'd much rather have my pet do it outside and clean it up later with a pooper scooper.
3. Okay, yeah, not gonna lie, dogs can be stinky and unhygienic.
4. This wouldn't happen if owners weren't stupid enough to put their dog out at that time in the morning. And not all dogs are annoying barking machines.
5. That number seems a bit high, but yes, I won't argue that some dogs can be dangerous; if owners raised them better, there wouldn't be so many problems. Also, heard of cat scratch Fever?
6. My dog catches mice!
7. Huh? Dogs do this all the time! They make great pillows too! In my experience, I've found that dogs tend to be more affectionate than cats.
8. Dogs do love to eat. But you can train a dog to leave food alone; you can even put a treat on their nose and train them not to eat it until you say so. That's some serious self-control right there!
9. When dogs are entertained, you can be too. With a dog, you can have some quality outdoors time; it's so cute watching a dog be happy outside in the fresh air, sniffing and exploring. And it can be great exercise for you! You can't really take a cat for a walk or run, or throw things for them to catch or retrieve.
10. I'd have to agree with this.
11. Cats can scratch things up, and they shed a LOT. Though dogs do too. That's the price of having a pet; at some point, something's going to be damaged by them. We've had really good luck with our dog; she doesn't make messes on the floor and doesn't chew anything up. When we had a floor in our house redone, we only had to tell her once to stay  it, and it was kind of funny and sad how she went out of her way to obey. How respectful of her!

Dogs have their merits too. And, Depending on how patient you are and how smart/obedient your dog is, you can solve almost any problem with training. The same can't really be said for a lot of cats.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yvq27i</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/qlek</id></website><link>http://iwastesomuchtime.com/on/?i=23816</link><postedTime>2012-02-11T03:58:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-12T04:58:45+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mm3ezz</id><link>http://iwastesomuchtime.com/on/?i=23816#comment-436568486</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/61slv</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-11</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>