<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mko9la/post/2012-03-26T15:39:01</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>And Peanut Jimmy wuz only a lowly Nuk-leer injun-eer by trade.

Just imagine how our Harvard Boy-Lawyer-cum-Leader from Behind, kin massage the numbers &amp; wring celestial energy out of the stars to power our Kloud Kars in his vision of a Progressive Science future. Oops, I fergot, that ain't gonna happen seein' the Dear Organizer and his Democrat minions already spent our great-grandchildren's future tax payments with ObamaCare now officially costing twice what he said it would, and we're scheduled to crash and Burn by 2025. AS for the Keystone pipeline, why "O"-Boy-won has the 'farce' with him, is slicker'n David Copperfield and kin levitate oil through an invisible half-a-pipeline all th' way from Alberta without it touching all the other oil and gas pipelines that criss-cross  spaceship earth! And Master Yoda would kill for those ears.

As fer BP, lets not forget that is was the FedGov that pushed'em that far Off the Shelf. If they had been allowed to drill in waters 1500 ft. deep the spill would have been rapidly dealt with. The venture instead, became the oil industry's version of a moon shot. They sunk a shaft 5,000 ft. to the floor of the sea and then drilled nearly 5,000 ft. INTO the earth. Only an idiot would think that is a risk free venture. BP's mistake was not in drilling, but in its on-site corporate leadership exceeding the safety protocols. 

Brazil's PETROBRAS is currently drilling to the same depths that TransOcean was working at, and they're doin' it wih with $2 billion in funding from the American taxpayers and Obama's blessing, plus Lord knows how much more from Geo. Soros, but nobody on the socialist-Progressive Left seems to have a problem with that.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rukmj</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dndg</id></website><link>http://www.thestate.com/2012/03/26/2205335/monday-obama-favored-higher-gas.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T04:28:06+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T19:39:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mko9la</id><link>http://www.thestate.com/2012/03/26/2205335/monday-obama-favored-higher-gas.html#comment-476671825</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8v0lc</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>