<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi6qs2/post/2012-03-22T22:11:00</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>NC Day 14. I absolutely can't believe it. Though I've been away for most of the time, it seems amazing to me that I haven't uttered a word to him in 2 weeks. wow! I guess I'm in a better place. I still wake up on the morning with the thought of him. He's Always there before bed. He still lingers during the day from time to time. But his presence isn't as strong as before. He's fading slowly. Is it foolish to still miss them? To still want to share something that happened with them? To stil wonder where they are or what they're doing? I guess it's normal. I go back to the real world on Saturday. I go back to the neighborhood we share, and the tiny office we have to cohabit. I go back to seeing the person who almost broke my spirit. But I'll do it with a stronger sense of who I am. I'll do it knowing that I deserved better than I got. I'll do it with pride in who I am. I'm sure it won't be easy, and I'm sure I'll crack from time to time. But I know I'll be fine. I know I'll be alright. 

In other news, I met a guy the other day. It's a guy I've known for a long time. I actually had a crush on him 15 years ago. I saw him and immediately noticed how handsome he was. I was Blushing. How silly. It's the first time I've actually felt attraction for someone else. I don't know if it means anything, but it felt good to not think about my ex for a brief moment and to think another guy may be capable of making me happy again.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/5ue3j5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gz5e</id></website><link>http://lovesagame.com/no-contact-help-how-to-fight-the-urge-to-contact-your-ex-part-3/</link><postedTime>2011-04-16T08:19:25+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T02:11:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi6qs2</id><link>http://lovesagame.com/no-contact-help-how-to-fight-the-urge-to-contact-your-ex-part-3/#comment-474144048</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hbsmj</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-04-16</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>