<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mirazi/post/2012-03-22T22:55:25</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Stop trying to sell pet rocks (PC laptops) and come to the future. Slide 2 - cloud computing Slide 3-Security? There's probably an app for that. Plus PCs and Viruses are like pb&amp;j slide 4- Post PC pain...ha ha have you ever lugged around a PC laptop for work. I'm sure there are millions who are shorter on one side of their body because of it. Yeah, an  causes more strain than crouching in at a laptop. I'm sure you've also got an ergonomic sundial to sell me so I don't hurt my eyes looking at my watch. Slide 5 - yeah iPads stink and gaming but so do laptops. You know what games look great on...my 50 in TV. Slide 6 - you put this in to make a deadline,right. You're telling me PC driver software for printing was a calming, easy experience. Are you serious? Slide 7- be a grownup and stimulate the economy. Have someone upload all that crap oh I meant important information stuff to carbonite and never look at it again. Slide 8-Power software is where we agree it sucks for the . But that's where the money is...cloud software is what the  will do best. Product cycle folks are getting ready to start the carpet roll. Oh you PC people will need to own your software..hope you have a big cd rack ;) Slide 9- Jeff, Jeff, Jeff your hand on your coffee as you wrote this story was hotter than any . They figured out swipe, touch screen technology, gorilla glass, but they won't solve Heat dissipation. Well I'm Off to the future you enjoy your PC paperweight and your AOL account.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yqgv8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/txkp</id></website><link>http://www.informationweek.com/news/galleries/personal-tech/tablets/232602971</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T14:03:49+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T02:55:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mirazi</id><link>http://www.informationweek.com/news/galleries/personal-tech/tablets/232602971#comment-474166758</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zd1fl</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>