<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk9gbw/post/2012-03-26T13:15:51</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I really love this place, it has a unique charm to it.  The ambiance is what I like about a place like Paulie's.  Being a Pizzaiolo and a chef i will say that they have all the right tools to become a great pizza place.  Ingredients are fresh, great short menu, the dough taste great.  One thing that I will like to point out, is that went you you have a wood oven pizza it cooks a bit different than the gas ovens. The Heat come from the direction of the wood if the the pizza is not turn quickly it will Burn on that side looking towards the Burning wood.  This ovens cook very fast it takes about over a minute Depending on the Heat of the stone.  I observe the guy turning the pizzas, struggling to cook the pies on the bottom, because of the Cold stone.  The Blasting of the wood will only increase the Heat on the top, resulting in a Burn top, and light bottom.  Charcoal  tasting pizza is not good, there is ways to adjust the dough to achieve a more brown not black product with the same taste.  This is achieve by looking at the original Pizzaiolo from italy.  There is a reason why the dough is made softer.  The whole process has to be execute properly for a superb product.  

Good Luck Pauli keep up the good work.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/8wxoqg</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6ees</id></website><link>http://gothamist.com/2010/03/29/photo_tour_of_paulie_gees_pizza_in.php</link><postedTime>2010-11-25T01:05:41+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:15:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk9gbw</id><link>http://gothamist.com/2010/03/29/photo_tour_of_paulie_gees_pizza_in.php#comment-476551690</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zry3n</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2010-11-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>