<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gslv06/update/2011-11-05T18:06:38/1f15f07084b64996bc970aefd4115067c617e86eb0747b57635942d2122fe0c9</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Canada is not alone in having hordes of people trying to enter their country through legal and often illegal channels.
There are people who target certain countries to claim refugee status in not because they have a real Burning desire to be an active citizen of that nation and respect and participate in all of its cultural diversity and official languages , but in many cases its because its  a paid holiday . Sometimes it takes two years for their claims to be processed. 
They can expect to get free housing, transportation, food , clothes, medical costs and if they have dental or eye care needs this is also paid for by the Canadian taxpayers to the tune of    50,000 a year per claimant . ( sometimes more but rarely less)  
When our refugee program gets thousands of claimants a month this becomes a serious drain on our tax dollars .  
If an applicant is accepted it also opens the door up for their aging relatives and once their aging relatives get their citizenship and start collecting CPP . What has happened is they sometimes return to their country of origin while the CPP checks get mailed or direct deposit into an acct that their son or daughter has access to in Canada
The aging parents can pass away in the country of origin and no one is the wiser here in  and that CPP checks just keeps coming in .
The bogus refugee claims and the constant abuse on our different Social programs ,  it is no wonder many of these programs are going broke.
What we are seeing today is for every contributing immigrant coming into Canada we are also getting two to four aged relatives coming as well that immediately get to collect on programs they have never paid into . 
We already don't have enough infra structure to deal with the needs of our own aging population nevermind having that added to . 
Canada accepts anywhere between 250,000 to 450,000 immigrants a year and times that by 4 for aging relatives and this quickly becomes a runaway horse.
Years ago when western Canada was being settled immigrants couldn't be older than 30 years old and they had to be very healthy and physically fit plus meet a job requirement need. 
Today many countries like New Zealand have that same policy .
Canada needs to completely  our refugee program due to the constant abuse and we need to put in laws that if you haven't paid into a program then you are not eligible to collect from that program .
If we are going to be fair and responsible to the people that have worked all their lives and contributed to that program and who now must Depend on CPP  and its continuation , then only those that have paid into it should be allowed to collect on it .
The ways things are going I seriously doubt that people who retire in 15 or 20 years from now will be able to collect on a program they have paid into for 40 plus years .
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/mbs0rs</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/4r1e</id></website><link>http://fullcomment.nationalpost.com/2011/11/04/chris-selley-canadas-immigration-system-is-badly-in-need-of-fixing/</link><postedTime>2011-11-04T11:05:33+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-11-05T22:06:38+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gslv06</id><link>http://fullcomment.nationalpost.com/2011/11/04/chris-selley-canadas-immigration-system-is-badly-in-need-of-fixing/#comment-356660470</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rgwxy</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-11-04</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>