<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tna7/update/2012-03-29T10:00:50/5dd970dbaaf01004f9a4c6a1b0f6a7cfab903295ac619b7f0d0646090de28d09</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>For years the gutless wonders on Capital Hill have shirked their Constitutionally assigned duty, and legislated by committee.  They farm out their jobs to the agencies and whoever else they can push it onto so that they do not have to take the Heat.

Bills such as ObamaCare are not law, they are simply an authorization for someone besides lawmakers to concoct all the regulations, award or take away whatever "rights" they deem necessary, to whomever and whatever.  Sebillius and her "death panel" for instant, ARE NOT congressmen, therefore they cannot legally write the law, but that is exactly what is happening.  Look at the EPA, who is coming up with more and more regulations daily, thousands of them which affect every portion of our lives but HAVE NOT been passed by elected lawmakers.  Therefore all of these "rules" DO NOT represent the will of the people who voted for a Congressman whose job this is supposed to be - not an apparatchik inside the monster which is our Federal gubmint.

This is not representative government, but tyranny by a faceless, unaccountable bureaucracy, pure and simple.  If your Congressman doesn't write the laws he introduces, and instead pushes it Off on somebody else, you need to get rid of him/her.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z6oxl</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yv37</id></website><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/blog/2012/03/m-political_cowardice_in_the_senate_and_house_isnt_unconstitutional_but_the_individual_mandate_is.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T12:15:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:00:50+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tna7</id><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/blog/2012/03/m-political_cowardice_in_the_senate_and_house_isnt_unconstitutional_but_the_individual_mandate_is.html#comment-479509683</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mmwkd</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>