<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jgok/post/2012-04-02T02:38:05</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m09wtx</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zv36q</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>First , please learn english, its this language thing we use here in the states and happens to be the language that this page is written in.

Now as for your improvements: there is a reason that small form-factor devices (phones and tablets) get very warm with faster processors, its because they use passive cooling (no fans) and the processor creates much more Heat when its clocked to run faster. 
It seems as though you spend an awful lot of space telling them to make it more like the iPhone, why dont you just go get an iPhone?
I have yet to see a GNex, or any android phone for that matter that doesn't work, some may have small bugs, and the cheaper ones may not have all the features youd like, but in general they make calls, send/receive SMS/MMS, and will run apps designed for their OS version
You ask for a smaller phone with a smaller screen that is slimmer, yet you want a larger , you cannot have it all. Be realistic, if you make the phone smaller, then  will also have to be smaller, thats just how this works. There is only so much energy density that we can squeeze from a  at this point in time and until we can find a better way of powering our devices we will have to live with large bulky Batteries or charging it every 6,8 or 10 hours.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6v730h</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/y2ru</id></website><link>http://www.engadget.com/2012/04/01/how-would-you-change-samsungs-galaxy-nexus/</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T11:13:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T06:38:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jgok</id><link>http://www.engadget.com/2012/04/01/how-would-you-change-samsungs-galaxy-nexus/#comment-483317023</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dkz2p</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>