<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4ns6/post/2012-03-30T17:46:55</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3wj58</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Good one Ric_Roc, a very well thought out post. When the euphoria about KK's appointment had died down, he was  going to have the weight of this once great (how it pains me to say that) great club on his shoulders. And of course if he could't turn the club in an upwards direction, which despite what he is saying, sadly I don't believe he has in 15/16 months, then that weight and pressure was  going to increase. The God awful signings have not helped him at all and of course he is being crucified for this and the wastage of money. I go back to the late 1950's when I first started to support and follow our club and every time I post something on here that appears anti LFC I feel guilty, but you are right I think when you say it is largely the older fans who soemhow want to protect KK and the image they have of him as a player and as a manager. None of that can or will be taken away, but I just don't think KK will be allowed to go on for much longer. John Henry is a sharp businessman and he is NOT steeped in English football tradition (he said so himself when he arrived) so weilding the  probably won't be too difficult for him to do. However if KK is to go, the next and probably even bigger question is who would replace him. You are not a Benitez fan. I was and still am. As Cold as a dead fish but who did very well when here but got stuck with Hicks and Gillette. And before someone criticises some of his signings, yes I know he signed Voronin and Jovanovic - who were also God awful.  However I would have him back here tomorrow if KK was to go. I dislike Mourinho with a passion but he would be the other one who I would have come to Anfield. He takes no prisoners, plays no favourites and for me would give the players the proverbial kick up the backside which about 80% of them need at present. We are in a strange position as a club at present, FA Cup semi finalists yet going backwards in the league. When I watched our game against Everton on replay I was really, really impressed with our passing, pressing and DESIRE to get the result. Then another team of Redmen appeared at Loftus Road and Anfield last Saturday! Who would be a manager? .</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zu3jz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/fbj8</id></website><link>http://anfieldred.co.uk/kenny-insists-liverpool-have-moved-forward-have-your-say/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:14:32+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:46:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4ns6</id><link>http://anfieldred.co.uk/kenny-insists-liverpool-have-moved-forward-have-your-say/#comment-481237066</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>