<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xlp3/post/2012-03-29T13:43:07</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Im sure no one will read this but just a little FYI. This case is 4 years old. My name is Heather Daly I am Chris wife. Chris and I have been friends for over 10 years. I knew Christina in high school. Chris and I got together in September of 2008. I was with him through this whole thing and even being his friend at that time i was wondering where the hell he was when all this was going on. Anyway, I didnt come here to get defensive because this is all over. I just wanted some of you that really seem to care about the boys an update on her them and us. Christina got 10 years. The DA dropped all attempted murder and dropped the agrivated meham which we were not happy about. She obviously will get time served for the 2 years she was in jail before she actually got convicted and sent to prison she has about 6 years left. By that time i hope to adopt the boys and have her rights compleatly removed. The court wont remove mothers rights unless the kids are adopted. For all of you that were questioning Chris being violent and thinking because he made stupid choices ( who hasnt) that that would be the reason he wouldnt get the kids back. My husband NEVER gave up on those kids. He worked full time, made sure that he was there 2 days a week for visits with his boys ( while in foster care).  Seperate couseling for himself, kids, &amp; family each week. He had to do sarms ( drug rehab ) even though at that time he hadnt touched a drug in 11 years and parenting classes. I may have left a few things out. I started doing the couseling with him but I asked but the court would only let me do so much. We were in court all the time. They almost adopted the boys out so it made us just push harder. We are still in contacted with the boys foster parents. They were great and took great care of them and we are exreamly thankfull. Anyway, We picked the kids up January 28th, 2010 for good. The greatest day of our lives. Christian ( hes in kindergarden) will be 6 in a couple months ( the one who ingested the drano and ) he is doing great. Hes all the way healed. We thought he was going to need surgery to remove the scar tissue from his throat and stomach because of the Burns but there will be no surgery for this little man hes all good to go. Hes super smart, the smartest in his class and deffiantly has a good sence of humor. He knows who Christina is he remembers being in the hospital but he doesnt remember when or why. We will deal with that when the time comes. As for Cyle just turned 4 a couple months ago. He wasnt really affected by this. He was pretty much taken and stayed with one family. She didnt do anything to him. He remembers nothing. He was only 8 months old he couldnt pick her out of a crowd. He only knows what his brother tells him. The boys are happy healthy and awsome. They are so funny and fun to be around. They are my entire world. As for Chris all the counseling changed him. hahaha... Hes going to be so mad at me for this. hahaha hes so emotional now. But I wouldnt have him any other way. When we first got together he was so angry and for good reason. Everyone seemed to bail on him when he needed them the most. Hes a happy stay at home dad and has been since the kids came home. He gets frusterated at time as well as I but who doesnt. We are just a normal family with kids that miss behave sometimes 2 dogs 1 cat. Economy sucks. Its nice to have our lives back. Took some time to get adjusted but we did it and its something that we will never forget. We will Always remember the pain and suffering our son went through as well as ourselfs  but in a different way. I dont know what drew me to write this or even look at this site.  I just got to reading coments that some were really hurtful twords Chris and he was suffering just as much as Christian was. I hope someone reads that this was infact a happy ending after 2 years of suffering on all of our parts. See Prayer does work.  You may go to my faceboook for updated photos. But PLEASE no comments on my wall about all of this its something we would like to keep behind us. Thanks.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/3mhsb</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gvlu</id></website><link>http://www.dreamindemon.com/2008/06/22/christina-howell-is-poisonous/</link><postedTime>2010-01-04T20:26:35+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:43:07+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xlp3</id><link>http://www.dreamindemon.com/2008/06/22/christina-howell-is-poisonous/#comment-479686965</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzr2q</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2010-01-04</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>