<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3wg23/post/2012-03-30T01:30:43</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ajk2</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>
how about Donna? 
She's my favourite female companion of the new series.

don't know about Mickey... but Rory is freaking amazing!
He so seamlessly and flawlessly went from. "Dude, what is this poor sod even doing on this show." to. "OMG! fucking Rory, BUYA!" 

Seeing him standing in a centurion outfit in front of a window handing out a message from the doctor in the form of exploding ships in the background is sooooo much more satisfying and impressive cause he is such a big every-day man and we know where he came from, that scene wouldn't have been nearly as impressive had Amy done it or.. even less with Rose or Martha as they were presented as Kick as girls from day one, which is honestly rather boring. 
John Watson in sherlock is probably the most kick-ass john watson ever, and it comes  as so much stronger as this john isn't showy in any-way what-so ever. He just walks around in his big sweaters and looks so innocent secretly being bloody stealth.. 
I think the term is "If you show  then you all ready told us you have some-thing to proof, if you never ever show  but just do when the time comes it's by default hardcore."

I would honestly love a down to earth sweater wearing female doctor who companion having a very Rory like personality, maybe even more timid than what you usually see in who companions. 
It would also bounch lovely  the doctor and show-case two opposites this enhancing the two personalities, and in the end, probably give the companion more growth through-out the way.
It would be interesting if the Doctor one day picked up a grey timid mouse secretly wishing she was more, to drop Off a straight backed smart woman at the preciess same Spot in time having all her colleges go. "wtf happened" ?

And I ended up ranting now... sorry.  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66bw42</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/4ydc</id></website><link>http://www.agonybooth.com/video354_My_Little_Pony_Friendship_is_Magic_Five_Arguments.aspx</link><postedTime>2012-03-24T06:25:55+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T05:30:43+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3wg23</id><link>http://www.agonybooth.com/video354_My_Little_Pony_Friendship_is_Magic_Five_Arguments.aspx#comment-480283377</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rrr6u</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>