<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/chw6f1/update/2011-05-16T22:17:47/4de21c226984e117d3dbab4fe3c140216faae4cda95fa7668f107f1636b83b86</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/chs6hx</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/efl8i</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Wrong, Wrong and Wrong - but ok&#13;
&#13;
1.  The reason vouchers and charters are bad for public education is that&#13;
they take money away from public schools. Two systems are more expensive to&#13;
run than 1. The vouchers and charters usually perform below the public&#13;
schools.&#13;
2.  When the charter and voucher schools fail, the students go back to the&#13;
public schools. I don't remember where I read this, but one school district&#13;
will stop accepting charter and voucher students if they get kicked out. The&#13;
past few years, charter and voucher schools would keep kids long enough to&#13;
put them on their state counts then jetison them to public schools. They get&#13;
the money and the public schools get the Headaches.&#13;
3.  Many things are run better by government and monopolies. Rural electric&#13;
cooperatives work because of government assistance, but they all pay the&#13;
bills at competitive rates. Municipal water, sewer, electric, and cable&#13;
systems work much better and much cheaper than the for profit competitors.&#13;
Example is medicom.  In Spencer Iowa, a small northwest Iowa town, Medicom&#13;
cable package is 1/2 of what the same package is in Des Moines, Why -&#13;
government run cable - you would think this evil, but medicom is making&#13;
money.  Municipal electricity in Milford, my home town, is much cheaper than&#13;
for profit electricity in Spirit Lake. Spirit Lake is nearly twice as big,&#13;
so should be cheaper. It is much more expensive, less responsive and much&#13;
older infrastructure. Let's face it. The line that government can't do&#13;
anything right is just wrong. Most of the rest of the world has private&#13;
water supplies. US is dominated by public water. US water supplies are much&#13;
less expensive and have better quality of water.&#13;
&#13;
Education can improve, but arguments that schools are made for the teachers&#13;
and not the students are just not helpful. As we get into the techonological&#13;
Era, we need to reform schools and how teachers teach. Much more personal&#13;
instruction and probably individual education plans for every student.&#13;
However, as long as we have a commitment to nonsensical standardized tests,&#13;
school can't reform. As long as teachers are seen as the enemy, treated with&#13;
continued disrespect, their is no reason they would change.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/5whd3j</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/eyjq</id></website><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2011/06/klein-school/8497/</link><postedTime>2011-05-09T22:11:26+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-05-17T02:17:47+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/chw6f1</id><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2011/06/klein-school/8497/#comment-204833724</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5xi0w</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-05-09</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>