<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3s2ny/post/2012-03-29T23:05:21</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Greta,

In lat 2009 I went to Scripp's hospital emergency room as I had Chest pains that I identified as signs of a heart attack.  I was admitted and due to my fast  of taking an aspirin, my symptoms had diminished.  They kept me for observation and soon my blood tests showed cardiac enzymes that indicated a mild heart attack.  I was put on a number of drugs and scheduled to have a cardiac catheterization to check heart artery blockage.  I waited the entire day in the emergency room as I was bumped by other cardiac patients.  Soon I was told I had to spend the night but my turn would happen early in the morning.  I had not eaten all day but a nurse found me half a sandwich.  The next morning I was told that I would be taken soon but, again, I was bumped.  No food as I would be under anesthesia.  Finally at 5 pm and still not having had the procedure, I convinced a nurse to get me something to eat.  This proceeded for 2 more days, continually getting bumped.  Finally on the 4th day I had the procedure and received several cardiac stents and was sent home.  I had insurance through Kaiser and though Scripps was not associated with Kaiser, Kaiser had a reciprocal agreement for emergency care.  I received my bill from Kaiser along with several Scripps doctors and lab bills.  The total I paid was nearly $5000.  2 years later I received nasty calls from a collection agency for a Scripps hospital bill of $130,000.  It seems Kaiser refused to pay Scripps charges since they bumped me several days and took other patients ahead of me.  I was in stable condition and could have been transported to a Kaiser hospital.  Scripps, instead of working this will Kaiser, put me out for collections.  It took me several weeks and numerous calls to Kaiser and Scripps to get this cleared up.

No wonder our health care system is in turmoil.  First, it was clear from the beginning that I had insurance but somehow the starting point is to bill the maximum and try to get payment from all parties.  When that failed, put me out for collection.  I would like to say that this is the only time this has happened but every time I have has hospital care the bill not only takes forever to get  but there are Always errors, overcharging and mismanagement.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zotaf</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t33k</id></website><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/have-you-had-any-medical-bill-nightmares/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:45:56+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T03:05:21+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3s2ny</id><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/have-you-had-any-medical-bill-nightmares/#comment-480184281</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>