<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrzvt/post/2012-03-30T12:11:02</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwdrit</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Scarborough is absolutely wrong. Since the first report of this story, the liberal media has hyped it as a "White on Black" racist murder within a lawless racist community. The usual race baiters immediately jumped on the band-wagon as did the loser-in-chief (who I ague below is undeniable racist himself) and all thes race-merchants do so without having all the facts. Furthermore, these race hustlers continue mistating known facts. but they do foment more &amp; more anger as more inconvenient facts come out which do not support their racist view of America.

Facts:

-From the start these race merchants (MSM too) called Zimmerman white until they found out he was hispanic; now he's a white hispanic. That's a first for the liberal media.
-95% of Trayvon's pics shown on MSM are several years old. More recent pics shown him much more buff as he really was at his age.
-These smae race merchants want Zimmerman both convicted in the press and otherwise (by any means whatsoever- consider Pelosi's recent statement). Yet recent tweets by Trayvon are considered to be a smearing of the dead even though they expose an angry yound black man- wanna be gang-banger was my impression.
-Blank Panters are threatening vigilante justice in addition to offering a Bounty on a citizen not yet charged. Their claim is they don't abide by "White Man" laws.
-Mainly black politicans are grandstanding (politicizing) this issue proclaiming facts not in evidence- that Zimmerman hunted Martin down like a dog, murdered him in Cold blood etc.

While the president's orginal statements need not be constued as racial, he now has has the higher duty to address the Black Panter's call for vigilante justice; he also has the duty to attempt to calm racial tensions, yet he remains silent, why? If he does nothing in calling for order/respect for the law, then by his silience he condones subverting it and for that reason he can justifiably be considered racist since he seeks justice for not all, but only those he considers his protected class- much like Holder has proven himself to be racist. 

Scarborough and the rest should merely let all the facts come out first. Also, vetting Trayvonm (his tweets/emails etc.) is nothing short of responsibly investigating this case as eveyone says they want! </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/675j3b</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/egg0</id></website><link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2012/03/30/scarborough_the_right_is_politicizing_trayvon_martins_death-comments.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:50:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:11:02+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrzvt</id><link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2012/03/30/scarborough_the_right_is_politicizing_trayvon_martins_death-comments.html#comment-480902129</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>