<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3q7z1/update/2012-03-29T11:51:46/5593c57d395d7bbd4b6ec1dc386f113832ac2a2576e8d74a4b2606dfad8b1c94</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tjyh</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hd7yl</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Darn straight there buddy. Pot kills how many people every year, ZERO? I don't partake but alcohol and booze kill more people than a lot of drugs combined. Easily.I say we legalize mary-jane and people can grow it. THC concentration on the package (light, regular, and high-test ;) ) 

People want to use pot so it's not going away. It's not as harmful as people claim it is. It's "evil" because it's a DRUG and DRUGS are BAD M'KAY?! Nonsense. Nobody in their right mind, aside from the indoctrinated and brainwashed Holy Moral Majority, can say with a straight face that pot is worse for you than cigarettes or alcohol. The only reason many harmlesss drugs are "BAD" is because we make them illegal and create an ocean of underground black-market criminal activity. Then we spend millions and billions policing "bad" drug dealers.

The guys who drank all weekend are NOT more prepared to work on Monday morning that a guy who smoked a couple of joints with pals over the same time period. It's debatable whether or not a functional alcoholic is less productive and more dangerous than an occasional pot smoker, but the pot smoker is IMMEDIATELY escorted  site. 

It's time to lose these ancient Judeo-Christian based beliefs. Good Lord, I'm surprised we're still not chucking women Off cliffs to see if they can fly or Burning witches at the stake.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zmvm2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7maa</id></website><link>http://www.edmontonsun.com/2012/03/28/canadians-coming-around-to-brothels-poll</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T09:07:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:51:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3q7z1</id><link>http://www.edmontonsun.com/2012/03/28/canadians-coming-around-to-brothels-poll#comment-479596992</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h2m8h</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>