<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9efdt/update/2012-03-16T16:27:34/bad5e73d47c0caa4f5d254e32500a48f8b70eeaae4d0a842c62a4c3ffd820c52</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I am enraged to no extent after reading the details on this sweet innocent little girl. So much so I have Vomited, humanity is so unkind, being the mother of a 5 year old daughter, I cannot imagine what the pain must be. I am a person of faith and my heart and prayers go out to not only Tori's loved ones but to Tori herself, in praying that she is at peace.  I am  enraged that the justice system here in Canada cannot do its job, and Act accordingly to how these two lousy excuses for human beings are able to live and breathe without the pain and torture they deserve. The death penalty would be the easy way out for these to evil souls, I do believe their judgement day will come, and will pay the ultimate punishment when the time comes.  Their faces should be posted everywhere and anywhere so the world can know if they ever step a foot out the door to their freedom they will have no chance at survival seeing as that society will not accept them. The death penalty should be allowed only for the ultimate horrific crimes. If you can take another's life for any reason other than self defense *and even then its hard to determine due to so many wrongful convictions in this world* then I truly think the death penalty should be enforced.  But to hurt a child in any way shape or form is inhuman and just down right evil. I wish more people would step up, but the world is coming to nothing but politics  and hatred, yet all we see in advertisements is about making the world a better place. The world goes because humanity allows it. People want to feel superior to others. and because of this, people suffer. I am disgusted that the people like these to murders can be allowed to exist. I do apologize if i have offend anyone, this little girls death has made many put to tears, and she will not be forgotten, everyone will be looking for their own justice with their own opinions on this one.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/65lvcs</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/4r1e</id></website><link>http://fullcomment.nationalpost.com/2012/03/15/tasha-kheiriddin-stafford-case-shows-why-canada-needs-the-death-penalty/</link><postedTime>2012-03-15T12:02:08+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-16T20:27:34+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9efdt</id><link>http://fullcomment.nationalpost.com/2012/03/15/tasha-kheiriddin-stafford-case-shows-why-canada-needs-the-death-penalty/#comment-467245889</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zceyu</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-15</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>