<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msb2x3/update/2012-03-27T23:06:24/2e066e51169977bb4a568132f3acdd502db6d76601687a4f1c261d03086067b3</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>- I like how Duffy is able to talk so frankly to Quarles. Also "You can't have the Duffy without the Wynn" hahaaha what? That was deliciously crazy.

- Michael Ironside? Whoa. Not used to movie actors showing up here.

- Does anyone else get mad when they hear the Always Sunny music on other shows or commercials? I know it's not their original music, but it still feels like other things are stealing it. (it was the Sprint commercial)

- Dickie's mustache might be giving Boyd's hair a run for its money

- Was not expecting that face slap

- Somebody really needs to Burn Art's tie &amp; shirt combos. Poo brown and red checkers... egads man

- Finally we get to see Quarles use his sleeve gun! "What a dick" hahaha It's taken me a while, but I'm really starting to love Quarles

- Does Art have a hearing aid in his right ear?

- Dickie is like one of those guys you meet at a party who swears he has the best story ever to tell you, but he has so many prefaces and caveats that you stop caring before he starts telling the actual story

- Whoa Art with the quick shot. Busting those two Detroit guys seemed like a pretty bonehead move. I don't get how neither Art nor Raylan thought that was a good idea. Either way, nice to see all of the Marshals actually doing their jobs.

- Well, now we finally know what happened to Ethan Zobelle!

- Wynn Duffy finally plays his cards

- Kind of funny to think that this is the first time Duffy and Boyd have come in contact with eachother. I guess Duffy stays pretty clear of Harlan.

- Quarles naked and chained to a bed... that might actually be to his advantage. 

- Lots of tenuous alliances being forged this episode. Quarles &amp; Limehouse, Dickie &amp; Errol, Wynn Duffy &amp; Boyd, Boyd-Errol-Dickie three way? (ew)

- Oh my god why did the episode have to end!?!?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hasuz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/measures,71247/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T03:00:26+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T03:06:24+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msb2x3</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/measures,71247/#comment-478038165</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rvvwz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>