<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms0sn0/update/2012-03-28T15:32:06/2f604d0366f92686216d92e9be5f92c382d8bae5892a53475f7301530a18cea0</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>What a great article. The person being interviewed is very articulate and did a good job of being straightforward about the reality of Mormonism. I was so Mormon for 45 years of my life I Bled green jello. If someone had told me I'd ever be a non-believer I'd have been mortified that someone could think that of me. I went through the temple many many many times before and after 1990 and I also pantomimed my own violent demise, vowing to suffer my life to be taken before I'd reveal the  passwords and handshakes and things I learned in the temple. And there was probably a time I would have. Not any more, however, what do you want to know? I'll tell ya.

The Mormon church does not have to tell Mitt Romney what to do. He's been steeped in Mormonism, the temple, the high power positions of the church for over 60 years. He knows his duty. He vowed in the most "sacred" (not Secret, ha ha) place in the world that he'd give his time, talents and EVERYTHING with which the lord had blessed him or will bless him to the building up of the kingdom of zion (the Mormon church). This, if nothing else, certainly means using the gift of the presidency to derail gay marriage and to fight against women's rights. What more does anyone need to know? You think you're getting a Christian? The Lord God Almighty himself told Joseph Smith that all other sects besides Mormonism were an ABOMINATION to him. Romney will use Christians to help him get elected, but he is NOT one of you.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hcpj2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ant8</id></website><link>http://www.alternet.org/story/154710/former_mormon_what_americans_need_to_know_about_mormonism/comments/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T04:55:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T19:32:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms0sn0</id><link>http://www.alternet.org/story/154710/former_mormon_what_americans_need_to_know_about_mormonism/comments/#comment-478686131</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zh7h5</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>