<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw9w4q/post/2012-03-31T03:41:31</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwy4s1</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6jq4s</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>A few things:
1.  While you may personally believe all of what you said - in which case we have a simple disagreement - a lot of conservatives are not on your page.  I read and hear people saying all the time that there have been no changes in climate, CO2 emissions are unimportant, etc.  

2. Graduate students and scientists are not the 1%.  Graduate students make between $8-30K/year, Depending on exactly what sort of program they are in.  Scientists make more, but still not a ton.  Certainly not in the millions, unless they are also business people and have leveraged their science knowledge to become CEO or something.  Perhaps they are in the top 1% for amount of time spent in school, but certainly not in income.   Given that "the 1%" has come to mean something very specific in our country's vernacular (and is linked to income), its really either disingenuous or uninformed to suggest that many or most scientists/graduate students fall into that category.  Its more accurate to say that scientists are general middle or upper-middle class (making enough to easily support themselves in most cases and in most regions but not so much that they're the wealthy folks often talked about in conversations about raising taxes on the wealthy/ending tax breaks/etc).

3.  This is purely opinion: most customers are more interested in the cheapest option, not the cleanest option.  If you could find a way to produce a dirty energy technology (like Burning coal) cheaper than producing a cleaner technology (like solar...ignoring whatever goes into initially making the equipment), people would often go for the dirty but cheap option.  Especially in this economy.  Most people like the idea of saving the earth and being good stewards, but its hard to focus on when there are so many other pressures - like feeding your kids and having shelter.  I'm not so optimistic that the market would sort this out on its own.  I'd need more evidence to be convinced.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z1cyl</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ydw9</id></website><link>http://motherjones.com/node/169876</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:22:37+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T07:41:31+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw9w4q</id><link>http://motherjones.com/node/169876#comment-481627963</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lwpo5</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>