<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xxo7/update/2012-03-29T13:57:28/7d311f0254601fc0fc5e66ba53718f72b9d9116bdb50f96d686b209c2a2e94bc</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkbw64</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6gqj0</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Europeans perpetrated the Holocaust, and the US and the other Allieds were indifferent to it while it happened.  We now know that they were fully aware of it (you know, the old question:  why didn't the Allieds bomb the railroad tracks leading to the extermination camps?)  And why were the US and much of the UK closed to Jewish refugees?  Ultimately, wasn't it more convenient (or was it out of guilt) to give them Israel?   

What extremist hatemongering rightwing radicals are doing does not  justify what other extremist hatemongering rightwing radicals are doing.  Some of those extremists have bombed schools (even a UN school) and bombed ambulances, and some have used their enemy's children as shields. 

Two wrongs don't a right make.  I am not afraid for Israel who is estimated to have between 200 and 300 nukes along with a lot of "conventional"giant  bombs and whose right wing govt (increasingly a right wing theocracy) is Itching to drop on the Iranian folks who already risked their lives and limbs protesting against the present Iranian theocracy.  Do you actually think that bombs would fall on the leaders?  (actually the US bomb manufacturers hope they get used so they can sell new ones to Israel, or rather to the US govt because it takes the form of military aid -- remember Eisenhower's warning about the military-industrial complex?)

I wonder what will  happen when the last of the Holocaust survivors generation dies Off (I'm 70 myself, I was born in 1942 in Budapest and while my father and grandfather were murdered in Auschwitz by rightwing extremists calling themselves Christians, my life was saved along with that of 300,000 Jews by a righteous gentile, Raoul Wallenberg).  (but does any history exists in your eyes if it isn't in the Torah?  And is the Torah and the whole of the Tanakh, actual history or is it a compendium of oral myth tranformed with each telling and again transformed with when written down and with each new copying and with each translation?  Have you actually read it, end to end, withough the mask of countless interpretations?  Need I remind you that the Christian Old Testament and  much of the Koran  have put those those tales of violence and murders in  their own sacred texts?)

You know, Jewish history did not end a couple of thousand years ago and restarted only in 1948.  Much happened in between, and in the meanwhile:  Jews in Europe and in the US have participated in every movement for social justice, often at the price of their own lives (recent example: Andrew Goodman and Michael Schwerner, both white and Jewish,  who were lynched along James Chaney in Mississippi while the three of them were attempting to register black voters) 

I feel a lot of affinity for Israeli secular progressives who want peace and are striving for a genuine two states compromise.  It's the only thing that will secure Israel instead of keeping taking over more and more Palestinain land.  I have nothing in common with the Israeli Right and the brainwashing of so many Israli children to hate "Arabs" because they are not "Europeans".  And why on earth would Israelis want to be "Europeans"?  Is it because, even though they speak a lot of the Holocaust, they have actually forgotten it?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ycdej</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/l7r5</id></website><link>http://chronicle.com/article/Israels-Moral-Peril/131273/</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T22:24:48+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:57:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xxo7</id><link>http://chronicle.com/article/Israels-Moral-Peril/131273/#comment-479698575</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5lzf3</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>