<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m10c32/update/2012-03-14T12:26:47/afbbd2517c413db292ebc430195b41a4ea7fe3ffbce98e3600cb4bc89ecf9d4d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Despite the obvious leftist undertones of “Personally I find abortion reprehensible but I have no right to tell others what to do and killing babies is the only solution I can think of to fix our societal woes” I do have to commend the left for at least being honest.  Leftist opinion on abortion does follow the liberal boilerplate argument of “sure, it would be immoral for me to do it but I cannot dictate morality and it’s not against the law anyway.”  If that is our mindset, why do we bother with laws at all?  I call the left  “selective moralists.”  Why stop at babies who have committed no crime against society whatsoever?  Why not extend this philosophy to criminals?  You break the law, any law, you die.  We could eliminate prisons altogether which would have a huge financial benefit to society.  See how that works?  Once you get liberal fascism rolling along its hard to stop.

 In my mind the only valid pro-abortion argument is that the fetus is not yet human, why don’t leftists ever use that argument?  Could it be that science does not support that premise?  Given that the 1) The babies heart starts beating between 18 and 25 days, 2) EEGs show the presence of brainwaves at 43 days (we accept the absence of brain waves as an indication of death, may as well accept their presence as an indication of life), 3) All brain and body functions are present at 8 weeks, 4) At 8 weeks the baby will wake, sleep, make a fist, suck his thumb, and get Hiccups 5) At 10 weeks the baby is sensitive to Heat, touch, light and noise I don’t blame the left for hiding from scientific fact.

Does the left endorse slavery?  They must as their abortion argument mirrors pro-slavery arguments.

The 1857 the Dred Scott case had a 7-2 Supreme Court decision which stated that black people were not legal persons; they were the property of the owner. The owner could buy, sell, or even kill them if he wished. At that time Abolitionists objected that the ruling was outrageous; it was immoral and discriminated against an entire class of living persons solely on the basis of skin color. But those who supported slavery argued that if those who had a moral objection to slavery didn't have to own slaves; no one was forcing them to own slaves. The core premise of their argument was: "Don't force your morality on the slave owner, he has the right to choose to own slaves if he wishes."

The 1973 in the Roe v. Wade Decision followed this exact pro-slavery logic. The Supreme Court decided that according to the U.S. Constitution, by the same 7 to 2 majority, that unborn people were not legal persons; they had no civil rights, no human rights and were therefore legally the property of the owner (the mother). The mother had the absolute legal right to keep or destroy her unborn baby. Pro-life people objected  that he ruling was outrageous, that it was immoral and discriminated against an entire class of living people solely on the basis of age (too young) and place of residence (the womb). But those who support abortion argue that those who have a moral objection to abortion don't have to have abortions. The pro-abortionists say: "No one is forcing you to have an abortion. But don't force your morality on the mother. She has a right to choose to kill her developing baby if she wishes."

I struggle to understand why the left supports the extermination of a few million/billion humans in order to make life more comfortable for those who remain. As Mao, Pol Pot, Hitler, etc. showed us, murder for a perceived benefit to society is really not all that big of a deal, as long as you aren’t the one being murdered.   </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/68spt8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q0fi</id></website><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/13/the-next-big-scandal-taxpayer-funding-for-abortion/</link><postedTime>2012-03-13T14:44:14+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-14T16:26:47+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m10c32</id><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/13/the-next-big-scandal-taxpayer-funding-for-abortion/#comment-465212052</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6xyve</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-13</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>