<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34k1e/post/2012-03-29T11:20:48</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ti1y</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h9qv5</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Id actually enjoy having a real conversation with you as I do see your points but I am not convinced. I feel that its not only the president that is the source of the rampant corruption. Manguang is the problem. Those behind the scenes are the most corrupt and will put the man they can bend and blackmail into power so they can continue their course of self-enrichment.


We desperately need a USA type of vote (although I am not a fan of the USA) I feel this would stop this rot that is behind the government and policies of the ANC, let the people vote for the man, not just the party!


The NDR as you call it will not be what you think, it won't be the blacks taking over, thats already happened, that is simply an excuse to continue racism and hatred in SA.
The new NDR will be the millions upon millions who have been cheated and robbed by those who they held in high esteem, The NDR will be the civil war, the stance that the people make against the oppression we live under from a corrupt semi-dicatorship who refuses to listen to the people who pay their salaries and whose money they steal day after day.
This is something we should all fear and do everything in our power to stop.


The problem is that people still see the ANC as freedom fighters fighting for their rights. That ANC is in the past, its gone, the great men retired or resting in peace. 
The ANC of today does not hold the same morals or promise. It has become the terrorist group that it was labelled in the past, financial terrorists taking away our freedom piece by piece while they rob us blind and smile and joke about it.

Maybe not all ANC members are corrupt, I am sure they are not and some must be so frustrated and sad that they are trying to do good while others are literally turning the country into a sewer. The problem is if you look at any organisation it is the leadership that represents it, the top manangement that in the end is responsible for the actions of that company/government, whatever. If you look at the ANC from out of SA all you see is a president that should be in jail. It is blindly obvious he is guilty with all the cover ups and his financial manager being found guilty but not punished so he has no reason to talk.

Until those behind the scenes that are electing the president and calling the shots are removed and more power given to the citizens as it should be in democracy, ("And the people shall govern") there is little hope for an honest ANC. Thats the whole thing democracy is meant to give power to the people, those elected should be of the people but as you can see it is more of a dictatorship, look at the e-tolls, they refuse to listen to the people, the deal was done in Secret and it is designed to stream money out the country while a few cadres reap in millions and now they are threatening/blackmailing us at every turn to pay these fees. This is corruption, blackmail and worse its a dictatorship. This kind of behaviour would NEVER happen in a true democracy!


I understand your hope in the ANC, I wish I had the same but I simply cannot ignore the facts and dream about the days of Madiba, I am forced to be a realist and to see what the nature of the ANC is, what they do on a daily basis and that is to keep the poor poor, uneducated and hungry, America does the same but it is not right. People are dying at the hands of Zuma and the top cadres hourly, those in desperate need of food, warmth, water are being ignored to fund parties, BMWS and mansions in Sandton, doesnt that make you even the slightest bit sad/angry/hateful? Becasue I knwo it does me, we are all human beings trying to just get through life and some are never given the slightest chance and if Madiba was president today I think they would have had that chance to live and not die skinny, alone and Cold like they are under a corrupt politician.

If you read what happened or is happening in Italy you will rewalise I am right and that the way the ANC is now will be their very downfall and in times to come they will be remembered as crooked, spineless dictators who took what they could while they could with no care for their own people.


And just as an after thought....if you insist the ANC is serious about corruption please name one, just one cadre who is in jail for corruption, not simply put on paid leave for a year and then use tax payers money to defend themselves then dismissed, actually someone sitting in jail for rampant, obvious corruption, theft of resources etc. Its not possible becasue they are all protected by the ANC, given a free pass, the ANC does not look down upon corruption it sees the elite few making and taking everything as ok. You simply cannot argue that fact, the ANC says one thing but actions speak louder than words and their actions speak volumes about their stance on corruption, saying its ok, enjoy yourselves, we all do it, join the ANC take,take,take party we have all been having. Pull up a R6000 chair and enjoy your expensive whiskey with us.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h5fn4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/jn2h</id></website><link>http://www.iol.co.za/news/crime-courts/i-ll-never-talk-says-lolly-murder-suspect-1.1265212</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T05:48:57+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:20:48+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34k1e</id><link>http://www.iol.co.za/news/crime-courts/i-ll-never-talk-says-lolly-murder-suspect-1.1265212#comment-479571414</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hq1nu</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>