<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39dy7/post/2012-03-29T17:27:05</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m378cn</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Hi Mrs Weka, thank you for the compliment and welcome to the comments section of my blog.

To answer the question literally it could do that and for a while it might look like it was working but it would in the vast majority of circumstances fail.

Let me give you the likely response of one instrument the exchange rate of the £. It would fall and probably heavily as we would be correctly perceived as monetising our debt. In simple terms increasing the supply of pounds with a fixed demand would reduce the price.

This would generate inflation and possibly a lot of it Depending on how far the £ fell and against which currencies ( because so many goods are priced in the US dollar it is the most important of our exchange rates).

The problem with controlling inflation by taxes would be that you would probably have to take most if not all of the money out of the system to stop the inflationary fires Burning...

So it could but the costs which are indirect are likely to be worse than the direct costs of issuing bonds.As I often write on here if you get a real.surge in inflation it is very hard to get it back under control if our economic history is any guide.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hy93q</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6xfm</id></website><link>http://www.mindfulmoney.co.uk/wp/shaun-richards/the-problems-with-gross-domestic-product-statistics-explained/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T10:11:15+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T21:27:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39dy7</id><link>http://www.mindfulmoney.co.uk/wp/shaun-richards/the-problems-with-gross-domestic-product-statistics-explained/#comment-479914323</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5sopd</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>