<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3mgmn/update/2012-03-28T22:45:45/f22e86570911292ced54024065da906b4cab35e2721dac6bb8d35c4ffe56624b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m38k8i</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Hi Al, thanks for sharing. And thanks for listening to my thoughts.

While I have only read one or two of Lewis' books, I have often seen quotes from them, like yours here, used as possible examples of how people "end up in hell." Lewis is very popular among Christians, and I think a big reason why is that he was very good at what I would call, "separating God from hell." Because most Christians are very much against any notion that "God sends people to hell" (and rightly so), and that He is  hoping that they won't end up there, Lewis' depictions  seem to work towards putting the blame on someone's damnation on them, and keeping God innocent in the whole ugly matter. 

As in your quote, the idea seems to be that our poor choices continue to corrupt us more and more until finally there is nothing human left. I have also heard it called "becoming seared in their sins," meaning that they have sinned so long that they cannot stop... any good in them has been Burnt out... and again they have become essentially un-human. And where do non-humans - those who have removed all traces of God's image in them - end up? In hell of course. And somehow, interestingly enough, they seem to prefer it there.

If you happened to catch any of the discussions here concerning Dr. Beck's book Unclean, as well as others concerning our tendencies to "dehumanize" our enemies so that we can more easily see them as worthy of torture and destruction, you may see where I am going with this. Very simply, I think Lewis, as great of a writer as he was, fell prey to the same tendencies that most Christians do -- they don't want to blame God for anyone ending up in hell, so they must find a way to separate Him from the equation. 

But the problem is, they end up doing just that... COMPLETELY separating God from the equation! He is no longer the sovereign Lord of the universe, but only an interested observer; watching and hoping that everything will turn out alright, but impotent to do anything about it. As far as I am concerned, the word "hope" is not in God's vocabulary. Only we humans would use it. It is certainly a precious word to us - the hope we have that things will turn out alright carries us through the suffering in our lives and in the lives of those we love. It represents the faith that we have that God can actually DO something. But to even consider that God ever says, "I hope this works out," is completely ridiculous to me. God did not "hope" that He could resurrect Jesus. He does not "hope" to defeat death. He does not "hope" to "destroy the works of the devil" - sin, evil, ignorance, deception, bigotry, etc. He does not "hope" to reconcile/restore all things to Himself, or to be "all in all." It's a done deal. He said it will happen.... and it WILL happen.

The questions that I would have for anyone who chooses to use Lewis-type examples of people dehumanizing themselves are these: "Where the heck was God - the potter - when that person was apparently molding himself into something beyond the potter's power of redemption (as if there is such a point!)? And as we are all sinners, why is it that all of us don't sear ourselves beyond that point? Why do some have the personal power to see and avoid that trap and save themselves?

Well the answer Always comes back (though they won't admit it) as pointing to something in themselves that was somehow stronger, smarter, wiser, etc., etc., than in the ones that are eternally lost. They might even *say* that "only through the power of God were they able to overcome their sinful natures," but that simply begs the question again... "Where was God while those others slipped away?" It is nothing other than salvation by works - the "better" ones save themselves.... the weaker, "lesser" ones, don't. And God is just sitting back watching this all go on but can't do anything about it. He's a good guy though, in that He "hopes" it will all work out, but after all... He's only God... What can He do?

Forgive me for rambling, but I "hope" that I've gotten my point across. To me, anything other than universal salvation - the restoration of ALL things - points to God as either unable, or unwilling, to save His creation. And I will simply not accept either one. In the first He ain't GOD... and in the second He ain't GOOD. 

Thanks again for allowing me to share my heart with you. Take care, Al.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l40g4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/m7z5</id></website><link>http://experimentaltheology.blogspot.com/2012/03/parable-of-lost-sheep-calvinist-version.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T10:35:25+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T02:45:45+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3mgmn</id><link>http://experimentaltheology.blogspot.com/2012/03/parable-of-lost-sheep-calvinist-version.html#comment-479023904</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>