<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwth7d/post/2012-03-30T16:46:42</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3s804</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h28mo</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Anti-White Left? As if the Right isn't anti-White?

The Left wants more Blacks because they're a goldmine for government bureaucracy, while the Right wants more Mexicans 

because they figure, being superstitious beadmumblers, they're fall into their conservative Christian camp after getting their 

"green cards." In both scenarios Whites are clearly the losers, as both Blacks and Browns breed like cockroaches. Which isn't 

so bad when left in their natural environments of unchecked crime and famine. But when let loose in the US with its superior 

standard of living, they'll begin producing in numbers that would make in influenza virus Blush.

As to what will remain when whites leave, well just take a look at what happened to Detroit. The degeneration of that city into 

a festering cesspool of Negro squalor is just a shadow of things to come once Blacks and Brown achieve numerical 

dominance over Whites. Once that happens, expect America to collapse as a functioning world power within 20-30 years 

maximum. 

As for their being no mainstream pro-White political party, well how could there be when the government is in the business of 

abbetting White genocide? Also, don't bet on Whites "waking up" anytime soon, not when shackeled with the duel yokes of 

liberal humanism and Christainty keeping them enslaed. 

About this gap between mainstream conservatism and White racial politics. Honestly, it doesn't exist. The Right, meaning the 

mainstaream conservative neo-cons take their order from Israel, not Elm St. To them, white racial politcs are the worst thing 

imaginable for "business," as they'e set their collectivist sights south of the border. For them, that's where theie new markets 

will open, and those are the, and I use the term loosely, people they'll be courting for votes from now. Whites have been left to 

high and dry to hang in the wind. This is why any group advocating any sort of pro-White agenda is immediately vilified in the 

press as a crypto Nazi cult.

What Whites reeally need to do is remove themselves from the system entirely, as neither the Left or the Right has interest in 

advocating on their behalves anymore. Also, there's another problem plaguing Whites that other races don't seem to politically 

suffer from, and that's diversity of opinion. Unlike Whites, Blacks and Browns are easily led from above. All you need to do is 

 some simple slogans at them, preferably ones that rhyme, and Off they go, rioting in the streets. Whites, by contrast, do 

not seem to be so susceptible to the sloganing of Jewish Marxists, (Hmm, Jewish Marxist, isn't that an oxymoron?), nor do 

they possess, to the same degree as Blacks and Browns, that primitive hive mind. You could say that White intellectual diersity 

, which should be one of our races strongest traists, has, paradoxically, become its greatest weakness. I'm thinking more and 

more thesse days that Whites, in order to survive the anti-cultural onslaught of bone-heaed Black savages and south of the 

border La Rasa Cucarachas, they need to once more descend into the atavistic depths of savagery that they'e been endeavoring 

the past seeral thousand years to evole up out of.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hc70w</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/e57v</id></website><link>http://www.alternativeright.com/main/blogs/zeitgeist/why-we-don-t-care/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T04:33:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T20:46:42+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwth7d</id><link>http://www.alternativeright.com/main/blogs/zeitgeist/why-we-don-t-care/#comment-481180724</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z6qja</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>