<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwyefg/post/2012-03-30T10:31:15</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>People who believe that Godless events and evolution are how we originated, here's some logic for you:

It has been very important to your philosophy - for over 100 years - to prove your beliefs and eliminate God from the discourse.  During that time Science has made great , and discoveries and inventions unthought of  (even a very short time ago) are now part of our everyday life.  Has nobody even TRIED to create the simplest cell of life in the lab? If it can't be done ON PURPOSE in our modern labs, how can you believe it happened by accident? 

An icy rock crashed into a hot watery planet and it caused 1 cell to come to life? Or 1 million cells? This theory has been around for decades (centuries?) and now it's a news item again. I'm sure it will be big news again in 2035 or so - "Life brought to earth by Comets". Give me something real to challenge my beliefs - make a living blade of grass from its elemental constituents, that shouldn't be hard for some academic who says God doesn't exist. 

So far, your words leave me Cold, your random-event origin theories are stale and unproven. Stick to practical applications of science, keep advancing our understanding of the world and the universe, and leave philosophy to philosophers and theologians. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lsmsu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/space/9169518/Life-brought-to-Earth-by-comets.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T21:04:47+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T14:31:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwyefg</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/space/9169518/Life-brought-to-Earth-by-comets.html#comment-480798761</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7a2d</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>