<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/asevhz/update/2010-06-09T01:09:00/54235e3a7ad48352efc74a2f49ef764ebe477c734f8d120f98e2aa750dba703b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>MIAMI BEACH (CBS4) &amp;#8213; 

Artist Romero Britto was arrested Thursday morning for allegedly driving under the influence on Miami Beach. 

Related Slideshows
Miami pop artist Romero Britto bonded out of jail Thursday night after being arrested and accused of DUI in Miami Beach earlier in the morning. 

According to the Miami Beach police report, Britto was pulled over shortly after 3:00 a.m. in the 500 block of Washington Avenue while driving his black Bentley. The report also indicated he was given a breathalyzer test and blew a .161 and .158 which is twice the legal limit of .08. This information was confirmed by Jenny Velazquez of the Miami Beach Police Department.
"I feel very embarrassed about the whole thing; l think drinking is not good," said Britto. "I had a few drinks, and that's what happened."

The police report states that arresting officer, P. Socarras, witnessed Britto weaving while driving in the southbound lanes of Washington Avenue.

Socarras wrote in his report that Britto "crossed into the left lane on three separate occasions and on the third time almost struck another vehicle which was in that lane." Britto also "drifted into the right lane almost striking a parking vehicle," states the report.

After pulling Britto over, Officer Socarras described Britto as having "a flushed face, bloodshot Watery eyes, slurred speech and a strong odor of an alcoholic beverage on his breath."

In addition, the report states "he did not perform to standards" in a roadside sobriety test. Britto even stated to the officer at one point, "Officer, I live across the bridge, give me a break."

Britto was arrested on the scene and transported to the Miami Beach Police Department for further processing.

Britto's artwork can be seen throughout South Florida. 
(© MMIX, CBS Broadcasting Inc. All Rights Reserved.)
Cristina Getty says: 
He is a binge drinker and is very dangerous, he is a danger to society and needs to go into rehab or to jail, he doesn't even paint his own art anymore, it is all done by teenagers...

Posted On: Friday, Mar. 27   @ 12:39AM Allen D. Porter says: 
Artists, celebrities, athletes and others who can afford to drive a Bentley can afford a driver when they are partying. 

There are Always alternatives to driving drunk. But you have to be smart enough to look for them, Romero!

Posted On: Friday, Mar. 27   @ 4:21AM Count LF Chodkiewicz Chudzikiewicz says: 
For what, 2 decades the Miami Beach faux-artists community lead by ex-Commissioner Nancy Liebman aided and abetted by Mayors David Dermer and Matti Bower and with useless footsoldiers like Michael Vita, Claire Tomlin, Laura Jamieson, all with "created" unnecessary publicly supported jobs have gotten zillions for drunken artists,non-functioning artists, bad artists, and non-artists so as to get funding for themselves and political minions. Like every one of them didn't know Britto was a ticking bomb? Like Nancy Liebman didn't see what everyone else did at event after event over the past 10 years? Anyway, he had to be a drunk to say on Miami Beach, where all the sober artists have long ago left.

Posted On: Friday, Mar. 27@ 5:24AM Anon says: 
It just makes me sad that so much taxpayer money for art in public places is gobbled up by this BORING behemoth of an "artist" and his crew of lobbyists...money that gets spent on drunk driving in Bentleys, apparently. I can't imagine how Miami's REAL artists must feel about seeing his crap everywhere.

Posted On: Friday, Mar. 27@ 6:43PM 

-04-23T15:41:52</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/cmyela</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6q0t</id></website><link>http://www.miaminewtimes.com/2010-06-10/news/for-romero-britto-luck-and-charm-trump-talent/</link><postedTime>2010-12-18T22:03:53+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2010-06-09T05:09:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/asevhz</id><link>http://www.miaminewtimes.com/2010-06-10/news/for-romero-britto-luck-and-charm-trump-talent/#comment-114515042</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2010-12-18</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>