<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwh7kf/update/2012-03-30T13:43:26/82e9b34365e4047e447ce0b251841dd27530c9e610f9e0c5c79872a8a86d7250</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwy8d8</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h8yjr</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Why the Face? Jena posted a similar comment in the ratings earlier this week, and I agreed with her wholeheartedly that there were other possible explanations that he could and perhaps should have considered, including interrogation BS. However, I didn't expect Castle to realize those options himself.  When he was talking to Martha, I expected her to  him by saying either she was lying in the interrogation or that she lied to protect herself in case Castle hadn't meant what he said...and had only said it in the Heat of the moment because he thought Beckett was dying.  But for Castle to see the options himself?  I don't know.  That means that he has to push aside his emotions and think logically.  That takes some maturity, in my opinion.  Not to mention, in a way, it may be Comforting for him to think that he's been rejected. Now he doesn't have to address his feelings anymore.  He doesn't have to put himself out there and risk confirmation of the perceived rejection.  Maybe it's just me, but I think it all makes perfect sense.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z90t3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q4ud</id></website><link>http://www.tvguide.com/news/moments-mad-men-ron-burgundy-1045457.aspx</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:15:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:43:26+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwh7kf</id><link>http://www.tvguide.com/news/moments-mad-men-ron-burgundy-1045457.aspx#comment-480997285</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hrbfg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>