<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m09bt7/update/2012-04-02T01:01:08/6ea11b436cf8f6aef5ac52c5c53363934a3afddd70fef1c1981ff74cf1bae568</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This incident had nothing to do with race.  Z would have called in any unknown person inside of a gated community which has been the target of numerous robberies and burglaries.
You article shows you are operating on preconceived notions and trying to make the facts fit that flawed notion.
-  A gated community is not public space.  It is private property restricted to the residents and their guests.  (By the way, 49% of the residents are white and the ret are various minorities)
-  Black communities expressing outrage over police "inaction"?  NO.  They want CHARGES filed but I bet not one has read the Florida statute that requires police to have probable cause which includes ruling out the possibility of self-defense.  Since they cannot (yet) rule out that possibility, they have no probably cause.
- "...  the violent policing of those bodies by other citizens, as in the Trayvon Martin slaying."  All evidence to date indicates M attacked Z and Z responded in self-defense.  But you Bleeding hearts don´t want to believe that.
- "...when George Zimmerman approached Trayvon Martin ..."  Where did you come up with this whopper?  How do you know who approached who?  Cite your source, please.
- "..not because of any aggressive or illegal Act .."  Again, how do you know this? Cite your source.


I do thank you, though, for showing to me just what sort of mentality runs rampant at The Nation.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hvrv5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q2aj</id></website><link>http://www.thenation.com/article/167085/what-its-be-problem</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T15:28:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T05:01:08+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m09bt7</id><link>http://www.thenation.com/article/167085/what-its-be-problem#comment-483291987</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cx3rt</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>