<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw70q3/post/2012-03-30T15:40:10</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7p43</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l0p0c</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>While I'm not ruling out the possibility that the stressor in George Zimmerman's life (Loss of jobs, domineering father probably disappointed in him, ex-fiancee filed restrainign order) have  a point where Zimmerman was actively looking to MURDER someone, as many serial killers who shares his profile do (white, male, age 30s, loss job/wife macho loner), I think what was far likelier is this:

Zimmermand is a sad and desperate cop-wannabe, he did go looking for trouble that night, maybe he's seen too many episode of Cops or whatever, but this loser, he had been fantasizing for some time now, that he could personally take down one of the thugs who have been breaking into his neighbourhood - something that both made him powerless and appeal to his police Itch.

He needs to do it, be /the one/ who take the thug, he needs a thug to exist, and when night after night, in his van, with his gun, he fails to find and catch a criminal, he made one out of a kid who was just innocently walking along.


..but he's still guilty.  Making in your mind a thug out of an innocent kid because you couldn't find a real criminal is still murder, as much as deluding yourself into thinking she said yes because you couldn't find a real woman who really said yes is still rape.  Even if the crime in question wasn't your GOAL, you planned the Act and did it.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hlb5t</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ewhe</id></website><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/trayvon-martin/trayvon-martin-george-zimmermans-story-may-not-hold-up-to-scrutiny.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T12:43:40+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:40:10+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw70q3</id><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/trayvon-martin/trayvon-martin-george-zimmermans-story-may-not-hold-up-to-scrutiny.php#comment-481116093</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zywb0</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>