<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3n9sk/post/2012-03-29T13:08:19</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34zhn</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lqq1r</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> "Is this the level of intelligence of members of our Government?"

Unfortunately, that may be the case. Remember Chris Lee? Up &amp; comer, great promise, then puts himself out like a school boy jock in Heat. He knew he had to resign as soon as found out, because he had lost all respectability. Remember the other goofball congressman from east of his district who was having tickle parties in his office with male pages? He, likewise, had to resign because his constituents weren't going to put up with that. We now have one better congresswoman in his former district, and at least, tho' of communist (meaning Democratic) bent, a congresswoman who replaced Chris Lee who understands where her bread is buttered, and is pro-gun (as a commie can be for the time being). Of course, there are  the one's like Pataki who turn on their pro-gun constituents, and Gillibrand similarly. And at the local level in NYS, you can't trust Republican, or Democrat. It's like they are trying to provoke the body politic with outrageous laws which make it illegal to take anything which can be construed as a weapon into any town/county buildings. The whole of the Orleans County (NY) legislature Acts as if they are the be all &amp; end all, having passed this law, and after my appeals, refusing to repeal it. So, they walked the walk. There rhetoric means jack.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h3ua8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rlyt</id></website><link>http://visiontoamerica.org/8947/dem-congressman-goes-hoodie-on-house-floor/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T23:52:33+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:08:19+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3n9sk</id><link>http://visiontoamerica.org/8947/dem-congressman-goes-hoodie-on-house-floor/#comment-479658559</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ya80j</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>