<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7dcr/update/2012-03-30T15:04:50/3c37c607b870bbf35b31e99f3a0717ca0f7e0749760ba15fd5cfe77e59d431a8</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>

"The complete barter system platform is almost
ready. Russia and Germany
are behind its design. China
will support it. It features Russian resources, Chinese funds, German know-how,
and Persian Gulf cooperation. The collection of
participating nations is called the Eastern Alliance. The
system will have a Gold core for its short-term finance features. It has a
couple smaller elements remaining to be put in place before complete. But it
will not be launched until the current US/Anglo system collapses, a process
which is occurring before our feet."


 


The Source has mentioned that he himself was on a specific
task force whose name tells almost all, described by him as the Dollar Kill
Switch. He is tight lipped about it, since personally involved. My usual device
is to inquire further while offering my best guess about its nature. He agreed
that the switch centers on the abandonment of the Petro Dollar payment system.
The sale of crude oil eventually will not be exclusively US$-based, which will
put a stake in the heart of the USDollar and USTBond global demand in support
of the reserve banking system. When pushed that the Saudis were the center of
the kill switch, he didnt respond (which could be interpreted as silent Yes).


 


Germany has been drained of well over $3 trillion in
savings over the last decade, at $300 billion in annual PIGS welfare, which
will be halted. He has mentioned consistently that Netherlands
and Austria
and a few other nations will band together. Their identity will be made known
only after other nations are splintered Off, cast to their fates in an isolated
currency situation, ready for devaluation. He has made a few comments in the
recent past that France
will not be brought along with Netherlands
and Austria.
That decision was made about six to eight months ago, not made public. The
complication there is that Germany
owns 85% of French Govt debt. He has confirmed a few times that the new barter
system platform is the physical manifestation of the Nordic Euro system, its
designers and chief promoters sometimes called The Group. Apologies for not
being a definitive response in update, but the project is not on the public
stage for review, nor revealed much in private circles. The entire platform and
barter system awaits an event for its birth.


 


RUSSIA WILL BECOME A MUCH BIGGER PLAYER IN THE NEXT CHAPTER,
DURING THE NEXT TWO DECADES. RUSSIA
IS TO EMERGE AS THE CENTRAL PLAYER IN A UNITED EURASIA. RUSSIA
IS AT THE CENTER OF EVERY MAJOR MULTI-NATIONAL PROJECT AND MOST CONSORTIUM
GROUPS. SEVERAL KEY MOVEMENTS PLANNED BY THE UNITED STATES HAVE RUSSIA
IN A KEY OPPOSITION ROLE. AMERICAN DOCTRINES ARE BEING DISCARDED AND DISPOSED,
FOLLOWING HEATED FRICTION ON NUMEROUS FRONTS. EUROPE WILL
LOOK EAST, NOT WEST, AS THE FINANCIAL IMPLOSION CONTINUES ON COURSE.


 


Here is a direct quote related to the battles. He wrote, "I doubt
very much that the major Western banks have any Gold left at all. They are
tapping deep sources like at the Bank of England
and Swiss banks. However, some of them hold Gold bullion for clients.
CommerzBank of Germany is the continental precious metal bank in Europe like
HSBC is in Asia. In 24 to 36 months, there will be no
bank left trading and/or holding precious metals. They are being wiped out. As
for the arrival of [the replacement monetary and trade system], it is very
complex to explain. The banks cannot be destroyed overnight without having a
plan B, well along in implementation, ready in place to take over. There is a
self-cleansing component that will kick in while the demolition will be
controlled. The Boyz know that they are finished. What you are witnessing is
the tail end of a dying system. That is all I can say."


Willie


</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zqiaw</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/finance/financialcrisis/9173668/Why-a-Brics-built-bank-to-rival-the-IMF-is-doomed-to-fail.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:07:20+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:04:50+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7dcr</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/finance/financialcrisis/9173668/Why-a-Brics-built-bank-to-rival-the-IMF-is-doomed-to-fail.html#comment-481080503</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8eluo</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>