<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpqhdb/update/2012-03-21T18:42:32/17fdd3a275eea86bc07583b478aed26550f08a73d409c324c34233c3af9b860e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpv8df</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/aeh7a</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Gypski, I don't need to get a permission slip from a doctor to justify my marijuana use, which is likely to be more frequent and heavier than most medical marijuana patients.  I have been driving on the West Coast, including Washington, over 14,000 miles over eight years, and I have been pulled over exactly once, for a Burnt headlight, and despite smelling like freshly trimmed weed and having NORML stickers on my beat-up Jeep, he gave me a warning and sent me on my way.  I just don't believe the risk of getting that blood draw increases post I-502.

Find me the current Washington State medical marijuana patient who meets all these criteria:
* Driven in the state over a year
* Been pulled over by a cop
* Been suspected of impairment
* Failed a sobriety test
* Was taken in for a blood draw
* The blood draw came in at &gt;5ng/mL
* The suspect was acquitted of DUID in court.

...because that's the person who is at risk under I-502.  You mention the patient show can only afford a public defender... well, how does that patient escape a DUID at &gt;5ng/mL with a public defender?  Please, show me the case!  100,000 patients, 13 years of medical marijuana, and nobody can find me that 5ng/mL driver acquitted of DUID?

I'll take you up on the challenge if you can provide me a fair counter.  For instance, if I-502 passes, I'll make sure my ng/mL are above 5ng and drive the length of every freeway in the state and visit the city Hall of your five largest cities over the course of a year.  In exchange, if I-502 fails, you find me 10,000 patients willing to drop their medical recommendations and carry around an ounce in their pockets at all times next year.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6d0ftx</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/h98u</id></website><link>http://www.tokeofthetown.com/2012/03/marijuana_duis_went_up_76_in_nevada_with_per_se_li.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T19:30:18+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-21T22:42:32+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpqhdb</id><link>http://www.tokeofthetown.com/2012/03/marijuana_duis_went_up_76_in_nevada_with_per_se_li.php#comment-472875718</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8ayri</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>