<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwi4wr/update/2012-03-31T08:34:54/a7e2262fb95239d0c265f5868727f3647266e6b10b7aa47f539c957cd25de0b3</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Nancy Pelosi is tolerated because she has big titts! lets face it and that is all the little boys in congress and the white house see- 

next if you can get past that then we can  discuss Trevon-
Notice that the city is well integrated, blacks in every position-
today from the top  down  it is black- black , black  black-
reperations, quotas, looking the other way  at hate crimes, setting
people on fire, killing for sport , beatings at county fairs, etc-
every white had their story of being beaten and nothing came of it -
yet......

White are now called crackers - well then i call them niggers it is the same thing so no one says a thing! 

The
man who killed or was killed or who provoked and is it a justifiable
homicide or and unlawful killing are ideas and determinations that are
of no matter or even understood in there distinctions- just hate and
justifing it from congressmen to the president to the attorney general
looking the other way on the Bounty of the New Black Panther Party-

It is
clear we have on parade not blacks protesting - but hate mongers
manipulating the last vestige of blacks that missed the boat  of the 
Luther revelution- the welfare baby the slacker, the manipulator, the
Cry baby the poor me that  love to make a living out of  the garb of it
is all the other guys fault! 

What we see  is
angry demaders who should be booted out on their own and not feed like
bears at the park- they then become dangerous and as animals- be
careful not to feed the bears they will attack- keep your window rolled
up!

Mr Manion</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zxusd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rrah</id></website><link>http://cnsnews.com/node/529377</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:26:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T12:34:54+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwi4wr</id><link>http://cnsnews.com/node/529377#comment-481794419</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/3q0v</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>