<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ftpw/update/2012-03-29T16:52:28/d2dcf7dfd60234d4a4c32864302bd4ce78a2058ee6acd0902900ff8702a7eac2</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>My name is Thubten Namdrol and I am a Tibetan now living in Australia. I am from the Kham region of Tibet, which the Chinese communist rezoned and mapped it into Chinese Sichuan province, thus the common mistake of referring that region of Tibet as western China. I escaped from my hometown after my father was executed by the Chinese on trumped up charges of subversion and demonstrating against the state. Even though we all knew him not to be involved at all that day, we had no say and my dear father and 18 others were executed within three days of the event that took place. During that time our home was  three times and everything was destroyed and smashed without explanation. After my father was murdered by the communist army police, they came to us and said that they will be sending us to retrain us in patriotism for china because our father had influenced us. That night, even with our town crawling with PLA, my mother put a small sack of food and told me to escape, I did and went to India, I was sixteen at the time. Since then both my sister and mother have disappeared and I have given up a long time ago for any hope of them alive. 
When I tell my story to The Chinese students that come to Uni to pretend study, most of them say I am lying and not to make up story, because for them what happen to us Tibetans is like a story, they have no idea what really happens in Tibet. Even Chinese that take holiday, simply go to designated safe Spots, stay in chinese hotel in Lhasa and then leave with a good impression. They then go back and say OH Tibet liberated now so happy because of CCP. But the real story remains. 
When I read this report, my mind flashbacks to the time of teenager and the murder that happened in my town, truly thank you for this information, tears are even now in my eyes. The past month of this life has been most upsetting for me as I get news from my uncle about many of our people being taken away and more and more dying strangely, even the CCP is getting cunning now on how they get rid of us Tibetans, before they had a pretend communitst court, but now, just the army with order to smash. For example: an excellent famous tibetan singer in our town was caught on camera  for our Lama to come back, the Chinese arrest him and found his lama photo, they took one of his eyes out and cut his tongue out, destroyed everything he owns and took his wife and kid somewhere, where?
Most upseting in this world is those chinese that call us lies and making story, Tibetans are happy they say, really, look at them what they wrote in comments underneath in this section, they have no heart, no compassion. Many of them joking about Tibetans Burning and being killed by Chinese, they are the ones who know what is happen in Tibet now. Some of them confused but still taking CCP side, they are the brainwashed with propaganda but don't know what is happen in Tibet, they are taught Tibet was liberated and now paradise because of China, all this lies but what can I do, they are ignorant of truth situation. 
Now as a free educated Tibetan in my pursuit of Masters, the Chinese try to superior to me but they fail, when approached they Always say: during some dynasty Tibet belong to China. That is a lie, Tibet never belong to china, during the Dynasty of many emperors of China in history both Tibet and China have invaded each other, including MOngol. During Qing, Tibet was a tribute state for Emperor of China, that is all, just like Turkey, Burma, Nepal etc...we only had 200 Han chinese in Tibet, it is in records that ccp try to destroy. To those chinese who talk of Dynasty, I say: where is the Qing Emperor, bring him back because Tibet was free of Chinese during any Chinese Emperor reign, now? It is hell on earth. We are full of the worst Han, the most desperate Han. Time for them to leave our land and stop destroying it. We don't want roads and railways to China, no thank you, they are for Chinese not for us. 
Dear reporter. thank you from my deep heart for this report that show the world what is happening in Tibet, Thank you.
People and supporters of Tibet, Never give up and stand tall above the Chinese invaders and army, they are people but they have no heart. 
Bhod ranzen thop par shok
Lha gyal lo
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z604w</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/opinion/ghitis-tibetan-protests/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T12:26:08+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:52:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ftpw</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/opinion/ghitis-tibetan-protests/index.html#comment-479880070</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/goj0e</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>