<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m38ssb/update/2012-03-28T18:04:59/b8d009055bae1723f54cdf57c26f693083590aedc8bdf6d0d1f1c38526bdabee</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I am concearned that companies such as EDF who are currently trying to build yet another nuclear at Hinkley Point and other sites around Britain will offer a great deal on their energy prices to this campaign. Giving themselves greater validation for the need for this nasty; destructive and extremely harmful form of energy.
 
Plus the energy companies  offer the best deal to entice customers to them, then shortly afterwards put up their prices higher than other companies. Further more they all reduce their prives in spring summer when consumption is lowest(ie. no Heating on and greater length of daylight), then hike their prices really high once autum/winter comes when they all know our consumption is highest(Heating and increased nighttime periods). 

Maybe 38 degrees would be better  concentrating on pushing politicians into making businesses turn  all un-necessary energy consumption at night time, when people are not purchasing products they so love to display. And councils to shut down all un-necessary energy in their buildings and park and rides, which seem to be lite up like christmas trees at night time.Councils also need to invest in a lighting system that works on a security light basis, with sensors that light up 2 or 3 lamp-posts when they sense the movement of people or vehicles. But will switch Off again when no movement is detected after 60/120 seconds.

Because reducing consumption on a mass scale will reduce the need for these so called safe; clean nuclear power plants; it would also reduce the price we all pay as a whole as the need for energy is so called priced on an as needed basis(the more we need the greater the cost.  
    </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yh4raa</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/egca</id></website><link>http://blog.38degrees.org.uk/2012/02/07/the-big-switch-q-a/</link><postedTime>2012-02-06T23:25:51+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T22:04:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m38ssb</id><link>http://blog.38degrees.org.uk/2012/02/07/the-big-switch-q-a/#comment-478826518</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-06</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>