<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpdq2f/update/2012-03-21T10:16:48/a324c4571ecc1e7f42d909dc60c6d7cb87ef481a461153c94a5b11b1d06f56e2</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Yes, I saw the Keith Allen ‘interview’ on Channel 4.
I have been a member of the BNP since 2004 (before that I was with the National Front), and have been through all manner of attempts to slander, scandalise, ridicule, silence or suppress the legitimate and well-founded views of the British National Party (I’ve even had my e-mail account trashed; my mobile phone number scrambled and closed down (by Virgin Mobile); I’ve been prevented by my local public libraries (run by the local council) from accessing the BNP Web site on their Internet computers, and have even been blacklisted by the on-line news media and Face Book and barred from posting any comments—not because I have committed some sort of heinous crime, like push drugs, traffic people, molest children, robbed a bank or flown a jumbo jet into a skyscraper, but simply because I have a difference of opinion), but after watching the puerile and amateur attempts of the alleged ‘comedian’ Keith Allen to humiliate and embarrass Nick Griffin in the above television program, I feel I have no choice but to retaliate to this latest and spiteful attempt by the Marxist Left to denigrate and insult someone with a perfectly legitimate and valid opposite opinion (an opposite opinion that is held, I might add, by millions of indigenous British people here in the UK—but who are too frightened of the Marxist Left bullies to stand up and say so).
The very first thing that struck me immediately (and remained with me throughout the whole broadcast) was how the interviewer and the program format itself, slavishly followed the same old predictable routine of confrontational hostility (in fact, this approach has become a major hallmark of interviewing technique with the Marxist Left for quite some time now).  I don’t know about the rest of you, but I really am tired of seeing and hearing this sort of insolent approach to someone—anyone—who has a valid critical opinion of the lawless, fear-ridden and degenerate society the Marxist Left have forced every indigenous person in Britain to submit to and accept.
This sort of interviewing template has become so common and so predictable that it has actually become a hackneyed interviewing cliché (you know what’s coming before it happens—the institutional prejudice of the Leftist BBC proved that back in 2009 when Nick Griffin appeared on Question Time) and it is because of this that such interviews are not only predictable in their content and approach, but tiresome to watch and boring to listen to as well.  But what these ‘interviews’ also illustrate is the prejudice, the discrimination and the frightening depth and degree of the stranglehold the Marxist Left now have on our alleged ‘free speech’; our radio and television broadcasts; our publishing media, and even on the minds of the population.  British people were once free to speak their minds openly and without fear on any subject they wish, but now they live in fear of upsetting the Marxist Left in case they are bullied, pilloried, victimised, persecuted or even prosecuted.  This is how ‘free’ we have become in Britain now!
Before proceeding further, let me introduce a disclaimer here: for the benefit of the Marxist Left and all those who hate hearing the truth (and all those who would bully and insult anyone and everyone who seeks to speak the truth—including those who read and scrutinise everything on our Website in order to try and find someone to prosecute), there are things happening in our society that the indigenous people of Britain don’t agree with (and never have agreed with) but are being forced by threat of law or victimisation to accept or at least keep silent about; things that need to be said if only for the sake of the safety and welfare of the people and the safety and security of the realm—and it’s about time someone stood up and said them!  Therefore, everything that follows in this posting is not necessarily the official or general view of the BNP, or of the Web master of the BNP Web site, or of any of its party members.  The following views, comments, opinions and observations are exclusively my views and observations and mine alone (the principle I invoke is this: as long as I don’t tell lies about anyone, or slander or dishonour the good name and character of an innocent person, then I will say whatever I please in whatever way I please in my own country), so if you don’t want to hear the truth about the kind of Britain we are living in, then don’t read this posting; better still, leave this Web site now!
First of all, I am very angry with Nick Griffin, not because of his performance in the actual interview (Nick’s performance was okay), but because he actually allocated some of his valuable time to a scruffy Marxist anal dysfunctionary like Allen to interview him.  Personally, I would not have given Allen the time of day, let alone an interview, until he had at least smartened himself up a bit and made himself a little more presentable.  Apart from the fact that Allen had an atrocious dress sense and a limited vocabulary, he was also in desperate need of a good wash and a shave (he has to be the scruffiest looking interviewer I have ever seen).  Allen’s persona was even worse!  The character and demeanour Allen projected was about as pleasant and palatable as drinking a pint of tubercular phlegm!  Allen was typical of the great unwashed Marxist street bully now at large in our society.  I would also have arranged to have an independent video recording made of the entire interview (recorded by our own BNP technicians) in case of any ‘politically correct’ editing or ‘accidental’ omissions of the main points of contention brought out during the interview.
Lefty Alan, replete with obscene language, insults, puerile schoolyard graphics, scurrilous remarks and, for some strange reason known only to himself, clutching a silly little ukulele throughout the whole program (at one point I thought he was going to break into a George Formby routine), Allen displayed the very attitudes he accuses Nick Griffin and the Far Right of having, but then Allen (like all good Marxists anal dysfunctionaries) was too stupid to realise this.  It goes without saying that in ‘politically correct’ Marxist Britain today, if Nick Griffin had been a black or mixed race sodomite with multiple ‘partners’ fathering illegitimate children and championing ‘politically correct’ Leftist views he would be in Westminster by now along with all the other Leftist Anglophobic quislings.
Lefty Allen promised the viewers at the start of the program to conduct a ‘fair’ interview without insult, barracking or  anyone down (is Allen trying to be funny?).  Allen didn’t  anyone down, but he certainly reneged on the other salient aspects of his promise (once again, what else can you expect from a good Marxist anal dysfunctionary?).  His amateur schoolyard efforts to ‘interview’ Nick Griffin did nothing to vindicate his claim of being ‘fair’ and ‘unbiased’ or even ‘tolerant’.  In actual fact, as the program progressed, Allen was (of course) the exact opposite: instead of allowing Nick Griffin to express his views without any hostility or interjection, Allen went out of his way to be confrontational in almost everything Nick said.  Not only that, but I happen to know for a fact that many of the major salient and pertinent points Nick brought out in the original interview were deliberately edited out (deleted) from the final cut by the Channel 4 program producers (for ‘politically correct’ reasons you understand) before being broadcast.  That’s why I would have arranged to have our own BNP recording of the interview made.  Even the Cannel 4 camera crew seem to be going out of their way to find the most unflattering camera angle of Nick Griffin as the interview progressed.
Allen (a convicted criminal, a drunkard, a serial fornicator and father of several children by different women) even let his equally brainless and malicious daughter (who looks like a mongrelised individual with no genuine Anglo Saxon identity—and was perhaps conceived and born out of wedlock as well in order to reflect Allen’s politically correct Marxist Leftist morals) stick her twopenn’orth in by ‘composing’ some sort of a silly schoolyard ‘song’ she had allegedly written.  This monotonous ‘song’ (a tuneless rant would be a better description) had no sense of musical melody or synchronised rhyme, clumsy syncopation and, yes, you’ve guessed it, verbal insults, obscene language and anti-BNP rhetoric (like father, like daughter, eh?).  Well, there’s nothing like keeping Marxist anal dysfunctionaries all in the family is there?!  This is an example of good old-fashioned Marxist ‘fairness’, Marxist ‘equality’ and Marxist ‘tolerance’ in action.  It would appear that the only practical function that Allen and his ‘daughter’ (and all those like Allen) have is to convert oxygen into carbon dioxide.  If this had been Communist Soviet Russia, Nick Griffin and everyone in the BNP would have been rounded up and packed  to a Gulag in Siberia for ‘re-education’ years ago (in fact, there have been many in the Marxist Left who have actually gone on record as recommending that all BNP members should be rounded up and shot in the back of the head).  I daresay it will come to this in the end.  God, where the hell do these two-faced hypocrites come from?
Unknown to himself, Allen betrayed his Marxist Leftist credentials right from the very start: he came out with the usual ‘politically correct’ Diarrhoea of platitudes and phrases now so familiar to all of us and inserted the customary ‘politically correct’ caveats and provisos required of every interviewer if they are to have their interview broadcast on national television: ‘politically correct’ caveats like ‘tiny minority’ (this despicable caveat is now so common and nauseous to listen to you will never see or hear an interview dealing with crime and terrorism in the UK without it; it is forever being invoked and used to excuse the alarming spread of armed black criminal gangs on our streets; to excuse Muslim terrorism in the UK; to minimise the massive influx of organised crime from Eastern Europe; and even to justify—or at least camouflage—the presence and growing menace of militant Islam in Britain and Europe).  Yet another caveat often heard is ‘celebrate our rich diversity’ (this daft and wholly offensive phrase is used to justify the lawless multicultural sewer of crime, terrorism and fear the Marxist Left have forced the British people to accept over the decades without their consent).  In actual fact, you can Spot a Marxist Socialist immediately from their use of these daft politically correct phrases they parrot.
Keith Allen displayed and defended these exact same attitudes and hostility in his interview.  You have to understand, dear reader, that ‘fair’ and ‘unbiased’ interviews dealing with politically incorrect subject matter do not exist in the UK.  All information and imagery you see on television (which is the biggest and most far- influential ‘politically correct’ brainwashing tool in existence today) are all strictly controlled, scrutinised and vetted for its ‘political correctness’ before being released for public consumption.  A major part of this deliberately engineered brainwashing control is to brand the truth about many social and religious ills as ‘racist’, ‘offensive’, ‘fascist’ and ‘phobic’.  Consequently, simply speaking the truth on many social and religious issues is now openly branded a ‘hate crime’ (in politically correct Britain you can be prosecuted and sent to jail for speaking the truth—much like the Middle Ages where it was a capital offence to read or even possess a copy of the Bible).  This is why the Marxist Left are trying so desperately to get a stranglehold on the freedom of the Internet.  The Internet is the last bastion of free speech left.  Once the freedom of the Internet goes, your free speech is gone forever.
You may have also noticed that for all the years the British National Party, the National Front, the English Defence League, and all the other right-wing movements have been going, no one has ever stood up and accused any of them of telling lies!  This is because these organisations have not told any lies about anyone or anything, they have only told the truth!  We have centuries-old laws protecting people from malicious lies, slander and libel, so why haven’t these groups been prosecuted if what they are saying is untrue?  So, to get round this predicament, the Marxist Left came up with an idea: the way to stop people telling the truth about all the negative aspects of their ‘social engineering’ program is to outlaw the truth and brand the truth a ‘hate crime’.  What was it the great political and social seer George Orwell once said?  “In a time of universal deceit, telling the truth is a revolutionary .”  I don’t know about the rest of you, but I rather like being a revolutionary!
Free speech in Britain is a Marxist myth, peddled by the Marxist Left in order to keep the unthinking population of Britain intellectually anesthetised and submissive to Leftist views (more on this later).  The reason for this is simple: Britain is in a ‘politically correct’ Leftist straightjacket (and has been for quite some time) where only ‘politically correct’ Leftist views are allowed.  Anything outside of that is either ridiculed, insulted, condemned, suppressed or even prosecuted—in most cases all five.
In case you hadn’t noticed, traditional free speech and the right to freedom of expression has been quietly and covertly destroyed in Britain (Enoch Powell found that out to his cost back in 1968); they have been expunged from our politics and social thinking and supplanted by compulsory ‘political correctness’ and consequently, do not exist anymore (except in the BNP—much to the fury of the Marxist Left who are continually trying to suppress it under the hypocritical façade of United Against Fascism).  Today, you are only allowed ‘politically correct’ views and ‘politically correct’ free speech (which isn’t real free speech at all, but simply a compulsory parroting of Marxist ‘politically correct’ phraseology designed to make people feel good about themselves and at the same time deny their own racial and cultural identity).
Compulsory ‘political correctness’ has four major effects on the individual person: the compulsory suppression of your traditional right to free speech; the strangulation of your own logic and common sense; the compulsory denial of all the negative aspects the Marxist Left have inflicted on Britain and its people over the decades; and perhaps the most sinister aspect of all, the fear compulsory ‘political correctness’ generates if anyone dares to question it or oppose it.  If you don’t want to lose your job or be passed over for promotion, or be insulted, harassed, bullied, victimised or persecuted, then you must become a ‘politically correct’ automaton (anything outside of that and you’ve got trouble on your hands).  There is no room in the politically correct world of the Marxist Left for free thinkers, critics or honest, real-world observations (in the same way there is no room in the BNP for the politically correct brigade).  If you want to be a ‘politically correct’ automaton, then be one, but don’t force others to be one if they don’t want it.
What Keith Allen proved in his ‘interview’ (if he proved anything at all) was that he is typical of the unwashed Marxist socialist bully that people have to contend with in Britain today.  You will all have to reconcile yourselves to the fact that there is no such thing in ‘politically correct’ Marxist Britain as a ‘fair’ and ‘unbiased’ approach when dealing with opponents and critics of this oppressive and wholly suffocating destructive system of procrustean socialism (a system of socialism that completely wrecked communist soviet Russia and is now in the process of completely wrecking Britain, Europe, America and the rest of the western world).
In the world of the politically correct bully, you are told what to think; told what to believe and even told what you should see!  Just like a ‘politically correct’ Dalek that goes around patrolling and monitoring its slaves, screeching its bullying orders in that caustic, grating computerised voice: ‘Obey!...Obey!...Obey!...We command you to obey!  Or you will be exterminated!’ You can thank the Marxist Left for this situation—and all those nitwits who keep voting them into office all the time.  They have systematically taken over and now control the whole of the news and broadcasting media in Britain, Europe, America and everywhere else where political correctness has a foothold.  They even control our educational systems as well (in fact, it all began in our universities and colleges back in the 1950s where it then percolated down into our politics, our communications media and social thinking).  Even with our own children today, we have to literally debrief them when they come home from school and rip out all the ‘politically correct’ wiring that has been ‘engineered’ into their thinking during their classroom studies.  This has to be done if our children are to keep a firm tight grip on their own national identity, pride, culture and patriotism.  If you want to see a fair and unbiased interview on any subject, you have to watch foreign programs like RT.com
As the closing credits of the Keith Allen program were rolling, there was a semi-literate young man struggling to express his views to Allen’s cameraman.  This was a deliberately engineered ploy by the Allen program makers to suggest that this is the sort of semi-literate moron who supports the BNP and the far right in Britain.  But this backfired on Allen and his program cronies because what this imagery showed was the horrendous damage the Marxist Left educational system has done to our young people in Britain today.  Official statistics reveal that in 1959 the proportion of young people leaving school who couldn’t read or write properly was 3 in every 1000.  In the mid-1960s the Marxist Left began to abolish and dismantle our Grammar Schools and Secondary Modern Schools, and replaced them with the Leftist sausage machine of the ‘Comprehensive System’, at which point the British educational system began to rapidly disintegrate at an alarming rate.  Today, in the ‘politically correct’ world of the Marxist Left, the proportion of young people leaving school who can’t read or write properly has plummeted to a scandalous and shocking 3 in 7!  That means that in less than four decades, our traditional educational standards have been virtually wiped out by the Marxist Left—all in the name of politically correct ‘equality’.  And it’s getting worse with every passing year!  Now that our young folk are all ‘equally’ illiterate, where do they go from here?  Welfare benefits, that’s where!  This is what the Marxist Left has done to our young people and to our educational system.  The Marxist Left have destroyed the future and sense of self-respect of Britain’s youth by making them dependant on welfare benefits for their survival because no one is going to employ someone who is illiterate or even semi-literate.  Today, youngsters leave school clutching qualifications and diplomas they can’t even read.  Employers are continually complaining to Job Centres about the appalling level of illiteracy among young school leavers.
It never ceases to amaze me how far the Marxist Left will go to suppress the voice of the indigenous British people and ridicule and insult its critics and legitimate opponents.  If the BNP really are as bad as the Marxist Left say they are, then what are the Marxist Left so afraid of?  Surely, if the BNP really are that bad then no one will vote for them!  And if that is the case, then why did the British people elect Nick Griffin as an MEP?  It really is like being back in school again watching the schoolyard bully and his gang of like-minded thugs bullying and persecuting anyone who is not like them.  For those of you who have been bullied at school you will immediately recognise the symptoms.
Also, if you have often wondered about the reason for this hostile attitude, the answer is simple and right there in front of your nose: the Marxist Left have no logical or sensible counter-argument to present, so all they can do is ridicule, insult, threaten, and  down anyone who doesn’t agree with them and then outlaw the truth.  The Marxist Left have created a world where traditional values have been turned on their head: i.e. the truth is a lie and the lie is the truth.
We in the BNP refuse to kow-tow to this Marxist dictatorship or toe the ‘politically correct’ line.  We don’t care about being persecuted.  If we are being persecuted and hounded by the Marxist Left, then we must be doing something right!  Our own history has shown that for the past two thousand years the British have had to fight to secure their freedoms and fight those who want to take them away from us.  Today, Britain is awash with those who fear and hate the truth.  Today, Britain is awash with those who fear and hate the British indigenous people—including the Leftist politicians we keep voting into office.  You don’t think so?  Then just listen to this:  In April 2009 (and unbeknown to the British people) over 122 MPs at Westminster (including Labour, Conservative and Lib-Dem MPs) signed a clandestine declaration affirming that there was no such thing as an ‘indigenous’ people of Britain!  The reason for this is that the Marxist agenda in Britain is to deliberately destroy the indigenous status of the people and replace it with a multicultural and multiracial zoo.  The idea being that anyone coming to Britain has the ‘right’ to stay in Britain and be a British citizen regardless of who he is or what he is or where he has come from.
Where, you may ask, did this ‘right’ come from?  It came from the Leftist politicians themselves who sowed the seeds for this social catastrophe just after the Second World War, and to support their ‘social engineering’ policy they draw upon the ancient demographic history of Britain to sponsor and maintain this ‘right’.  This wicked policy is, of course, an absolute godsend not only to international criminals and terrorist, but to militant Islam, who see this as a golden opportunity to invade and occupy Britain and Europe through mass immigration, asylum and burgeoning birth rates without having to fire a single shot!
Thus, the political and socialist thinking now emanating from our political elite in Westminster is that the white ‘indigenous’ people of Britain does not exist and that consequently, have no legal recognition and no ancestral, moral, or patriotic right or claim to their own country, and that anyone who can get to the shores of Britain can become a ‘British’ citizen merely through the simple expedience of coming here!  This insidious and evil declaration drawn up by these Marxist politicians is not only a bare-faced lie, but it also flies in the face of scientific historical evidence of the mitochondrial DNA of the British people, and is still further positive proof that the trusting British electorate have been naively voting into office a succession of politicians secretly bent on the racial and cultural destruction of the British people through the tool of mass immigration and multiculturalism—all in the name of ‘political correctness’, ‘human rights’ and ‘diversity’.
And remember this fellow patriots: The truth will  prevail in any dictatorship as long as there are strong and patriotic individuals who are willing to stand up and defend it, and fight the militant bullies who want to suppress it, and as long as we are a legitimate party we will continue to tell the truth about any issue, regardless of who it ‘offends’.  This has  been the backbone of our political ideals and policies and Always will be.  Those who run and hide at the first sign of trouble are not the kind of people we in the BNP want to attract.  There is no room or place in the BNP for paper patriots or fine-weather patriots.  Militant Muslims living in the UK (and at taxpayers expense) tell us there’s a war coming; a war that will overthrow the British ‘kuffaar’ and turn Britain into an Islamic republic.  They are right!  There is a war coming!  But it won’t be to turn Britain into an Islamic republic, it will be a war to jettison Islam from Britain altogether.  And if the Marxist Left physically assault you, then you can invoke the universally recognised common-law right of self-defence and retaliate—regardless of what the secular law says!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ycyozk</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/y81i</id></website><link>http://www.bnp.org.uk/feedback/website</link><postedTime>2012-01-23T14:05:16+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-21T14:16:48+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpdq2f</id><link>http://www.bnp.org.uk/feedback/website#comment-472369993</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zggfa</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-01-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>