<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6z7k/update/2012-03-30T11:26:16/6540854e6bc77928e7a9f00c52a60a3f7a121c2a5a680ab7fd63891d0b5fd37e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I am not a RIM user, but I feel really sorry for RIM, I really do.  I have watched this great company declining for years even when their sales number was saying otherwise because I saw the competition coming.  They did very little to fend Off them, now they got nothing but wind in their faces and sand in their eyes.  For RIM to make a come back, they need to have 2 things done quickly.  1) an easy use, trouble free, hassle free smooth OS (no rebootings every time you install apps, or freezes over).  2) a beautifully designed all touch screen phone, or at least one with a side slide keyboard.  I know some of your keyboard lovers will say that you are buying BBs because of the keyboard.  Well, if RIM doesn't come up with some cool touch screens phones with larger screen, there will be no RIM after a few more years.  I loved physical keyboard, my first smart phone years ago was a Samsung Blackjack running windows mobile 6.1.  As soon as I mastered the typing on a touch screen, I never looked back.  It is just some much easier, quicker and less stress on your fingers.  Not only that, my eyes are thanking me because of the larger screen.   No more bullshit music services, no more gimmicky Porsche Design repacked old phones.  RIM should make the new touch screen design as their focal point for the coming hardware development, make their already perfected keyboard based design as a additional addons to the collection, kind like what HTC is doing, instead of the other way around.  Then apply their new polished and revamped OS to the design, maybe that will save RIM.  Otherwise, I just don't see them survive. Remember Nokia, the platform is Burning, however with RIM it's Burning in both hardware and OS departments.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67gunh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/y2ru</id></website><link>http://www.engadget.com/2012/03/30/rim-sticking-with-consumer-goods-just-refocusing-on-enterpris/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T14:31:02+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:26:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6z7k</id><link>http://www.engadget.com/2012/03/30/rim-sticking-with-consumer-goods-just-refocusing-on-enterpris/#comment-480855451</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ebqtx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>