<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp4fpa/update/2012-03-21T18:09:13/29845e82a573354bf7c2c46c9fc47cf50dd5a2f875ac1b2163521de8c40ac245</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>DEAR PARENTS: if you want people to be understanding of your kid screaming and crying during a flight, YOU have to be understanding that it's obnoxious and painful for everyone else of the flight and not throw a fit over dirty looks and sarcastic comments! IT GOES BOTH WAYS PEOPLE!!!!

Gotta say shitty parents with screaming kids on flights has been a major pet peeve of mine since I flew alone for the first time when I was 16 and experienced the Flight From Hell. It was a Red-eye from Oregon to New York. I was sitting by the window and there were a set of parents with their baby next to me. Baby started screaming before we even took  and the mom ended up demanding fairly early on that I turn  my reading light, refrain from making any noise or getting up, and not look in her direction because she was going to breastfeed the baby to calm it down. It would only take 30 minutes, she said. The problem is that the baby didn't want to breastfeed, didn't want to calm down, and continued to scream for the ENTIRE trans-continental flight, but every time I made a noise/wanted to get up/motioned to turn on the reading light I would get the deathglare treatment from the parents for disturbing the baby. I understand that sometimes babies throw uncontrollable screaming fits, but it would've been nice if the parents would have eventually apologized to me for the inconvenience and told me it was okay to get up/make a noise/turn on the light. GAH it still makes me angry thinking about that flight!*

*Not the baby's/parents' fault, but that flight was extra hellish because I had been sleeping on the floor of my grandparents' unairconditioned, cuckoo-clock filled house during a heatwave before I got on that flight so I had gone three days with minimal, shitty sleep. And the Batteries for my CD player ran out, and the extras I brought were duds. I was seriously hallucinating and involuntarily weeping by the end of that flight.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y8cfm</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/c8h7</id></website><link>http://www.stfuparentsblog.com/post/19695102286</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T21:24:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-21T22:09:13+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp4fpa</id><link>http://www.stfuparentsblog.com/post/19695102286#comment-472845349</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>