<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39l2e/post/2012-03-29T17:32:04</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The facts seem to be quite clear, if a person can see, hear, read, and think for themselves.
 
Zimmerman was not authorized to carry a gun as a neighborhood watch captain.  But he did, and called police for the 47th time in a year, he described the Martin Kid as a black male, then muttered a vile racist term, then he pulled out his 9mm weapon and pursued the kid despite the instructions not to do so by the police dispatcher.  Then Zimmerman caught up with with the kid, neighbors heard a young boy scream, then a pistol shot and the screaming stopped, then Zimmerman was observed standing over the body with his drawn pistol in his hand. Facts ? Yes !
 
The racist Sanford police responded, saw the boy was African American, and released Zimmerman with no investigation, no forensics for gun fire residue test, no questions, and no excuse for the shooting, other than to say he felt threatened by a boy weighing more than a hundred pounds less. 
 
The facts are clear, but the evidence is sketchy, except for the witness statements that verify that Zimmerman killed the boy in Cold blood.
 
Racism is alive and well in America, but it is Always denied most loudly by the racist themselves, and the tendency toward racism is evident in the Republican party.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zq6hj</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnm3</id></website><link>http://www.sacbee.com/2012/03/29/4375839/trayvon-martin.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:43:50+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T21:32:04+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39l2e</id><link>http://www.sacbee.com/2012/03/29/4375839/trayvon-martin.html#comment-479919174</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/czbn1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>