<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkopqz/update/2012-03-26T15:43:41/7c4977c80f60a843bd80e2fa8b7b36583340a0feff5e09f9ae639ec5778c2c9c</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mko28r</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6pqg3</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>That does not mean that we can not speculate in a non-conclusory way. That is simply the method that anyone seeking to understand the truth would use. But sure, we wait for the evidence to be gathered. Here is what I speculate:

Zimmerman is afraid of "hoods" invading his neighborhood so like a good member of the NRA, he packs Heat as he drives the neighborhood looking for suspicious hooded black men, of any age. Question: Did the local police know that Zimmerman packed Heat? On the night in question, he came upon Trayvon who fit the description (a hooded young black man, or "coon" as they are called in Florida law enforcement) of what the dilligent and probably paranoid Zimmerman was on the look out for. He called 911 and reported that he was following Trayvon. He was told to not follow him. Meanwhile, Trayvon reported to his girl friend on his cell phone that he was being followed by someone, who was driving slow and staring him down (not a good sign in the hood). Trayvon was scared, and so was his girl friend who told him to run. Then what happened? The 240 lb Zimmerman, gets out of his truck, armed, confronts the 140 lb Trayvon and demands to know what he is doing. From Trayvon's perspective: Zimmerman has a gun, he is Acting menacing. His gun is not concealed. Before he was stalking, now he is out of his truck in his face with a gun talking mean. Trayvon must have felt (justifiably)  that his life was in grave danger. Then perhaps he tried to "defend" himself. He had no gun, so he scraped with the bigger man. Of course the gun never left the 240 lb shooter's control and he pointed it at the victim's chest and fired.

If the shooter was on the sidewalk confronting the victim with an "unconcealed" weapon, that is, brandishing a weapon and demanding to know what the victim was doing there in a hostile tone, that sounds like the crime of assault to me. Even before the shooting, that is assault by Zimmerman. Afterwards, he probably did not intend to shoot, but they scuffled and Trayvon maybe put up a good fight (for his life) so Zimmerman felt like he was justified to shoot. To me, with those facts, that is involuntary manslaughter. But of course we can draw no conclusions until all the evidence is gathered, though without all the publicity that may have never happened. And sadly, now, after the case was so badly messed up by the local police, much of the evidence has been compromised or lost, including the contents of the shooter's house, his computer, and who knows what else that he was given the opportunity to clean up after he finished his night's work of defending the neigborhood from hoods.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l2wet</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tz1k</id></website><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/george-will-on-trayvon-martin-case-when-everyone-got-on-high-horses-about-duke-lacrosse-they-were-wrong/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:04:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T19:43:41+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkopqz</id><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/george-will-on-trayvon-martin-case-when-everyone-got-on-high-horses-about-duke-lacrosse-they-were-wrong/#comment-476675978</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dt9db</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>