<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/236286/post/124312667/comment/329815040</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>#165 DANIELLE, NY  Thank you, now I do not have to do the work on looking htgnis like that up  .you seem to have better records than most anybody ..it is nice of you to share your information and work with us ..we do appreciate it.#167 MODERATOR we know you cannot work 24/7, and it was a weekend morning to boot, I bet you just missed it and I bet a  once in a life time  thing like this would never cross your mind at our zoo.  Thankfully we got to see it, Rita Petita got photos of it, and we would love to find somebody with the sound on in their video camera who also captured it .we are not sure that Rita can replicate the sounds.#172 PANDAFAN-NORTH  The thing that I feel most when seeing Princess Lin Ping and Prince Fluffy-Butt nurse is the reminder that they are still babies.  Her size may be one of the reasons, plus like in the case of Fu Long getting to occupy a section of the exhibit with his mom to about or just over 2 yrs of age .there is no room in the Panda Castle for a large male, growing daughter (or son), and mom too.  Thankfully we could keep up to 6 (including a nursing mother) or 5 adult Pandas.  Not all zoos have that option, especialy in parts of the world that have been occupied by larger, longer civilizations than we.  I think it was one of the reasons we got to keep our two girls until the younger was 3 ..earthquake made for no room there, and we had room.  Not all zoos have the room to grow.  I was at our Wildl Animal Park the week it opened, and was  amazed when it grew, and grew, and grew.  If I am not mistaken it could still grow and not use up the piece of land it has.  It is Too hot for Pandas, but it means other warm weather animals could be transfered, to make more room for pandas.Thank you for sending the link I enjoyed it.#173 LINDA LUVS PANDAS  It is not yet known if nurturing past the 6th or 7th month is needed, the bears to seem to just know htgnis.  Case in point Gao Gao was rescued, injuried and malnurished at an unknown age, but less than a year old for sure.  Bai Yun was born in captivity (a daughter of the Great Pan Pan-wild/and a captive bred mother), and was removed at 7 months old to the care of the nannykeepers.  That pair alone has produced 4 cubs.  Bai\'s daughter with Shi Shi already has doubled that number of cubs, Bai has birthed and raised 5 successfully, and Hua Mei just had her 8th cub this season.  The best news is that both Shi Shi and Gao Gao were wild born, helping to make the gene pool deeper, or wider -whatever is appropriate.  This information was gathered by reading the blogs, and comments.  The unknown status was part of an answer fromt he staff, nannykeepers, or the moderator.  None of us can know what is  right , some think that rescuing Shi Shi and Gao Gao is the wrong thing to do, but it sure has brighted up htgnis here in San Diego.#178  LUCILLA  nobody, but nobody could so quickly get a look at Prince Fluffy-Butt\'s diary than you.  Did you hack his computer or what????  Well I don\'t care how you come by such important information  thank you for sharing it with us. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:236286:124312667</id><idPostId>124312667</idPostId><idBlogId>236286</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:236286</id><idBlogId>236286</idBlogId><link>http://titties.dk</link><displayName>titties.dk | blog om patter</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://titties.dk/weekendmusik-rammstein-mein-land</link><displayName>Weekendmusik: Rammstein - Mein Land</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T08:14:29.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:236286:124312667:329815040</id><link>http://titties.dk/weekendmusik-rammstein-mein-land#IDComment329815040</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T08:14:29.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Weekendmusik: Rammstein - Mein Land by Pedro</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>0001f762b58d00add60a8fba53a0185e</idEmailMd5><displayName>Pedro</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>Pedro commented on &lt;a href="http://titties.dk/weekendmusik-rammstein-mein-land"&gt;Weekendmusik: Rammstein - Mein Land&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>