<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6403/post/2012-03-30T11:32:01</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwyxlh</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7akx</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>"
If someone would do something, who do you propose it be?  We are the only ones.  The UN can only talk about it, all of Europe has the combined strength of the Texas National Guard, and the rest of the Middle East has neither the interest, nor the capability, to do anything."

Ok... first Off... that's a bit "superior" of you to say....
Second.. other's have just about as much ability to "do something" as we do, but choose not to, because they don't have to. We are already "doing it" for everyone. and third.. Have you taken a look at the most recent list of countries by economic power? News flash: The USA is not top of the list. In fact, there are a few countries who are a bit further up the list than us, and you want to take any guesses about where they are at? I'll make it easy.. google will you give you the answer, there is a wiki page for quick reference, and Forbes just released a detailed account of it all in February 2012. 

Point being... There are a few countries with the capability of handling this situation, and who would have a stronger vested interest in doing so than us. If push came to shove, then they would probably have to step up. But I guess who wants to spend their own wealth in dealing with a Headache when the US will come do it for you for free!  

And before you say "we are the only ones with the military superiority to handle this".... 
That also is not true, though it could be argued that we have some of the best military to deal with it, it is far from the "only" that could deal with it. That still does not explain the financial end... It is bad enough we are giving our lives, but to add insult to injury, we are also footing the bill. Why are we, half way across the ocean, more concerned with what is going on over there than their own neighboring countries are? If they really viewed it as a threat, then they would fear the threat spreading.  This argument could continue on and on,   but I think everyone is already dead set in their opinions and nothing, no matter how logical, will change it.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67a8ht</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/world/asia/afghanistan-police-attack/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T10:35:30+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:32:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6403</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/world/asia/afghanistan-police-attack/index.html#comment-480861357</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7akx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>