<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkx1gi/update/2012-03-26T07:46:29/027d4ea15d5e077f1ae552c0c8d3d92213165b55ae025a6a7be98149f6fb722e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkqk3u</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8f1zf</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> I don't observe the reflection of those death throes in the corridors of power; rather, a stiffening of Resolve, even to the extent of the demonisation of secularists expressed by Baroness Warsi, Ratzinger (as applauded by 'athiest' Nick Clegg), the Bishop of Oxford, and so on. 

Correct me if I'm wrong, but what the CofE seem to be saying is "&lt;i&gt;For our own selfish advantage, we are going to abuse millions of innocent, trusting children (intellectually, at least) and there is nothing you can do about it because we have the Government generally under our control and have the support of all three main parties. What's more, you taxpayers are going to pay for it. Who says there is no God haha! Some secularists do? Then all secularists are damned and deserve to suffer the worst punishment our sadistic minds can imagine. Sadly, these days, Burning must be postponed until the after-life, but what is such a short delay compared with the eternity of suffering? In this life, we will condemn them to a lifetime of exasperation via our 'focused expert communications arm' propaganda machine. Our intention is that they will die knowing that they have failed. As Gove says, once we are academies, the secularists will not be able to touch us. Indeed, once we have established our strategic partnerships, nobody will be able to touch us.&lt;/i&gt;"

(This despite modern knowledge and the realisation that God is really neither controlling the climate nor feeding all non-sinners.)</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y0we4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/educationnews/9160498/Religious-education-undermined-by-Coalition-reforms.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T06:08:14+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T11:46:29+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkx1gi</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/educationnews/9160498/Religious-education-undermined-by-Coalition-reforms.html#comment-476342418</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/asltd</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>