<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwudl9/update/2012-03-30T22:39:24/0a91c417c8f1f1d098ee4f2960ed32e99775da6d258191f67087a264fdc43ea2</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwbq5n</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/58znt</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Craig could be back as soon as 5 days into the season if they backdate his DL stint, which they can do if he starts the year on the DL. I read today that Skip resumed some baseball activity, stretching stuff with the rest of the team. 

I don't see the pressure on MCarp. He's backing corner IF and can do the same in the OF, while the guys coming  the DL are primarily outfielders. The pressure is on Robinson and Komatsu, IMO. A lot will  on how the bench guys do when games start to count. These questions often have a tendency to answer themselves. 

Everybody on the team (to whom it matters) has options except Greene. Skip is out, but he's got more than 5 year's service time now and cannot be sent out without his consent. If he withholds it, the only thing the team can do is release him or keep him on the roster.

Rule 5 guys can be put on the DL, and that was done (I think) with Brian Barden in 2009, even though he wasn't really hurt. But it's dicey to do that... fraudulent, actually... and could cause some trouble if someone was to object.

If the Cards want to take Komatsu Off the 25-man roster, he has to be immediately offered back to the Nats for half the price the club paid for him... $25K. If they don't want him back, then he has to go through the waiver process... where every other team has a shot at signing him before the Cards could go after him, presumably, to put him in 3A. I also read that the same is true (waivers) if the club want to make some kind of deal/trade with the Nats. 

So keeping him will be awfully tough, but not impossible. If the team was to have a poor year and fell out of contention... not as much of a problem to tie up one roster Spot. But if as we expect, the team is in the mix for post-season, it's harder to do that.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/677g9a</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lz6q</id></website><link>http://stlouis.cardinals.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120330%26content_id=27755094%26vkey=news_stl%26c_id=stl</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:57:31+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T02:39:24+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwudl9</id><link>http://stlouis.cardinals.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120330%26content_id=27755094%26vkey=news_stl%26c_id=stl#comment-481454090</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/csz4h</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>