<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kmzx/update/2012-03-29T22:12:11/729b0ae57a277bcc5bedc96d6fe42c2370b41767fa6915fada20746a9e51822b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3j739</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cmout</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>This has turned into a 'gloating contest' and You are actually a part of it observing your post. You've passed  judgement on something you know no more about than anyone else sitting here. 

If you've never lost someone in the 'twinkling of an eye' especially a child ;

You know nothing about how that person handles such and it isn't being the center of attention on an hourly basis. That person "99.9999%" of the time;goes into a deep depression. It is called "Shock" and what follows are the steps and stages of mourning.
It's better known as the stages of grief!

Shock is the first stage of Numbness, disbelief and unreality.Denial is thoughts or words such as, "I don't believe it -- It can't be!"Bargaining involves making promises such as, "I'll be so good if only I can 
awaken to find this hasn't happened" or "I'll do all the right things if 
only..."Guilt is a hard stage and difficult to deal with alone. This is a normal 
feeling characterized by statements such as, "If only I had ... If only I had 
not..." done or said or thought something. Guilt may ultimately be Resolved by 
understanding that all of us are human beings who give the best and worst of 
ourselves to others. What they do with what we give is their responsibility.Anger is another very difficult phase, but it may seem necessary in order 
to face reality and get beyond the loss. We all must heal in our own way and 
anger is a normal stage along the way. However, you may feel guilty because you 
are angry at the person who died or because your life is continuing while his or 
hers is not. If you don't feel anger, don't manufacture it!Depression may come and go and be different each time in length and/or 
intensity. Give yourself time to heal.Resignation means you finally believe the reality of the death.Acceptance and Hope come when you finally understand that you will never be 
the same, but you can go on to have meaning and purpose in your life.

These stages can take literally "years" to work through.

And since I've walked that path; I feel that family has and is being used and it is simply a crying shame.
And it is sickening.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zat8d</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dndz</id></website><link>http://www.macon.com/2012/03/29/1965685/this-is-viewpoints-for-thursday.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T04:03:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:12:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kmzx</id><link>http://www.macon.com/2012/03/29/1965685/this-is-viewpoints-for-thursday.html#comment-480146493</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8p5hp</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>