<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/136753/post/26057847/comment/329958373</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>was usury debt collection Hengyang City People\'s Procuratorate accused, Zhang Jian, the business partner of the defendant Luciano spring in order to attract investment to the grounds of its borrowings, Luciano spring to find a loan-sharking Fu Jianwei Zhang Jianbing borrowers. In January 2009, by Luciano spring guarantees, Zhang Jian Fu Zhang Loans 1.35 million yuan, the monthly interest rate of 12%. After Zhang Jian, no repayment of principal and interest,louis vuitton sunglasses, Fu Jianwei Zhang Jianbing will be to find Luciano spring for money in the debt collection process, to take to limit the personal freedom of Luciano spring means to compel him to pay back the money, Lu was forced back to Fu, Zhang 1.73 million yuan in cash and his son under the name of a facade and they live in housing arrived to Fu. Fu, not give up, continue to force LU to pay back the money. In July 2010, Luciano spring in his office to write a suicide note. In August the same year,coach outlet store, Fujian Wei once again to Luciano spring dun. The next day, Fu Jianwei car and the Zhang Jianbing with to Luciano spring downstairs, To Lu downstairs. Bring Luciano spring loaded an imitation of Tiananmen-style pistol, a dagger, a bottle of petrol bag, ready to die with Fu. When the car driving to the Hengyang City Development Zone, Baiyun, Zhang Jianbing Fu Jianwei To Luciano spring Yexia Luciano spring afraid to be Zhang Jianbing head open on a shot, Fu Jianwei heard gunshots,coach outlet online,  for help in the the revolver process, Fujian Wei escaped from the car, Luciano spring and then committed suicide with a dagger, and the Burning car. Forensic identification, Zhang Jianbing in line with the head being shot intracranial injury deaths. Focus of debate Recently, Hengyang City Intermediate People\'s Court public hearing of the case. Up to three half-hour trial, the prosecution and the defense around first as collateral for the loan sharks after being dun and shot the arson-murder defendant Luciano spring constitute the focus of intentional homicide,coach outlet, a fierce debate. Hunan Province, Hengyang City, the new Development Zone, Ferrari shoes, Baiyun, with the result of economic disputes caused gunmen kill arson scene, resulting in one person was killed and two others injured, an -road vehicles were Burned this case - 8 months ago in the Hengyang local once aroused widespread concern in society. handling the case of language Lu defense lawyer for Luciano spring made the defense of self-defense. The defense counsel argues that Fu Jianwei such as several of Luciano spring and their families to take a means of intimidation, restriction of personal freedom to compel repayment, under the particular circumstances at that time, Fu Jianwei, who resorted to violent means of coercion Luciano spring repay their alleged  of robbery, Luciano spring for self-preservation to take defensive, their actions constitute self-defense or gone too far. The defense lawyers also presented to the court a certificate of honor over the years by Luciano spring and write 119 people signed a petition the court to leniently dealt with the petition. trial witnessed location: Hengyang City Intermediate People\'s Court halfway recess to participate in the gallery, some people gather together to talk. Some people usurers detest sympathy for Lu suffered; some people think that Lu as adults, should know the consequences of borrowing to usury, breach of the law, they should be severely punished by law. April 12 in the courtroom, the Luciano spring mood has been very stable, the face is not too expression do not see any fluctuations. But when you hear the prosecutor accused arrested for murder, destruction of property, shoes, Lu slightly excited, raised his voice, resolutely denied. Finally, after two rounds of intense court debate, the Full Court that the case is significant, and will choose a sentencing date. is intentional homicide, or self-defense the the trial ended, Hengyang City Intermediate People\'s Court judge said in an interview, our law clearly stipulates that the civil lending rates four times higher than the bank lending rate, store, not protected by law. However, in the economic and social part of the enterprise to solve the funding problem, at a loan shark in the face of high interest rates, borrowers tend to go bankrupt, more harm than good. Encounter illegal detention of sharks and even the threat of violence, victims are often not taken as a legitimate means to protect their interests, so that the market for usury. To this end, the judge in the face of unlawful infringement, we must choose the legal means to Safeguard their legitimate rights and interests. the face of more than 10 copies of the evidence presented by the Public Prosecution Service, Luciano spring justify the need for development of the company and Zhang Jian, in the repayment of the Chapter in order to fulfill the obligations of the Guarantor, total repayment to the Fujian Wei has 384 million yuan (including its corporate borrowers to 1.2 million, own 530 000, his son under the name of the facade of the market value of 1.63 million, the housing market value 480 000), the outstanding debt has been repaid in full, the two sides dispute has been end, there is no intentional homicide motives. this year, 49-year-old Luciano spring, Hunan Heng room incident before the Department of Real Estate Operation Corporation Vice Chairman and the League of Nations, Hengyang City Real Estate Development Co., Ltd. General Manager. newspaper Hengyang, April 15 &amp;#30456;&amp;#20851;&amp;#30340;&amp;#20027;&amp;#39064;&amp;#25991;&amp;#31456;&amp;#65306; 7&amp;#23681;&amp;#22899;&amp;#20799;&amp;#30097;&amp;#22240;&amp;#25298;&amp;#32477;&amp;#29238;&amp;#20146;&amp;#34892;&amp;#31363;&amp;#35201;&amp;#27714;&amp;#34987;&amp;#24320;&amp;#27700;&amp;#28107;&amp;#28907;(&amp;#32452;&amp;#22270;) High school students playing basketball was hacked to death continued Each side The Wenchuan men traveled thousands of miles to fi </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:136753:26057847</id><idPostId>26057847</idPostId><idBlogId>136753</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:136753</id><idBlogId>136753</idBlogId><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com</link><displayName>HOCKEYCENTRIC</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-canucks-are-more-than-one-line-and-luongo/</link><displayName>The Canucks Are More Than One Line And Luongo</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T13:18:02.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:136753:26057847:329958373</id><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-canucks-are-more-than-one-line-and-luongo/#IDComment329958373</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T13:18:02.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The Canucks Are More Than One Line And Luongo by nhuiy5k8</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://www.cheapoakleysunglasses-sale.org/</link><idEmailMd5>665562fef382046cad167337c1b4773f</idEmailMd5><displayName>nhuiy5k8</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://www.cheapoakleysunglasses-sale.org/"&gt;nhuiy5k8&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-canucks-are-more-than-one-line-and-luongo/"&gt;The Canucks Are More Than One Line And Luongo&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>