<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwv3yw/post/2012-03-30T16:24:43</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7iko</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hz2lk</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>""Anecdotal claims" LOL!

"I repeat:

"The more you think, the dumber you get""

In other words "I have no proof and I'm hoping pretending this is obviously true will suffice". Nice try, but no.

"Your still an idiot!"

Yes, I'm going to take you seriously when you still don't know the difference between "your" (as in belonging to) and "you're" (as in contraction of "you are"). 

"You seem to be arguing against the "4" original race groups, and if so, who are the rest; where do they come from, and more importantly, how do you know this."

I'm arguing against your ridiculous claim that Mesopotamians are Black. Old_Geezer has already covered this.

"Actually, Google (Wikipedia) only list "Neanderthal" for extended information."

You made a false claim; it's your own fault if you don't know how to verify it or how to do a comprehensive search.

""You truly are an "IMBECILE", and I mean that from the top and bottom of my heart!"

Gosh, that hurts. I Always take to heart the opinions of lying fools on the internet, especially when they try to mock me ("google is your friend") only to have it backfire on them (your inability to actually properly use a search engine). 

"6). Wow, you really are a retard.

"Correlation does not equal causation""

I'll take that to mean you have no response and are hoping your attempts at insulting me will suffice. You also don't seem to know what "correlation" means, or that entire sentence, really. 

"You do realize the interbreeding occurred 45,000 and 80,000 years ago, so the fact that it's "close" is quite telling."

Still can't read, I see. 

""Again, beauty is in the eye of the beholder".

Hope this helps your inability to "reason properly"."

Repeating an idiom I already told you makes no sense here doesn't help with anything, unless your goal is to remind me that you're too stupid to understand most of what you say, in which case you've been immensely successful!

Here's a quick list of other things you don't understand:

What "fact" means.
What "theory" means.
The difference between "fact" and "theory".
Why "your" and "you're" are not interchangeable.
That your opinion is not a fact.
That anecdotal evidence is not a fact.
What "correlation does not equal causation" means and how it applies.
How quotation marks work (hint: to actually quote someone).
How search engines and seeking out credible sources works.
Basic grammar and spelling.
How to properly interpret facts.
What "beauty" means.

Whew! I'd be here all night if I were to try and type out a comprehensive list.

"A "pure" race of people is a rarity."

I notice you skipped most of the questions, so I'm going to take those as concessions. The point is anyone mixed with non-Africans has a good chance of possessing those genomes. 

"Your truly a complete retard, no doubt about it. I've already told on at least "6" occasions; "The Journal of Science""

So you've claimed, but haven't presented it. I've googled this claim myself, and come up with nothing. Not a single article I've found reporting on this result has this figure, and I've looked at at least ten. Why is that?
You also haven't answered the question about credible sources; if the figure is 16%, why did you use one that said otherwise?

"I think this goes without saying by now:

"The more you think, the dumber you get" "

You've repeated that a lot; has your lone brain cell Overheated and gone haywire from trying to do this "thinking" thing, or is it that you're hoping if you say it enough times, it will come true? 

Let's see what you've done here:

- Provided no evidence to back up your claims and tried to cover up that fact by attempting to insult me (and failing miserably, by the way. Being called an idiot by someone like you can only be a good thing, as I would hate to be your idea of intelligent, not that you know what that means).

- Claimed to have used a source you cannot present, which, if it truly says that, is in opposition to your other source, so either way you lack credibility.

- Skipped most questions you had no response to.

So, to conclude, you're still a pathetic liar who is scrambling to cover up the glaring holes in his argument and the lack of proof for it with "insults". All you've succeeded in doing is sounding like a very boring, very desperate broken record and displaying your ignorance in the process.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hqaeg</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ewhe</id></website><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/the-dish/hunger-games-fans-outraged-over-black-characters.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T16:38:37+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T20:24:43+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwv3yw</id><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/the-dish/hunger-games-fans-outraged-over-black-characters.php#comment-481159798</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/amynt</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>