<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwsvjy/post/2012-03-31T10:46:28</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>If we can keep this event from being swept away by outrageous rascist remarks and I'm hearing more of these from some Blacks than others, curtail those who would incite violence and mayhem and soften the rhetoric; just plain let the facts come out on this case, then I believe overall, emotions will die down as we learn exactly what happened.  At this time we do not know.   And to have a group of people, the New Black Panthers putting a  on Zimmerman's head of $1M is tantamount to me, anyway, of Murder for Hire.

Where is the DOJ regarding this?  

However, we will still have those who stubbornly cling to the notion that this was a deliberate  of violence (not self defense) perpetrated by a White (who is really not White but a Hispanic/White) who still wish to live during the Civil War /Civil Rights  and are unwilling to let go of past grievances.  Didn't we pass the Civil Rights Act to remedy these grievances?  At least this country DID something.  When or where have you seen this done anywhere else?  AFRICA?  What a joke.  They are still slaughtering one another (Black on Black).  

And we have Black on Black crimes in Black neighborhoods that are at a Fever pitch with no so-called leaders noticing from the Black community.  

When we have a group of people who will not integrate into a society, who wish to live in the past, spew hate and incite violence because they have not learned to get on with their lives, let the past be just that (the past), a society will not be cohesive or able to work together.If we as a nation of many different races and ethnicities are to prosper, we all must be willing to forgive and forget and prosper together.  Not just one particular group.This is where liberty and freedom come in to play.  For without one or the other, no one will be able to live out their lives, in peace.  I believe many have forgotten this.  And many have sacrificed so that we all have the opportunity to excel or fail.   If we let the violent factions that lie at the underbelly of any country, take hold and cause great harm, then we have really let the barn door open all the way to what lies in store for us and it isn't going to be pretty.So where are the leaders on this issue?  I believe they are slowly speaking out, both Black and White, to stop the rhetoric and let justice unwind.  Maybe we still have a chance to grow, together as ONE NATION UNDER GOD not a bunch of fractured factions who care only for power and crises to seize upon.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67vci4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/8nmh</id></website><link>http://www.clickorlando.com/news/Civil-rights-leaders-condemn-Sharpton-s-call-for-escalated-civil-disobedience/-/1637132/9863196/-/owq31pz/-/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T22:54:07+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T14:46:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwsvjy</id><link>http://www.clickorlando.com/news/Civil-rights-leaders-condemn-Sharpton-s-call-for-escalated-civil-disobedience/-/1637132/9863196/-/owq31pz/-/index.html#comment-481884885</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/euhz1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>