<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkbgwx/update/2012-03-26T08:40:16/d46fe2cf9c9e79d6fe890d9931cb68269c84501dcfcd5278d9ae117df1c90b25</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk4slx</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yv009</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Doc, spring training is such a short time to judge someone.  For starting pitchers they will get 20-25 innings, or 3-4 starts worth.  For hitters, maybe 50 AB's, or about 2 weeks worth.  Hard to judge how a player will perform over a whole season in such a short time frame.  And if you just look at the numbers, you can find most players will have a two week stretch where their numbers are ugly.  So yes, they do look at what they see more than the actual numbers.  For the kids vying for the last rotation Spot, they look for location (are they hitting their Spots), velocity and how well they change speeds, etc.  For hitters, they look at swing mechanics, timing, are they hitting the ball hard, etc.  And often both hitters and pitchers are working on things; a new pitch, going the other way ( a point of emphasis for Inge this spring).  For Below yesterday, his location was Off, and had several hard hit balls, so while the numbers were not all that bad, it was far from a stellar outing.  For fans, this is hard, because we don't see many of the games, so we have to look at the stats.  That is the best way I can explain why Inge is heading north.  His play in the field must look good and he has to be hitting the ball hard (when he actually makes contact).</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rq3f2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lz6q</id></website><link>http://detroit.tigers.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120325%26content_id=27609164%26vkey=news_det%26c_id=det</link><postedTime>2012-03-25T23:13:51+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T12:40:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkbgwx</id><link>http://detroit.tigers.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120325%26content_id=27609164%26vkey=news_det%26c_id=det#comment-476365485</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hsiw2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>