<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjeg5/post/2012-03-26T14:16:25</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk1l7z</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lkgm1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>You trying to out-moralize me?

My Cherokee ancestors were told that if they became Christian, if they learned English and if they lived in peace like the Englishman, then we would be accepted in their society. The Five Civilized Tribes did just that. They were model citizens of the United States. 

Then, your husband's ancestors talked Southern Christians into &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;ethically cleansing&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; the Five Civilized tribes so their slave trading ships could fill up the South with black slaves from Africa. Your husband's ancestors became greedy filthy rich trading in the souls of men, women and children.  

Only when the British navy halted the trans-Atlantic slave trade did your husband's ancestors turn on the people they sold the slaves to and started the Civil War. The very same Civil War you say your ancestors fought and died for trying to free the black slaves your husband's ancestors had imported for greedy profit. 

BTW, in WW1, your husband's ancestors sold your ancestors down the drain with the Balfour Declaration, promising Britain that they would get America men to Bleed and die for Britain, if Britain would have their men Bleed and die to invade Palestine for the Jews.

In WW2, FDR was so cozy with the world's worst genocidal maniac ever, Joseph Stalin, supported by your husband's ancestors, that Japan became violently alarmed we were supplying Stalin with weapons of destruction, which in turn Stalin was using against Japan's attempt to keep Communist atrocities out of Asia..

As for my ancestors, they were sent Off on a &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;death march&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; we call the Trail of Tears to a &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;government concentration camp&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; we called Oklahoma.  I was born and raised in Oklahoma.

I would say that Jews have not been good friends at all to the Indians. Obviously, you are willing to "bury the hatchet".</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rira9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rlyt</id></website><link>http://visiontoamerica.org/8899/santorum-romney-worst-republican-to-face-obama/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T11:34:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:16:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjeg5</id><link>http://visiontoamerica.org/8899/santorum-romney-worst-republican-to-face-obama/#comment-476599000</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/layza</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>