<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msbkah/update/2012-03-28T00:17:36/2b21785b6dd83288db46220161a33824ce7179d2d84dcca665ce8d73ce21ee80</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms65te</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l5pal</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> I think the thrust of this article was largely looking at the 7 million younger Americans who are not going to school at all, rather than the harder to follow value of a non-technical degree.  

I could be entirely wrong, but it would seem to me that the MAJORITY of those who are not going to college/not finishing high school don't value pursuing a liberal arts degree for the breadth of 'mind-sight' that it offers.  Obviously, there are many reasons why a person might not finish high school or go to college, but I think it is safe to say that a majority of people in this category do not have a lot of interest in pursuing a degree in philosophy, nor would have the interest/ability in/to transform(ing) that education into a marketable skill.

For example, the image of the starving artist/philosopher most likely does not hold a lot of appeal to most of the people in this category.  At least, not as much appeal as making some money and being able to support their families without thinking about how they are going to afford the next meal.

Some people are passionate enough about an art or an idea, that suffering financially is more than worth it, as long as they are able to do what they feel passionate about.  Most people obtain more utility from making enough money to be comfortable and reduce financial strain.

And from this perspective, any medium that provides marketable skills to those who would not be able to otherwise go to a regular university is an excellent solution.

It Burns the government's/economy's problem on both ends of the candle, so to speak, by removing people who statistically and historically are lower wage earners (thus requiring more welfare) and turning these individuals into people who are increasing GDP, taxes, and filling and creating jobs.  Wealth is being added to the population through a value-added concept of producing things demanded by people world-wide.  This created wealth can be distributed to the lower number of people who now need it.

To clarify my personal bias:
I am a student at a private university majoring in Finance and Economics.   I would be majoring in Philosophy and Sociology, but I was pushed to  a formal education in an area that I would find a (hopefully) definite demand.  It is my opinion that much of a liberal arts education can be Gained through reading outside your course materials.  If liberal arts is your passion, then you will still have plenty of time to read and discover after your engineering/finance/nursing/law homework and studying is done.

This is not to say that a formal liberal arts education is of no value.  My brother was a Philosophy major and is now a highly successful estimator at a residential construction firm.  But often the pursuit of such a degree is not the safest or most realistic option for a person. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lbqcw</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/eyjq</id></website><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/business/archive/2012/03/whats-more-expensive-than-college-not-going-to-college/255073/</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T13:42:07+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T04:17:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msbkah</id><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/business/archive/2012/03/whats-more-expensive-than-college-not-going-to-college/255073/#comment-478077601</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ry764</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>