<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwwqtp/post/2012-03-31T12:41:50</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw3d79</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lvnc0</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>to save time I'm just going to roll both of your comments into one. 

as a child you don't need a loophole to receive a lessened punishment. he's 13, so there is an absolute zero chance he'll be charged as an adult, and if you contest that if he were black that he would be, point out one 13 year old currently in an adult penitentiary. And if you're still pissy about that story possibly not going national, I suggest you look up the murders of Channon Christian and Christopher Newsom. ever hear of them?as for the white kid with the Coke: was it his first offense? if so it's a pretty good defense to state that "it was a mistake he'll never make again, he's got a support structure and blah blah blah". it works pretty much all the time. it's the repeat offense that you get fucked on. all in all I don't understand what you're trying to get at with this hearsay.


as for the "all drugs are made from illegal drugs": no. they aren't. hell, the only drugs actually used in meth is Cold medicine and it isn't even CLOSE to illegal. herbal weed? made from chemicals extracted from legal herbs. Salvia? under state regulation. in some states its legal, others not. Mephedrone(bath salts)? made from synthesized compounds which are all perfectly legal. prescription drugs? regulated. which is why you need permission(prescriptions) to used them. 


as for the catholic priests bit: you know that race does not dictate religion correct? the catholic church is made up of a variety of races, including African Americans, and the catholic clergy is the group who protected their priests from legal retribution.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67bd97</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/u6cr</id></website><link>http://www.worldstarhiphop.com/videos/video.php?v=wshh4ztHC3lOQj6Jd7A3</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:59:55+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T16:41:50+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwwqtp</id><link>http://www.worldstarhiphop.com/videos/video.php?v=wshh4ztHC3lOQj6Jd7A3#comment-481981745</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zl8v6</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>