<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gqbdjs/update/2011-10-15T05:50:31/4ea2bca36dcfebabc4563fa4c7a952f4ea8927f3c78fe05838dfc81b0bd9c558</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Thank Wu very much.. This is PRECISELY why I love PetaPixel and is my top 3 daily reads. Seriously. - I am very well aware this is the longest response ON THE PLANET TO DATE. But, knowing that is first step to healing a warped mind!

My response is 5000% for newbs. So, the other 12 million of you, don't read further! :)

There are no droids here - move on... 

I know it's long, and I am sorry. - but, if one thing I say can ring a bell for a newb. So please don't flame me or try to contact me or be nasty. I'm trying to point some things out that maybe someone who just 'happens' across this entry. 

 My response, is unnecessarily VERY long, and provides way too much 
information, but - I don't care.  I'm writing this in hopes that maybe 
it will give a little insight to a new-tog on  a variety of things, and 
some advice in general. I have way TOO much experience with doing freebies because I can't say NO - and it's cost me tons of money and a bit of self respect. But, I know my heart is in the right place, and thank god I have a mate who understands my need to try and do good for our struggling society. (blah blah blah)

First, I've been shooting for over 10+ years and never call myself a professional photographer because of the negative overtones associated with professionals. Alot of pro-togs have over inflated egos and charge so much that the only people who can afford them are the 'elite'. Now, that is NOT a bad thing, but, what IS obnoxious is the attitude and total lack of humility involved. Just because you really are technically or creatively advanced, it doesn't give these types of photographers the right to be jackasses. Yet, again, it's everyone's right to charge what they want, and treat others how you want. But, whatever you toss out there you  get back. Jus' sayin those are the types of people who are going to be annoyed with my response - but, as I said before: THERE ARE NO DROIDS HERE, MOVE ON..

Second, you can still be a nice photographer without being taken advantage of. Just because you are nice - doesn't mean you are a push over or easily guilted into someones sob story. Being nice and being taken advantage of are NOT the same thing. But, unfortunately they go hand in hand. 

Please learn from MY mistakes - PLEASE...

And, as for this response from Jedi Wu, no way Jose' , not even a SINGLE person who asked for freebies read past the: "due to, blah blah". The realized there were no droids here and moved on.. So the point is 5000% LOST.  None of the rest of it matters and the bite that was intended was a mere whisper of a breeze of a thought.

Either be a jerk or don't.


They won't read any of the passive aggressive 'sting', even though it feels so good sending something like that sometimes - especially to the excessive requests or the rude requests or the annoying ones - it's simply not worth the time to even respond with a phuck  - seriously. That even cost you money. Even though we are thinking 400x worse than this NO response could ever have attempted to resemble. 


I am not calling myself a wordsmith or an editor, either,  but - this 'essay' from Mr. Wu, has not been reviewed or edited by anyone other than himself. The beauty of it is that he doesn't obviously give a shit which in itself is refreshing. 

Again, that is totally okay because he is a photographer not a literary genius. However, along with the territory of being a professional photographer - you  in all respects should represent yourself as a professional and this Andy Rooney letter is very far from it so, I wouldn't use this as a template. It is just all over the place and is so passive-passive-agressive-back to neutral-agressive it would confuse even the most intelligent bargain hunters out there if they bothered to get past the: yeah but - NO. I mean the point is NO. But all the other fluff is not necessary, in my opinion, either be a dick or don't. Pick a side already! 

We as adults know EXACTLY what we are doing when we ask for free sheit.. We aren't stupid. However, 99% of the asshats who do ask for free photography only know it as being an expensive luxury that they really do need. Yet somehow we as creatives don't 'deserve' to be paid for our services? Are we all hobbiests and do this just for fun or because we are bored? 

Do people pay for web design? Do people pay for a nice building? Do people sit on furniture that is comfortable (even uncomfortable) -? Someone had to work out a creative process to create and design those things. All those nice folks got paid (some in China) :) some in America, but regardless Photography is the same 'idea' - but it's something you have to create from scratch EVERY SINGLE TIME YOU GET A NEW CLIENT WITH NEW REQUESTS. If you truly love your craft and everything about it - then you will need to do an awesome job free or not.

Unless they at one time were or are at present a photographer, then people  have NO CLUE how much money we have tied up in our gear. They've no CLUE how long it takes to prepare and pack for a shoot, cumulative traveling,  set up and tear down. They have no clue what's involved with the process, the shoot, the editing, the cropping for multiple images. Then, final push of print, delivery of prints and or digital files. They don't 'need' to know either, they just need to be happy with their 'finals'. Whether free or not - 


If you do happen to charge like any NORMAL person out there, then CHARGE ACCORDINGLY. If you think you may be charging too much, for service, fuel, or even prints,  - top it  with another 15%-20% ... If folks scoff a bit, then you have room to go down. Never box yourself in -  leave room to grow and bend and stretch and mature. But don't underestimate yourself if you continually are getting compliments and bookings - you should reevaluate your pricing, then grow a pair and call other photographers and ask for their HONEST opinion on what they think of your work and pricing. But if you suck, then you suck there's no charging for suck - unless you find an idiot.

Even when we aren't working on an actual job, we are still working. (if we take our 'jobs' seriously) Even counting the minutes.. It all ads up to a tremendous amount of time, energy and money. Not to mention there's  marketing and design of our websites, blogs, biz. cards. There's sending tweets, updates on facebook, new images posted on our websites and flickr etc. However, if you can afford it farm it out to someone who is better than you and charge them for it.

Let me get this straight non-paying-client:  you want me to provide you with free photography, free editing, free time, free printing, free paper, free ink, free electricity, my free time I spend either making money on a paying job or spending time with family, friends or my own personal hobbies outside of photography. You want me to travel for free and plan for free and fuel my huge ass Suburban, again that is going to be a minimum of 30$ unless you are a few blocks away. The second I agree to a freebie, it's literally COSTING ME MONEY. - NOT TO MENTION losing the opportunity to recoup if we havent already, the thousands and thousands of dollars put into just the essentials: your rig, lenses, filters, flash, reflectors, tripod, pocket wizards, computer, hard drives, online storage, software. If we do have these things then there is  something to upgrade or repair. 

FREEBIES ARE NEVER FREE, THEY  COST THE ONE PROVIDING SAID FREEBIES. Unless you can afford to GIVE FREE MONEY AWAY TO STRANGERS, or even people you know or organizations you are passionate about then don't do it. At MINIMUM tell them you need 100$ to help pay for fuel costs. (And what are you going to do if you pop a tire out on their remote dirt road? 150$ minimum for a tow and 100$ for a tire. How are you going to change a tire on your truck?) They aren't going to pay for it unless you have it in your contract, and then - good luck collecting EVER if something like that god-forbid should happen to you.

You have to realize that every SINGLE move you make after you made that decision to be a photographer for PROFIT,  affects the amount of green in your pocket. PERIOD. 

Unfortunately, non-profits are the-w.o.r.s.t. PERIOD. I've provided over 8K in free creative work not including about a grand in fuel and coffee. I don't over-price my work and don't charge a 'session' fee or anything like that to paying clients, I charge 75$ - 125$ an hour, dependent upon the shoot plus fuel and 100$ an hour for an assistant + fuel.  with a minimum of 250$, minimum 150$ for the assistant. If there is more than an hour trip time, I charge 30$ an hour drive time and will only travel 4 hours each way (driving) - and won't leave the state.  Editing  on how many images they choose based on straight out of the camera choices. I charge 75$ also for editing every hour 1/2.

And no, I don't purposefully take my time - once I am done with a shoot, I am usually over it and want to get them gone. *yeah, kinda like this post* Your charges are going to vary obviously, but - the fine line and balance is between getting what you deserve and donating yourself right out of your home. 

If my husband didn't work full time, I would have NEVER been able to give a single service away for free, at ALL because of the amount of time that it takes away from the people who pay your bills. 

Paid or not,  give 101% - . As you never know who will see your work - and you need to  have pride no matter how annoyed you are with them or over you are with a non-paying client. Or just over the 'idea' of now being stuck and tied down by this non-payer. Somehow being paid justly for your skills and your services is a great motivator and aid to keep that ball rolling. And a great deterrent for telling said paying clients to pound sand... 


No need to be a douche bag when telling them no - but, you need to be prepared, especially if you live in a small town like I do - that if you are a jackass to someone and are rude or obnoxious, word will be guaranteed to get around and you will lose potential business. But, on the other hand, if you do say YES to the freebie, I guarantee they won't call all their pals and say oh - 'xyz photography' said HELL YES TO MY FREEBIE REQUEST. They are going to give me free prints, free fuel, free time, free creativity, free electricity, and let me put wear and tear on their gear they spent thousands of dollars on. Not to mention if they get a flat tire in their truck on their way here or back they are screwed out of 300$ easily!!! 

I digress:...  You have to keep in mind that every single person and company out there is a potential client, everyone has pets, kids, dogs, a project car, quilts to put on Etsy, models, senior portraits, educational materials and text books, ebay stuff,  family reunions, family portraits, weddings, engagements, food for menus and websites. Everyone who owns a website needs photography. Let me say it again: EVERYONE WHO HAS A WEBSITE OR A BLOG NEEDS PHOTOGRAPHY. If you need practice go do it on your OWN time or do it for family so if you get a paying client in the meantime, you can  put  family and friends. *unless it's a wedding* weddings are the spawn of satan. Next to big corporations and doing commercial shoots weddings are the biggest money makers - and for good reason.. Just DONT DO IT - do yourself a favor, if you have the wedding 'Itch' that needs to be scratched be a second shooter or 3rd shooter if you are super new. You don't want that responsibility. It is a ridiculous amount of time, prep, planning, post production, emails, phone calls, neurotic brides, drunk groomsmen, ovebearing mothers and mother in laws, the obnoxious pocket photographer, Uncle George who is standing 3 feet to your right and now 1/2 your people are looking at you the other half are looking at him and the rest are blinking.. (did you catch my killer math skills?)


Know this:  If you are looking for adoration, appreciation, a thank you card, an 
email saying kiss my ass, you will never get any of that. My thanks has been in the 
form of: We want more sheit for free.. so you really need to go into freebies knowing you won't even possibly be paid with a thanks or even a kick in the ass afterwards. 

The hardest part is to know when to trust your instinct on when it is a MUST to say NO and when it's okay to budge and play with the numbers or do something for free or give a print for free or a couple of small digital images for facebook for free.  The more freebies you do, the cheaper your work becomes.

Let me say it again:  THE MORE FREEBIES, THE CHEAPER YOU ARE. Don't cheapen your  craft no matter what urges you may have. Have someone whose been doing this for years punch you in the face to wake you up!

Unless you can literally afford to take cash out of your pocket or are independently wealthy and want to give money away - then go for it. If you say no, im sorry I can't - you wont go to hell. Even tho knowing Karma is there with a few extra points to balance out your past doesn't hurt.   

Saying no is uncomfortable for a lot of people. But if you say Yes to them - then you will ultimately be saying NO to your house payment or new tire or new lens.

For me,  It would be easier as a parent to say no - or if my husband didn't work. But, I am the luckiest girl on the planet because I don't work anything other than a camera. If I had to live  of my income I made from photography and were divorced, I would be dead.. My gear would have been sold a long time ago.

I have given away and done so much for non-profits, I have freebied myself to a point of no return and I am Burnt out. Being Burnt out is awful because of all the feelings which surround that and that TOO affects your income.  Vicious, perpetuating circle.

Think about yourself FIRST and then everything else will fall in place if it were meant to  be with hard ass work, your own formula, and of course tenacity and humility.

I know I am a partial hypocrite as if I get a request for recovered abused animals looking for adoption, I am a sucker for it and will almost  say yes. So, saying NO Depends on your hearts full or empty gauge.

I also know it's my OWN fault I am Burnt out on  doing the freebies now.  I had noone to turn to and learned the hard way and it hurts falling on your face multiple times. Thank gawd I have a supportive husband I would have to be working a fulltime job outside of the house and would NEVER be able to put in the time I 'need' to. I love photography, yeah - I get Burnt out, but photography is my life. 












































</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/mrvrc1</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/8xvb</id></website><link>http://www.petapixel.com/2011/10/13/how-to-respond-to-requests-for-free-photography/</link><postedTime>2011-10-13T20:57:57+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-10-15T09:50:31+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gqbdjs</id><link>http://www.petapixel.com/2011/10/13/how-to-respond-to-requests-for-free-photography/#comment-335281388</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-10-13</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>