<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3vp7h/post/2012-03-29T09:08:22</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The white people of this country need to stand together and stop this black is  right and innocent. maybe we should Burn a few neighborhoods down to make a point . The blacks do it all the time that's why they get all the media. Just another news story to make money. Whatever happened to reporting facts and not opinions. As for the blacks the slavery day's are over except in Africa and Sudan where blacks enslave blacks, mutilate and rape daily. Don't believe then go see for yourself I've had the opportunity to spend time in those places. All we did was remove the chains and fool ourselves into thinking blacks can be civilized and be a productive part of society. There are more victims created by blacks than any other race. You do this to yourself because you are bred to believe everything should be given to you and nothing earned. You embarrass the hard working blacks world wide who actually want to better themselves. From now on every WHITE should protest, riot, murder and destroy neighborhoods when a black is found innocent or if we don't get our way. As for Sharpton and Jackson haven't you ever notice they never show themselves unless there's an opportunity for riots or protests because that is where the media is. King was a true activist he didn't care about the spotlight and he didn't rely on the media, violence or stupidity of the American blacks to motivate him unlike Sharpton and Jackson. Where are they on a daily basis? living  of the money the naive blacks give them. They do not care anything about you to bad you can't see it. Am I a racist? No I have friends of all colors I consider myself a realist because I have seen the world good and bad, lived with different cultures and races and the worse by far is the American BLACKS who have this belief that everything about them is racism, my suggestion is stop yelling racism, stop the crimes, protest, riots and murders just because you don't get your way. If you want to see how today's blacks  and I'm serious watch a show on Chimps and how they fight and destroy for no reason other than sport I have  buddy of mine laughing and guess what he's pure black except he has a Masters in Psychology and he can't agree more. Again to all the whites it's time to riot, protest and beg for welfare if you want to be equal to the black race who seems to know how to manipulate the media and system. as for equal opportunity stay in school, get an education, stop the gold teeth and thugging and get a real job and life it's hard I know I've been doing it for almost 50 years but it's doable. Be proud of your race don't disgrace it by Acting like marauding chimps. The USA is falling and its because of YOU. BLACKS, WHITES, HISPANIC , Jew Christian or whatever. Time to grow up, Not everyone is and innocent victim, not every kid is good, but this is what happens in reality if the parents are bad examples and can not or will not teach and raise their kids right. So to Treyvons mother, maybe you should have done something to stop his violence, drugs and whatever instead of just saying he's black and that's the way it is and pass the welfare check. I feel no pity for a kid that has had the issues Tryvon had.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zcxr4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T06:16:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:08:22+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3vp7h</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html#comment-479475193</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h0ik3</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>