<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0j127/post/2012-04-02T04:10:35</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0fxxy</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h2k1k</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>The problem is, yazidi, that it has as much common direction as the cabinet/government. I am sure the poor soldiers would love to actually take action when they are in the middle of the stupid situations, but being more professional than the 'armies of gods', they have to follow orders. And the orders come from the mixed bag holding the purse strings. Now, you may say this is not uncommon for an army, but look at the messy mess at the top. Put the blame where it lies. That 'sectarian' batch of incompetent purse-string controllers.
I remember talking to the cousin of a friend in the 'army' back when it had no weapons and Assad was in control, in his small neat room at a pleasantly quiet dormitory overlooking a lovely valley - and he spent his days tending a garden that augmented the food supply, or reading books. On occasion they would gather - like boy scouts - to have a camp-fire on a beach, or to help some community with a small disaster - or to pretend using sticks as guns they were Acting as a cohesive 'force'. But there was no real force - it was a sham. And he laughed at the whole situation, but I could see the sadness he felt in his 'military service'. He read the books to keep his mind alive ... and looked forward to a time he would not need to be 'in service' to have a livable income, although there seemed no other options at that time.
Over 40 years I lost contact, and cannot tell you an ending ... but in my mind I see the place still, and think how pleasant it was there on a warm serene day surrounded by vegetation and a quiet vista. Perfect vacation Spot. In a way, I envy still his 'moments of seclusion'. But I understand his depression too at being there, and the lack of real direction in a life.
These days, the LAF (laugh ??) has equipment ... but even yet, where is the direction? They ARE and want to be professional soldiers of their country, yet are ordered to 'accommodate' that sectarian stupidity which is Lebanon. So they become, more or less, professional mediators between the various factions.
(Although I was happy to see them take on that bunch from the north who came out of the refugee 'camp' to rob banks. The purse-string-holders didn't like that bit I guess.)
That kind of professional 'choice' takes more courage than just shooting at anything that moves or talks. Like the UN peacekeepers in the south, willing to try at least - by being targets too often. And for the most part (unlike the police) most soldiers I have met seem friendly enough in their professional way, and willing to help a citizen - or a tourist too, if any show up.
 Have some feelings for the 'boys' who wish to serve. Direct your shots much higher up the food-chain.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6vr1d5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6594</id></website><link>http://www.yalibnan.com/2012/04/01/unidentified-gunmen-open-fire-on-lebanese-army-in-tripoli/</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T06:53:58+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T08:10:35+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0j127</id><link>http://www.yalibnan.com/2012/04/01/unidentified-gunmen-open-fire-on-lebanese-army-in-tripoli/#comment-483340623</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g5po2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>