<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwquk7/update/2012-03-30T18:48:58/cf283dc77e8a78e958f30c4369744fbd9f9ca06d535414a72338f67f5a6785be</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwen49</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mbm5</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Your lil DNC 'Plantation' has a 90% success rate only because the racist, pro-active DNC will strip the hide Off any bIack folk who dare to leave the DNC .... how extremely racist is that the world wonders?    A real racist lil feather in your fascist lil cap.  

I saw that on Roots (runaways being punished) and it's some sick sh t!!! (and yet you're still runnin' bIack folk down, every day, whenever one decides to actually participate in our nation's cherished TWO PARTY SYSTEM .... the NERVE of some people!).  White people take it for granted that they have a choice at the ballot box.  But thanks to the still immensely racist DNC .... bIack folks still don't .... unbelievable.  One gets ostracized and intimidated and made an example of if they even turn on Fox News, much less preach conservative values.  Values the bIack man used to have back when he got married and stayed married and produced the finest children you ever saw.  Smart, strong, proud and independent.  God I miss those values in the bIack community.  

Rabble Rousers like barack owebamao and al sharpton personify who and how conservative values were snuffed out in the bIack community to pave the way for the white mans' progressive movement that would be so heinous and feared by the American tax payer .... it could ONLY work if they secured and retained 90% of the bIack vote.  How do they manage that after 200 years of intense racism?  Sophisticated indoctrination and more and more free stuff every year.  We know the cesspool that deal with the devil has produced.  It makes me sick!

But anywho .... back to your dumb post.  People who vote for the DNC are generally addicted to drugs and or welfare .... the dregs of society who are desperate for wealth redistribution and lower sentences for felons.

Legal Hispanics are for the GOP .... particularly the small business owners.

Our side consists of patriotic tax payers, your side is the entitlement society hooked on handouts and drugs.

Pug, your political accumen is non existent ... no go Burn the flag, scooter .... you're wasting our time.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zpy1h</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tz1k</id></website><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/hannity-tells-president-obama-to-give-spike-lees-money-back-says-its-the-right-thing-to-do/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T03:33:02+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T22:48:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwquk7</id><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/hannity-tells-president-obama-to-give-spike-lees-money-back-says-its-the-right-thing-to-do/#comment-481287579</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/euu2h</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>