<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3o31b/post/2012-03-29T19:51:54</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>&lt;i&gt; Objectivists who write movie reviews tend to read their own politics 
into movies they like. But here it really does seem to be correct that 
the author intends some kind of left-wing critique of the 
"military-industrial complex." That doesn't mean you shouldn't like the 
movie. But I wish more Objectivists would realize that just as they read
 their own politics into a movie, all the other people who like the 
movie are reading in their politics.  knows this, so 
purposefully makes the movie in a way that people can read in any 
politics they like. So the interest in this movie isn't a result of some
 sudden upsurge of anti-statist sentiment. Much the same can be said, I 
think, of many Objectivists' reaction to Firefly and Serenity.&lt;/i&gt;

This is Spot on. I never agree with Objectivist movie reviews and I am an Objectivist. This movie seemed to me to be a Leftist critique of the "1%".  is dominated by Leftists. 95% of  screenwriters are leftists. The game the Left plays in _everything_ is to hide their true agenda and capture the culture; ie Alinsky (don't Objectivists get this). This movie is _not_ an anti-big-government movie. Just the same as "V for Vandetta" was not a "pro-liberty" film. These are Leftist critiques of their view of the Right (evil, greedy, capitalistic, war-mongering white people, largely white-male-hetosexual-devils, ie 'Avatar'). 

Diana's review is wrong but then every review of movies or TV she's given shows little understanding of this. I have never agreed with her once. And that includes Serenity and Firefly which was typical Wheedon feminist girlie-power nonsense. 

By the way, do Objectivists think that the girlie-power meme is healthy? There was no girlie-power crap in Rand's novels. Her novels glorify male psychological dominance, which in my opinion is in line with the biological reality of the human species. Do Objectivsts not see how Hollywood demonizes males and has done so for the last 20 years? Do you honestly think women need to be "empowered"? My god, what world are you observing? Not this one. 

I loathe girlie-power movies and that includes the piece of crap that was 'Hunger Games'. 

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zh8ni</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cb1y</id></website><link>http://blog.dianahsieh.com/2012/03/hunger-games.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:09:46+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T23:51:54+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3o31b</id><link>http://blog.dianahsieh.com/2012/03/hunger-games.html#comment-480040582</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>