<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/226676/post/127809241/comment/327697781</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>To anyone contemplating paying the household stealth tax: 
 
In January alone, Fine Gael handed over &amp;euro;1.25bn of YOUR money to bondholders in Anglo Irish Bank. This is equal to the amount of new taxes in 2012 that were set out in Budget 2012. So on one day, we paid over all our new taxes to unsecured, unguaranteed bondholders &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;speculative investors&amp;rdquo; as Michael Noonan called them last June. A recent recommendation by economists recommended the gov&amp;#039;t of FG-LAB immediately Axe the bondholder payments. FG refused, arguing that it&amp;#039;s supposedly in our interest to keep paying an unsustainable burden which we don&amp;#039;t owe. Last year, Noonan Burned &amp;euro;5bn and this didn&amp;#039;t upset the ECB or the financial markets. Noonan is too busy capitulating to the illusion that we can continue when clearly we&amp;rsquo;re heading down the path of Greekification. Since the promissory note hasn&amp;#039;t been paid yet, the opportunity exists to ring fence it by a simple means of refusing to use it on Anglo Irish Bank thus giving it back to the ECB. 
 
The guarantees that Ireland had given for the Banks (&amp;euro;200 billion if you add the bad loans) match the order of magnitude of 37% of GDP. This can easily be wiped if FG-LAB do not pay it, in which case they money WILL be there to fund services. The solution: Don&amp;#039;t pay this stealth tax. 
 
 
 </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:226676:127809241</id><idPostId>127809241</idPostId><idBlogId>226676</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:226676</id><idBlogId>226676</idBlogId><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie</link><displayName>BreakingNews.ie</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/lgma-expects-increase-in-household-charge-payments-545513.html</link><displayName>LGMA expects increase in Household Charge payments | BreakingNews.ie</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T09:12:27.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:226676:127809241:327697781</id><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/lgma-expects-increase-in-household-charge-payments-545513.html#IDComment327697781</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T09:12:27.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on LGMA expects increase in Household Charge payments | BreakingNews.ie by Jim</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>7f8dbc2cef5e6bed7c9fc81e1012559e</idEmailMd5><displayName>Jim</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>Jim commented on &lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/lgma-expects-increase-in-household-charge-payments-545513.html"&gt;LGMA expects increase in Household Charge payments | BreakingNews.ie&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>