<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ktp4/update/2012-03-29T22:31:06/aff1fc8fcd6d6f262b345397bbb1c102b0d92985619a20e18cfad21961f27066</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>You know, I  wanted to be a Video Game Tester. And I actually knew it wasn't all fun and games, but this article, this one article, has ruined it for me. I have no interest in being a slave for six months just to be left out in the Cold. Without even being compensated decently.  This is sickening, it truly is, especially that they aren't even allowed to talk about it, what these testers have done is bold, and the moral move. People need to know it isn't fun and games with testing. I think the game testers should really just be treated better overall. I do wonder, if all the game testers just stopped, flat-out stopped and had a riot, what would happen. Certainly some companies would just switch to public testing, but it'd Gain a ton of attention, and allow them to speak their mind, without even having to censor which game company is worse about it than another.  This needs to change, because good game testing can make or break a game. GT's are just as important as the programmers and story writers in my opinion.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zt292</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7d9s</id></website><link>http://games.ign.com/articles/122/1221612p1.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:03:15+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:31:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ktp4</id><link>http://games.ign.com/articles/122/1221612p1.html#comment-480159990</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g19ri</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>