<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3b3e9/post/2012-03-29T14:55:44</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Pageant
Training Course for Femina Miss India 2013, Femina Miss India East 2013 ,
Femina Miss India South 2013, Femina Miss India Maharashtra 2012, Femina Miss
India Uttar Pradesh,I am She 2012/2013, Megamodel 2012/2013 and Gladrags Mrs.
India 2012/2013

Breaking News

The Tiara’s Prachi Mishra
wins Miss Congeniality and Ipsita Pati wins Miss Ravishing at Pantaloons Femina
Miss India 2012. Anvita Sudarshan Trained by the Tiara wins First Runner up at
the 2012 Miss India Worldwide Pageant held in Suriname, South America.The
Tiara’s Pageant Aspirants make it to Pantaloons Femina Miss India 2012. The
Tiara congratulates Ipsita Pati, Prachi Mishra, and Ruhi Singh for making it to
the Femina Miss India 2012 Finals. Dipna Patel and Huzan Mewawala win Femina
Style Diva Winner 2012 and 2nd Runner Up.

 Course Details

·       Filling up Forms and Registration Help

·       Developing a Pageant Strategy

·       Pageant &amp; Ramp Walk

·       Personality &amp; Grooming

·       Posture &amp; .

·       Camera Facing Techniques &amp; Portfolio
Assistance

·       Public Speaking
&amp;Voice Modulation

·       Modeling Technique &amp; Body Language

·       Making a Positive First Impression

·       Wardrobe Analysis &amp; Customized Wardrobe
Assistance

·       Diet, Nutrition &amp; Fitness Assistance

.       Confidence Building

·       Mental Preparation

·       Question Handling (Preliminary Round,
Prejudging, On Stage and One-on-One)

·       Personalize your answers so that you sound
original

 ·       Connecting with the Judges and Handling the
Stage

·       Platform Development

  Don't be dismayed if you find that we are at Pune.
You deserve the help of a Pageant professional; don't let location stand in the
way of your dream. Assistance with accommodation provided. Limited seats.
Reserve your Spot now! To Ensure that you have your seat please pay the booking
amount of Rs 5000 which will be towards your course fee. For the hostel please
call Mr. Anil Shinde 9822282817

We train you for Femina
Miss India, Gladrags Mega Model Hunts Miss India World, Gladrags Mrs India,
Miss Universe India, Miss India International, Miss India Earth, Miss India
North, Miss India South, Miss India North – East, I Am She, Femina Miss India
East, Femina Miss India West, Femina Miss Gujarat, Miss Punjab, Miss Andhra
Pradesh, Miss North India, Miss Delhi-NCR, Miss Noida, Miss NCR, Miss
Chandigarh, Miss Jaipur, Miss Uttar Pradesh (U.P.) Miss Mumbai, Miss Goa, Miss
Kolkata, Miss Banglore, May Queen Ball, RSI May Queen, Navy Ball Mumbai, Miss
Kerala, Navy Queen, Mumbai, Kochi, Miss South India , DSOI May Queen, May
Princess, Summer Princess, NDA Ball, NDA Queen, Miss Pune, Mirchi Queen Bee,
Dabur Vatika, Miss Kolkata, Miss Mumbai, Miss Bombay, Miss Nagpur, Miss
Devlali, Miss Nasik, THI May Queen, Princess, Reality Modeling Hunts like
Karnataka, Miss West Bengal, Miss Maharashtra, Miss Punjab, Miss Uttar Pradesh,
Miss Delhi, Miss Pune, Tilottama, Miss Nagaland, Miss Shillong, Miss Goa, Mrs
International Miss India World-wide, Miss India- Teen , Miss India- Tourism ,
Miss India , Miss India State Pageants, Miss India U.P. (Uttar Pradesh) Miss
India Punjab, Miss India Jaipur, Miss India Delhi-NCR, Miss India Maharashtra,
Miss India Goa, Miss India Gujarat , Miss India Karnataka, Miss India Andhra
Pradesh ( A. Gladrags- Mega Model Hunt, Kingfisher Calendar Girls, Airtel Grid
Girls, Get Gorgeous, Diva Next Door, I-Diva, Teen Diva

The Tiara,

Tel: +919823156193

ritika.ramtri@gmail.com

 http://thetiara.net/

 

 

 

 

 

 

 </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/m2aion</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6esi</id></website><link>http://2threads.com/article/jessica-hart-victorias-secret-angel-is-back</link><postedTime>2011-09-23T06:32:29+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:55:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3b3e9</id><link>http://2threads.com/article/jessica-hart-victorias-secret-angel-is-back#comment-479760002</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzl05</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-09-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>