<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3s80h/post/2012-03-29T23:09:42</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Greta, 
I am a fan, but your story related to the ED charges was not "Fair and Balanced", where was the other side of the story. Any hospital administrator could have presented the other side, if the hospital involved in the care refused to participate.

First, the father chose a high deductible insurance policy of $5,000, most likely to reduce his monthly premiums. Second, without tort reform doctors and hospitals are obligated to perform all required test to rule out any possible diagnosis, because if they miss diagnose, they will find a summons being handed to them. Third, if they did not run the test to Ensure timely surgery of a potential appendicitis, leading to a delay in surgical intervention resulting in sepsis, the story would have been for inappropriate care. Lastly, using the ED for a Stomach ache, a more appropriate choice would have been a doctors office. 

Further, federal law, EMTALA requires a medical screening examinations must continue until the existence of an emergency condition has been ruled out, otherwise you are in violation and the fines are substantial for both the hospital and the doctor.

Thank you </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zotaf</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t33k</id></website><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/have-you-had-any-medical-bill-nightmares/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:45:56+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T03:09:42+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3s80h</id><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/have-you-had-any-medical-bill-nightmares/#comment-480187417</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>