<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwx0ak/post/2012-03-30T21:12:34</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ssux</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/fdwt</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>This isn't a bill, this is a regulation being imposed by unelected bureaucrats with little to no scientific backing. CO2 is not a pollutant. It is a naturally occurring gas. The remainder of the pollutants coming from Burning coal have been reduced to virtually non existent levels. China is opening a new coal fired power plant every week, and they aren't killing themselves economically with pollution controls either. I agree with the Nuclear power plant option, but don't expect any of them to open up soon. The environmental groups will do to them what they do to anyone wanting to open a new refinery, tie it up in court with nuisance lawsuits for decades. One way to reduce emissions from coal fired power plants is to mix the fuels, wood pellets being the fuel of choice in Europe with many plants going completely to the renewable biomass energy pellets. One power plant in Nebraska (IIRC) is using pellets made from left over corn cobs and stalks. Europe is Poised to put into place mandates requiring that wood pellets for power plants come from certifiable renewable forests. The Obamao EPA has put into place pollution standards aimed at keeping wood pellets from being used in power generation in only one state - Texas. Which state has the highest acreage of certified renewable wood forests in the US? Texas. I looked into building a pellet business here, but without a local buyer how am I supposed to get the funding for the factory?  Coal can be Burned cleanly and efficiently but not to the ridiculous standards that the Obamao EPA are mandating. This is the same idiocy that Jimma Cahtah did in the 70s. Cost thousands of coal miners their jobs and raised electric bills across the country. As for the pollution caused by Burning coal, Mt St Helens belched more pollutants into the air when it erupted than all of the coal fired power plants in the US had done in the previous century combined.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zf59x</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zmzu</id></website><link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2012/mar/29/obama-kills-coal-as-promised/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T23:22:14+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T01:12:34+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwx0ak</id><link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2012/mar/29/obama-kills-coal-as-promised/#comment-481395379</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8n7n8</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>