<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9ku9k/update/2012-03-18T12:24:22/c852d469ed535e834d2055113671909dbe13f941a0c82aaef1d5e62cb4a88a36</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9j5ox</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6a5aj</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Yes, same claims were made about Iraq in the frenzied Republican drive to start the "shock and awe" and I bet right wing morons like you actually "think" they found WMD in Iraq- huh?

Again, the world should be prohibited from having nuclear weapons when all those that have them get rid of theirs.

Your position of might makes right came out of the Neanderthalic period of human development from which Republicans like you directly descended.

And don't forget to vote for the 1%'s filthy rich Mit Romney, he knows a lot about common folk plus he likes war too, or that Bible-thumping nut Rick "Mental" Sanitarium he would love another war. That way we can start praying for war in classrooms again. 

And I am sure both them will shut down schools, libraries, and gut social programs like Heating oil assistance to the poor and elderly to pay for their murderous, obscene and unjust wars!  That is soooo Republican!

For double standard, hypocrite, right-wing-nut-Republicans like you, 
it's Always a good time to start another war.  And that's the truth!

p.s. I notice you right wingers aren't clamoring for Israel to come clean with its nuclear program- brain too jam-packed with Rush Limbaugh talking points?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6c9xtq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ant8</id></website><link>http://www.alternet.org/world/154542/how_netanyahu_seeks_to_change_us_elections_by_pushing_war_with_iran_/comments/</link><postedTime>2012-03-14T16:32:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-18T16:24:22+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9ku9k</id><link>http://www.alternet.org/world/154542/how_netanyahu_seeks_to_change_us_elections_by_pushing_war_with_iran_/comments/#comment-468410359</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/r2lno</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-14</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>