<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3f55o/post/2012-03-29T16:34:32</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The tragedy here is Zimmerman didn't stay put when told too and Trayvon was feeling like he was in danger so he possibly crept on him to get the first punch in..which I dont blame him if he did.. if I were in his shoes? I would have done the same..

The hoodie was also a contributing factor..even when my kids wear them it better be Cold outside and not an every day occurance so it appears their trying to relate to a criminal influence..Hoodies ARE connected to the gang bangers etc I dont care what anyones saying..Guilt by association will Always be a disturbing factor every parent needs to teach their children.Any parent worth their salt agrees that if a person runs with a certain crowd and that group does something wrong you will also be a suspect.

Everything that happened that night was a formula for disaster. Both of them no doubt felt like they were in danger of being harmed so they fought to defend themselves..unfortunately Trayvon lost.. The media.. Sharpton.. Jackson and Owebama's statement have hammered this story so bad its gonna be tuff to please everybody no matter what the outcome.

One day its Zimmerman's fault the next its Trayvon's...Ive seen evidence from both sides and now Im ready to sit back and let the courts decide..All the arm chair lawyers and speculators can say what they like but nobody will have the facts until this goes to court. 

Sadly no matter who wins they are both losers ..ZImmerman will have to watch his back and carry this guilt for the rest of his life.. Nobody but a Cold blooded murderer could not be affected..Trayvon?? May God rest his soul!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zahhb</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gbgg</id></website><link>http://www.bakersfieldcalifornian.com/archive/x1282766267/March-for-Trayvon-draws-crowd</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T03:57:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:34:32+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3f55o</id><link>http://www.bakersfieldcalifornian.com/archive/x1282766267/March-for-Trayvon-draws-crowd#comment-479862316</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/amtad</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>