<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tk3c/update/2012-03-29T10:22:42/6021f7c3a14c3376c6929bba2a43bed011e3957d3ad8bdc1e387c1a829875423</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Is it malpractice for lawyers to lie about the actual public facts of a possible crime, the potential prosecution of which they are a part, in the national media? 

The police report, which if the Martin lawyers can't find it in the Sanford PD, they can find here on Daily Caller, clearly indicates that Zimmerman received first aid at the site from Sanford Fire Rescue, because, as the police report (Sgt  -- Officer -- Smith?) notes, Zimmerman was Bleeding from the nose and the back of his head at the site. So of course he isn't Bleeding as he walks into the police station.  Oh!  Wait!  The first stories the Martin lawyer (and the complicent incurious media) put out were that the Sanford PD did nothing.  Yet there Zimmerman is, handcuffed, walking into the SPD.  Dang.   -----&gt;  Squirrel!

It seems the Martin lawyers are not looking for a trial, they are looking for $$$ from a civil suit or settlement.  This kind of publicity completely skews any kind of fair trial.  But when it turns out that the somewhat thuggy picture Michelle Malkin (and now Daily Caller) posted IS Martin  ... the angel boy facade is blown.   (Withdraw your apology, Michelle.)  And no, how one looks isn't justification for being killed.  But the facts are the facts.  (Jessie Jackson would not be relieved if he turned around and the guy in the picture was behind him.)

But this so clearly demonstrates that it is not rule of law here, or justice, as much as unseemly manipulation and provocation.  

And ABC?  You are a joke.  Mr. Gutman, *you* owe Zimmerman an apology. (Another report I saw indicated Zimmerman sought addition medical arttention the next morning.)  

How about letting due process and get Off your lazy fanny and let the facts, not the "narrative" be reported?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6za97r</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q0fi</id></website><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/29/police-surveillance-video-of-zimmerman-may-show-head-injury/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T04:19:40+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:22:42+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tk3c</id><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/29/police-surveillance-video-of-zimmerman-may-show-head-injury/#comment-479525079</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c2jz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>