<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwm9zf/update/2012-03-30T09:20:47/c8b147ac4449e449bb1a0c48c6f0c574cfe403db630f41c5f0a3bbf6792cd68f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>What in the world is wrong with this kid?He has practically owned everyone he faced in the minors since becoming a relief pitcher.He go's out and wins the carribean Series MVP &amp; Atlanta doesn't have a Spot for the kid?.I get that he has not overwhelmed in his whole 15 or so innings in the majors but comeon.There has to be more to this story than he used to call himself Luis Valdez.
what did he do?Most teams would take a guy who pitched like that even if they found out his real identity was Juanita Gomez.They would just have to find some place for her to get in uniform other than the locker room.What could he have done that Atlanta had no use for the kid?Did he get in a fist fight with the manager?Did he sleep with the GM's wife or Daughter.Maybe he slept with the GM's son.
Teams just do not get rid of kids with this kind of record of success unless they know that Surgery is imminent or that a Colombian Drug Cartel has put a contract out on the guys life.
Don't get me wrong as a 40 year Indians fan who grew up in the Heights area I am Glad we got this kid.But even I wonder why?Even odder is that we have a relatively stocked pen if we keep him who do we send down or let go.I Realize we picked him up so Hernandez would have a buddy on the club who could say I understand and mean it.But I still have a lot of questions.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z7hlw</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lz6q</id></website><link>http://cleveland.indians.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120329%26content_id=27728764%26vkey=news_cle%26c_id=cle</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:49:47+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:20:47+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwm9zf</id><link>http://cleveland.indians.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120329%26content_id=27728764%26vkey=news_cle%26c_id=cle#comment-480730993</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/csznn</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>