<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3gqdz/post/2012-03-28T20:58:28</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3g5r9</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/506ju</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>so when he stands up for a presumed racist white guy, he's not black, he's light skinned?? But prior to this, he would just be a black dude?? And by the way, NOBODY would want THIS kind of negative attention. There is NO F***ing WAY this guy is doing this just so he can get some face time on TV. WHY WOULD ANY BLACK MAN DO THAT??!! When, being black, he would know that he is at risk of being called "Uncle Tom" for the rest of his life!! God, I just wanna stay out of this WHOLE mess because all it is, is an excuse for black people to be racist as shit. Nobody's talking about the white couple that was brutally murdered by a group of black people (the boyfriend had his penis cut Off after being beaten half to death and THEN he was Burned alive in front of his girlfriend and THEN they proceeded to do unspeakable things to his girlfriend and then murder her.) Yeah NOBODY is talking about that Charles Manson bullshit they pulled. Oh no no no. Who CARES, right??!! Because it was black on white and not white on black. This kind of racist behavior from MY people disgusts me to no end. Wipe your ass, take a shower, clean the crust from your eyes. You are DIRTY!!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ht8sy</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/vkpb</id></website><link>http://hellobeautiful.com/gossip-news/dyoung/top-5-quotes-from-george-zimmermans-black-friend-joe-oliver/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T16:02:08+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T00:58:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3gqdz</id><link>http://hellobeautiful.com/gossip-news/dyoung/top-5-quotes-from-george-zimmermans-black-friend-joe-oliver/#comment-478948766</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gq98b</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>