<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m77702/update/2012-02-26T04:58:26/631c1fcfd34884034de7292ecc66a98cb791b8b963ff9d056c6f4f542bc33504</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body> just sayin.....

The Quranic text can actually be used in such situations to control the Afghan anger and prevent its spread.
 In fact, the religiosity of people in these parts of the world makes 
the use of religious text more effective in controlling people's anger 
than using formal apologetic approaches.

For example the Quran stated clearly that the Lord forgive unintentional mistakes and only consider an action as a sin if it was intentional. Quran Al-Ahzab 33:5:

"But there is no 
blame on you if ye make a mistake therein: (what counts is) the 
intention of your hearts: and Allah is Oft-Returning, Most Merciful."

The point to be used with Afghans in 
this situation is that how could they know that the intensions of those 
who Burnt the Quran was to insult it. They must bring evidence that the 
intention of the NATO personnel was to insult the Quran - as the Quran itself describes those who accuse others without having evidence as "dishonest" people. Quran Al-Naml 27:64:

Or, Say, "Bring forth your evidence (proof), if ye are telling the truth!"

The third Islamic Caliph Uthman Ibn 
Affan (who is considered to be one of the greatest Is disciples of 
prophet Mohamed) Burnt the Quran and his actions were not considered as a
 sin - by either him or by the disciples of the prophet - since the Act 
of Burning was not associated with intention to insult it. Similarly, 
the Afghans must not react with anger against the Burning of the Quran 
as they do not have a proof that it was associated with an intention to 
insult it.

In addition, even if the action of the two personnel who Burnt the Quran was intentional, it is forbidden in the Quran to react against others.
 For example, the Quran forbids any angry reaction against the NATO 
soldiers who actually did not commit the Burning and are likely to be 
against it. The Quran stated clearly in four different positions that 
not one should be punished for the mistake of another person Quran: 
Al-Isra 17:15; Al-An'am 6:164; Fatir 35:18; Az-Zumar 39:7:

"Nor can a bearer of burdens bear another's burdens."

Finally, there is no single verse in the Quran that considers its Burning as 'Haram' or forbidden.
 (Afghan Muslim need to be challenged to bring this verse from the 
Quran!). On the contrary, there is a clear verse (Quran: Al-Imran 3:134)
 that asks Muslims to control and restrain their anger:

Those (the true 
believers) who spend (freely), whether in prosperity, or in adversity; 
who restrain anger, and pardon (all) humans;- for the Lord loves those 
who do good.

To conclude, because of the nature of 
the Afghan culture and the importance of religion in their life, the use
 of Islamic jargon and Quran text can aid in controlling the anger of 
the population in response to the Burning of the Quran.

Note: some reports mentioned that 
these books (Quran, plus others) were being used to convey violent 
messages and communicate between Taliban prisoners.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/y9o0uc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dneq</id></website><link>http://www.adn.com/2012/02/25/2336301/gunman-kills-2-us-advisers-in.html</link><postedTime>2012-02-25T21:20:18+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-26T09:58:26+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m77702</id><link>http://www.adn.com/2012/02/25/2336301/gunman-kills-2-us-advisers-in.html#comment-449178012</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>