<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkj3le/update/2012-03-26T14:56:59/b7d9daf413f92c0dc61f61c5d8077bfa542ed4cacaa238178878d329fbddc8b9</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>1. Martin  suspended from school 10 days for having an empty marijuana bag at school.  (SELLING DRUGS or a DRUGGEE)  He was also 17 years old  (5 Feb 1995 dob) AND A JUNIOR in high school  not a senior so he was either a truant not getting credits because he skipped or stupid and held back. 

2. Martin not in school is sent to his father where he wonders around behind apartment complexes where he does not belong

3. Zimmerman Spots him - calls the police and follows him. Police say not to follow but there is NO LAW BROKEN by following him.   Martin had a cell phone - if he felt threatened by Zimmeramn he should have called the police. 

4.  Zimmerman breaks Off following Martin and walks back to his vehicle.  Martin jumps him from behind.  Zimmerman - short (5' 2") and overweight/out of shape jumped by a tall teen age 17 year old thug lands on his back and is hit in the face repeatedly by Martin.  Zimmerman  has grass stains on his back/cuts/bruises on his face and is heard by bystanders and on video YELLING HELP CALL POLICE HELP!   Not Martin - Zimmerman!    

5. First witness SAME TIME as assault tells police say Martin on top of Zimmerman - backs Zimmerman story.    Zimmerman only one with grass stains on the back of his shirt and cuts on face.  Martin has no grass stains and no bruises/cuts - he is shot dead by Zimmerman defending himself. .       

6.  a MONTH AFTER the event dirt bag blond looking for publicity says Zimmerman sitting on Martin - makes her LSM rounds - probably paid also.  15 minutes of fame starting.  

</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r0c13</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yzhx</id></website><link>http://www.miamiherald.com/2012/03/26/2714778/thousands-expected-at-trayvon.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T15:37:07+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:56:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkj3le</id><link>http://www.miamiherald.com/2012/03/26/2714778/thousands-expected-at-trayvon.html#comment-476634246</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cxvhs</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>