<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwqe9z/post/2012-03-30T18:19:44</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwvcq3</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>There is still over a day to wait until 1st April.

So, you think we should plan to Ensure that our brightest and best leave the country of their birth and upbringing, given the absence of foreseeable employment opportunities in this country for most of those graduating from our educational system, particularly at third and even fourth level for many years to come.

Meanwhile we tax our captive citizenry until the pips squeak so that the expectations and sense of entitlement of all of the additional uninvited and presumably non taxpaying inhabitants of our fair land can,which you envisage in your nightmare scenario, be fully satisfied.

Have you had any thoughts or ideas for what language(s) would most profitably be taught in our schools to enable the conquered minority of native Irish in their own land, better cope with your "more productive and more competitive" brave new world.

By the way, I fully agree with Ed who is merely stating what should be obvious, namely that the level and extent of taxation in any society is as good a measure as any of the size and beyond a certain point wastefulness of government and its agencies which can be applied the writ large to our own quangrocracy.  These quangos are not only non productive but are all too often counterproductive. In in our current economic circumstances this type of governance amounts to the fiscal and financial equivalent of fiddling while Rome Burns.

And you want to add treason to this already toxic brew! 
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/675n0v</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/qxal</id></website><link>http://www.independent.ie/national-news/just-under-600000-sign-up-for-household-charge-ahead-of-tomorrows-payment-deadline-3066924.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:41:07+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T22:19:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwqe9z</id><link>http://www.independent.ie/national-news/just-under-600000-sign-up-for-household-charge-ahead-of-tomorrows-payment-deadline-3066924.html#comment-481265366</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>