<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkju7q/post/2012-03-26T14:42:47</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkb5c1</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Okay, I tried to follow the conversation here, but it's better to ask you directly. So, you are saying that k-vips were  stuff like ''G-Ri'' and ''ToDae'' in the past? Or do you mean they were  ''Nyongtory'' and ''Topseong''? Or both? And the members reacted negatively on it even GD and Panda? So, you guys stopped using it...and think that we should too? 
~
Question: Did k-vip's used these couple names to refer to fan's ''yaoi'' fantasies or the boys being gay? Or like most of us i-vip's who use it to describe ''bromance'' [watch the origin of the word: youtube(DOT)com/watch?v=Uv7SUncOAAQ]. Like what is the definition of having a ''couple name'' in korea? 
We normal i-vip's ''ship'' BIGBANG's close friendship together between certain members (not meaning that they are actually gay...only the actual hardcore shippers do) Hyung-dongsaeng, chingu-chingu like GDYB(GD&amp;YoungBae/Taeyang), Tom and Jerry or G-Ri (GD&amp;Seungri), Choi Brothers(TOP&amp;SE7EN), ToDae(TOP and Daesung), GTOP(GD&amp;TOP) etc Another example for 2NE1 like ChaeRa(Chaerin&amp;Dara),Park Sisters or fake maknae's (Park Bom&amp;Sandara Park), Bomji(Bom&amp;Minji),Real Maknae's(CL&amp;Minzy). It's referring to their fun, cute or crazy hyper interactions. 
~
Also it's not like we would make signs or scream ToDae or G-Ri to the boys.It's just noticeable and truth that they are close brothers.Both GD x Seungri, TOP x Daesung have been Spotted holding like hands while walking at the airport...recently as well.Some will think they  gay and others just see it as them showing brotherly affection.It just is really obvious that GD and Seungri for example are really close together..like  around each other it's a fun plus cute hyung-dongsaeng relationship and it's easier to use terms as G-Ri to point them out on a video, show or photo. TOP and SE7EN are totally putting on this crazy  were they are totally doing fan-service for us all. So, I kinda Always thought that they knew of it (the couple names thing and fan-service stuff), but didn't mind and even stimulated it themselves (like again I'm gonna point out Nyongtory). It really is like a kpop-world thing. The shippings and the couple names. Maybe it is us ''international fans'' being ignorant to BB's opinion about that, but still. Do all k-vip's agree with you on this one?
~
Also have k-netizens ever accused the boys of being like actually gay or just shippers did who want them together? Is that why they reacted like that?
~
Btw, when did that whole incident happen &gt;_&lt;'? Like since when did you guys stop using it?
~
Sorry, but I'm totally confused now.Thank you in advantage ^_^</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rkgpf</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/g1xx</id></website><link>http://www.bigbangupdates.com/2012/03/daesung-said-physical-appearance-is-not.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T12:22:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:42:47+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkju7q</id><link>http://www.bigbangupdates.com/2012/03/daesung-said-physical-appearance-is-not.html#comment-476621407</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/r71bq</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>