<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjqhy/post/2012-03-26T14:36:47</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkja7q</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dif9n</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>This is excellent. I think the comparison with the UK Office is extremely good - there is indeed a sense of real-life stakes and despair that comes through all the zaniness. A lot of people here (Jeff, Troy, possibly Britta and maybe even Abed) are facing uncertain, possibly disappointing futures, and they are deep down struggling with Anxiety and uncertainty. I can see how there can be a weird dissonance between this and the very broad style that the show has  played with, but by an large the show has tapped into this feeling of disappointment since S2 and has stuck to it consistently and realistically.

Also Urban Matrimony was meant to air after this episode, but your analysis still holds very well.

--------------------------

You finally gave me an explanation about why I fell Off the P&amp;R wagon: there are no real stakes there anymore. The Harvest Festival was a great arc which was weird and zany, but also created real tension among the characters - they were after all fighting to keep their jobs. Now this tension is completely gone, and since the show never had as strong a cast of characters as Community does, there's very little that interests me.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yk4a1</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/contemporary-impressionists,70958/</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T00:30:37+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:36:47+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjqhy</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/contemporary-impressionists,70958/#comment-476616141</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dpa41</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>