<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/253053/post/96019847/comment/327539394</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Dear Katie, I am sorry to hear that your doctor made a mistake and put you on Depo injections. You say which you are nonetheless obtaining injections? These injections are created from progestin, a synthetic form of progesterone which is used mainly as a method of birth control for ladies who cannot use any other form of birth control. Among the drug’s side effects is weight . A single injection lasts for three months. So in case you are nonetheless obtaining these injections, please, please, tell your doctor which you don’t want to receive them any longer. The effects with the drug will remain inside your body for three months, so during these three months, it may be difficult to shed the added weight which you , no matter what you do. You will find other far more gentler ways to regulate your periods and menses, particularly at your tender formative age. Here are some with the negative reasons for not using Depo-Provera: it can cause decreased bone density which can lead to osteoporosis, depression, increased blood clots, liver damage, Headaches, hair loss, Leg cramps, nervousness, Dizziness, abdominal bloating, and weight Gain. For your stretch marks on your stomach, you are able to rub some vitamin E on them. Just puncture a capsule of vitamin E and gently apply to your stomach location once or twice each day. The stretch marks will respond towards the vitamin E in the event you use it regularly and use it as soon as they appear. The older the stretch marks, the longer and more difficult they are to rub away. It\'s very best to use natural vitamin E, which can be distinguished from the synthetic form by the following small print and notations on the vitamin bottle: d- could be the natural form, and dl- could be the synthetic form. Use only the d- form which could be the natural form. I believe that synthetic substances have caused enough harm already, and need to be laid to rest. Discover a doctor who will listen to you, have patience until the Depo drug gets out of your system and body, and continue follow a healthy diet and exercise regimen to get back to your former weight. Please read the posts above to learn more about dieting. Excellent luck. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:253053:96019847</id><idPostId>96019847</idPostId><idBlogId>253053</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:253053</id><idBlogId>253053</idBlogId><link>http://reneedmd.com</link><displayName>Renee DMD</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.ReneeDMD.com/stinky-breath/</link><displayName>Stinky Breath</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T03:01:39.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:253053:96019847:327539394</id><link>http://www.ReneeDMD.com/stinky-breath/#IDComment327539394</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T03:01:39.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Stinky Breath by cash for gold melbourne</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://www.goldbuyersmelbourne.com.au/</link><idEmailMd5>4e20676b8ee031699580de8e8b04798e</idEmailMd5><displayName>cash for gold melbourne</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://www.goldbuyersmelbourne.com.au/"&gt;cash for gold melbourne&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.ReneeDMD.com/stinky-breath/"&gt;Stinky Breath&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>