<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/edszub/update/2011-12-02T12:30:03/3e484b65c2e943db44fcfcbeb8df206596ce33d5461123761e5c27a4830dff39</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I've had generalized Anxiety disorder since I was 15, so my problems started before Columbia. I feel like Columbia attracts people like me because it provides the constant distractions of living in New York while still allowing complete anonymity, which is very Comforting. 

As I sit in a Columbia library and look around, I know almost none of you will ever meet me, and even fewer of you will ever know me. I have one more year to go here but at this point I've completely retracted from the Columbia community. There are a lot of reasons for this but perhaps the biggest disenchantment came when I learned of the terrible things that were done to someone I loved here by another classmate. There is no hope for justice (because we began the process together only to find that everything would be a dead end,) and all addressing the issue causes is pain. 

After Columbia, I will only keep in touch with two of my classmates, and I certainly won't carry Columbia's flag for the rest of my life the way so many of my friends from other schools will for their alma matter.I immensely grateful for the community of friends I have found outside of Columbia and have carried with me from my hometown. I am also forever grateful for my parents who never once blamed me for my problems and were able to help find me a therapist in NYC after I had tried to find someone in CPS for weeks. When my attacks were preventing me from going to class by keeping me in bed staring at the ceiling and waiting for my heart to stop exploding out of my chest as dread enveloped me, it was only because I had parents that not only wanted to help me, but knew exactly how.  These are both advantages I know so many people who are suffering here may not have. I pray that everyone like me can find something or someone to keep them stable, but unfortunately even when support is there, sometimes it's not enough.I also hope that something will change for me in my last three semesters at Columbia, and I connect with more of you. I am not emotionally unavailable, and if you ever met me you might call me charming. I make friends easily but I have not found many here. No matter what happens here I will have a happy life, but it would be nice not to look back on the good ol' days of college and realize it was nothing more than a decent education.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/dc7pgj</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cwqo</id></website><link>http://eye.columbiaspectator.com/?q=article%2F2011%2F12%2F01%2Fhow-were-doing</link><postedTime>2011-12-01T09:22:28+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-12-02T17:30:03+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/edszub</id><link>http://eye.columbiaspectator.com/?q=article%2F2011%2F12%2F01%2Fhow-were-doing#comment-377745970</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-12-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>