<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwx2s1/post/2012-03-30T20:13:32</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwnooo</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zh852</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Hubert Lamb, the first director of the Environmental Sciences department of the UEA  was also known as 'the ice man' but changed seamlessly to promoting global warming;

"Lamb was one of the first to propose that climate could change within human experience, going against the orthodox view of the time that climate could be treated as constant for practical
purposes. He developed early theories about the medieval warm period and little ice age, and became known as the "ice man" for his prediction of global cooling and a coming ice age.

At first his view was that global cooling would lead within 10,000 years to a future ice age, but over a period including the UK's exceptional drought and Heat wave of 1975–76 he changed to predicting that global warming could have serious effects within a century. His warnings of damage to agriculture, ice caps melting, and cities being flooded caught widespread attention and helped to shape public opinion. He Gained the unit sponsorship from seven major insurance companies, who wanted to make use of the research of the unit when making their own studies of the implications of climate change for insurance against storm and flood damage."

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hubert_Lamb</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hthio</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ms5i</id></website><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/jamesdelingpole/100147742/queensland-turns-the-tide-of-environmental-lunacy/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T16:15:26+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T00:13:32+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwx2s1</id><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/jamesdelingpole/100147742/queensland-turns-the-tide-of-environmental-lunacy/#comment-481351128</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cum3l</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>