<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpp0ma/update/2012-03-22T02:21:58/e0fe93bb7131b506c9e2dddc9befeaaa8b8ca6b0aaafc07be7a2306485305be3</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I am fairly new in Eatonville - my family moved here from Seattle for the peaceful community and proximity to Mt Rainier for hiking and snowshoeing.  We are law abiding citizens.  My spouse was recently pulled over for what was described as a Burned out license plate light. One of the lights around the plate was Burned out and we didn't know.  We replaced it the next day.  The officer was not unfriendly but it seemed like an odd thing to be pulled over for. We have seen the local officers pull vehicles over and block driveways to the Post Office and other businesses.  We saw a car get pulled over by three separate police cars - two behind and one across the street.  The car was on it's way pretty quickly so the stop must not have been for anything too serious and the driver looked young and scared.   The youngsters in town are learning to fear and dislike the police rather than seeing them as protectors.  This is a community that has seen tremendous loss (Kent Mundell, Ranger Margaret Anderson) and has supported local law enforcement wholeheartedly - most of us highly respect those that uphold the law. Until the new chief took over, you could pass an officer and wave, and they would wave back.  Now if you wave, the friendly gesture is not returned.  It's easy for people to say 'obey the law and you have nothing to worry about'.  Intimidation is Always something to worry about.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dh3m6</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnmp</id></website><link>http://www.thenewstribune.com/2012/03/20/2075677/police-crackdown-stirs-up-eatonville.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T04:11:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T06:21:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpp0ma</id><link>http://www.thenewstribune.com/2012/03/20/2075677/police-crackdown-stirs-up-eatonville.html#comment-473370733</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zd2oa</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>