<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/c3w3c/update/2009-02-25T17:01:58/ec3a15df2fecbb770866c580b73c1dd83625ccf1dc120e2279935f79cd5c76d9</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/c3wtk</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8m3w</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I'm not sure if I understand the post correctly, but it seems that I Samuel would support his claims.  Israel's asking for a king was a rebellion against God's rule, and the Israelites were warned of the consequences and asked for one anyway.  There is certainly a need for governance and I think both Christ and Paul addressed that, but I think it was accompanied by the understanding that it was of the world and inherently sinful.  &#13;
&#13;
It is probably possible for the government to  like the Kingdom of God for a short time, but rarely.  Somebody's ox is Always gored with even the best of intentions.  The government's standards are arbitrary and they cannot provide God's justice.  Take welfare for instance.  God calls us to help the poor, and the government tries to do that, but it is the Kingdom of God when the system is abused?  Perhaps I'm too cynical, but I don't believe that any government can do God's will in a meaningful way.  God is personal (I'll probably take some Heat for that) but government is necessarily bigger than all of us.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/mtduu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/p8t</id></website><link>http://blog.sojo.net/2009/02/25/obamas-call-to-rebuild/</link><postedTime>2009-02-25T17:00:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2009-02-25T22:01:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/c3w3c</id><link>http://blog.sojo.net/2009/02/25/obamas-call-to-rebuild/#comment-6623751</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2009-02-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>