<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jr14/post/2012-04-02T03:07:21</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jepv</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8r6b1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Let us not forget, no one is ever calling for this 18 or 19 year old to in as a starter and play in the CL final right away. All people like myself ask for is for a chance. Look at Mata for example. Because he didn't get a chance, he ended up leaving the club, only to be sold after 2 or 3 years for 20+ million. 

Also, a lot of people complain about Sarabia and his situation at Getafe. Do they look at anything other than the fact that he hasn't been getting as much starts as he would like when they evaluate the situation? Or is it the same evaluation that deems Carvajal not good enough after watching him from one game? 

Sarabia is a great talent. Unfortunately for him, he is at the wrong club. Getafe are not the same club they were in the past. When Soldado, Granero and De La Red were shining there, they had managers like Loudrup and Michel that were pro youth teamers and attacking football. At the moment, they have Luis Garcia, a manager that relies on experience rather than youth. Not to mention, he doesn't rely on a player like SArabia because his formation doesn't have a place for such a player. With that said, when Sarabia has played, he has done a very good job. He started against Barcelona and he ran circles around their defense, assisting the only goal of the game. 

Not to mention, the player is still 19 years old for goodness sake. Never seen a set of fans that are soo ready to write Off one of their own so fast. Rodrigo had a horrible first season last year, being loaned out to Bolton and rarely earning a start. What is he doing this year? He is starting for Benfica and scoring goals left and right. 

Also, people forget that these 18-20 year olds are playing all together. Nobody is saying that all these players in Castilla are worthy of a starting Spot. Hell, no one is saying there is more than 2 or 3 that can make it to the first team. But look back on when Castilla players were really given a chance. Has any of them done anything not to impress? Nacho started 2 games out of position at left back and was very good even against Valencia. Joselu scored from his first touch. Morata did very well. Sarabia impressed when he made his debut. Jese had a great preseason. At the end of the day, if you give a talented youngster a chance to play alongside 10 other experienced players, he will grow in confidence and his talent will grow. Let us not forget that one player won't lead to a 10-0 loss. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6v4vyr</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7fee</id></website><link>http://www.realmadridfootballblog.com/2012/04/peaking-at-the-right-time-osasuna-v-real-madrid-review/</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T13:36:50+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T07:07:21+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jr14</id><link>http://www.realmadridfootballblog.com/2012/04/peaking-at-the-right-time-osasuna-v-real-madrid-review/#comment-483324642</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8rv1j</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>