<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwt5dn/update/2012-03-30T16:34:08/15594143eac4753e43e98067c41399f83933977ee5b61f0175d93b80deff21f1</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw75fz</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Cheryl &amp; Pepper,
Skin Itching issues are frequently a sign of detox. The four main venues for the body are sweat it out, pee it out, poop it out or puke it up. While most people think that diarhea and Vomiting are due to toxins "something they ate", it appears that most don't think about skin Itching is due to toxins. Even less think of environmental toxins. So, I'm going to list a few examples of environmental toxins, just incase. And I'm going to tell you that some toxins don't  out of the body for months, and may continue to  for years. It  on the individual toxin and the state of the person/pets immune system.

Meds are toxic. will can cause skin reactions? It's one of the most frequently listed adverse reactions. 

Flea, tick &amp; worm "Meds" are pesticides and are highly toxic. They are a registered poison, according to the EPA. There are safer practices available, though not widely accepted by allopathic vets.

Fragrances, &amp; fragranced products. All fragrances contain pesticides,or you'd be swarmed by bugs. Mostly the biting stinging kind. This includes shampoos (your or the dogs) lotions, deodorants, hair glue (spray, gel,whatever...) make-up, Dryer sheets, fabreeze, "air fresheners, garbage can liners...

Cleaning chemicals. These are highly toxic, and the majority contain petroleum based chemicals. 

Yard and garden chemicals. Even granulated fertilizer contains fungicide (mold poison) and petroleum distillates.

Just some ideas.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ylta4n</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ukja</id></website><link>http://www.dogfoodadvisor.com/dog-food-reviews/blue-buffalo-freedom-canned/</link><postedTime>2012-02-05T13:40:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T20:34:08+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwt5dn</id><link>http://www.dogfoodadvisor.com/dog-food-reviews/blue-buffalo-freedom-canned/#comment-481168820</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hzpmw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-05</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>