<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/129639/post/127809243/comment/328804423</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Its the mechanism for much &amp;quot;crony capitalism&amp;quot;:  the Bootleggers are the favor-seeking groups and the politicians are the Baptists pretending their policies are in the public interest. Solyndra was a Bootlegger, green types were the Baptists. 
 
Its a useful tactic for libertarians to be aware of since is so widespread, so  I&amp;#039;ll pass along a bunch of links in case you are ever bored enough to read them :-) 
  &lt;a href="http://www.artdiamondblog.com/archives/2012/01/_source_of_book_13.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.artdiamondblog.com/archives/2012/01/_s...&lt;/a&gt; 
&amp;quot;Buffett pushed for government action and called attention to the problems, looking like a noble Baptist, but profited from the bailouts, like a bootlegger, through investments in Goldman Sachs, General Electric, Wells Fargo and other financial companies.&amp;quot; 
  &lt;a href="http://www.cato-at-liberty.org/bootleggers-baptists-sugary-soda-edition/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.cato-at-liberty.org/bootleggers-baptis...&lt;/a&gt; 
&amp;quot;Baptists-and-bootleggers coalitions underlie almost all government activities. Defense spending: (neo)conservatives and defense contractors.  President Obama&amp;rsquo;s new health care law: the political left and the health care and insurance industries. Ethanol subsidies: environmentalists and agribusiness. Education: egalitarians and teachers&amp;rsquo; unions. The list goes on... 
This morning, NPR reported on another bootleggers-and-Baptists coalition: anti-immigration zealots and the prison industry... 
It may seem counter-intuitive that Bleeding-heart anti-hunger groups and &amp;ldquo;Big Food and Big Beverage&amp;rdquo; would ally to oppose Mayor Bloomberg&amp;rsquo;s request to prevent New Yorkers from using food stamps to purchase sugary sodas [&amp;ldquo;Unlikely Allies in Food Stamp Debate,&amp;rdquo; October 16].  &amp;quot; 
  &lt;a href="http://volokh.com/2012/02/23/baptists-and-bootleggers/" target="_blank"&gt;http://volokh.com/2012/02/23/baptists-and-bootleg...&lt;/a&gt; 
&amp;quot;Now comes the emerging story of an alliance between leading environmental groups and the natural gas industry to advocate for the elimination of one of natural gas&amp;rsquo;s leading competitors: 
&amp;#039;Just four years ago, shale gas king Aubrey K. McClendon told shareholders of Chesapeake Energy that &amp;ldquo;finally, we made some new friends this year.&amp;rdquo; 
The chief executive sketched a vision of working hand in hand with &amp;ldquo;leading environmental organizations&amp;rdquo; on issues &amp;ldquo;where our interests might be .&amp;rdquo; He said, &amp;ldquo;We believe this collaboration is unique in the industry and will benefit both Chesapeake and these environmental organizations for years to come.&amp;rdquo;&amp;quot; 
 
  &lt;a href="http://www.perc.org/articles/article1358.php" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.perc.org/articles/article1358.php&lt;/a&gt; 
&amp;quot;BOOTLEGGERS, BAPTISTS, AND THE ENVIRONMENT 
Just why would bootleggers and Baptists favor statute-based federal regulations to common law? Common law is tough. At common law, somewhat unpredictable judges actually shut down polluters. More to the point, industries with national markets cannot create cartels around common law. Federal command-and-control regulation leads to uniform, entry-inhibiting standards that are advantageous to old sources. Environmentalists like federal statutes because it is easier to lobby for all-encompassing federal laws than to work the  of 50 state capitols. And it is easier to bring suit over technical violations of statutes &amp;mdash; and, incidentally, to serve the cartel&amp;rsquo;s interests &amp;mdash; than to prove damages at common law. 
The infamous scrubber regulations in the 1977 Clean Air Act, which should win the bootlegger-Baptist award for the 1970s, offer the best illustration of bootleggers benefiting from Baptist-supported, technology-based standards. The statute required costly scrubbers to be installed at all newly constructed coal-fired electric plants, whether or not a particular plant Burned dirty coal. Interest groups tied to high-sulfur coal production in the eastern United States celebrated the statute, as did most environmental groups. Miners of western low-sulfur coal, consumers of electricity, and (in some cases) lovers of clean air had no cause for celebration. 
 
Things such as tech nology or specification standards, differential requirements for new and old sources, grandfather clauses, and procedures for new-source performance review are clues that bootleggers and Baptists are at work. Sometimes, though, a simple output restriction marks a B&amp;amp;B success story. 
 
The theory explains why holders of permits to produce and market EPA-approved insecticides value the efforts of environmental groups who oppose rule changes that facilitate the entry of new, and sometimes less risky, substitutes. Indeed, once the theory is explained, bootleggers and Baptists seem to come out of the woodwork. They are every where.&amp;quot; 
 </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:129639:127809243</id><idPostId>127809243</idPostId><idBlogId>129639</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:129639</id><idBlogId>129639</idBlogId><link>http://www.dailycamera.com</link><displayName>Daily Camera.com:</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.dailycamera.com/letters/ci_20282757/dave-lane-federal-government-doesnt-have-authority-over</link><displayName>Dave Lane: The federal government doesn\'t have authority over medical marijuana - Boulder Daily Cam</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T22:29:15.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:129639:127809243:328804423</id><inReplyTo><link>http://www.dailycamera.com/letters/ci_20282757/dave-lane-federal-government-doesnt-have-authority-over#IDComment328703330</link></inReplyTo><link>http://www.dailycamera.com/letters/ci_20282757/dave-lane-federal-government-doesnt-have-authority-over#IDComment328804423</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T22:29:15.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Dave Lane: The federal government doesn\'t have authority over medical marijuana - Boulder Daily Cam by 123CommonSense</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://intensedebate.com/people/123CommonSense</link><idEmailMd5>b409baca8a24726a39eb74fd8bb66ca7</idEmailMd5><displayName>123CommonSense</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://intensedebate.com/people/123CommonSense"&gt;123CommonSense&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.dailycamera.com/letters/ci_20282757/dave-lane-federal-government-doesnt-have-authority-over"&gt;Dave Lane: The federal government doesn\'t have authority over medical marijuana - Boulder Daily Cam&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>