<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31510/post/2012-03-29T15:50:38</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Syrian Troops 'Overrun Last Major Stronghold'
SKYNews text and video http://news .sky .com/home/world-news/article/16198628
    
Regime forces have overrun the last major opposition-held stronghold in Syria and left a trail of destruction, according to activists.
In a four-day attack on Saraqeb, corpses were left in streets and homes Burned to the ground amid wholesale looting, they said.

The Local Co-ordination Committees network (LCC) issued an appeal for international humanitarian organisations to urgently visit the town and said there were many unidentified corpses and wounded people there.

"Regime forces have forcibly displaced a large number of activists' families, and Burned and shelled approximately 300 homes," the LCC said in a statement.

The London-based Syrian Observatory for Human Rights confirmed the reports and said most of the town's residents had fled along with the rebels.
It said more than 40 people had been killed during the fighting in Saraqeb, a large town on the main highway linking the northern city of Aleppo with the capital Damascus.

Activist Fadi al Yassin, in the northern province of Idlib, said the army was now in full control of Saraqeb, stationing snipers on rooftops and conducting searches and Raids using civilian cars and taxis to confuse residents.

He said army defectors in the Free Syrian Army resisted on the first day but then pulled out, fearing they would bring more destruction on the town.
"They fled because there was no way they were going to be able to face the regime's huge military force," the activist said by satellite phone.
 </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dkvsy</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cjnq</id></website><link>http://blogs.aljazeera.net/middle-east/2011/10/20/syria-live-blog</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T16:11:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:50:38+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31510</id><link>http://blogs.aljazeera.net/middle-east/2011/10/20/syria-live-blog#comment-479816387</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g2pn1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>