<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwn9wa/post/2012-03-30T19:56:35</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body> And there is just the fact that most conservatives don’t get involved in
politics unless they don’t perceive a dire threat. 

I mean they don't get involved unless they perceive a dire threat.


Look, what we have here is a mirror image of the 1990s and Clinton.  I remember going to the "Preparedness Expo" in 1995.  I remember talk before 2000 of "I bet Clinton will call  the elections and declare Martial Law".  He was going to use the whole Y2K bug as an excuse.

We might not have used the term "Prepper" or "Tea Party" in the 1990s but we had their equivalents and I would say back then they were even STRONGER than we are now. Since the 1960s (or perhaps even earlier) the clock has been ticking as the understanding of how things should be in America has been fading from the mindset of Americans.  People who knew what America was like before "the New Deal" are getting fewer and fewer these days.  No, as time goes by we inevitably get weaker as a conservative movement if only because there are fewer of us around who know how the American Dream can be.  More of us have been raised in the post hippie generation.  We are products of public schools. 


So sorry, as time goes by we become weaker as a movement. Unless there is some real "revival", unless the "battleship changes directions" unlike what has happened the last TWO TIMES now the Republicans have taken over, then yeah, we are just postponing the inevitable and in doing so giving up our last chance, mind you a slim one still last chance of rescue.

We are as conservatives in the Galileo Seven.  And the ship will lose orbit and we will Burn up in the planet's atmosphere. And the only chance, the only chance we have given it's a slim one is that a major change of our situation changes place, knowing that yeah in talking that chance we might speed up our destruction.  But again, our destruction is inevitable so all we are talking about here is the timing of our destruction and quite honestly we aren't  that much time. But we are losing our chance be it a slim one to save us from our fate.

Sorry, I am going SPOCK here and voting for Obama (if Romney takes the nomination as I fear will happen)  hoping for one last final battle in 2016. Damn it if conservatives can't get their  together by then then then indeed we would have just been putting  the inevitable. 

Obama has never been the problem. He had Always been just one SYMPTOM.  Before him there was Clinton. After him...I can't even imagine but that person will even be worse than Obama!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hg5j6</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/znxz</id></website><link>http://stevedeace.com/news/national-politics/obama-makes-the-case-for-his-defeat/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T06:12:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T23:56:35+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwn9wa</id><link>http://stevedeace.com/news/national-politics/obama-makes-the-case-for-his-defeat/#comment-481338217</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>