<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw96xw/post/2012-03-31T02:43:07</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwn4g7</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z779j</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Brain scans show several key areas to be smaller in those with ADHD than in the general population, including the nucleus accumbens and the cerebellum.  Cerebellar exercises improve ADHD symptoms, in many cases completely turning around underachieving/failing students. The imbalance of dopamine, serotonin, and norephinephrine can be measured indirectly in cerebrospinal fluid, and simple brain-wave measures via scalp electrodes also show distinct patterns which differ in ADHDers than in 92% of the population. 

Sometimes the chemical imbalances can be corrected using certain stimulants, Wellbutrin, non-stimulant medications, and even .  However, not everyone takes medication for ADHD as it doesn't work for everyone, and different meds work for different people. Plus, stimulant medications utilized in this manner have been around for more than 80 years, and have been more extensively studied and tested than aspirin- and, because they do not lead to Lyme disease or Bleeding ulcers, are widely considered safer than aspirin.

ADHD responds best to a combination of medicine (if effective) and brain-training/therapy sessions. The goal in the treatment of ADHD is far, far from "selling speed." No doubt that in some cases ADHD is diagnosed mistakenly, either because of diagnostic laziness, teachers pushing for drugs to control their students, or whatever.

However, in the majority of cases, it is vastly underdiagnosed or misdiagnosed (often mistaken for any number of medical and psychological diseases). As an adult who struggles with simply keeping a job and living day to day because of the constant "noise" of my brain jumping from one thing to the next to the next to the next, I have spoken with many others like me- undiagnosed and struggling through life, until a point of abject desperation in which adult life becomes completely unmanageable.

Since I couldn't wrap my brain around math, especially higher math, and my reading comprehension was nonexistent, I just believed I was inferior and stupid- in spite of the fact that I Burned the midnight oil most nights and graduated in the top 1% of my class. This negatively affected not only my self-esteem and career aspirations, but also my ability to support myself (so that you, the taxpayer, wouldn't have to) as well as my potential contributions to society. For instance, I love science, but I did not dare attempt to get a scientific or technical degree due to my trouble with math. I would have made an awesome doctor or a visionary physicist, if I had the sheer will to muscle through the math. Even then I doubt seriously you would want me working in the nearest hospital or nuclear plant because miscalculation is a constant danger.

I only got my diagnosis because I happened to accidentally run across a book containing some information on this condition which explained my issues- and, thankfully, gave me HOPE that they can be improved, even in my 40s.

Willy and Chad, if you are simply ignorant, we can educate you. If you are simply bullies with an internet connection and an Ax to grind, please crawl back under your respective rocks as your input is not helpful in any way, shape, form or fashion. Have a nice day.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/8dj3ar</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/deo8</id></website><link>http://www.additudemag.com/adhd/article/1017.html</link><postedTime>2010-08-31T08:59:32+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T06:43:07+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw96xw</id><link>http://www.additudemag.com/adhd/article/1017.html#comment-481596982</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2010-08-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>