<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miy1ml/post/2012-03-22T20:52:31</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body> FOR THOSE WHO DOUBT HOLMGREN....
 Well, the basics of the WCO were first conceived by Bill Walsh under the tutelage of Paul Brown. Bill Walsh took it to San Fran and perfected it while tutoring Mike Holmgren, a highly unknown and highly doubted young OC. Under that tutelage the young and inexperienced Holmgren began his journey to being the bigger than life figure he is today.
 He then went to Green Bay and tweeked it some more in a much Colder and windier clime and revived a poorly run and stagnant franchise and returned them their grand tradition. While there, he tutored Andy Reid who then took it to Philly and revived another poorly run and stagnant franchise and revived their grand tradition. While there, Reid then tutored Tom Heckert on the personnel end of it.
 Meanwhile, Holmgren then went to Seattle and revived another poorly run franchise without hope and nursed them to their very first taste of prominence.
 Then he took a couple years , vowing many times to not return, until he saw the similarities of ALL his experiences right here in Cleveland. Went out and hired his best pupil's best pupil in Tom Heckert and now here we are full circle where Paul Brown got it all started and modernized pro football.
 This is a legacy thing most undoubtedly for Holmgren and he wants nothing more than to repay the football gods for one of, and arguably, the greatest football dynasties of all time and the coaches it spawned, whom without, he'd not have his livelihood and opportunity for the Hall of Fame....
 When he said that he wanted nothing more than to restore the famed Cleveland Browns tradition, I'm a firm believer that he meant it. He went to Green Bay and did it, he'll most certainly will do it here, too. 

 FOR THOSE WHO DOUBT THE WCO CAN WORK IN THE AFC NORTH....
 San Francisco is cool, damp and windy city that at the time had an acient stadium that was wide open to the whims of the great bay in which it rested next to.
 Green Bay is a much Colder and forbidding clime with, you guessed it, an open and ancient stadium also at the mercy of the great bay it rests upon.
 Philly is a city with some of the most rabid sports fans, and although the climes are not as much a factor, has another ancient and foreboding stadium and with all the hot air it's fans can muster can be just as difficult a place to operate as the formers.
 Cleveland, on the other allows for a little of each. The unpredictability of a San Fran winter- by -the- bay, The Cold and wind of Green Bay, and the demon spawn that we lovingly call fans that's found in Philly.
 San Fran's rivals are the Cowboys (brought to prominence by another pupil of Brown's), Green Bay's is the most storied of all franchises in the Bears and Philly has to deal with the Giants and their even blustier fans along with Dallas to boot. See some similarities here with Cleveland and Pittsburgh ?!?!? Not to mention the whole Modell and Baltimore thing.

 In summary, if any thing can turn our beloved franchise around it would be the experiences of a man who worked hard and earned the experiences he has the hard way with a system that many have doubted time and again to be as successful or as resilient to the constant changes of this league. To doubt his method is foolish pride, and quite honestly, possesses an aroma of ignorance and bad attitude. 
 
 Thank You for playing along, 
        A TRUE AND DEVOTED BROWNS AND NFL FAN.   </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6eyvmq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/918x</id></website><link>http://www.clevelandbrownsreport.info/2012/03/cleveland-browns-and-west-coast-offense.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-18T09:34:14+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T00:52:31+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miy1ml</id><link>http://www.clevelandbrownsreport.info/2012/03/cleveland-browns-and-west-coast-offense.html#comment-474102984</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hkqq2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-18</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>