<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m73xd0/update/2012-02-27T12:17:21/9f70c0664dfbece44a2e1e40c473d78a07f7e728d1a011bda7ce7f3a8dacc392</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m72ph6</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lyhk8</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>W, I can imagine making 65 works of Art, but I`m afraid imagining is as near as I`ll ever get :)  Unless dodgy paintings count, I could easily manage 65 of them, given a little time.  Not sure I could quite generate the same love and affection that we have our band though.  Funny that 1984 should be the most...I was going to say unloved, but that`s the wrong word, so is unpopular...most unrepresentative is the word.  In a way, and this is the easiest way I can deal with the 28 years of hurt, a break was needed.  I`m pretty tired of Panama too, my fault though because it`s the first song I learnt to play properly, including the solo, and it`s my default song if I don`t know what to play or someone hands me a guitar lol. I don`t understand why people say how Dave should try and put lyrics to the Hagar- music - ok, I`ve been guilty of suggesting it myself when younger, because I thought it might save Eddie`s work - but I mean it is just not right, not DLR-right, and Ed and Dave were needing time apart.  I would have favoured a year or two, but I`m sure they knew what they were doing... 

Some people forget that the internet is like etching in stone, it isn`t like utterances spoken into the air that disappear, it is a permanent record; and with that in mind, I want to return your cyber-hug and let you know again I love the fact you offer me so much time crafting thoughtful and insightful replies :) 

I wasn`t evading the question about what would make me happy, I don`t think, not consciously anyway; but I don`t think I have an answer.  You are Spot on with your observation about reality-aware/complicated-happiness surely being better than regular-person happiness.  Nothing more terrifying than being conventional, and the horrible limitations that creates, but I don`t think we need to worry about that :)  And you are again correct to talk about giving oneself to others and the cost.  It`s something I`ve talked about before to people, how my work can be quite draining, emotionally, and I have little left to give to the people who are most deserving.  I`ve  been a believer in the idea that everyone should have a one-hour therapy session after work on a Friday, so they could leave their negative emotions behind, and spend time with the people they love in the right frame of mind.  Leaving the baggage at the office. 

I think my chances of happiness are dependent entirely on whether I can find some sort of fulfilment in terms of employment because frankly I`ve got the leisure time sorted!  I have few interests but many passions, if that makes sense.  And the thing that kills my mojo is the fear I have about work.  But if I can stand up for myself a little more - or at least put myself down a little less - that would help.  I don`t really know why I have such a chronic lack of confidence but it is pretty incapacitating, hence a lot of my time at home being spent doing things that I not only love, but am good at.  It`s important to have things that make you smile.  So I guess I do try to do things I love each day.  The (slow) pace does kill though, I`d much rather live like there`s no tomorrow.  I`m an appalling planner because I remain convinced that if you focus on making the next ten minutes great, then the next ten etc., everything will Always be great lol.  I`ve not quite figured how to do it, but it`s a decent goal.  Perpetual searching, yep, I like that idea; it removes the concept of failure and replaces it with experience.  Dave`s approach, right?  If you want to be a monk, you`ve got a cook a lot of rice.  That metaphor can serve us well.

Happy Trails, mighty Whispergirl :)
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ytu891</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/fbtm</id></website><link>http://www.vhnd.com/2012/02/12/rock-fans-give-van-halens-a-different-kind-of-truth-4-star-rating/</link><postedTime>2012-02-13T00:30:34+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-27T17:17:21+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m73xd0</id><link>http://www.vhnd.com/2012/02/12/rock-fans-give-van-halens-a-different-kind-of-truth-4-star-rating/#comment-450024659</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-13</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>