<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms1hub/update/2012-03-28T02:46:29/9349bc49781215cf2fbad0c69d888d33e8abf8690cdc1af20e20ef971f3b9176</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mipkpv</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hpzl7</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> Whether he is White or Hispanic, which I believe him to be 100% Hispanic, wrong is still wrong and, if he truly racially profiled the young man (which most of we know that he did) and if he did in fact use the word 'coon' then he has completed a hate crime.  Racism does not begin and end with White people, remember.  In the case of Black people, racism is almost Always the result of racism experienced by a racist person who has shaped that Black person's view.  The same applies to many people of color.  Now, in dealing with White racism, this can be the result of racist actions against that person specifically but is all too often the result of culture and upbringing.  

Views about other cultures of people passed down from generation to generation.  In this case, too many times, the person of color has to 'prove' that he/she is a good person before not being treated to racial indifference and/or the Cold treatment.  

The above are generally speaking but do not apply to every single person within the respective cultures.

Long story short: Zim, Lopez is Hispanic (probably of Mexican origin) and he wanted to be White because his step-father is white.  If his crimes were hate crimes, then they were the actions of a Hispanic racist person who wanted to be of the White racist variety - an Uncle Tom.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ybcfy</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ydw9</id></website><link>http://motherjones.com/node/168681</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T16:19:16+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T06:46:29+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms1hub</id><link>http://motherjones.com/node/168681#comment-478148386</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zlpcm</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>