<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/209309/post/127962932/comment/329759942</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Simple and decent?  There is nothing simple or decent to suggest that we ride and bilk ad revenue to raise money for an idea that you didn&amp;#039;t suggest before volunteering Rebecca to donate her money for anything. The mere suggestion could cause her to lose advertisers. 
 
As for the &amp;quot;anonymous&amp;quot; part.  Look around, the names here are not exactly telling of who is who.  Most people have made up names and clever ones at that.  For anyone to take charge and collect personal information, via Pay Pal is a very iffy thing.  Who does anyone trust with their real names and Pay Pal accounts, seriously?  Which one of us do we trust to gather funds and to deliver them? 
 
I tried to dance around your suggestion nicely, seriously.  You have a lot of nerve to tell Rebecca that she should be your muse to come up with funds for anything. 
 
For you to try to deflect this and &amp;quot;feel terrible for Fukui...&amp;quot; is cowardly.  Many people realize that your half-baked method is not the right way to go about this. I stepped up, I gave my e-mail address, I suggested that we go about this without implicating anyone, via Pay Pal, putting  Rebecca on the Spot to fund your half-baked idea and to try to do this in a decent, safe and somewhat assured way.  What did you do?  Hey Rebecca, let&amp;#039;s do something and YOU are going to take the hit!  I didn&amp;#039;t see you telling your e-mail address, suggesting a safe way to Reach this goal or do ANYTHING that would put you at risk. You passed the responsibly to Rebecca, someone you&amp;#039;ve had contact with for a brief month. 
 
I suggested, ad nauseam , that your idea was so super sweet.  I tried to inject humor into it.  I didn&amp;#039;t come right out and outline how your idea was so wrong. I tried to be cute and dance around it and obviously, I failed. 
 
User-of-Owls, take responsibility for your magnanimous suggestion.  Don&amp;#039;t pass the buck here.  Just DO IT.  You came up with the idea and I would like you to follow through with it.  I challenge you to do this and to do it right.  The ball is in your court.  I am starting to feel terrible for Fuki-san&amp;#039;s sake if you don&amp;#039;t deliver. 
 
 
 
 </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:209309:127962932</id><idPostId>127962932</idPostId><idBlogId>209309</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:209309</id><idBlogId>209309</idBlogId><link>http://wonkette.com</link><displayName>Wonkette</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://wonkette.com/468742/here-is-your-latest-obama-speech-for-you-to-fap-to</link><displayName>Here Is Your Latest Obama Speech, For You To Fap To</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T06:05:18.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:209309:127962932:329759942</id><inReplyTo><link>http://wonkette.com/468742/here-is-your-latest-obama-speech-for-you-to-fap-to#IDComment329389644</link></inReplyTo><link>http://wonkette.com/468742/here-is-your-latest-obama-speech-for-you-to-fap-to#IDComment329759942</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T06:05:18.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Here Is Your Latest Obama Speech, For You To Fap To by Barb</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://intensedebate.com/people/Barbara_i</link><idEmailMd5>2766bb4457adf6900cbbdbe1578d7208</idEmailMd5><displayName>Barb</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://intensedebate.com/people/Barbara_i"&gt;Barb&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://wonkette.com/468742/here-is-your-latest-obama-speech-for-you-to-fap-to"&gt;Here Is Your Latest Obama Speech, For You To Fap To&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>