<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwsmzb/post/2012-03-31T10:30:09</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>We are being ripped  for petrol tax, but the reality is, the government (for once) gave good advice on this.

If there is to be a strike, anyone with an empty tank will wish they had filled it. Yes, panic buying can make garages run dry, but at the moment, there's no actual strike, so the pumps can be refilled.

And aside from extra containers of a few litres more, people can't actually buy much more petrol than their car tank can store anyway.

We are being ripped Off for petrol by the government, and this is an argument in itself, but considering that it's possible there will be a strike, then it's only common sense to tell people to buy fuel when they can now, even if it's going to make garage's run dry (before being refilled again).

If we are all unprepared for a fuel strike, then when it comes, a panic buy will happen then ANYWAY, by those people who don't already have the fuel in their cars, and then after that, there will be no refills whilst the strike happens.

People seem to forget what happened in the last petrol strike when they we were all unprepared for it. It wouldn't be as bad for us all as last time, if we were all a little more prepared for it.

Better to Bleed the petrol stations dry now whilst they can be refilled.

And as for labour asking for resignations - I wish politicians of all parties would shut up with their knee jerk demands for resignations, it's ridiculous. 
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67i87f</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/earth/energy/fuel/9177951/Fuel-strike-government-fails-to-calm-panic-buying.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T13:44:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T14:30:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwsmzb</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/earth/energy/fuel/9177951/Fuel-strike-government-fails-to-calm-panic-buying.html#comment-481872766</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8cicl</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>