<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jcok/update/2012-04-02T02:28:14/4a73fde9a60bae6e9cf9382abd1e21cee92edb7bd0b18c6451d5412bf543a78e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>&lt;b&gt;Faaack.  Does anyone write like this anymore?&lt;/b&gt;

----------------
&lt;i&gt;"The ground belongs to me. It is the only possession I have not relinquished. Everything else has gone from me, little by little, but I have kept this. It was the subject of the only determined resistance I made in all the wretched years."

"Is it to be built on?"

"At last it is. I came here to take leave of it before its change. And you," she said, in a voice of touching interest to a wanderer, "you live abroad still?"

"Still."

"And do well, I am sure?"

"I work pretty hard for a sufficient living, and therefore - Yes, I do well."

"I have often thought of you," said Estella.

"Have you?"

"Of late, very often. There was a long hard time when I kept far from me, the remembrance, of what I had thrown away when I was quite ignorant of its worth. But, since my duty has not been incompatible with the admission of that remembrance, I have given it a place in my heart."

"You have  held your place in my heart," I answered.

And we were silent again, until she spoke.

"I little thought," said Estella, "that I should take leave of you in taking leave of this Spot. I am very  to do so."

"Glad to part again, Estella? To me, parting is a painful thing. To me, the remembrance of our last parting has been ever mournful and painful."

"But you said to me," returned Estella, very earnestly, 'God bless you, God forgive you!' And if you could say that to me then, you will not hesitate to say that to me now - now, when suffering has been stronger than all other teaching, and has taught me to understand what your heart used to be. I have been bent and broken, but - I hope - into a better shape. Be as considerate and good to me as you were, and tell me we are friends."

"We are friends," said I, rising and bending over her, as she rose from the bench.

"And will continue friends apart," said Estella.

I took her hand in mine, and we went out of the ruined place; and, as the morning mists had risen long ago when I first left the forge, so, the evening mists were rising now, and in all the broad expanse of tranquil light they showed to me, I saw no shadow of another parting from her. &lt;/i&gt;
---------------

How beautiful and wise and heartfelt is that?  Just...gah.  I still marvel at that ending after all these years.  Writing like this just comes from a special place that few writers can ever go, especially in this day and age (grumble, grumble).

God bless you, Charles Dickens.  You ramble on so, but when you geot it right, you hit it out of the goddamn park.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6v90q4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/great-expectations,71670/</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T21:00:31+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T06:28:14+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jcok</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/great-expectations,71670/#comment-483314431</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dod6i</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>