<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miybbb/update/2012-03-22T20:48:38/b8d08b3d4d39c45e6f5c6cd5865307618409a86cdcc269b817ba5b704cb38b8c</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The common thread is: Sidney Crosby makes his team better. Even in what for most players would be a lost season, Crosby has played only 12 games, but has 19 assists on the season (plus 2 goals) and is +14. 

It can be said that he's underpaid for the value and intangibles he brings to the Penguins...and he deserves that "C" on his jersey. The only problem with Sid: you can't predict concussions. That said, the real Headache for the Pens will be after the 2012-13 season when Crosby (and teammate Evgeni Malkin) both become pre-age 27 UFAs. 

But in the present, even though I see the Rangers holding Off the Pens for the top seed in the Eastern Conference, it can be argued that the Pens, with two weapons scoring at better than a point-a-game, and Crosby making bottom-6 linemates that much better, that the Pens should now be the favorites to come out of the East. Sid's a guy who can play on any line, first through fourth, and improve the play of his linemates and score. 

Yes he will have detractors whenever he is seen as embellishing a hit, but that aside, he's the symbol of today's NHL. 593 points in 424 regular-season games and another 82 points in 62 playoff games will do that.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yaace</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/r2nb</id></website><link>http://www.thehockeynews.com/articles/45621-THNcom-Top-10-Sidney-Crosby-moments.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T20:33:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T00:48:38+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miybbb</id><link>http://www.thehockeynews.com/articles/45621-THNcom-Top-10-Sidney-Crosby-moments.html#comment-474100942</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8if1v</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>