<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0owte/update/2012-04-02T06:18:17/c375dc09f6466f941078805b74ee5837a1df9b7611c50b631c4475e19477b4c2</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Kathlene Parker does the best she can bring herself to do in being "fair". 

She puts the best light possible on the life of Trayvon Martin...he's just a normal teenager....everyone gets suspended for marijuana use at school. Everyone posts obscene and threatening things on face book, 

We are not supposed to look at the facts of Trayvon Martin's life but we are supposed to make all kinds of assumptions about why Geroge Zimmerman followed him? "His suspicious behavior seems to have hinged on the fact that he was wearing a hoodie." Really? I didn't even hear that factoid until several days after the news broke. It may be something that the race baiters siezed upon as to how and why George Zimmerman "profiled" Trayvon. But as Kathlene says...everyone owns hoodies. I own a hoodie...although I didn't know it was called that until recently. And there is a difference between wearing a hoodie on a Cold winter day and wearing one in the dark in a gated community that had been subjected to break-ins in Florida...isn't there? 

Can't we use a little common sense? George Zimmerman was doing exactly what he was supposed to do...checking out a suspicious person in the neighborhood. He should not have had a gun. Trayvon Martin did only have a pack of skittles. But was that only because the police had already confiscated his backpack which purportedly contained burglery tools and women's jewlery? Ms. Parker leaves that tidbit out of her list of "normal" teenager activites from the "not quite as cuddly but no less attractive" Trayvon.

But all of this still does not justify Trayvon Martin being shot just for being there. And if that is the case than George Zimmerman should be prosecuted. If, however, Zimmerman was going back to his truck and he was jumped by Trayvon and being beaten than that is a different story. The race baiters have decided that the grainy video is "proof" Zimmerman wasn't beaten. This despite the fact it shows a police officer examining something on the back of his head. And isn't there a report from the paramedics? None of this will matter to the people invested in and whose careers Depend keeping the racial fires Burning in America. Even if there is paramedic report that confirms Zimmerman's story..... Even if the only witness on the scene says Trayvon was on top Zimmerman beating him.....won't matter. They will all just be part of some large conspiracy to hide the truth....as the Florida Congresswoman says..."he was profiled and hunted down like a rabid dog." No other story will suffice.

Meanwhile, in the past few weeks of the Trayvon Martin national spotlight, hundreds of blacks have been killed by other blacks (93% of black murders are by oither blacks) and no one really seems to care. Tywana Brawley, Duke Lacrosse...none of those gives the people rushing to judgement and politicizing the death of Trayvon Martin the slightest cause to step back and let the facts come out. The facts will never be allowed by some to come between them and their agenda.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6vsxm2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnei</id></website><link>http://www.charlotteobserver.com/2012/04/02/3139886/the-trayvon-martin-case-is-appalling.html</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T04:02:01+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T10:18:17+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0owte</id><link>http://www.charlotteobserver.com/2012/04/02/3139886/the-trayvon-martin-case-is-appalling.html#comment-483400842</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/chonk</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>