<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/e8wliy/update/2011-11-18T14:31:00/4fedae1c0255bbb60b663eef554cdb2312af1eedd8e4bc41b753e741a83af8fa</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/e8jjsu</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/asltd</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Several remarks:
I've never heard it said that atheists Burn in hell for all eternity.
In fact, you'll hardly ever hear hell being talked about in Catholic schools. If you ever spent any time in one you'd see that for yourself.

I like your argument that Catholics are just very good at brainwashing, it boils down to this: The fact that there's no evidence of indoctrination is proof of said indoctrination! LOL! Whose lacking empirical evidence for his arguments now? You're a parody of yourself, sir.

Indeed it is totalitarian to forbid the religious education of children IF THIS IS WHAT THEIR PARENTS WANT. You seem to have failed to understand an absolutely fundamental truth: the State should be wary of meddling in the family. It's a slippery slope towards benign paternalism at first, and then more and more coercive measures in the end. What you are basically saying is that you have understood what is best for (all) children - and be damned the parents who disagree with you. 

Religious Faith isn't irrational, although it can be. You seem to have confused reason with the natural sciences - but, as Dawkins himself admits, the natural sciences can't establish what our ethical norms must be - it is beyond their intellectual remit. Presumably, you hold that these ethical norms are not irrational. Therefore, reason has a wider  than the purely scientific. The Church would agree and say that philosophy, too, is reasonable, and Faith also. 
The false dichotomy and opposition you allude to here comes from Martin Luther for whom human reason was "the devil's harlot". Prior to him and indeed after him the Catholic Church Always maintained that reason and faith were complementary not hostile to each other.

You seem to forget that Catholic schools were started because either the state didn't bother to educate poor immigrant Catholic children or because bigots didn't want to have them in the same school as their own children. This is not the Catholic Church demanding to be supported by state funding in illegitimate fashion - this is the Church doing what the State failed to do and only subsequently being recognised for doing sterling work in education: that people of all Faiths and none acknowledge. Except ignorant people like yourself who prefer to remain in the certitude of their ill-informed prejudices instead of seeing how Catholic schools work in reality.
Pitiful.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/mk5j31</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/educationnews/8897782/Faith-schools-admissions-policy-discriminates-against-single-mothers.html</link><postedTime>2011-11-17T22:04:50+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-11-18T19:31:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/e8wliy</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/educationnews/8897782/Faith-schools-admissions-policy-discriminates-against-single-mothers.html#comment-367759233</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/m383b</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-11-17</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>