<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3uts1/post/2012-03-29T15:21:42</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xe87</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>That is the biggest set of nonsense to ever be published. It ignores reality and fact. this is arguing that selective breeding disproves evolution when they are completely different things lol.Yes some species can be altered through selective captive breeding. You used all selective man created version of animals. Now lets go to the horse. The wild stallionn has many different traits then say a crated by man clydsdale horse although the reasoning and thought of why it was done is similar. Ancient horses before domestication were much larger and varied greatly by the region they became entrenched. Horses that became landlocked in Cold areas changed and evolved as the weakest of that herd died  and the gene pool became smaller and more refined. Horse that wear heavier thicker coats or larger hooved for better travel in that terrain bred and became a subspecies of the same species. Horses that were broken Off and lived in hot climates thinned out leaving horses that were better suited to that climate and had thinner coats and better Heat tolerance.This is evolution in your face and easily seen today. That was funny what you posted as it was the worse attempt to dicredit the fact evolution does in fact take place by using domestic selective breeding as your example lol..Good laugh though</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zywi9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ogrn</id></website><link>http://godfatherpolitics.com/4435/another-stupid-argument-atheists-use-to-support-evolution/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T11:29:51+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:21:42+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3uts1</id><link>http://godfatherpolitics.com/4435/another-stupid-argument-atheists-use-to-support-evolution/#comment-479786856</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cadqq</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>