<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkpzhl/update/2012-03-26T16:13:51/9f8b8392b09151658e6fb31ae72702e930c2ef11b05ba24e9d0b86dbca38c7b2</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkfke5</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>You seem to have a different definition of "facts" than most dictionaries. Here are the facts, based on eyewitness testimony and police reports:

"Zimmerman called police and reported a suspicious person, describing Trayvon as black,  strangely and perhaps on drugs.Zimmerman got out of his SUV to follow Trayvon on foot. When a dispatch employee asked Zimmerman if he was following the 17-year-old, Zimmerman said yes. The dispatcher told Zimmerman he did not need to do that.There is about a one-minute gap during which police say they're not sure what happened.Zimmerman told them he lost sight of Trayvon and was walking back to his SUV when Trayvon approached him from the left rear, and they exchanged words.Trayvon asked Zimmerman if he had a problem. Zimmerman said no and Reached for his cell phone, he told police.Trayvon then said, "Well, you do now" or something similar and punched Zimmerman in the nose.Zimmerman fell to the ground and Trayvon got on top of him and began slamming his head into the sidewalk, he told police.Zimmerman began yelling for help.Several witnesses heard those cries, and there's been a dispute about from whom they came: Zimmerman or Trayvon.Lawyers for Trayvon's family say it was Trayvon, but police say their evidence indicates it was Zimmerman.One witnesses, who has since talked to local television news reporters, told police he saw Zimmerman on the ground with Trayvon on top, pounding him and was unequivocal that it was Zimmerman who was crying for help.Zimmerman then shot Trayvon once in the chest from very close range, according to authorities.When police arrived less than two minutes later, Zimmerman was Bleeding from the nose, had a swollen lip and had bloody lacerations to the back of his head."

If you can square away your accusations of Zimmerman being a stalker or a loose cannon with the account of events as it currently stands, by all means, enlighten us.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66oer2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/b0vv</id></website><link>http://www.insidehighered.com/node/36668</link><postedTime>2012-03-24T13:28:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T20:13:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkpzhl</id><link>http://www.insidehighered.com/node/36668#comment-476702976</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>