<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpo8u5/update/2012-03-22T01:18:56/f0491d1cc57a48fd321c155bf1ec48f38c1802abf6c53c3bf4c3995ca93c3377</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>














Children
sleep less .As pediatric sleep specialists and board members for the

American Academy of Sleep Medicine and the Society of Behavioral Sleep

Medicine, we feel compelled to point out that the critical tone of this article

is misleading and over-simplified. While there is still much we need to learn,
pediatric sleep

investigators have performed a significant number of rigorous studies to help

address the issue of optimal sleep duration for children. Research has helped

us establish the most appropriate range for total daily sleep time at each

stage of normal childhood development. These recommendations are used by

physicians who encounter pediatric patients with Sleep problems, and they

provide standard guidance for parents who are often concerned about their

child’s sleep.  Moreover, these guidelines on the recommended number of

hours of sleep are Always given in the context of other clues that parents can

use to determine whether their child is getting sufficient sleep.  For example,
well-rested children should wake spontaneously in the morning and should not
require additional sleep on weekends and during school vacations.  I thank
you Firozali A.Mulla DBA





</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6diaxn</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/bpum</id></website><link>http://ideas.time.com/2012/03/21/how-to-talk-to-young-black-boys-about-trayvon-martin/</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T15:08:27+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T05:18:56+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpo8u5</id><link>http://ideas.time.com/2012/03/21/how-to-talk-to-young-black-boys-about-trayvon-martin/#comment-473281888</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a6eq0</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>