<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gr17up/update/2011-09-28T13:36:58/e140d46e6a4a6e1d6a22e4b957e18817a63bfaf41c5e6532d5dfcad2eebea9a8</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gr4zeo</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zmkr</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>The key to giving up being 'Big Brother' would be to license your software, much as Microsoft do now, that way you really encourage innovation and encourage yourself to be more innovative in order to produce better kit than the people licensing your tech. 'Big Brother' methods would wholly include eradicating your opposition by suing the hell out of them. Most people not wearing the Cupertino issued rose tinted spectacles know that Apple are that 'Big Brother' now. Maintaining their iron grip over what you can and can't do with something that you have purchased  them, is 'Big Brother'. Randomly  'apps' from your app store, that's 'Big Brother'. Forcing everyone to vend their stuff your way so that you can take a hefty fee, that's 'Big Brother'. Telling you're users that 'there is no problem', 'it's you that's causing the problem', 'there may be a problem', 'there is a problem' like they did with the Antenna problem, that's definitely 'Big Brother'. 

Apple may not be claiming to have invented many things, but they sure as hell keep silent about the people who have whilst they patent features that have existed long before they used them. The rose tinted Cuppertino spectacle wearing iFans certainly claim that they invented all sorts of things that they so clearly didn't. They had a CEO who issued the famous quote about 'Great Artists' etc. and then happily sues the ass of all and sundry who he unashamedly claimed did exactly what the 'Great Artists' that he admired did.

As for the 'Touchscreen phone's didn't work' comment. Nice try sunshine, but I still have some of those old touchscreen phones and they did and indeed do still work. Don't be like the rose tinted people claiming all sorts of alternative histories. Touchscreen phones did work and sold in their millions before the iPhone and continue to still sell to this day. I'm assuming that you are based in the U.K. if you still need convincing, lets meet up and I'll show you them. I touch the screen and something happens, a touchscreen phone if you will.

Ah the 'Prada phone' chestnut. I wasn't actually going to quote it but seeing as to how you are obviously spoiling for a fight I will. What people said about it, thought about it doesn't matter. What does matter is whether it existed before or after the iPhone. It existed before and incorporated possibly more similar features than the supposed 'iphone copy Samsung phones' being wrangled over today. The absolutely laughable stream of rubbish that the rose tinted people Always come out with goes like this. There was nothing before the iPhone. Then when you point out the evidence it's. 'But nobody liked that, nobody bought that'. The last time I heard, nobody was sued because they were popular, they were sued because something they made existed before in some format or other.

You like your chosen tech? Good on you, I'm pleased for you. Me I like what I've chosen, but do me this one favour. Don't pretend history never happened, and don't pretend that Apple are the good guys. They are a corporation like anyone else out to make money, end of story. My main beef with them is that they are a corporation using the kind of practices that I and loads of others find very very distasteful. That alone would be enough, but then denying that you are using those kind of practises and claiming to be the innocent party is going one bit too far. If I'm going to be mugged, I'd far rather be mugged by someone who has the decency to admit that they are mugging me than by someone who tries to convince me that they are doing me a favour.

Before you answer this, unless you are actually going to read this and be reasonable, I'd rather you didn't bother. I've heard it all before and argued against it all before. I'm an educated person who works in the tech industry and have a hunger to learn as much as possible about everything. I do my best to be as correct as I can with my posts but where I'm not, I'm quite prepared to be proved wrong. Unfortunately you won't be able to prove me genuinely wrong without using conjecture, I'm not interested in conjecture just Cold hard facts. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/m2oikr</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/nw4s</id></website><link>http://betanews.com/2011/09/24/apple-patent-lawsuits-are-hypocritical/</link><postedTime>2011-09-24T14:30:35+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-09-28T17:36:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gr17up</id><link>http://betanews.com/2011/09/24/apple-patent-lawsuits-are-hypocritical/#comment-321946697</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/glco9</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-09-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>