<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mil75g/update/2012-03-23T01:33:51/326d2f455d34096ae05278f492cccc0ce70990950d4d04b00b0964e32dab48c8</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Well, in the vain of Touch going with a one word title, let me give you a few more words:

Great. Brilliant. Exceptional. Outstanding. Emotional. 

Touch is yet again another notch in Fox's belt of great television shows. Yes, yes, I know what your going to say: Well this was just like the premier. And honestly, your right. But should it have been any different? Should it have changed the way the first episode works? 
For the second episode, I would say 'No'. '1 Plus 1 Equals 3' was a Pilot 2.0 if you will, and I think it was a great thing to do. For people who didn't watch the Pilot 1.0 this was a great introduction into the relationship of Martin and Jake. For those of us ( myself included ) that did watch Pilot 1.0 it was a great reintroduction to an Idea/Concept we may not be exactly 100% fresh on ( it was almost 2 months ago ). Relationships and characters we may have not fully remembered.

The big question will be: Can the show continue in this same fashion, running the risk of being more procedural with hints of mythology here and there. I really do believe it can. First and foremost the preview for next week looks like it's attempting to bring in more of the bigger picture and foreshadowing Jake may be needed for a much larger purpose. I feel like every episode there will be some mythology elements here and there ( think Alcatraz ) to point us to something larger they have in store. However, even if they don't include as much mythology as I'm thinking they will, I think it will still do just fine as a procedural. There are so many things about this show that hooks me in ( and hopefully others ) that they don't necessarily NEED a larger mythology hook ( at least this season ). 

The relationship between Martin and Jake is just emotionally jarring. My god do they know how to pull at those heart strings. You feel so bad for Martin and you just want to  through the TV and give both him and Jake a huge hug and help them figure this all out. Jack Bauer ( I will never be able to call him Keifer Sutherland after 24 ) is just fantastic. He had some emotional stuff on 24 but NOTHING like this. And yet again, he knocks it out of the park! He is obviously a 'Tour De Force' when it comes to . Round of applause Jack. And Jake, my god can that kid . The "tantrum" he had when Martin picked him up in the apartment, just superb. For playing a Mute kid that little man is just talented. 

The stories this week were great as well, and your heart just warms when pieces of each of them come together. Hearing Pavlev talk to his dad and ask him "Dad, you aren't a bad man that hurts people are you?" and watching his Dad tear up and hesitate to answer before finally delivering the answer was just powerful. The middle eastern man coming back to the US to bury his dad the way he wanted, the dog that lead the flight attendant to her sick dad ( and Martin &amp; Jake ), Pavlev to his Dad, and of course Jake leading Martin to Arnie all just great stories. I swear I gasped in shock when Arnie still tried to jump Off the bridge even after Martin told him how he and his daughter still cared about him. After knowing this man, and his story for only 40mins you rooted for everything to be okay with him. Great storytelling. 

I know a lot of people have a problem with Tim Kring but I personally like him quiet a bit. I even liked Heroes throughout ( it wasn't as good towards the end, but far from terrible ). This is a much better outing for him though. His writing was Spot on tonight ( and Pilot 1.0 ). Emotionally gripping.

I love this show. For numerous reasons as I've said. The Pilot sold me so well, I'm hooked from here on in, however long that is. I can't wait to see where things go from here. If we are all really connected like this show displays, we live in a crazy world beyond my wildest dreams. I can't wait to continue the journey with Martin and Jake to bring people together who just need to be TOUCHED. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ys1gn</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/g6o1</id></website><link>http://www.spoilertv.com/2012/03/poll-what-did-you-think-of-touch-1-plus.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T01:56:21+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T05:33:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mil75g</id><link>http://www.spoilertv.com/2012/03/poll-what-did-you-think-of-touch-1-plus.html#comment-474231173</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gdlmt</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>