<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkfjf3/update/2012-03-26T12:52:53/805b2a42f8b4d0fb72a1c21f5ccbf82c98886f4cb0a09f616e8ef43899c7e255</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>AT LAST..... Some truth. Well done "red issue", time to stop this ghastly grief-fest, especially the teddy-bears and sea of flowers by complete strangers who seem to lead very shallow and unfulfilled lives if all they can do is wallow in someone else's grief or misfortune.

We had it with Diana and how every bloody "expert", pundit and joe bloggs could state with authority on whatever issue that "It's what DUYANNNAH would have done".

But the WORST, by FAR is Liverpool and their total Paralysis, locked in a timewarp over HILLSBOROUGH.

Yes it was terrible, but where is the grief over the thousands killed when Liverpool was blitzed. Although Yorkshire Police were bloody awful, sorry lads, but there WERE a lot of drunken, loutish Liverpool fans pushing to get in without tickets. Why else would every bloody football stadium have wire fencing all over the place?? To keep the police out?? Or to keep stupid drunken berks from beating seven shades of shit out of eachother because they were "wearing the wrong scarf/hat/colour"?? 

Funny how selective our memories are. The Nazis and Communists also attacked and killed people who were wearing the "wrong" clothes, wrong colour/religion/ideas... PATHETIC.. 

And every bloody year we get the whining mawkish bitching about "Hillsborough" and how "nobody understands" poor us.... It's TWENTY THREE BLOODY YEARS FFS.

The worst bit is there is ALWAYS some bloody Labour MP, or political leech attaching themselves to the "event" raking up the past like a cat uncovering the crap in its littertray and bleating about the "Tories". 

Oh yes and at least one dopey and pathetic fading "celeb" grief-parasite using it to relaunch a dying career or release yet another bloody version of  "You'll never walk alone" that all of the Anfield-Inadequates will snap up, together with the commemorative black arm-bands.

Sorry, but it's gone much too far. It is ludicrous that an entire city, once the powerhouse of England, Liverpool, is now known for two things, one of the highest benefit bills in the universe, and of course its mawkish fixation with "Hillsborough". And why no similar outpouring of communal grief over the dreadful events a Heysel and the useless Belgian police and authorities??

Manchester doesn't have an annual Sob-fest and puke-a-rama over the tragic loss of life from when their team was decimated in that awful air-crash in 1960.  Bad things happen and I just about remember that one.

It's SICK, it's UNHEALTHY...... Not so much Walk On, as MOVE ON.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r0ybp</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/sport/football/teams/manchester-united/9167751/Manchester-United-fanzine-Red-Issue-defiant-over-Fabrice-Muamba-grief-junkies-cover.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T15:44:56+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T16:52:53+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkfjf3</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/sport/football/teams/manchester-united/9167751/Manchester-United-fanzine-Red-Issue-defiant-over-Fabrice-Muamba-grief-junkies-cover.html#comment-476533653</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a0hih</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>