<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/midyau/update/2012-03-22T18:55:14/3e3ff158995770a39ffb5ecc97235ad047ec8821a0b750fef46801a51764921e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Thank You President Obama for doing what you said you would do regarding healthcare reform.

I remind myself the ultimately the vast majority of my personal health Depends on me and my actions. A healthy mind and body is created over a lifetime of good eating and exercise habits. 

The sad truth is that in America, 1/3rd of us are overweight, and another 1/3 are obese. Think about this for a moment. Just one in three of us are of a healthy weight. Being overweight is caused, by and large, by two things: poor eating habits, and little or no exercise. These two things are fully within the power of each of us, either as adults, or as parents. This is why we must do the hard thing and pay attention to our bodies and minds, and eat well, and exercise on a regular basis.

When I drive by McDonalds at 3:00 pm in the afternoon and see a line of cars wrapped around the drive-thru window, I realize that all the healthcare reform in the world will not change our fundamental problem of overeating of unhealthy and toxic junk food. 

As many of you know, 20 months ago my wife and I made a conscious effort to eat well and exercise, and to teach our two small children good eating habits. Since then, our children consume more vegetables (willingly!) than any children I have ever seen. We all four exercise (my wife does Roller Derby believe it or not), and I run. The result? None of us have been sick (not even a Cold) during the past two winters' "Flu seasons." Our immune systems are healthy, strong, and taking care of our bodies because we eat mostly organic meats and vegetables (and recently, milk). I dropped 25 lbs. and am now within the "healthy" part of the Body Mass Index chart (just barely though).

For the vast majority of us the best insurance for a long, healthy life is in our hands. 

Yes We Can!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yo646</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7ngc</id></website><link>http://www.barackobama.com/news-secure/entry/the-story-of-the-affordable-care-act</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T21:14:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T22:55:14+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/midyau</id><link>http://www.barackobama.com/news-secure/entry/the-story-of-the-affordable-care-act#comment-474036683</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gxoj2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>