<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/323728/post/127788901/comment/327476404</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>R.I.P. David S Joyner 9-1-1953 / 9-15-2010 
You taught me that hatred, anger, and fighting is of no use. 
 
&amp;quot;Nothing else matters; all that truly matters in the end is that you LOVED!&amp;quot; 
 
I see it as a rare occasion to have someone else touch my life so deeply and yet so unconditionally. Going though the process with David was a long hard road but I would do it all over again for him. David touched many people in so many different ways. He sort of just craved a place in your heart and he entered - silently. 
David had an opinion and he was not afraid to share it with you. He liked to be in control and he was one person who could put me in my place when I was out of (or even IN) control. I will never forget our long hours and hours of talks about everything and anything. Sure he made up stories at times but he never hurt anyone with them (that I know of). You just knew he had some secretes that were too deep to remember so he just changed the characters and story line to one that he could hold on to. He only wanted to see me happy. He never, ever, EVER crossed a line, hurt my feelings, disrespected me or expected anything other than true friendship from me. 
 
We often discussed &amp;ldquo;what forces brought us together as friends?&amp;rdquo; I had met David through a mutual photographer friend. At first it was sort of an occasional passing hello when we were both over at our friend&amp;rsquo;s house. Then they moved to Bellingham and I went up for a holiday dinner. David and I both loved to cook! He liked to cook alone and I like group kitchen kayos. So I slipped right in with him and we cooked together like we were dancing the most organized, choreographic dance. We laughed, and we bonded like no other 2 people that day. Who knew???? We began our journey there in that kitchen on that (Thanksgiving?) Day. 
 
We were sort of the odd couple &amp;ndash; me a petite 5&amp;rsquo; 2, (kinda preppy) (very) white girl and him a 6&amp;rsquo; big teddy bear kind of (very) black man who sort of looked homeless most of the time. We had NO inhibitions about who we were and what we felt for one another. If it was grocery shopping (one day I even took him clothes shopping with me. He would put up with a lot from me). We took trips to Bellingham, Ocean shores, Portland &amp;ndash; we would hit the big Seattle events: Hemp Fest, Bumper Shoot, and Gay Pride, anything he felt he had the energy for. He was ONE OF MY KIND &amp;ndash; He loved to watch people (from afar), He walked this earth with his eyes wide open. He Loved with pure, raw love. The world and the people in it was both our living breath. We skipped down streets arm in arm, we sang at the top of our lungs (he actually was a good singer &amp;ndash; for me &amp;ndash; he put up with it &amp;ndash; God bless his soul). We ate a lot of good food, we took care of a lot of &amp;ldquo;business&amp;rdquo; and people looked and whispered but nothing mattered! We did not flinch from one another&amp;rsquo;s side. He was rough, He was tender, He showed me what an unconditional friend really is. I learned a life time of lessons in a few years of knowing him. He is a mentor in many ways and his little carved Spot in my heart will  remain open so he has a safe, loving place to rest when he needs to. May he (were ever he is right now in his spiritual world) be at peace, laughing and feel the love that we all shared. 
 
People come and go in our lives &amp;ndash; but no one has given me such Joy. As he would have said &amp;ndash; take it as it is but be gentle. Farwell my dear friend I will see you again&amp;hellip; someday&amp;hellip; </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:323728:127788901</id><idPostId>127788901</idPostId><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:323728</id><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><link>http://www.chrisisright.net</link><displayName>Chris Is RIGHT</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2010/09/18/rip-david-s-joyner-911953-9152010/</link><displayName>RIP David S. Joyner: 9/1/1953 - 9/15/2010</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2010-09-19T08:48:26.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:323728:127788901:327476404</id><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2010/09/18/rip-david-s-joyner-911953-9152010/#IDComment327476404</link><postedTime>2010-09-19T08:48:26.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on RIP David S. Joyner: 9/1/1953 - 9/15/2010 by Sri R.</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>5842bcb95eee9142c66e62ac40ee9e5e</idEmailMd5><displayName>Sri R.</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>Sri R. commented on &lt;a href="http://www.chrisisright.net/2010/09/18/rip-david-s-joyner-911953-9152010/"&gt;RIP David S. Joyner: 9/1/1953 - 9/15/2010&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2010-09-19</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>