<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miyln8/post/2012-03-22T20:24:19</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>You know, the Chance Vought SLAM would be the perfect weapon for a nuclear ingenue.  It is so simple they called it the flying crowbar.

Best competition for DU ever, just fly the thing for an hour, or a couple of weeks, and Fukushima wouldn't seem so bad at all for the northern hemisphere.

You see, it doesn't have a conventional jet engine, just a very hot radioactive pile that Heats the air up hot enough to  hot gases and radioactive particles out the tailpipe. If you blow it up, you contaminiate whatever it blows up over and everything  for several hundred miles downwind. Plus it can fly under the radar. At mach 3. With no jet fuel - NO KEROSENE, GASOLINE or OIL.

Now Iran could make one as a test bed for peaceful aerospace applications for nuclear power. Hey, if we can do it, Why not them?

The program was cancelled in 1961, so the technology is old, simple and easily duplicated.

We have used DU on Iraq and Afghanistan. Hell, all you have to do is set one of these babies flying circles Off the coast of someone you feel is threatening you and just leave it cruising around and around until someone decides to back down. What are they going to do? Blow it up? Sure, that just spreads all the radioactive material out at once.

Imagine a sexy Fukushima or Chernobyl with sleek wings flying at mach 3 spewing out radioactive fallout!

Hell, that could earn Iran a permanent seat on the UN Security Council.

Of course, landing the thing may be a bit of a bother.

Then again, who wants a peaceful solution?

Certainly not any of OUR leaders. Look what happend when Gaddafi sued for PEACE.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y9zxj</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lk8h</id></website><link>http://www.wired.com/dangerroom/2012/03/secret-nuclear-drone/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T19:47:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T00:24:19+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miyln8</id><link>http://www.wired.com/dangerroom/2012/03/secret-nuclear-drone/#comment-474087890</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dlnxd</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>