<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwcigp/update/2012-03-30T05:18:17/51c164b74eb6e3c4ed88f5255fcb3850db084f9babaca6ef65535f81628ba6c9</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwc8sw</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g2lpd</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I saw you gave it 2 stars on Goodreads. It could be anything, but like I said I found myself bound to the book.
Interestingly enough, I was talking about our lack of bra Burning events with my husband last night. We grew up very strong women in our family, ladies who can stand on their own two feet at all times, but never were we made to feel like men are the enemy, or that we were in any way inferior (although I do let my husband open stuff for me, doors, cans and bottles - makes him feel purposeful). I never even knew there was a battle going on. I lived my life, and I have never been discriminated against for being a woman. Not that I can honestly say I would've noticed. Maybe I just thought they did not like me. This is both a good and a bad thing.
This book did however open my eyes to the exclusion of women, something to which I never paid attention, and for which I am not about to go and stand on the battle line for. It is just good to know that despite legislation, women are still not seen as equal in their contribution to the world we live in.
But maybe we have our own battles. Being a generation X-er, we fought hard to  a purpose, we wanted to change the world, but no one before us was able to show us how (it is Always hardest to be the first ones out), but we cleared for the ones that followed a way to find purpose in their lives. We also have the eco battle, the destruction of our earth. Some of us are growing up blind to that, and some of us are tying themselves to trees in the forest. Maybe this is our battle, it just lacks a
very definitive battle ground. For us to win, everything must change. But
we are getting there, one little step at a time.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zl0q9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/qx8t</id></website><link>http://www.journey-keeper.com/2012/03/review-unless.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:05:53+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T09:18:17+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwcigp</id><link>http://www.journey-keeper.com/2012/03/review-unless.html#comment-480549233</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dr4jk</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>