<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwf9db/post/2012-03-31T01:39:30</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Let's look at 2 scenarios:
The first one has Zimmerman walking in the neighborhood, legally carrying his concealed weapon, he Spots this 6'3" "person of interest" skulking thru the homesites, very close to the houses, calls in to the Police.

At that time they tell him that he shouldn't continue to follow him. While he is talking to them the "suspect" disappears.

He decides to go back to his car, when at that point the "suspect" appears and confronts him.  
They exchange words and the younger, larger "suspect" attacks him, a fight ensues and he is threatened with death, fears for his life.....the suspect is shot and killed by Zimmerman.

The second scenario has a young, intelligent, articulate boy who has never been in trouble, that leaves his house to run to the store to get some skittles. 

While walking home and trying to stay out of the rain, he decides to walk under the eaves of the houses as he cuts thru the private property of the homesites, where upon he attracts the attention of the local neighborhood watch person. 

Since there have been several burglaries in the area this person is concerned and calls the police to make them aware of the "person of interest". 

They tell him to not follow, so he goes back to his car, where...while walking back to his car the 2 cross paths. 

He asks the young man what he is doing there, accuses him of "sneaking around the houses" (as it appears to him) and the young man is insulted and tells him to F Off.

 A fight ensues and supposed threats are made and the Z Man fearing for his life or that at the very least he is going to get the s h i t  beat out of him..... pulls his gun and shoots the young man dead. 
______________________________________________________________________________________

Either story is possible....or any combination of these scenarios are possible......we don't know!!!!!!
______________________________________________________________________________________

What we do know is that Obama, Jesse, Al Notsosharp ton and Spike Less have decided to make this into a race issue.......where one NEVER existed!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!

B  l  a  c  k  s are being played by a 50/50 b l a c k /w h i  t e president, to stir up h a t  r e d , r a c i s m  to make the b l a c k s hate the w h i t e s  so they won't vote for a white person for president!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!

Even tho the 50/50 b l a c k /w h i t e  p o t u s has done nothing for the b l a c k  people since he has been in office......less jobs, more foreclosures, higher gas prices, less "hope" more "change" for the worse ......

And, made this country a worse place to live in 3 short year than it ever has been at any time in the American history!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zp9dz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yjmx</id></website><link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2012/03/29/trayvon-martin-witness-casts-doubt-on-shooters-self-defense-claims/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T04:01:25+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T05:39:30+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwf9db</id><link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2012/03/29/trayvon-martin-witness-casts-doubt-on-shooters-self-defense-claims/#comment-481570582</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z68oa</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>