<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3pxbm/post/2012-03-29T20:32:31</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>There are many things in this world that are safe to eat, but does that mean we  really want to? Is it wrong to at least be informed of what we are eating? If it  is so good and so safe, why has the industry worked so hard over many years to  keep you from knowing about it? Sometimes the real truth is better   hidden.

I have known about, and have been disgusted with "Pink Slime" for  years. "Pink Slime" is a fairly new name. Its  just been known as filler  in the past. But with its new name and the speed of the internet, many people  are just coming to know about it now. For years before quitting meat altogether,  I would just buy roasts and make my own burger.

The meat industry likes  to describe the product as "Fatty Bits of Meat" left over from other cuts.  Sounds benign enough, doesn't it. If that is all it is, it really didn't need a  flowery name of its own. "Lean Finely Textured Beef." Thats just to throw us Off  track. And notice that the finished product is now called beef. Any part of the  cow can be called beef, even if it is no longer classified as meat.

And  the finished product is not meat. Parts of the cow are used that are only safe  to eat because of the stringent cleansing and Heat treatment ritual it must go  through to remove and kill the pathogens. Skin, hair, noses, sinew, tendons, etc  are not meat.. Industry whistleblowers have even stated that floor sweepings are  thrown in the mix. This product was produced long before it started showing up  in our burger. It was added as a filler to Dog and Cat food. And don't be  fooled, it was an extremely profitable move.

I don't care what people  choose to eat for themselves and their families. I just don't take to well when  folks are not given the information they need to make informative choices, if  that is important to them. And in cases like "Pink Slime" there is actually a  concerted effort to keep the buying public from knowing what they are consuming.  When I lay out cash, I like to know what I am buying. And I hate being  deceived...

Many would rather not know or deny than to have to make  choices or changes..Thats up to them. But even if the truth is ugly and hard to  swallow, it still truth, and that is important to me.

Read more: http://democratherald.com/news/headlines/pink-slime-producer-defends-its-product-as-safe/article_4c5d2eb6-79bf-11e1-8e9d-001a4bcf887a.html?mode=comments#ixzz1qXeTKhM7</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ldd71</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6rx1</id></website><link>http://www.sltrib.com/sltrib/money/53795345-79/beef-product-company-letch.html.csp</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T23:01:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:32:31+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3pxbm</id><link>http://www.sltrib.com/sltrib/money/53795345-79/beef-product-company-letch.html.csp#comment-480071599</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g4n72</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>