<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3sedd/post/2012-03-29T23:15:29</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>They brought their child to an ER for a Stomach-ache. They should know that it will cost them about $4000. I did the same thing this Monday night. My 14 yr old had a Stomach-ache. My daughter's urine came back negative, her blood work came back negative, her white count was normal. (The Grandpa on your segment said that his granddaughters blood was fine so they should have known it wasn't her appendix. Sometimes that isn't the case) They gave my daughter an ultrasound...which also came back negative. She did not have a Fever, but kept saying her stomach pain was an 8. The pain was under her rib cage, and was not presenting at all like appendicitis. The last test they gave her at midnight was a CT scan, which revealed that she did indeed have appendicitis. She had surgery at 7AM Tuesday. (they bumped her ahead of the other scheduled surgery's for that day) If the ER doctor had just sent her home, it would have ruptured. I will double (triple) check my bill, however I expect it to be towards $4000+ just for the ER portion of our stay at the hospital. The family on your segment should be lucky their child was OK...and pay the bill...minus any charges for tests that were not done. (Always check all hospital &amp; doctors bills, and then double check with insurance on coding and coverage! Insurance companies mess up too) This story just hit home for me this week.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z16m7</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t33k</id></website><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/2012/03/29/have-you-ever-looked-at-your-hospital-bill/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:33:23+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T03:15:29+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3sedd</id><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/2012/03/29/have-you-ever-looked-at-your-hospital-bill/#comment-480191624</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzf34</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>