<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpdj6r/update/2012-03-21T10:28:11/f031e06ceb110895f8eab81cbbcbba7275c4b757a5f61a028792933be467a9af</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Great Article! I would also like to say it is great to see those that do support Arlington Voice &amp; have taken the time to talk to Arlington Voice as I have seen no other media outlet doing the job of The Voice. As for Capehart &amp; her comment "the Arlington Voice lacked the integrity to report on anything fairly" how would she even know when she has never spoke to Arlington Voice. Like the recent forum she chose not to attend, she is speaking volumes to the citizens of the city of Arlington as where she stands &amp; it is not the best interest of this city or citizens. I am sure her clucky has lied to his council about The real VOICE of Arlington but what does one expect from gov that claims to report news. After all, those that lie don't like to be put on the Spot for it makes them look bad &amp; cluck would know all about that since he has an tendency to forget what his action &amp; words are but thank goodness for Freedom of Information Act and Videos. I think any council that refuses to speak to the citizens &amp; rather bash what they don't approve of should be replaced. I love that Arlington Voice is shaking things up this next election with the truth and citizens are opening their eyes to what this council is doing to OUR city. Darrell Castillo did an excellent job at the forum and if he can't unseat Capehart I think his name has a great chime as Mayor Castillo in the next round of elections! </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6d7rh8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/9xch</id></website><link>http://www.arlingtonvoice.com/content/councilwoman-possible-victim-internet-sabotage</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T05:14:06+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-21T14:28:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpdj6r</id><link>http://www.arlingtonvoice.com/content/councilwoman-possible-victim-internet-sabotage#comment-472380707</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>