<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0pme9/post/2012-04-02T06:41:48</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Mr. Romney Im sure is a nice guy, but we are not here to elect a nice guy, we are here to elect a Presidential
candidate a leader, Mr. Romney is a finger in the wind candidate and is a afraid to make a decision until he checks the pools, if Mr. Romney truly cared for the United States of America, he would be the one who would step aside.

Mr. Romney is not from the Ronald Reagen School of the Republican Party, Mr. Romney comes from the
Bush school of the Republican party as I call it, It believes in using Ronald Reagan's messages but does not 
believe in it, they are Big Liberal lite, they believe in big government, just like the Democrat's, and these guys
helped  the democrats get the country in the trouble it is in.

One of Mr. Romney's big supporters is Mr. Bob Dole a true American Hero and a good senator but as exciting as a turnip falling Off a turnip truck, He once ran for president I supported Mr. Dole but he blew it
and was crushed, the fact is he comes from the Bush wing of the party, he like Mr. Romney are believers
in the new world order, not the United States of America!

I will not support Mr. Romney he is A big government liberal republican.


See I happen to believe in the Constitution of the United States Of America, and the Will of We the People.
to many people like the author above want to shut out American voters and deny them the chance
to vote on their candidate. from Pennsylvania to Texas we are being denied our chance .

People like this need to keep their mouths shut and let the process continue, telling people to get out is a
sign of weakness, beause they fear a brokered convention.

they also fear the political process of the republic.

by this very message.

I have been a republican since I turned age eighteen, Iam now Fifty and this will most likely is the end
of my membership, I think I will become an independant.

My advise to the party is make Paul Ryan Speaker of The House.

and get rid of the Cry baby.



</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6vm7ab</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rlyt</id></website><link>http://visiontoamerica.org/8999/its-time-for-rick-santorum-and-newt-gingrich-to-end-this-madness/</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T02:03:42+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T10:41:48+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0pme9</id><link>http://visiontoamerica.org/8999/its-time-for-rick-santorum-and-newt-gingrich-to-end-this-madness/#comment-483412130</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>