<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31pni/post/2012-03-29T16:21:02</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>1.) You have to do a press conference. It's lottery policy. Just quietly answer questions and leave it at that. 
2.) Call a lawyer. Don't tell him your situation (might want to go out of state for this one), and just explain that you have to make some financial decisions and need some advice. You want fair, good advice, and you don't want to be milked. If you Act based on his advice, any mistakes fall on him, thus if you are sued, you won't be responsible as long as you followed his advice. 
3.) Call an accountant for the same reason as #2. 
4.) Look into mutual funds. Investing $10,000,000 with a measly return will earn you big money as long as it can keep up with inflation. Assume a recently-typical year of inflation at 2.5 - 3%. If you can invest at 4%, that means you get $100,000 back ON TOP of the adjustment for inflation. 
5.) Know who your friends are, know who your family are. This is your money, so you can feel free to help out whomever you want. Do know that YOU WILL find every friend and family member come out of the woodwork hitting you up for cash. YOU WILL have a lot of scammers too.

My solution for #5? Ask them where they were when you were going through your divorce/family member death / some other major event (make one up if you have to). Their reaction or bullcrap response will reveal to you exactly who they are. 

Splurge, but don't be dumb. If you're responsible with your money, take the lump sum. If not, restrict yourself to the annuity payments (it's tough to say you'll be responsible when you have this major windfall). Buy yourself things, but remember that ALL things have hidden costs; sports cars have higher gas and insurance costs, big houses have bigger insurance, Heating, electric, tax, and furnishing costs. 

Enjoy yourself, and never forget who you are. There are too many sad stories where people turn into someone they're not, spend frivolously, and then end up worse than they were to begin with. You can enjoy massive amounts of money while still being humble at heart. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zvp8f</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ao2w</id></website><link>http://www.wivb.com/dpp/news/local/how-should-winner-handle-mega-millions</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:53:50+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:21:02+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31pni</id><link>http://www.wivb.com/dpp/news/local/how-should-winner-handle-mega-millions#comment-479848638</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ro60k</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>