<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk15k9/post/2012-03-26T11:09:40</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Ahh. Birth control... 

After several years of the pill and the NuvaRing, with one accidental pregnacy in between, I learned that my bipolar meds interfered with my hormonal BC. As a result, I did Depo for 4 years -- LOVED it, didn't  weight, loved not having my period, loved everything... except 1) after several years, you're encouraged to transition to a different sort of BC, because Depo causes reversible bone density loss [just how reversible - we're not sure - hence getting  Depo], 2) over time, it caused some weird menopause type symptoms for me [thinning of my labia, easy chafing, yuck]That said, I loved Depo but I had to get  of it after 4 years of . Then I had Mirena inserted - theoretically awesome, practically awful. To the point about expense - my insurance covered it, but it is worth considering cost if yours doesn't. It's helpful to know that you're saving loads of money that you'd spend monthly/yearly on other forms of BC, though. Anyway, back to that... Though I've had an abortion, I've never been pregnant past 7 weeks -- while prior pregnancy isn't a prereq for IUDs, a slightly stretched uterus may be beneficial. Apparently mine was too small -- but it took months to figure it out. Had the thing inserted in May of 2010; spent a full day in massive pain (I was convinced I was in labor and that my body was trying to birth this IUD); eventually got over the pain but never stopped Spotting. Had one really terribly embarrassing experience in December 2010 where a longstanding crush (gahhh, we high fived after we kissed - my high school best friend's twin brother - seriously, a 10 year crush) was going down on me and  up to grab my left tit, which was half-in a pretty lacy white bra... at which point we realized there was BLOOD, EVERYWHERE. Not my period. Just blood. Lots and lots of blood. I hid in the bathroom until he went to bed. I was 27 (no excuse for hiding in the bathroom). Awful. Anyway, I hightailed it to my gynie who:- quickly identified a friable cervix - sent me  for a transvaginal ultrasound- then quickly determined that, shit, my uterus was too small and the damn IUD was stuck halfway through my cervix- then removed the IUD, whew.NOW, I'm no longer on medication for bipolar. I'm back on NuvaRing. I love it, except when I wish that I could be on Depo again - I really don't appreciate monthly menstruation (especially once I've experienced living without it). But it's super convenient, you think about it basically never, and it can be funny during sex when it lassos my partner's penis. Fun times without pregnancy. Or Weight loss/Gain.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6elsek</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tdqu</id></website><link>http://www.xojane.com/issues/help-me-find-new-birth-control</link><postedTime>2012-03-18T13:48:02+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T15:09:40+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk15k9</id><link>http://www.xojane.com/issues/help-me-find-new-birth-control#comment-476457398</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/at5ox</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-18</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>