<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkpig7/update/2012-03-26T16:36:55/4d8a34120c8a4658bfce0dde5a03a47f19e7c94377fd62e5e7a5da0fa070ba0d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>For once I think I can speak with some authority on the matter under discussion. I live near Sevenoaks and have a daughter who went to Primary School there, passed her 11+ and now goes to a Grammar School elsewhere. I would love that she could have attended one in Sevenoaks and that there were sufficient places available for more of her Primary School friends to attend with her. 

This, I can assure you, is the attitude of most parents in Sevenoaks who recognise that a Grammar School education, if you don't have the odd £100K Burning a hole in your pocket, is the best way to help your children achieve good results. I love the fact that she is in an all girls school, not because I am a kill- and don't want her to meet boys. She does that outside of school hours anyway. What I don't want is for her to be distracted in the class-room by boys showing Off and girls pretending to be thick so they don't frighten them away.

So why not send her to a Comprehensive? Well those of her friends who failed their 11+ and went to the Comp are already very different in attitude and likely attainment. Parents throughlut Britain should be demanding Grammars for the bright ones and Tech schools for the less so. 'Comprehensive' is a misnomer that suits no one very well and destroys academic hope. They should be abolished.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l5dt6</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/secondaryeducation/9167347/A-new-era-dawns-for-the-grammar-school.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T19:35:02+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T20:36:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkpig7</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/secondaryeducation/9167347/A-new-era-dawns-for-the-grammar-school.html#comment-476723427</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/e2if3</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>