<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3i211/update/2012-03-29T20:57:49/aba2f2147f9cfab8b4770699ba6d52cd9a48d8ff953cccdef013574b66deed73</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The facts (this should be an article):

Just about every electronics company (including Microsoft, Intel, Nintendo, Sony, Samsung, and yes... Apple) uses this Chinese plant Foxconn to assemble their machines. While the jobs don't measure up to western standards, this is actually a pretty desirable place for Chinese people to work. Whenever there is a job opening, people line up around the block for a chance to work there. A few years ago, some Foxconn workers tragically committed suicide. Much was made of this story, but it turned out to be overblown. You see, Foxconn is such a large company that despite the number of suicides the rate was actually LOWER than the rest of China. This means that if you are Chinese and work at a Foxconn factory, your chances of committing suicide are less than if you didn't work at a Foxconn factory. Remember though that these guys make all your electronics. Foxconn workers making XBoxes threatened to jump  the roof last year if their pay wasn't increased. It was increased.

Now a little bit about Apple. Apple was flailing badly in the 90s and they finally returned to making a profit with the return of Steve Jobs and him introducing the iMac computer. Then they had a string of huge hits: the iPod, iTunes, iPhone, and now the IPad. But during the flailing, their far more successful competitors (Sony, Samsung, Nintendo, etc.) were using these Chinese factories to assemble their wares. No one said anything. It's now an issue because for as many people who unreasonably love Apple as a company, there are just as many who unreasonably hate Apple as a company. Remember that Microsoft was the largest computer company in the world and despite making mostly software, they also are in the hardware business with mice, keyboards, and XBoxes and all their other peripherals. No one mentioned factory conditions. Samsung is a giant and were MUCH larger than Apple in the 90s, but no one said a peep about factory conditions.

Apple is feeling the Heat because some people just hate them and want to see them fall. Performer Mike Daisey performed a stage play where he positioned flat out lies about working conditions as facts, news companies published these lies, and only a few retracted them when they were brought to light as being lies. Apple is investigating the factory that they (and many others do business with) and it's still looking like there's a hit job on Apple. Apple is not perfect but they are doing more than any other electronics company, doing audits and making promises to improve working conditions for workers at this factory that everyone does business with. What I want to know is where are all the other companies using Foxconn?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6znb8o</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rvx5</id></website><link>http://money.cnn.com/2012/03/29/technology/apple-foxconn-report/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:41:06+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:57:49+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3i211</id><link>http://money.cnn.com/2012/03/29/technology/apple-foxconn-report/#comment-480091128</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6cbkm</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>