<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6n5a/post/2012-03-30T11:33:26</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Rev. Boissiere was teacher, pastor, connector, mentor, motivator and inspiration to so many in the Union community--from prospective and current students to alums, staff and faculty.  The legacy of her service is considerable: Trailblazers, the Alumni/ae Council, the Henry Mitchell Preaching Series, launching the Jackson-Mitchell Chair and much more.  There is no excuse for having this central and accomplished community member fired and walked Off campus on the eve of a conference she championed and brought to Union to lift up Union's own legacy as the birthplace of Womanist theology.  No excuse.  (Thanks to NYTS for stepping into the breech that weekend.)

Supposedly protecting Rev. Boissiere from the shame of some horrid thing she did or would have done to harm Union, Pres. Jones said (quoted above), "there was not a disregard for the effects of this decision, but there was no way not to make that decision."  Hooey and for shame!  Rev. Boissiere did nothing but good for Union's administration--those who know her could never believe she had plans to do *anything* worthy of immediate termination.

Neither Rev. Boissiere nor anybody else could call down the kind of harm on Pres. Jones that she has brought upon herself through the years of truth-veiling and bold-faced lying this asinine firing brings to light.  May the spirit of truth and compassion visit Union's leaders and guide their steps.  May those who honor Rev. Boissiere's ministry and her legacy in our community keep the flames Burning.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/668dle</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/8eg8</id></website><link>http://www.columbiaspectator.com/2012/03/23/uts-pres-draws-ire-over-faculty-firing</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T08:53:08+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:33:26+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6n5a</id><link>http://www.columbiaspectator.com/2012/03/23/uts-pres-draws-ire-over-faculty-firing#comment-480862801</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>