<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mighmx/post/2012-03-22T16:11:52</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mps8lm</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/y8230</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Drugs Comapnies:

Autism epidemic but we are not allowed to comment on the story in this paper (see health section).

In 2003 they started to vaccinate babies at 2 months instead of the normal 3 months.

5 injections are given at 2 months

5 injections are given at 3 months

5 injections are given at 4 months


Its not the MMR which is given at 12 months this is a distraction often used by others. The babies are being damaged before they Reach 5 months but they cannot tell anyone and no one notices.

No one notices that the children have stopped looking for their parents and do not even try to turn their head when they hear their parents voice (a child who has not been affected by the vaccines will do this).

The huge increases in allergies also goes hand in hand with the damage caused by this attack on babies before they are 5 months old.

So why have they not done any research to compare countries without the vaccines to 1st world countries with the vaccines??

The drugs comapanies and governments do not want to do this research because they know what they will find. 

My advice is to delay the vaccines until the child is 12 months old when the child is already saying its first words. This is when the measles vaccine is given so why are the other vaccines being given at 2 months old?

It is £5 per vaccine for the doctor for each vaccine given so £75 per baby. Seems to me the doctors are forgetting to ask questions.

Proof of this lack of care is bourne out by the fact that Thiomersal (packing agent floats ontop of the vaccine) was in the whooping Cough vaccine for babies up until 2003. Doctors knew mercury was in this vaccine but dismissed concerns saying it was a very small amount even though they know it is extremely poisonous and cumulitive (it never gets removed from the body). The drugs companies eventually and very quietly withdrew it. 

Questions still need to asked. The rate of autism will increase until the correct research is done and the causes identified.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ylfwc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/finance/budget/9159673/Budget-2012-Glaxo-to-invest-500m-in-UK-and-create-1000-jobs-after-cut-in-tax-on-patent-profits.html?fb_xd_fragment</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T07:53:18+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T20:11:52+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mighmx</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/finance/budget/9159673/Budget-2012-Glaxo-to-invest-500m-in-UK-and-create-1000-jobs-after-cut-in-tax-on-patent-profits.html?fb_xd_fragment#comment-473902113</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cuhqw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>