<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39zc9/post/2012-03-29T17:34:45</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Well, I think your protest here is naive.  I'll echo what a few others have already said on this thread: 

The problem is that no other group in society claims the authority (sacramental and doctrinal) that the priesthood does.  They are supposed to be holy, and when they are not - especially when it involves the sexual abuse of innocents, in an Era of contention over Catholic sexual teaching - the scandal is inevitable.  

Also, in my eyes the problem is not the priests.  It's the bishops that committed a criminal conspiracy to cover up the malfeasance.  That's what Burns me.  All the apologies and prevention programs in the world will not erase that scandal.  not when the men who perpetrated it (with a few exceptions, like Cardinal Law, and even he enjoying a sinecure in Rome, and not in jail where he belongs) are still in power.  

I know of no major criminal conspiracy to keep abusive teachers in their jobs.  When they are caught, it seems that they are fired and jailed.   That's why there is no scandal there.

The bishops are to blame for this.  Mat God have mercy om them for their betrayal.  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/dvg69x</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/bj2j</id></website><link>http://www.patheos.com/blogs/badcatholic/2011/12/how-to-win-an-argument-with-a-catholic.html</link><postedTime>2011-12-20T19:09:49+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T21:34:45+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39zc9</id><link>http://www.patheos.com/blogs/badcatholic/2011/12/how-to-win-an-argument-with-a-catholic.html#comment-479921894</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-12-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>