<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/59j72d/update/2011-08-15T02:15:42/43edfed4341185bfbf4f9b71cf25ba2c031449cadd906b8949df878ce303abfd</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/599ky4</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g98hb</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>While I agree with you that Jesse is not a smart individual, I feel you miss some of the nuances of the character.  I do not interpret the actions that you cite as being indicative of a short attention span.  Rather, I think they reflect his increasing apathy to life.

Keep in mind, that Jesse has one of the most tragic character arcs in television. As the series has progressed he has become more intimately involved with death. In the beginning Jesse essentially witnesses the deaths of Krazy 8 and Emilio - Mr. White murders them.  Yet as the series progresses, he witnesses increasingly visceral deaths: Tuco beating his grunt to death (sorry I forget the name), and in Peakaboo, the junkie getting his head crushed by a ATM.  In addition his perceived involvement in the deaths around him increases.  He blames himself for the death of Jane (although he is only partially responsible).  This culminates in him being responsible for the death of Tomas.  Although he did not pull the trigger himself, he did initiate the series of events.  The descent is completed when he murders Gale in Cold blood.  And throughout the series, we see just how deeply these actions hurt Jesse.  Ever since meeting Mr. White his life has gone to hell.  In the context of the series he was  a junkie, but he was forced to become a killer.  So when Jesse leaves the money unguarded, or has the constant rave, he is not doing so because he is stupid.  He is doing so, because he needs to detach and numb himself.  I thought his actions made it pretty clear that he didn't care that the money was stolen, and his increasingly reckless behavior made it pretty clear that he didn't care about living... he was essentially just going through the motions.  

Throughout the show, Jesse has shown moments of being remarkably perceptive- not the most eloquent, but perceptive.  And was his comparison really that far Off?  He understands how the system works, regardless of scale.  I think it is also unfair to blame him for what happened to Combo, or to say that Badger winding up in jail is a reflection of his incompetency.  Remember that Mr. White pushed him to expand the territory and to take credit for his new found street cred...  And if it weren't for Mr. White, Jesse's life would have never been in danger to begin with.  Their relationship has been far from symbiotic - Mr. White has used Jesse again and again, all the while belittling him and treating him as incapable.

There have been many moments in which Jesse has been quite stupid.  But I think that the events that you cite certainly have deeper meanings than to just say that Jesse is an idiot...  I guess that was a little pedantic, but I hope I made some sense.  I absolutely adore Breaking Bad and I think there is a lot more to Jesse than simply being an idiot.  I would argue that he was the closest thing to a moral compass in the show.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ehsija</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7d9s</id></website><link>http://tv.ign.com/articles/118/1187819p1.html</link><postedTime>2011-08-15T04:30:00+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-08-15T06:15:42+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/59j72d</id><link>http://tv.ign.com/articles/118/1187819p1.html#comment-286813880</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ymjlg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-08-15</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>