<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/234352/post/86320894/comment/329743600</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Procuratorate handling the case: Song Mountain wood conviction chain of evidence complete without the polygraph victim voluntary sexual relations with the Song Mountain wood Rowan\'s statement Song Mountain Wood\'s testimony confirm each other, confirmed the Song Shan Mu reason with Rowan to the scene, is due to the resignation of Rowan is determined and explicitly rejected the retention of the Song Mountain wood, this fact can exclude the Rowan want access to work through the Song Mountain wood on the benefits of the possible. Rowan after the incident from a number of witnesses confirmed to return to his home in words and deeds of performance, take the initiative to tell her boyfriend Song Mountain wood sexual assault, and select the incident the next day early morning alarm the public the fact that such an important personal privacy,abercrombie, you can also exclude Rowan would like to obtain the benefits of monetary motivation from the Song Mountain wood body. In addition to Song Mountain Wood\'s counsel to attend his mother and relatives of three people to attend the sentencing, he sees his son very excited mother Song also loud solidarity with his son: related to the reaction of the sentencing scene verdict on the analysis of the three major focus of controversy Rowan also said that the incident occurred,monster beats solo, she is just out of college students, I would like to particularly asked just out of the female students\' attention to their own safety, be careful on the right to see and The thing to analyze, try to avoid harm is likely to make their own private contacts. And if it may be obscene, cherish life, and as much as possible to preserve evidence and to protect their interests. court held that the Song Shan Mu and his defenders polygraph test only to provide direction for the investigation one of the means test results do not have the exclusive, can not be used as evidence in the available evidence polygraph test can prove the facts of the case without the parties. Song Mountain wood emotional one killed in the barrier. Strong emotions, Song Mountain wood a lot of curse the foul language. Song Mountain wood to present new evidence that female subordinates voluntarily and its relationship support you! interview. She said that up to one year and five months, until finally a fair judgment, sorrow,polo Ralph Lauren, Rowan said, Rowan said from the beginning, Song Mountain wood sophistry, said she was for the money proved to Rowan just want a fair judgment rather than money, the so-called industry vicious competition in the trap does not exist, including the polygraph and so is just an excuse, he just wants his crime by these remarks to elution. of in December last year, Luohu District People\'s Court on Song Mountain wood case first instance verdict, Song Mountain wood rape, sentenced to four years, and compensation for economic loss in an incidental civil plaintiff Rowan (a pseudonym) 4205.87 yuan. After the verdicts, Song Mountain wood appeal that the statement of the Court of First Instance alone Rowan presumption against Rowan\'s will to forcibly have sexual relations with Rowan, finds that the facts are unclear, the lack of evidence, requesting the court to revoke the original judgment in accordance with the law. commuted the appellant not guilty, or remand the case to the people\'s court for retrial rejected the incidental civil action the plaintiff\'s claim. Song Mountain wood confession,ralph lauren pas cher, said Rowan said they did not not only under the advice of the Song to resign, and take the initiative to seduce Hill Wood Song, Song Mountain wood in the passive case and Luo Fasheng a sexual relationship. Rowan statements Song Mountain wood called about to shoot their nude threat, although did not get the wooden telephone call records of Song Mountain Song Mountain wood camera content confirmed, but can give a reasonable explanation of Song Mountain wood called about the intention to pose a threat to the Rowan heart, and there is no real phone call. In Song Mountain wood camera after May 4, and Song Mountain wood before May 4 content intentionally deleted out and to the memory filled with new content, May 4 a few days ago of the content can not be recovered, Song move suspicious Song nude delete, there may be no real camera, there may be a memory card is changed back into. Call and nude photos are Song Mountain wood used to a means of intimidation Rowan, Rowan inner fear, without requiring the call does occur from the camera found nude in order to identified Rowan statements as true. Song Mountain wood was the most unconvinced, is a huge difference, then he and Rowan, nearly the opposite case, why the court would adopt Rowan\'s words and not believe in yourself, and as a basis to judge he raped Rowan, he felt that the judgment said, He said that even if he is still serving a sentence, will find the opportunity to defend themselves while in prison, and also find ways to serve their sentences end polygraph, to see who was lying. Song Mountain wood respondent rape continued: the defendants requested the polygraph denied lasted 1 year I Song Shan Mu rape case was finally settled yesterday afternoon, the Shenzhen Intermediate People\'s Court of the Song Mountain wood case upheld the sentence, the appeal of Song Mountain wood,longchamp, the hospital announced to dismiss the appeal and upheld the original, is about to face up to four years in prison, this result feel dissatisfied with the sentence after listening to the emotion and adhere to the the court the victim\'s statement alone condemn him, He said in court that the report in the end, but also up complaints on this result. Rowan incident,chaussurefoot, a time when the menstrual period, in terms of its physiological, not possible voluntary and active with others to have sexual relations. Rowan in a sexual relationship before, during and after no to Song Mountain wood raised any interest requirements, and Rowan after the incident and did not remain in the Group of Mountain wood for Song Mountain wood alleged may give its benefits, so Rowan said forced the Song Mountain wood is in line with common sense. As for the Song Shan Mu said the complaint, Rowan said, I believe the law will give her a fair judgment. Rowan did not immediately report the incident, but call their boyfriend crying, whether or not to report the heart contradictions, this is in full compliance with the state of mind as the one just out of inexperienced young unmarried woman, after all, the report is tantamount to personal privacy made public, its reputation and future life will be a major impact. Rowan statements thought quietly left the company, but worried about nude after being shot against the encouragement of her boyfriend, she chose the alarm. Hill Wood Company remitted to 5772 yuan on its account reported, and some of them their wages, more part Song Mountain wood since that compensation given, this can not be identified Rowan was voluntary sexual relations and Song Mountain wood for the money. Song Mountain wood whether the threat to victims of the language and shooting nude Yesterday afternoon, the Shenzhen Intermediate People\'s Court took the second-instance verdict, said the Court held that the appellant Song Mountain wood contrary to the will of the victim Rowan,louis vuitton pas cher, Song Mountain wood by cleaning brought to the scene for the famous Rowan, and use Rowan on the scene of a strange, remote environment, the use of pretending called about intimidation Rowan Rowan adverse dared not resist, and then forced Rowan clothes Off to be shot nude, and put to nude photos Rowan further threat to the Internet, and ultimately achieve the purpose of the adultery Rowan. Song Mountain wood behavior constituted rape. Rape in the conduct of the appellant Song Mountain wood cause the victim economic loss, shall bear corresponding civil liability. The original verdict, the facts are clear, there is ample evidence, accurate conviction, the penalty was appropriate, legal proceedings. 3 &amp;gt; reports: the victim did not immediately report and after receipt of money the &amp;#30456;&amp;#20851;&amp;#30340;&amp;#20027;&amp;#39064;&amp;#25991;&amp;#31456;&amp;#65306; &amp;#33509;&amp;#30007;&amp;#23376;&amp;#22806;&amp;#36935;&amp;#36180;20&amp;#19975;&amp;#20928;&amp;#36523;&amp;#20986;&amp;#25143; &amp;#23130;&amp;#21069;&amp;#21327;&amp;#35758;&amp;#21523;&amp;#36305;&amp;#20934;&amp;#26032;&amp;#37070; School bus core set of 11 solid contained 27 kindergarten party without educational qualifications ( Husband hiding his wife 380 000 lover a court deci police criticism, the father of the baby Blushing even said: I remember the police officer told Mr. Jiang said 
 
[WORDPRESS HASHCASH] The poster sent us \'0 which is not a hashcash value. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:234352:86320894</id><idPostId>86320894</idPostId><idBlogId>234352</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:234352</id><idBlogId>234352</idBlogId><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog</link><displayName>Wanton Wordsmith</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/</link><displayName>The day he went away</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T05:32:04.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:234352:86320894:329743600</id><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/#IDComment329743600</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T05:32:04.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The day he went away by avfduwb55</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://www.abercrombiefitchh-fr.biz/</link><idEmailMd5>8b0ffcc4b7f6fc3d545fd6f1632399f9</idEmailMd5><displayName>avfduwb55</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://www.abercrombiefitchh-fr.biz/"&gt;avfduwb55&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/"&gt;The day he went away&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>