<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/maho8e/update/2012-01-31T12:57:01/7f6f9e521abda6fa37ff64940bc4de92bc792cdcd1c30be412e7398a73256d0d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Energy_guy:
Thanks for your elaborate answer.
But man you are stuck in the old &amp; failed paradigm of energy production &amp; consumption.

For example, you are right about nuclear being a massive waste of energy, because they produce alot more Heat than electricity.
You just fail to grasp the right conclusion and venture right into fantasy land.
You write it would be possible to utilize 2000MW of Heat from a 1000MW reactor... how? Concentrate all the consumers around the plant? But consumption is not centralized... build a massive distribution network?
And what happens when the nuclear reactor is down for regular or irregular maintainance?
Just in December a nuclear reactor in southern Germany had to make an unplanned shutdown due to 2 out of hundreds of fuel-rods being damaged and needed replacement. The sudden loss of available capacity seriously put preassure on the grid.
How is the Heat provided in that case? Or do you need an new backup system then?


If 2 out of 200 windmills need maintainance, the output drops 1 percent. Not to mention that 200 7,5MW windmills are less than half the price of a nuclear reactor.

We don't need a 100 year old concept to run the 21st century world. Furthermore I think you are too fixed on CO2 as a problem. The Ressource&amp;Availability Crisis is also problematic... relying more and more on Uranium or Thorium (if that would actually work) still leaves us stuck with a fuel-market and huge dependencies at infringe on our liberty &amp; ability to  acording to our believes.

Renewables are scaleable and allow massive efficency Gains due to synergy effects.
Take an average US county with say 5000  households:
-3 modern windturbines for cheap surplus electricity
-1 or 2 Biomass plant for electricity &amp; Heat
-roof top solar for individual energy production
-community storage with power-to-gas
-biogas fired co-generation in public buildings &amp; high energy consuming buildings
=&gt; more than enough energy for electricity, Heat ( and transportation).

Initial investments per household:
10.000 Dollar =&gt; cheap, clean and secure energy for 20-30 years.
More money stays in the community, a few more jobs and independence.

Add to that:
+better building standards to reduce energy waste
+convert or buy LNG/CNG-Cars to use biogas
+Use hybrids to utilize your own rooftop solar.

</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/djdyvk</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/amtr</id></website><link>http://www.treehugger.com/renewable-energy/over-half-germany-renewable-energy-owned-citizens-not-utility-companies.html</link><postedTime>2012-01-06T20:32:20+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-01-31T17:57:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/maho8e</id><link>http://www.treehugger.com/renewable-energy/over-half-germany-renewable-energy-owned-citizens-not-utility-companies.html#comment-425585742</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zrg3b</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-01-06</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>