<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mswp7o/update/2012-03-28T14:36:29/a62a30af04046cc4ccd82e059d80cdc6666c9b4ae5ba43e6a09ff4b58cdaec27</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Vieira is, of course correct. Henry Winter's column on the Fulham game was dreadful. He spent half of his allocated column inches trying to justify the referee's decision although he accepted it was a penalty. Is he a complete fool, or does he just get stupid when he is writing about his darling United? It really was pathetic, embarrasing and dreadfully tacky. His parents would be ashamed.
The referee against Fulham was a coward, he did not have the guts or the nerve to give what was clearly a penalty. At this stage of the season he should be struck  for being such a whimp. For goodness sake, why does Ferguson strike such fear into referees? Its only a piddle of a business, Uniteds turnover is around 300 million, a tadpole in the world of finance. He's only the manager for goodness sake, not the ruler of a far east Country that could have your hand cut Off for stealing an apple! 
Yet referees Shiver at the name, they stand transfixed like rabbits in a headlight. What a complete bunch of dipdops they are. As for Henry, well words fail me, it was embarrasing to read his words, nothing but sickly homage to his god Fergie. At least Patrick Vieira has the guts to say what 90% of supporters think, good on you Patrick, why don't you apply for a column on the Telegraph? It would be much more interesting I am sure than the sickly drivel Henry came out with recently, oh my, was his great, great, great Grandfather Uriah Heep? </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hvo7r</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/sport/football/teams/manchester-city/9171857/Manchester-United-benefit-from-refereeing-advantage-says-Manchester-City-executive-Patrick-Vieira.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T15:49:03+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T18:36:29+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mswp7o</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/sport/football/teams/manchester-city/9171857/Manchester-United-benefit-from-refereeing-advantage-says-Manchester-City-executive-Patrick-Vieira.html#comment-478635400</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ev002</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>