<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwq03t/post/2012-03-30T19:09:36</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>A Flash movie would be awesome.  The trick to telling Flash tales, though, is not to depower him (as others have), by taking away his ability to move at the speed of light, but to set well-defined consequences when he does.  This can create a specific reaction time for something that will not result in harmful consequences of his speed to his environment, a slightly shorter reaction time that will produce some consequences (blowing out windows and eardrums breaking the sound barrier), and an even shorter reaction time with much more severe consequences (Reaching critical mass and ripping a whole in Space/Time). The question for villains then becomes, "what can I achieve with a 2 second/0.5sec/nanoseconds/femptoseconds... window of opportunity?", or, "How can I expand my window of opportunity?", and Flash then needs to weigh the consequences of pushing the envelope of his speed.

This is why Flash's Rogues are special (he's the only hero who's rogues regularly team up against him), because they each have different methods of achieving that task.  Cold can slow him down with ice, Mirror can distract him with illusion, Trickster with traps, and, of course, Zoom creates a level playing field.

Anyway, Flash can do more than just move fast.  Vibrating his molecules through solid material is just one clever use of his powers, he can also vibrate through different planes of existence, and travel through time.  No need to have him start shooting lightning bolts or anything.  He is a complete character just the way he is.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67rnaq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/jybj</id></website><link>http://www.superherohype.com/news/articles/170051-screenwriter-dan-mazeau-updates-on-bleach-the-flash-and-jonny-quest</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:06:33+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T23:09:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwq03t</id><link>http://www.superherohype.com/news/articles/170051-screenwriter-dan-mazeau-updates-on-bleach-the-flash-and-jonny-quest#comment-481303205</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>