<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jxu6/post/2012-04-02T03:58:16</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Dyanna keeps getting brought into the boardroom, and Trumps likes it that way because he can look at her more. It's so obvious that Dyanna feels safe because she knows that Trump has, politely-put, a soft Spot for beautiful young women. And so do many of the men watching.

Adam Corolla, Dee Snider, Debbie Gibson, and Patricia Velasquez were all obviously stronger competitors than Aubrey, Lisa, Dyanna, and Lou. If you had to do business with someone, would you rather have the first four or the latter four?  I'd definitely choose the former four, with some reservation, maybe, about Dee. That's where Celebrity Apprentice competition gets silly. Last season, Gary Busey was kept around past the point of being ridiculous until he was finally fired. I could only conclude that it was because Busey was good for ratings.

The problem with both Lisa and Aubrey is that, while they have been the most pro-active,  they're also entirely obnoxious and poisoning morale everywhere they go.

While Debbie's dress was tight-fitting, her t*ts were far from "hanging out", and that was just a low-class attack. Let's put it this way; it's lower to repeatedly make that kind of personal attack in the boardroom than it is to wear inappropriate attire, and I don't think Debbie's attire was inappropriate. I wouldn't have hugged Theresa, either. Other than that, Debbie just rose above it, and she's done that a lot. Dyanna, Theresa, and Debbie...and Trump fires Debbie. Stupid.

BTW, how is it that Paul Teutel is the only person excused from ever wearing anything resembling formal attire? He dresses less formally than I do for my office job on a dress-down Friday. The guy's wearing jeans, a t-shirt, and windbreaker! Boy, he's good at flying under the radar.

I hope Penn wins, because he's the best of all of them. Clay and Lou don't like Penn, but he's been nothing but cordial in response to their objections, but both Lou and Clay conveniently ignore this. Also, they all acknowledge Penn's great intellect, but it appears that this has only been because Penn is so evidently smart--I don't get the impression that he's tried to push himself Off as being smarter. At the same time, he was entirely apologetic and open to Lou's and Clay's criticisms.

The finale should've been Penn versus Debbie. Now, it might be Theresa versus Paul. Ridiculous.


</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6vwvx8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/vh3p</id></website><link>http://tvrecaps.ew.com/recap/celebrity-apprentice-episode-7-aubrey-oday-arsenio/</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T06:00:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T07:58:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jxu6</id><link>http://tvrecaps.ew.com/recap/celebrity-apprentice-episode-7-aubrey-oday-arsenio/#comment-483337558</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>