<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwfgyw/update/2012-03-31T00:51:41/2a8dad12d9796f1a7f58da6907fcbe5cad9d23a394bfcfa4cfa176b3ed962d45</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The first thing that entered my mind when I saw that Spike had tweeted out that address was his portrayal of Mookie in Do The Right Thing. 

Mookie is the kid who, after an appeal for peace by the authority figure ("the mayor"), starts the riot instead by throwing a trash can through Sal's plate glass window.

I looked at Spike's tweet when it first came out and said to myself, "Spike, you really see yourself as Mookie, don't you?" Which explains why he didn't feel the need to apologize when this innocent couple was forced to flee their home.

But then, after several retweets of Spike's own home address and the kind of real-world pressure that never got applied to Mookie in the make-believe world of Spike Lee's imagination, our real-life Mookie decided to apply the better part of valor and retreat before his own house got Burned to the ground.

Do The Right Thing was a formative cultural happening for me. Really one of the greatest pieces of art ever made portraying the urban racial landscape. Now we have a better idea why Spike's character was so realistic in that movie--he wasn't Acting. He was hot to throw that trash can in real life. 

News flash, Spike: real life isn't like the movies. Real people get hurt when you do incredibly stupid things.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67ctrd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yv37</id></website><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/blog/2012/03/m-spike_lee_did_the_wrong_thing.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T12:47:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:51:41+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwfgyw</id><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/blog/2012/03/m-spike_lee_did_the_wrong_thing.html#comment-481543414</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mlhvf</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>