<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msxxqf/update/2012-03-27T22:36:55/a47658e682713816abd81a10c1715f4db8db2d1bab51e6edccb968fbb69b8d5e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Since this article mentioned Lord of the Rings, I'd like to rewrite the Lord of the Rings ending so that it now has the Mass Effect 3 ending. Since the Mass Effect 3 ending came out of nowhere and was logically, emotionally, and thematically inconsistent with the rest of the series it should have no problem being dropped at the ending of any story.

*Frodo drops the ring into mount doom and begins to Bleed to death. Suddenly, a white light appears! Frodo finds himself mostly healed and at the top of a tower somewhere. A small little magic child appears*

Magic Child: Hello. I control Sauron and the Orcs. This is all part of my solution. You see, advanced civilization will probably destroy the entire world some day, so I created these bad guys to wipe out all advanced civilization. But now that you're hear, I've changed my mind.

Frodo: Great, so you can just tell the Orcs to go home, right?

Magic Child: No, I don't want to. Instead, I'm going to give you one of three options. You can destroy the Orc, but this will also kill all non-human life on middle earth. You could control the Orcs, this literally has no downside and you're kind of stupid if you don't choose it. Finally, you can choose synthesis. This combines all Orc and non-orc DNA to create a new type of life. This sounds drastic, but mainly it just makes people's eyes glow in the dark. And no matter what you choose you die. And also all magic is sucked from the world. And all of civilization is completely reliant upon magic. In fact, without magic you won't even be able to travel between kingdoms. And the  of sucking magic from the world causes huge explosions that will wipe out every major city on the planet and probably kill more people than the Orcs ever will. Choose now.

Frodo: Ok, uh, I guess I choose control?

*We're treated to a brief montage of Orcs falling over and people Cheering. Suddenly, we see Aragorn in a boat trying to outrun a tidal wave. This makes no sense because he was in the middle of a giant battle just a few seconds ago. The tidal wave hits the boat. It crashes onto a tropical island. Sam gets out of the boat, even though he was right with Frodo and absolutely nowhere near Aragorn or a freaking boat*

CREDITS

*Bonus scene*

Old guy: ...and that is the story of The Frodo.

Child: Wow grandpa! That is a terrific story. This is no way a gigantic cliche at all. Tell me more about The Frodo!

Old guy: Well, I suppose there's time for one more... BE SURE TO BUY THE FORTHCOMING BONUS CHAPTERS 








</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ytp4s</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/vh3p</id></website><link>http://popwatch.ew.com/2012/03/22/mass-effect-3-ending-bioware/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T13:01:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T02:36:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msxxqf</id><link>http://popwatch.ew.com/2012/03/22/mass-effect-3-ending-bioware/#comment-478018645</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>