<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwr4vf/post/2012-03-30T12:15:49</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Mr. Rob Bricken's declining view on Bronies:


5/20/2011: "You know, I was going to feel bad that Hitler has become a My Little Pony: Friendship Is Magic fan like myself, but then I realized that's less a slight on MLP fans and more a credit to MLP's insane appeal  -- even mass-murdering fuckheads find the adventures of Rainbow Dash, Applejack, Twilight and the rest adorable! "

1/5/2012: "From the New York Times:
'An article on Monday about Jack Robinson and Kirsten Lindsmith, two college students with Asperger Syndrome who are navigating the perils of an intimate relationship, misidentified the character from the animated children's show "My Little Pony" that Ms. Lindsmith said she visualized to Cheer herself up. It is Twilight Sparkle, the nerdy intellectual, not Fluttershy, the kind animal lover.'

Allow me to sum up my feelings on this matter with one image:http://www.toplessrobot.com/assets_c/2011/11/fff%20joy%20picard%201-thumb-600x348.jpg"1/27/2012: You know what I like about Bronys? It's that while they enjoy a cartoon primarily targeted to young girls, they aren't necessarily perverts. They simply enjoy the show, realize there's something inherently ridiculous about grown men enjoying a girl's cartoon, and have turned it into its own little thing...I just appreciate that, for the part, the Brony movement is seemingly benign."2/28/2012: " For the record, I approve of MLP:FIM, but reading the Amazon reviews on this [DVD] is just terrifying."

3/30/2012: " The My Little Pony thing bothers me in the same way that things like cuddle parties do. Simply put, I find the manufactured cuteness of Brony culture disquieting."So from Happy Picard to Benign to Disquieting. At this rate, Rob, by this time next year you'll be ransacking stores for MLP merchandise, Burning it, and putting said Burning on youtube.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67cjiw</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/hjt8</id></website><link>http://www.toplessrobot.com/2012/03/winter_is_coming_also_friendship.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:01:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:15:49+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwr4vf</id><link>http://www.toplessrobot.com/2012/03/winter_is_coming_also_friendship.php#comment-480907321</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>