<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miyufc/update/2012-03-22T20:51:17/8ca03dc314d82f3d3a45642a26b2871f30c121862fee37269d7b6c4e8cac27e2</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>It's a shame it took people having to assemble, march, load buses and loudly voice their outrage for the authorities to actually look at possibly arresting George Zimmerman for this obvious, egregious and absolutely unnecessary Act of violence. The Sanford police department did a terrible job of investigating this murder. Zimmerman said he killed Trayvon Martin in self defense, the police took him at his word and let him go home and didn't intend to do nothing else until people started making noise. Zimmerman was not arrested, he was detained. Bill Lee should be fired, forget stepping aside temporarily. I'd like to know why Trayvon's body laid in the morgue for 2 days before his parents were allowed to see him. The Sanford police lied to Trayvon's parents saying Zimmerman was a model citizen when this nut has a history of questionable behavior. It's doesn't take a month to listen to 911 tapes and gather information. Bill Lee and his department had no intention of investigating this case. I could sworn my calendar says 2012, not 1912. Back then certain people could get away with Cold blooded murder of a black person, but I didn't think they could in this day in age. Boy was I wrong. I hope Trayvon Martin and his family gets the justice they so rightfully deserve and that is grossly overdue. I pray that God continue to keep and strengthen this family. I've said it before and I'll keep saying it, there is nothing worse on this Earth than for a parent having to bury their child. If there's something worse, I'd love to know what it is.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y9uhd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnmw</id></website><link>http://www.star-telegram.com/2012/03/22/3828915/fla-police-chief-steps-down-temporarily.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T19:58:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T00:51:17+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miyufc</id><link>http://www.star-telegram.com/2012/03/22/3828915/fla-police-chief-steps-down-temporarily.html#comment-474102327</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/81gxv</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>