<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kul4/post/2012-03-29T22:41:18</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>THE ZIONIST STATE 

[Harbinger of World War 
III] 

     It has been said by insiders from many quarters that three 
world wars will be necessary in order to complete the long-laid plan for World 
Dominion. 

     After WWI, the Versailles treaty - 
of which the measures against Germany guaranteed a second World 
War - M. Clemenceau boasted that 'we are 
carrying the war on into the peace'.   


"Full Responsibility for the First world 
War, lies squarely on the shoulders of the International Jewish Bankers. They 
are responsible for millions of dead and dying". -- U.S. Congress - Record 67th 
Congress, 4. Sitting, Senate Document nr. 346) 
"The bolshevik Revolution in russia was 
the work of Jewish planning and Jewish dissatisfaction. Our Plan is to have a 
New world Order. what worked so wonderfully in Russia, is going to become 
Reality for the whole world." -- The American Hebrew Magazine, 10, 
Sept. 1920 
"By using the new atheist exile politics 
they [the Zionists] provoked and increased anti-Semitism in Europe which led to 
the Second world War. . . The worldwide boycott against Germany in 1933 and the 
later all-out declaration of war against Germany, initiated by the Zionist 
leaders and the World Jewish Congress. . . " -- Rabbi Schwartz, New York 
Times, Sept. 30, 1997 

     On April 27, 2002 an article in the 
Arizona Daily Star  carried a report with a statement by Ra'anan 
Gissen, a senior adviser to  Sharon. 


 WWIII Is Coming 'Whether They Like It Or Not' - 
Top Sharon Aide 
"The Terror attacks on September 11 and 
extreme turmoil in the Middle East point to one thing - World War III, a 
spokesman for Israeli Prime Minister  Sharon said Friday during a visit to 
Tucson."   

"We've been fighting a war for the past 
18 months, which is the harbinger of World War III. The world is going to fight, 
whether they like it or not. I'm sure". [Gissen stated] 


          In the first half of this 
chapter of Douglas Reed's book, Controversy of Zion, we're given a 
detailed -- almost microscopic -- look behind the scenes at the manipulations, 
threats, bribes and murders committed in order to secure the vote by the United 
Nations, mandating the 'state' of Israel as a homeland for the so-called Jews. 
He describes the 'contest' between Republicans and Democrats -- their fawning 
promises of capitulation -- before the upcoming presidential election to garner 
financial support and votes from the Jews.   

     Many people died in their attempts 
to sound the warning, including Mr. James Forrestal, U.S. Secretary for Defence, 
when he failed to heed the warnings of Bernard Baruch to 'back '. 
  

     The second half of the chapter draws 
a gruesome picture of the bloody terror in Palestine that began simultaneously 
with the UN mandate. This a MUST READ, even for those who believe they know the 
facts. Reed's research appears to be indisputable and verifiable. 

     You'll read statements by many 
people in high places who feared for the future of the world if the mandate was 
passed, and they predicted it would lead to a third world war. 

    First, a couple of paragraphs from 
the preface to explain the twenty-two-year gap between the completion of this 
vital book and it's publication, which can be purchased from Omni Christian Book 
Club. You can find ordering information in our Resources section, at the 
bottom of the page. Here's the preface excerpt: 

". . . The disappearance into almost total 
oblivion of Douglas Reed and all his works was a change that could not have been 
wrought by time alone. Indeed, the correctness of his interpretation of the 
unfolding history of his time found some confirmation in what happened to him 
when at the height of his powers. 

"After 1951, with the publication of 
Far and Wide, in which he set the history of 
the United States of America into the context of all he had learned in Europe of 
the politics of the world, Reed found himself banished from the 
bookstands, all publishers' doors closed on him, and those books already 
written liable to be withdrawn from library shelves and 'lost', never to be 
replaced. 

"His public career as a writer now 
apparently at an end, Reed was at last free to undertake a great task for which 
all that had gone before -- his years as a foreign correspondent, his travels in 
Europe and America, his conversations and contacts with the great political 
leaders of his day, plus his eager absorption through reading and observation of 
all that was best in European culture -- were but a kind of preparation and 
education that no university could provide and which only the fortunate and 
gifted few could fully use. 

"Experiences which other men might have 
accepted as defeat, served only to focus Reed's powers on what was to be his 
most important undertaking -- that of researching and retelling the story of the 
last 2,000 years and more in such a way as to render intelligible much of modern 
history which, for the masses, remains in our time steeped in darkness and 
closely guarded by the terrors of an invisible system of censorship. . . " IVOR 
BENSON, Durban, Natal, August 1978 

     Benson goes on to tell of Reed's three-year 
period of research and writing the book, with the Epilogue being added in 1956, 
then, the book gathering dust for twenty-two years, until it was finally 
published in 1978 by the Dolphin Press, Durban, Natal, South Africa. 


     Knowing this, dear reader -- knowing how 
desperately you are NOT wanted to have this information -- I hope your desire 
for truth and understanding is strong enough that you will get the book and read 
it from cover to cover. It does, indeed, lay the groundwork for other smaller 
gems written by various authors -- several of which are posted here --  that 
help us to at least begin to grasp the breadth and depth of an International 
Priesthood's insidious, centuries-long plan for World Dominion. 

     This is not to say that Doug Reed is 
infallible, for, being human, that would be impossible. 

     We've given here a few excerpted quotes from 
the chapter as it so pertains to today, reminding you it was written fifty years 
ago. Many of Reed's statements appear to be prophetic. Actually, he saw the 
'writing on the wall'. We've broken the chapter into two parts as it's among the 
few longest chapters of the book and we present it to you, with love. 


-- Jackie -- 

January 27th, 2004 

______________________________________  

* . . . 
everyone connected with it will be hunted down and put to 
death 
* . . . this means that even the Zionist state set 
up after the Second World War by no means fulfills the intention of those who 
made the Balfour Declaration, and that further conquests of Arab lands 
have yet to be made by war. 
* As in American elections, so in this British one 
of 1945 the power to "deliver the votes" was shown. Mr. Churchill 
had gone far in "arming the Jews" and in privately committing himself to 
Zionism, but not far enough for Dr. Weizmann. 
* In England at the mid-century, control of the 
press was virtually complete. 
* They depict what will inevitably happen one day, 
but that day has been put back to some time after another ruinous  in 
Palestine, which will probably involve the world. 
* Then he [Harry Truman] turned his gaze on domestic 
affairs and the next Congressional and presidential elections. In these, he knew 
(and said), the Zionist-controlled vote was decisive. 
* The "activists" (as they prefer to call 
themselves) were left with power to ignite a third world conflict when 
they pleased. 
* Very large sums were obtained from Jewish 
contributors and they would be influenced in either giving or withholding by 
what the President did on Palestine". 
* If American troops in the 1950's or 1960's 
[or 1990's or in the 21st Century] 
find themselves in the Middle East, any of 
them who have read Mr. Forrestal's Diaries should know how they come to be 
there. 
* Mr. Forrestal must have  from a 
sense of duty, not of hope, when he implored Mr. McGrath "to give a lot of 
thought to this matter because it involved not merely the Arabs of the Middle 
East, but also might involve the whole Moslem world with its four hundred 
millions of people: Egypt, North Africa, India and Afghanistan". 
* His [Mr. Forrestal's] end needs to be 
described here, before the armed seizure of Palestine is recorded; it is the 
classic case of persecution by defamation, leading to death. 


______________________________________________ 

Here's the last two paragraphs of the preceding 
chapter, "The Talmudic Vengeance", for the sake of continuity. [All emphasis is 
the author's.] 

     This brings the story nearly down to our 
present day and what remains will be discussed in a concluding chapter.  When 
the revolution spread outward into the area abandoned to it by the West in 1945 
the history of 1917-1918 
in Russia was repeated. 

     A Talmudic vengeance was wreaked and Jewish 
governments were with obvious intent set up everywhere.  There was no great 
change in that state of affairs, either real or apparent, for another eight 
years,  What was done reaffirmed once more the nature of the revolution and of 
its directing force and Talmudic purpose. 

THE ZIONIST STATE 

pages 423 - 469 

     The revolution, having spread into 
the half of Europe held clear for it by the Western Allies, did one more thing: 
 in the manner of a serpent striking, it thrust out a tongue that  to the 
southern shores of Europe, across the Mediterranean and into the tiny land 
called Palestine.   

     The money, equipment, escort and 
convoy were provided by the West, but the revolution supplied the two 
indispensable constituents of the Zionist State:  the people to 
invade it and the arms which made its conquest 
certain. 

     The West connived, but the Zionist 
state in the last analysis was the creation of the revolution, which in this 
manner fulfilled the Levitical doctrine of "the return". 

     These incursions into Europe and 
into Arabia were the sole "territorial " reaped from the Second War, in the 
early stages of which the Western "premier-dictators" for a second time had 
publicly renounced all thought of territorial . 

     The result of these two developments 
was to leave, in bisected Europe and bisected Palestine, two permanent 
detonation points of new war, which at any moment could be set  by any who 
might think to further their ambitions by a third war. 

     The reader will recall that in the 
years preceding the Second War, Zionism was in collapse in Palestine; and that 
the British Parliament in 1939, having been forced by twenty years of experience 
to realize that the "Jewish National Home" was impossible to realize, had 
decided to abandon the unworkable "Mandate" and to withdraw after  the 
parliamentary representation of all parties in the land, Arab, 
Jews and others. 

     The reader then beheld the change 
which came about when Mr. Churchill became Prime Minister in 1940 and privately 
informed Dr. Weizmann (according to Dr. Weizmann's account, which has not been 
challenged) that he "quite agreed" with the Zionist ambition "after the war. . . 
to build up a state of three or four million Jews in Palestine". 

     Mr. Churchill  expressed great 
respect for parliamentary government but in this case, as a wartime potentate, 
he privily and arbitrarily overrode a policy approved, after full debate, by the 
House of Commons. 

     After that, the reader followed Dr. 
Weizmann in his journeys to America and saw how Mr. Churchill's efforts "to arm 
the Jews" (in which he was opposed by the responsible administrators on the 
Spot) received support from there under the "pressure" of Dr. Weizmann and his 
associates. 

     That was the point at which the 
reader last saw the Zionist state in gestation.  Throughout 1944, as Mr. 
Churchill records in his war memoirs, he continued to press the Zionist 
ambition. 


"It is well known I am determined not to 
break the Pledges of the British Government to the Zionists expressed in the 
Balfour Declaration 
, as modified by my subsequent statement 
at the Colonial Office in 1921, No change can be made in policy 
without full discussion in Cabinet". (June 23, 1944). 


     The policy had been 
changed after full discussion in Cabinet and Parliament, in 1939.  Here Mr. 
Churchill simply ignored that major decision on policy and reverted to the 
earlier one, echoing the strange words of another Colonial Secretary (Mr. 
Leopold Amery, earlier quoted) that this policy could not 
change. 

     Again, 


"There is no doubt that this (treatment 
of Jews in Hungary) is probably the greatest and most horrible crime ever 
committed in the whole history of the world. . . 
"all concerned in this crime who may fall 
into our hands, including the people who only obeyed orders by carrying out the 
butcheries, should be put to death after their association with the murders has 
been proved.. . 
"Declarations should be made in public, 
so that everyone connected with it will be hunted down and put to death" (July 
11, 1944). 

     Here Mr. Churchill, like President 
Roosevelt and Mr. Eden, implicitly links the execution of captives 
solely with their crimes against Jews, thus relegating all other 
sufferers to the oblivion into which, in fact, they fell.  Incidentally, the 
reader saw in the last chapter that Jews were among the tormentors, as well as 
among the victims. 

     To continue: 


"I am anxious to reply promptly 
to Dr. Weizmann's request for the formation of a Jewish fighting force 
put forward in his letter of July 4th (July 12, 1944). I like the idea of the 
Jews trying to get at the murders of their fellow-countrymen in Central Europe 
and I think it would give a great deal of satisfaction in the United States.  I 
believe it is the wish of the Jews themselves to fight the Germans everywhere. 
 It is with the Germans they have their quarrel". (July 26th, 
1944). 

     If Mr. Churchill, as stated by Dr. 
Weizmann, had agreed to the building up "of a state of three or four million 
Jews in Palestine", he must have known that the Zionists had a much larger 
quarrel with the population of Arabia, and that any "Jewish fighting force" 
would be more likely to fall on these innocent third parties than on the 
Germans. 

     Mr. Churchill's last recorded 
allusion (as wartime prime minister) came after the fighting in Europe 
ended: 


"The whole question of Palestine must be 
settled at the peace table. . . I do not think we should take the responsibility 
upon ourselves of managing this very difficult place while the Americans sit 
back and criticise.   
"Have you ever addressed yourselves to 
the idea that we should ask them to take it over?. . . I am not aware of the 
slightest advantage which has ever accrued to Great Britain from this painful 
and thankless task.  Somebody else should have their turn now". (July 6, 
1945) 

     This passage (considered together 
with President Roosevelt's jocular remark to Stalin, that the only concession he 
might offer King Ibn Saoud would be "to give him the six million Jews in the 
United States") reveal the private thoughts of these premier-dictators who so 
docilely did the bidding of Zion. 

     Mr. Churchill wished he could shift 
the insoluble problem to the American back: Mr. Roosevelt would gladly have 
shifted it on to some other back.  In this matter the great men, as an unwary 
remark in each case shows, behaved like the comedian who cannot by any exertion 
divest himself of the gluey flypaper.   </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l52ms</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry2d</id></website><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50458</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T19:24:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:41:18+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kul4</id><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50458#comment-480167154</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zd1dw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>