<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjqri/post/2012-03-26T14:36:43</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The author's comparison of being forced to purchase broccoli and being forced to purchase health insurance is, at best, a stretch. The broccoli market is not one that affects nearly every aspect of our economy and certainly not one that affects every single individual. 

Health care, however is one of those situations in which every single American is affected. It is safe to say that every person alive will need medical care or be involved in medical care at some point before they pass away. The vast majority of us are born with trained and licensed medical technicians at the ready, usually in a hospital setting, which means we are literally at the mercy of a health care system from our first breath.

The insistence on treating health care on par with broccoli is not only foolish, it is dangerous. In today's world, very few of us have experienced a pandemic, let alone an epidemic and we have no idea how such an abstract idea can level an entire society or government but it has and it will probably do it again. Our health care system has kept us healthy and even prevented additional epidemics (polio, Flu, smallpox, etc.). Could you imagine a country where only those that could afford it were given polio vaccinations? Or smallpox? Our country would fall to apart should an epidemic of such kind hit 20% or more of our population. Our hospitals would be full of the sick and dying, overwhelming and destroying the current system in place. Health care would fail, even for those that can afford premiums.

Health care can literally save a country or force it into ruin. Detractors of "Obama Care" (complete hooey, he may have championed it but no POTUS passes legislation, read the Constitution) continue to rely on governmental overreach as a complaint (but overlooking other government overreaches such as drones over our American cities to make sure we're "safe") while missing the larger point which is that health care is a "great pillar" of a modern society. Without health care, any country will fall to ruin or never become great. 

If America refuses to see that health care is a requirement no different than our Armed Forces in order to keep us safe then we are going to fail or become so hindered that our place on the world stage will become a distant memory. A country staggered by a health care crisis, such as an epidemic, are vulnerable to attack by a foreign enemy as it can leave a country reeling with infrastructure overload. Or, we could be so hobbled that a war isn't even necessary to topple us. They could merely watch us crumble from afar and then simply move in.

Those that complain that health care costs will rise once "Obama Care" takes hold have disingenuously decided to avoid the fact that health care costs have risen dramatically, year over year, for years and to assert that they will rise because of this legislation is not only laughable, it makes them look foolish. This legislation was passed BECAUSE of increasing medical costs, not because things were getting better. Prices will rise no matter what but the backbone of this legislation is that health care would cost ALL those that participate (which is all of us) which will stop, or hinder, unpaid medical bills which all of us are already covering via our increased premiums to recover those costs.

The complaint that were cannot be required to do certain things is also a stretch. We are governed by laws on numerous levels which disallow or require many things. We cannot exceed the speed limit, we must pay taxes, we cannot cheat others..the list is lengthy and it is what keeps our country running as smoothly as it does. Requiring health insurance is hardly burdensome to the insured but the up side to reducing, or even eliminating, unpaid medical bills that we all end up paying for is a worthy end and helping Ensure the health of our general population is a national concern.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rkm3o</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/26/opinion/somin-health-supremes/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T12:26:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:36:43+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjqri</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/26/opinion/somin-health-supremes/index.html#comment-476616090</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/uw3r</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>