<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mhjs20/update/2012-02-22T18:45:52/d9a914934c714837d5b76f1611e58f1ae6feb0502db29c46eda99987db7970c2</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gsfybm</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/goxgh</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>More importantly, it ignores that SCOTUS has never ruled on the issue, and during Heller it came up in orals indicating even the US Attorney arguing for the  saw machine guns as relevant to militia service. (assualt rifles are machine guns by the way).
SCOTUS orals discussion
GENERAL CLEMENT: Well, Justice Scalia, I think our principal concern based on the parts of the court of appeals opinion that seemed to adopt a very categorical rule were with respect to machine guns, because I do think that it is difficult -- I don't want to foreclose the possibility of the Government, Federal Government making the argument some day -- but I think it is more than a little difficult to say that the one arm that's not protected by the Second Amendment is that which is the standard issue armament for the National Guard, and that's what the machine gun is.
CHIEF JUSTICE ROBERTS: But this law didn't involve a restriction on machine guns. It involved an absolute . It involved an absolute carry prohibition. Why would you think that the opinion striking down an absolute  would also apply to a narrow one -- narrower one directed solely to machine guns? 
GENERAL CLEMENT: I think, Mr. Chief Justice, why one might worry about that is one might read the language of page 53a of the opinion as reproduced in the petition appendix that says once it is an arm, then it is not open to the District to  it. Now, it seems to me that the District is not strictly a complete  because it exempts pre-1976 handguns. The Federal  on machine guns is not, strictly speaking, a , because it exempts pre - pre-law machine guns, and there is something like 160,000 of those. 
JUSTICE SCALIA: But that passage doesn't mean once it's an arm in the dictionary definition of arms. Once it's an arm in the specialized sense that the opinion referred to it, which is -- which is the type of a weapon that was used in militia, and it is -it is nowadays commonly held. 
GENERAL CLEMENT: Well -
JUSTICE SCALIA: If you read it that way, I don't see why you have a problem. 
 
GENERAL CLEMENT: Well, I -- I hope that you read it that way. But I would also say that I think that whatever the definition that the lower court opinion employed, I do think it's going to be difficult over time to sustain the notion -- I mean, the Court of Appeals also talked about lineal descendants. And it does seem to me that, you know, just as this Court would apply the Fourth Amendment to something like Heat imagery, I don't see why this Court wouldn't allow the Second Amendment to have the same kind of Scope, and then I do think that reasonably machine guns come within the term "arms."
 
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/mu5pb5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6tdd</id></website><link>http://www.csmonitor.com/USA/Justice/2011/1104/Second-Amendment-Quiz/Topic-of-Second-Amendment</link><postedTime>2011-11-04T19:45:43+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-22T23:45:52+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mhjs20</id><link>http://www.csmonitor.com/USA/Justice/2011/1104/Second-Amendment-Quiz/Topic-of-Second-Amendment#comment-446399459</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mf73v</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-11-04</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>