<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msy1k2/update/2012-03-27T11:00:25/ac186c7e804dddb32b2ea9f3e958d56b8c0427773981f5847b9d6acc58c7616b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>"Yet to mold China's future requires a more honest and sober
reckoning with its recent past. That history is composed of my mother's story
and numerous others like hers, but it is told in abridged and truncated
versions by the Communist Party. It tells the party's history, not the people's."

Illogical and meaningless psycho-babble.  It is like saying Mr Ma's or anyone's future requires a more honest and sober reckoning with his recent past.  Actually, it makes more sense to declare the opposite. That is, anyone's  future Depends on his ability to overcome his history whatever it is.  

As a matter of fact, historical events are mostly a confluence of random events each unlikely to repeat during which humans are doing humanly things, good and bad. In the case of the GPCR, there will not be anyone like Mao who had established the New China. China is unlikely to be as  isolated diplomatically and economically as during the Cold War. The China people are more informed and more connected internationally nowadays. 

The Nazi had caused the Jewish Holocaust but its does not make the German people or Germany as a country evil. Japan had invaded China and it inflicted a lot of pain and suffering on the Chinese people but it does not make the Japanese people or Japan as a country evil. Of course,  the Jewish people and the Chinese people deserve apologies. But then the German and the Jew are two people. The Chinese and the Japanese are two peoples.  When atrocities were committed because one people saw the other people as lesser humans, the aggressor should apology not that it would diminish the pain of the victims but to remind themselves--  Germans and the Japanese-- that their mistakes of seeing other peoples as lesser humans. Similarly, apology should be accepted on the ground that  Germans and Japanese were then committing  no more than human crimes.  That is,  crimes all  humans would also commit under certain circumstance.  Not that Germans and Japanese are evil by nature. Otherwise, apology would be meaningless and its acceptance would be impossible.

 In contrast, the guilty and the victim of China's cultural revolution are of one people. An apology is not necessary to affirm the humanity of both parties. What China and the Chinese people should do is to focus on the future, not the past.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lnazc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/eyjq</id></website><link>http://m.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2012/03/children-of-the-revolution-the-history-chinas-new-leaders-wont-confront/254952/</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T11:36:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-27T15:00:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msy1k2</id><link>http://m.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2012/03/children-of-the-revolution-the-history-chinas-new-leaders-wont-confront/254952/#comment-477463068</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zlc04</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>