<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miyugk/post/2012-03-22T20:50:00</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miej9x</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Archos G9 was on the market in October. It does not matter for Archos that Texas Instruments 1.5Ghz wasn't ready before January or that the Ice Cream Sandwich firmware wasn't ready until last week. Archos pretty much sold 100% of the capacity of 1Ghz Honeycomb skews of G9 that they could afford to manufacture. And all of those are now upgradable to Ice Cream Sandwich by a one-click firmware upgrade.

Now having the 1.5Ghz 1GB RAM ICS-pre-installed version for sale nearly half the price of the  is only a super great advantage and a kick-ass product positioning for Archos to further expand their sales volume according to them having access to more and more cash to expand the manufacturing capacity.

You put the latest Archos and Arnova choices with ICS in the same stores that sell IPad3, Transformer Prime or Samsung Note 10.1, and it's quite simple to demonstrate and to prove that more than 50% of those consumers buy Archos if they decide to buy a tablet. It's that simple. Consumers aren't stupid. They see the Archos choices at half the price, and they see the Arnova choices at 1/4th the price, they get a feel that the Archos and Arnova products are absolutely just fine, nothing is wrong with them, and those even have a range of features that make them better than the other company's $499 (or $399 iPad2) choices, it's just plain common sense that Archos can take the top Spot of this market.

Obviously there is also Amazon in the USA who has no problem selling more than Apple if they want. And there is obviously the risk that Chinese brands like Huawei and ZTE come and decide to take some market share. But there is ample enough potential sales to be done for everyone wanting to grow to be able to grow by having the right strategy and it's absolutely obvious that Archos has a great strategy.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/658hfz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/g7o4</id></website><link>http://armdevices.net/2012/03/15/archos-g10-xs-archos-elements-and-arnova-50e-announced/</link><postedTime>2012-03-15T02:26:32+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T00:50:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miyugk</id><link>http://armdevices.net/2012/03/15/archos-g10-xs-archos-elements-and-arnova-50e-announced/#comment-474101635</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ii4</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-15</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>