<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3bgx8/post/2012-03-29T14:23:11</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3x01v</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h988z</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>You Act as though you were there. Let the investigation concluded what happened. Yes, indeed if Zimmerman, it turns out, was attacked and had to defend himself. Why should that be an issue? I'm sure if that Kid got a hold of Zimmerman's gun. Mr Zimmerman would of ended up like those British tourist. I wonder what some of you would be saying then? I heard nothing about those British tourist. They were gunned down in Cold blood. On the other hand if Zimmerman did something wrong, then he should get charged. But, to do what you and others are asking for, is nonsense. 

  What some are asking for is that he get arrested right now, forget the facts or the investigation. If there were evidence, he would of been charged. Now, they're going to do an investigation to find for sure if there was or isn't. But, it's not for anyone of us to find him guilty.

  One of my main points are: If you want to try and bring about credibility to your argument. Having, AL, JESSE and the New Black Panty party speaking for you, doesn't do you justice.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zzsxt</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnm3</id></website><link>http://www.sacbee.com/2012/03/29/4375840/land-park-gathering-in-support.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:29:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:23:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3bgx8</id><link>http://www.sacbee.com/2012/03/29/4375840/land-park-gathering-in-support.html#comment-479724230</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g5hpz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>