<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3aiwa/post/2012-03-28T17:07:45</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Business gets to write  the cost of educating employees along with many other write offs including capital equipment etc.   If they write it Off  somewhere in tax payer land someone else is picking up those cost.  Since Reganomics we now have 1% of the people holding 80% of the capital.  Since 2000 corporations now have a voice in Government just like anyone else who possesses a soul, and is accountable, and since about 2008  corporations can 
contribute as much to the Government process as they want.   Thus they can buy the affections of politicians.  And business still thinks it's unfair that they 
have to pay taxes.

With their wealth generated by going to China, industrialist have been able to isolate themselves quite well, and live in America with impunity.   Even though they are more parasites on the tax payers than contributing citizens. 
Why don't they move to China ?   Remember what Mao did to this same class of people in China in 1946 ?  At least back when there were plenty of jobs contributing citizens could exist, but many have had to live on their savings thus Bleeding them away from their assets at a time when so many boomers would be inheriting estates from their elders.   Since those like "Neutron Jack" Welch and others like Newt Gingrich with his "let them wither on the vine" attitude, America has been  plundered  for many years now.   But no one dare call that "class warfare" !   

Now the industrial sector is waking up and realizing they have been living in a
fools paradise in China.   They are realizing the message of Thomas Wolfe's book, "You Can't Go Home Again".   In short they have "crapped where they once ate" in their arrogance and self serving avarice.  Some of these corporations have CEO's making well over 700 times the wages of the average employee.  Then their annual bonus is in the millions of dollars which is probably more than the combined wages of their whole work force.  Yet
they need taxpayers assistance with educating workers.

And like innocent children, they just can't understand why those they ruined
starting in the 80's till now seem to have a distrust of business, and political leaders.     Just chalk it up to poetic justice.




  


.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h2mhe</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lznv</id></website><link>http://www.pbs.org/newshour/bb/business/jan-june12/skillsgap_03-27.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T05:08:48+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T21:07:45+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3aiwa</id><link>http://www.pbs.org/newshour/bb/business/jan-june12/skillsgap_03-27.html#comment-478777321</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zm1gn</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>