<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi5ic2/update/2012-03-22T15:38:59/2de8bb4f872f242cfd5a102d90ec71bf1e7cad2288099358a40de7843ea30297</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The mother who cried freedom
http://syrtimes. com/

They say time heals all wounds, but in an oppressed Syria, time is what is bought by the wound-givers to instill more pain on the wounded. Throughout Syria, the healthy are waiting to be wounded, and the wounded are waiting to die. And once the time comes for our martyrs to part us, their misery does not part with them. Instead, it is transferred over to the person that has Always taken the martyr’s stresses away, the mother.

Funneling mountains of pain into her own burden, every mother of a martyr endures a magnitude of emotional distress that only her counterpart could understand. It is a feeling that you might partially fathom if you were to imagine your loved ones gone. But that concept itself is only a fraction of what mothers have had to encounter throughout the past year.

When Syrian youth first began to protest, their mothers knew what kind of implications that had. Instead of choosing the easy way out by guilt tripping their children into not taking part in protests, they went out in the streets hand in hand with the youth. Since then, mothers wake up every day to the uncertainty of their children’s fate. They can only pray that it will not be the last day they pack a lunch for their sons.

The average mother of a protester in Syria lives on an excruciating dosage of Anxiety every single day. But it is none other than the mothers of martyrs who daily rebut what psychologists thought was the maximum elasticity of human stress adaptation. So what is it that makes these mothers so strong? How can they love so strongly and then adapt so bravely to loss? What is it that keeps them going?

Believe it or not, it is the cause. Nobody is more passionate about the Syrian Revolution than the mothers who in fact incepted its beauty into the minds of the young revolutionaries many years ago. The Assad regime has been oppressing Syrians for over 40 years, and when any innocent young man was detained and tortured before the Syrian Revolution sparked, it was his mother that protested outside of the prison day and night, pleading for her child’s freedom.

While young men and women were busy living oppressive lives simply to put food on their family’s table, it was the mothers who watched speechlessly, but cried for freedom while alone. That mother who cries freedom, look at her face as she raises her hands to pray to God today. Those expressions are that of someone that has not only been patient for a year, but for an entire lifetime. Syrian mothers are the most experienced protesters; revolutionaries today might have one unfathomably painful year of experience, but mothers in Syria have had an entire lifetime.

The mothers of martyrs lost their children for the sake of bringing hope to others. They care about our wellbeing and future as if we are their own children. It is our duty to show them in return that they are a mother to every one of us, and love them that way. A mother copes with life’s stresses with the smiles on her children’s faces at the end of the day. Maybe that is why our martyrs die smiling. Smile to a Syrian mother, and remind her why she is so incredible.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dkvsy</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cjnq</id></website><link>http://blogs.aljazeera.net/middle-east/2011/10/20/syria-live-blog</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T16:11:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T19:38:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi5ic2</id><link>http://blogs.aljazeera.net/middle-east/2011/10/20/syria-live-blog#comment-473877324</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g5x7z</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>