<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miecoj/post/2012-03-22T16:48:56</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi2qk5</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>you gave a nice answer. but, let me ask you one question. you are a sovereign country. you know how to deal with your own problems. but, how will you justify those rapes innocent killings of women and children. everyone can clearly see that sinhalese are dominating everything. forcing everyone to sing your national anthem is a perfect example. you have the upper hand now. unless you let the Tamil people to have their equal status, the same 1970s situation will crop up again and another fight will start. in India we have different culture and language for each and every state. yet we don't have any problem. my father was born in Sri Lanka. He'll  say that Sri Lanka is a beautiful country. your country has lost lots of resources fighting the brutal war. when a country is waging a war, no other development will take place in the country. All the resources will be diverted towards war. And Sri Lanka has been suffering from this ailment till now in this 30 years war. Now you are dependent upon India and China even to build some railways network and sea port. this is because, you have not made any reasonable development during this period. please try to have a peaceful development. please do not play geo politics card using India and China.India and China are helping you for their personal sake. you do have some cultural ties with India. but not with China. please ask sri lankans to read world war 2 history and Cold war history. if you play geo politics card, then in the future you might have to pay for it. A war that is not yours will be fought in your land.Look before you leap. a clear example is north Korea and south Korea. it all started as a war between US and Russia. first consider those Tamil people as Sri lankans. not as tamils. If there had been no internal conflict, you might have developed into a beautiful nation. try to Resolve your disputes peacefully and change your mindset. consider every Tamil as the Sri lankan. mingle with them. then you'll become as a beautiful nation in no time. all the best.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yes3l</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/776o</id></website><link>http://www.firstpost.com/?p=251910</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T02:14:28+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T20:48:56+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miecoj</id><link>http://www.firstpost.com/?p=251910#comment-473936571</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>