<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwoayc/update/2012-03-31T05:15:01/2a1a865a409f61c636270a017247dd10e6d443f5cc5bb60989f59f136d5806e9</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This list DESPERATELY requires a traditional RPG/JPRG that is strongly centralized around the plot, character development, and tactics ( on the jprg i guess), rather than this action RPG bullshit that is hogging the list.  It is obvious you have a bias towards Mass Effect because I really don't believe it deserves a Top 5 Spot.  Yes, an honorable mention, but nothing more.  Hmm... then again, I am INCREDIBLY biased towards JRPGs and nostalgic super nintendo games (for being less sell-out-y if you know what I mean and overall a pure transcription of creativity and thus Art).  Action RPGs can easily bore me, such as elder scrolls IV, which has dissuaded me from buying Skyrim (at the time I was playing WoW lol... plus ES-IV was NOT a hard game when I gave it a chance [prob gave it an unfair chance]...  idk.  Action RPGs are mainly fun when the story is exceptionally potent and/or the game has extraordinary gameplay, plus its challenging and not a fucking walk through preschool every boss encounter; like the sell-out vid games being produced today will do in order to be accepted by a larger demographic of people who would rather see the glittery graphics than something that is satisfying in some sort of human way rather than the primordial satisfaction of simply completing a task), despite all the circle-jerking that is rampant across gaming communities and the interwebz in general proclaiming Skyrim's unparalleled gaming experience.  I have yet to play Skyrim, and agreeably it looks pretty badass.  Fighting a fat dragon seems very appealilng haha, and the game is visually astounding which is Always a plus.  However, it just seems to be a semi-regurgitated form of ES-IV, and just another timedump of grinding pointless video game stats.


Anyways, I lost myself in my own rambling, and will be surprised if anyone reads this----my personal and high-as-fuck rant about how I dislike this list and dislike many modern video games.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hkhyh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/mbl8</id></website><link>http://blogs.phoenixnewtimes.com/jackalope/2012/03/five_video_games_that_could_be.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T21:50:26+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T09:15:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwoayc</id><link>http://blogs.phoenixnewtimes.com/jackalope/2012/03/five_video_games_that_could_be.php#comment-481678167</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7uzh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>