<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3q43w/post/2012-03-29T11:57:18</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Michael - In your last sentence you say that "all of this boiling and roasting is going to happen on Earth anyhow in a couple million years when the sun naturally gets brighter". Are you sure you don't you mean a couple of billion years? As I understand it, the sun has about another 5 billion years to go before it engulfs us as a red giant and 2 million years seems a very small step along the way. I had assumed that, without our intervention through the Burning of fossil fuels, life on Earth would have at least another billion years to run.

I recently attempted a calculation on how long it would take for the oceans to boil away. The answer came out at something like 100,000 years, assuming an ongoing imbalance of 1% between solar radiation hitting Earth and re-radiation. If my answer is in the right order of magnitude (my proneness to error is legendary) then even with your 2 million year horizon, we would be bringing life on Earth to a very premature end. 

Incidentally, where did you get your 1400C from? I thought the temperature on Venus was 460C, though I think I would personally find the difference between those temperatures to be largely of academic interest. 

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/d0a53t</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/uayi</id></website><link>http://motherboard.vice.com/2012/1/17/investigating-global-warming-s-absolute-worst-case-scenario-venus-syndrome--2</link><postedTime>2012-01-17T14:09:09+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:57:18+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3q43w</id><link>http://motherboard.vice.com/2012/1/17/investigating-global-warming-s-absolute-worst-case-scenario-venus-syndrome--2#comment-479601574</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-01-17</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>