<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi63n5/update/2012-03-22T22:45:29/746cfb9d1fcf30902f47de67d733b0b6d1fc3a9135d9177de72b018127505dd5</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The Water Bros "Bottlegate "video is interesting.

They invoke a presumption of scandalous or criminal behaviours to follow.

That would seem quite wrong to do, unless they did show something scandalous or criminal.

The Water Bros and Peter Gleick get it essentially right about quality. I trust the tested tapwater over bottled, unless it's the end of August and it might fail the sniff test. It's an aesthetic detail, but some years it just stinks.

They forgot about people trying to avoid excess flouride from drinking municipal water. It degrades the tooth surface and colour after a certain dosage.
 I believe I recall that even for Toronto water they allow usage of industrial flouride compound scraped from industrial smokestacks. Toothpaste would require a different grade. Dentists paint the kids teeth with it too.

Another expert on the video talked about the absence of  outright claims that bottled is purer.

From 2006 

Fiji water tried to frame it differently. 

"Fiji, not just an island but also a precious bottled water that 
fancies itself the Thirst-quencher of the stars, clobbered Cleveland 
with the same sort of tired humor that galls Pittsburghers. A full-page 
ad in national magazines boasts: "The label says Fiji because it's not 
bottled in Cleveland." Ha, ha.

An aroused Cleveland Water Department went into action. It ran tests 
comparing Fiji to Cleveland tap water and other national brands. Fiji 
Water took top Spot in arsenic and other contaminants, the Plain Dealer 
reported. It wasn't enough to make Fiji unsafe to drink, but Cleveland 
tap water along with , Dasani and Evian had no measurable 
arsenic. Fiji said the tests were rigged and made no move to change the 
ad.


Fiji's next ad can say it did better with Men's Health magazine than 
it did with Cleveland. The magazine deemed Fiji the best among nine 
brands."
Read more: http://old.post-gazette.com/pg/06201/707156-294.stm#ixzz1pu5LXFdu</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yb5hc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/njl0</id></website><link>http://theagenda.backend.tvo.org/blog/agenda-blogs/defence-bottled-water</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T16:20:08+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T02:45:29+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi63n5</id><link>http://theagenda.backend.tvo.org/blog/agenda-blogs/defence-bottled-water#comment-474161764</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z57fj</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>