<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fjhm/post/2012-03-29T17:04:43</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>  I have heard the tape and read the transcript. Seems to be pretty 
indecipherable to me as well. Could have just as easily been "Goon" in 
lieu of "Coon".


One thing is clear however, no matter what the race is of the persons  
that are involved in a fight, never wise for someone without a loaded 
gun to attack someone that is carrying a loaded gun - could easily 
result in DEATH to the initial attacker! Great thing about a Conceal 
Carry Permit - it is supposed deter some crime as it should encourage 
would be attackers to think about it before that Act as in "Hey, that Hispanic Man over there might just have a loaded gun on him, maybe my 
WannabeNoLimitNi_gaThugass might just want to leave him alone". In this 
case I guess Martin must have let his GangstaTestosterone overload his 
azzz which resulted in his death in the process of Mr. Zimmerman 
lawfully defending himself from further bodily harm at the hands of 
Martin.

All you idiots out there that think this just has to be murder need to read the 911 Transcript from Zimmerman's call and listen to what the eyewitnesses say. Zimmerman killed Martin in self defense and that is why Zimmerman was not arrested and charged with a crime. If you are stupid enough to attack a man with a loaded weapon don't expect that the outcome will be favorable with respect to your health and safety! 

What's next, all you Race Baiting Morons that want to Burn Zimmerman at the Stake are going to unanimously re-affirm that OJ didn't kill Nicole Simpson and Ron Goldman??</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hk0kc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f7e3</id></website><link>http://www.wnd.com/2012/03/post-racial-lynch-mob/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T22:22:14+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T21:04:43+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fjhm</id><link>http://www.wnd.com/2012/03/post-racial-lynch-mob/#comment-479892427</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lk6v5</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>