<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mq49s8/update/2012-03-04T12:37:25/2157d2bc9f1fa21cfdea5356ef4b3f3ff4f1fc384ee519c6e8616e7cc4fff045</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mqh58y</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Sure. Many artists offer us their considerable craft. As in all fields, a chosen few do so with great mastery (e.g. Meryl Streep). And again as in all fields, it is clogged with mediocrity. Below that are the poseurs if I spelled that right? Ms. Jolie isa poseur, no artist. But Thank You for a huge morning laugh! Laughed until my abs hurt. The woman cannot  to save her life. She has three and only three modes 1. Haughty and pompous 2. Beatific and Bleeding for the world and 3.Yelling and crying. (e.g. The Changeling. No one I know could take more than 20 minutes of it no exaggeration).
Yes she won a single Oscar 10 years ago! That was not for Best Actress, just Supporting. Ms. Jolie received that Oscar for playing herself. Pure Jolie in that film. An Oscar is definitive. All nominations or Globe or SAG awards are a distant second. The Oscar rules. Winning it rules. Ms. Jolies' is very dusty, despite all her movies. I don't think she has even been an Oscar nominee since?
The best  Ms. Jolie does is being Ms. Jolie every moment of every day anyone sees her or her seeming puppet Mr. Pitt. Thats exactly what has many here in such Heated snits over a complete stranger.
But a true artist? ROFLOL. She's is a mere phenomenon deeply invested in staying a phenomenon. Not an artist, icon, legend in the making. Sorry,
not even close. Still laughing.
Try Ms. Streep, Ms. Close, Ms. Mirren, Ms. Winslet, Ms. Blanchet for artistry and awesome craftwork.
No, I have no feeling about Ms. Jolie one way or the other. I don't know her. I only know she manages to keeps herself aloft, riding the media currents, as they all do. But this is the only area where any talent from her can be seen. She is shrewd. Not intelligent, but shrewd about media. And so she keeps her exalted status. If you want mountainous talent and intelligence, sample the works of the list of actors listed above.
Everyone is allowed their opinion. But I am not trying to cram mine down anyones gullet, although I'm sure I'll get shredded for this post. What for? Its simply my opinion.
It is fun to Surf and watch these often intense cat fights, particularly it would appear, from her defenders. What gets written is malicious, name-calling, unnecessary, and totally unacceptable. It surpasses funny and becomes pathetic. For no reason of any substance! So I sometimes post, then stop reading. Fervent, zealot like fighting over someone who has no part in our real lives. Do people here listen to themselves, really? Its ludicrous. And shrewdly evoked.
She's got you all right where she wants you. What did Mark Twain say? Something about be loved or be hated, just don't be ignored. That must be Ms. Jolie's mantra.
Do you fighters actually want to be the sort of people who attack each other over something of no consequence? Is that who you are?
Now, go ahead and proceed to rip me apart. That'll will show everyone the person you are.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yjx0ta</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t8ad</id></website><link>http://www.gossipcop.com/angelina-jolie-oscars-leg-video-descendants-mocked-jim-rash/</link><postedTime>2012-02-27T05:25:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-04T17:37:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mq49s8</id><link>http://www.gossipcop.com/angelina-jolie-oscars-leg-video-descendants-mocked-jim-rash/#comment-456050594</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>