<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3iu17/post/2012-03-29T21:37:00</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3u7ps</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>The differences between what you've been saying all season long and what people are saying now is VERY different overall. You came on this board and took a big ol' fat dump on EVERYTHING the Avs did, whether it was good or bad, while greatly undermining everyone else's opinions consistently, and quite obnoxiously too.

While you were ripping away on the team that we love, most of us actually found numerous positives about this team that we haven't seen in recent years. Granted, those positives came in very colors throughout the season, but the point is, this team is progressing, even if you think the progression is too slow for your tastes. Real fans should take some  in that piece alone, instead of bashing them after game, win or lose. 

Sure, it would be have been great to make the playoffs this season but it's not the end of the world that they probably won't. As long as there are steps taken in the right direction to keep getting stronger and better over time, than it's not a wash at all. We made some moves in the  season and trade deadline that made this team noticeable again, mainly with adding Landeskog, Johnson, McGinn, Downie, not to mention the goal tending tandem, which also improved as the season progressed. If we add a 2-4 missing pieces, we're right there with the best of 'em competing for a deserved Spot in the playoff run within the next 2 or 3 years. There's not much point in getting there if your team doesn't have what it takes to sustain the competition of other playoff caliber teams. The Avs still have a ways to go before they get there, but they will eventually get there. And most of us loyal fans will be right here spouting  the love for our team and fighting Off those who just want to complain about how imperfect they are. 

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z8phm</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5euq</id></website><link>http://blogs.denverpost.com/avs/2012/03/28/player-reaction-saccos-pending-contract-extension/10213/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T05:27:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:37:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3iu17</id><link>http://blogs.denverpost.com/avs/2012/03/28/player-reaction-saccos-pending-contract-extension/10213/#comment-480120927</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>