<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/312236/post/127937101/comment/328558395</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>go to foodnetwork.com 
Cucumber Salad  
3 large cucumbers, thinly   
2 teaspoons salt  
3 tablespoons fresh lemon juice  
1 tablespoon vegetable oil (kosher for Passover)  
1 tablespoon sugar  
2 tablespoons chopped fresh dill  
1/2 cup thinly  red onion 
 
Toss cucumber with salt in large bowl. Cover with plate that rests directly on cucumbers; weight down with 1-pound can. Let stand 1 to 2 hours. Drain in colander; rinse well.  
Combine lemon juice, oil, sugar, and dill in serving bowl. Mix in onion and cucumber. Refrigerate overnight. Serve Cold or at room temperature 
 
Cucumber Salad 
2 English cucumbers (2 pounds)  
1 small red onion  
1 1/2 tablespoons salt  
1 tablespoon plus 1 teaspoon white wine vinegar or sherry vinegar  
1 teaspoon sugar  
2 teaspoons dried dill or 2 tablespoons fresh 
 
 the cucumber lengthwise, remove the seeds, and  thinly. Thinly  the onion.  
In a colander, toss the cucumber and onion with the salt and let it sit and drain for 20 minutes. Press the liquid out of the vegetables and rinse well with Cold water.  
 
In a medium bowl combine the vinegar and sugar and stir well. Add the cucumber mixture and toss to coat. Stir in the dill. 
 
Cucumber Salad 
2 cups thinly  Japanese cucumbers  
1 teaspoon salt  
1 tablespoon sugar  
1 tablespoon soy sauce  
1/4 cup rice wine vinegar  
1 teaspoon sesame oil  
2 teaspoons sesame seeds 
 
If Japanese cucumbers are not available, English cucumbers can be substituted. The English cucumbers need to be peeled, cut lengthwise, seeded and  into thin half moons. In a large bowl, combine cucumbers and salt and mix well. Add sugar, soy sauce, rice wine vinegar and sesame oil and mix well. Sprinkle with sesame seeds and mix. Let marinate for 20 minutes before serving. Adjust seasonings before serving. 
 
HOPE YOU ENJOY 
i like the soysauce in mine i add about 1/4 cup sugar and 1/2 cup vinegar  how much u make i make a huge bowl for my guess, i add apples to mine as well and squeeze about 2  of watermolon juice from fresh water melons in mine as well gives it a great flavor.. top it  with some Sliced advacodos for extra richness and presentation. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:312236:127937101</id><idPostId>127937101</idPostId><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:312236</id><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><link>http://www.denpdf.com</link><displayName>denpdf.com</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.denpdf.com/cucumber-salad-cucumber-salad/</link><displayName>cucumber salad- cucumber salad?</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T18:00:09.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:312236:127937101:328558395</id><link>http://www.denpdf.com/cucumber-salad-cucumber-salad/#IDComment328558395</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T18:00:09.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on cucumber salad- cucumber salad? by thagrouch519</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>e4f397cf4fe902e1f2af6ec3629f4a82</idEmailMd5><displayName>thagrouch519</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>thagrouch519 commented on &lt;a href="http://www.denpdf.com/cucumber-salad-cucumber-salad/"&gt;cucumber salad- cucumber salad?&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>