<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3faqv/post/2012-03-29T16:31:08</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>As a guy with 3 BMWs in the garage, I have  understood that, until the last 5 years, BMW  believed in a design philosophy that placed a high value on painfully slow, deliberate development of basic concepts. The K1, rather than being a bike unto itself, was really a pilot test of a series of technologies that would see their refinement and perfection in subsequent models. In the K1, the technologies being tested were - as a previous posted pointed out - ABS, a 4 valve cylinder head on a motor that hadn't been designed for one, and an updated version of their motor control electronics. By positioning the bike as a speedster, their fondest hope was that people would buy the bike and just run the p*ss out of it by parking it somewhere on the high side of 100 mph to see if it would break.  

It didn't. ;-)

Doing that did reveal some other things that needed refinement -- namely aerodynamics, management of engine Heat, and structural rigidity/vibration. If one looks at the 1997-2007 k1200RS/LT series, one sees the successful results of that refinement. If one pulls the plastic  both bikes -- no mean feat -- the drivetrain that is underneath is fundamentally unchanged. As someone that owns a 2000 LT, i can attest to the fact that these are motorcycles that are happiest when they are going very fast indeed, and do it with remarkable control and Comfort. You may or may not come to like the aesthetics of the things, but what they feel like from the saddle, 800 miles into a 1000 mile day, is pure 'like' (apologies to the folks over at facebook). ;-)</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/cm8g3n</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cf5t</id></website><link>http://www.bikeexif.com/bmw-k1</link><postedTime>2010-12-18T08:18:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:31:08+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3faqv</id><link>http://www.bikeexif.com/bmw-k1#comment-479858956</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g2igs</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2010-12-18</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>