<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjx64/post/2012-03-26T14:39:35</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>It's a wise course of action, when dealing with disputes, or even just negotiations, to 'Always look at, and consider, the other(s)' point of view'. And thus, hopefully, arrive at a more just, a fairer resolution.

Now just for a moment consider a truly 'other' point of view, re: the US vis-a-vis Iran, or, for that matter, the US vis-a-vis The Rest of the World. 

Imagine you are 'god', and that you are a fair and just 'god', and you are perched on your favorite cloud, looking down, and you are omniscient, so you see and know all that is truly happening.

You see that the US, together with it's alter ego Israel, considers itself 'exceptional', truly 'appointed, chosen by 'god' (you), to guide and rule the Earth, in it's entirety, and all it's peoples. To rightfully wage 'pre-emptive', and 'defensive' wars, to 'Shock and Awe', invade, and occupy those who disagree with, or who own assets or locations desired by, themselves, the 'chosen ones of 'god' (you). To justify lying and denying and using whatever means necessary to overcome any questions or doubts of their own peoples, those few who have not been totally lulled by generations of propaganda and lack of education from their 'leaders', political and religious and 'teachers'. And, as 'god', you wonder 'WTF are they hallucinating? I never appointed them to lead the earth! Unless...OMG...did I get really wasted and just forget!?... Naw, they must be nuts'.

Now, as 'god', since you are omnipotent, what would you do? After you tear your hair out, and send down messages via floods and tornadoes and hurricanes and droughts and Heat waves and freezing spells and idiot republican candidates and greedy Koch Bros. and corrupted SCOTUS lawyers et.al., through one of your agents, Mr. Robertson or Mr. Hagee? Would you start a plague, via Monsanto or ExxonMobil or STD-ridden, non-condom-using politicians?

Or just throw your hands up, say 'Eff-It, I tried!', and go start another world someplace else, hoping to have learned from your mistakes here on Earth?</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rwcdi</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tsjl</id></website><link>http://truth-out.org/news/item/8099-andrew-bacevich-on-changing-our-military-mindset</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T14:48:32+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:39:35+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjx64</id><link>http://truth-out.org/news/item/8099-andrew-bacevich-on-changing-our-military-mindset#comment-476618634</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/arsks</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>