<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkxiyn/update/2012-03-26T08:06:02/61fa22af83d017d0984f5d331bbecc857b5febd05043b616ef0b201a12a17937</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shooting_of_Trayvon_Martin

 The community reportedly experienced numerous instances of burglary, 
theft, and one shooting during the previous year, with 402 calls made to
 the police.

Martin said "What are you following me for?" followed by a Zimmerman's voice responding "What are you doing here?"

Zimmerman called police to report suspicious behavior, which he described as Martin "just walking around looking about" in the rain.

The dispatcher recommended that he not take any action, and informed him
 that police were on the way. Zimmerman reported that Martin had started
 running. The dispatcher asked him if he was in pursuit and he affirmed 
that he was. The dispatcher informed him that pursuit was not necessary,
 saying "We don't need you to do that." Zimmerman affirmed "OK" and made arrangements to meet with police when they arrived.

Zimmerman stated he had stepped out of his truck to check the name of the street he was 
on, when Martin attacked him from behind as he walked back to his truck.
 He said he fired the semiautomatic handgun because he feared for his life.

Zimmerman told police at the scene that he was the one crying out for help.
 The statement was corroborated by an eyewitness who claimed that Martin
 was on top of Zimmerman, beating him, as Zimmerman called for help.
 One witness, who had only heard but not seen the events, believed 
Martin was the one calling for help, and claimed that the police tried 
to "correct" her into changing their assertion to Zimmerman as the one 
calling for help.  
 Another witness who also heard but did not see the events, Mary 
Cutcher, claimed that she believed the cry was from Martin and said that
 she did not believe that Zimmerman Acted in self-defense, contending 
that she and her roommate heard Martin cry out, followed by a gunshot, 
whereupon they saw Zimmerman standing over his body.

Statements by the police say Zimmerman had grass on his back and his 
back was wet. Zimmerman was Bleeding from the nose and the back of the 
head; subsequently his lawyer stated that Zimmerman's nose was broken.

In an open letter,
 Zimmerman's father, Robert Zimmerman, defended his son against 
allegations that his actions were racially motivated, stating that 
Zimmerman was part Hispanic,
 was raised in a multi-racial family, and "would be the last to 
discriminate for any reason whatsoever," claiming that the portrayal of 
his son as a racist "could not be further from the truth."  
 In an interview with Anderson Cooper, Zimmerman's lawyer Craig Sooner 
stated that Zimmerman is not a racist, and that he had mentored black 
youths in the past.  Another friend, Joe Oliver, 53, a former television news reporter, 
noted "I'm a black male and all that I know is that George has never 
given me any reason whatsoever to believe he has anything against people
 of color." 

Weeks after the event the national media picked up the story, President Obama chimed in and a racial issue is born.

Trayvon Martin was 6 foot 3 inches and on suspension from school at the time.  George Zimmerman is 5 foot 9 inches and was a chosen by his neighbors to be the neighborhood watch coordinator.

</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r9npa</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gblz</id></website><link>http://www.newser.com/story/comments/142660/witnesses-zimmerman-made-no-effort-to-help-trayvon.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T07:51:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T12:06:02+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkxiyn</id><link>http://www.newser.com/story/comments/142660/witnesses-zimmerman-made-no-effort-to-help-trayvon.html#comment-476350328</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hwlkb</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>