<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5irot1/update/2011-08-21T23:00:20/b03ea0ff465449ca076e4002e29c0ef8235ef05bb03c522a6d718e3e00cde2c5</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>OBAMACARE MAKES ME SICK!  MY VOTE GOES TO THE CANDIDATE I CAN TRUST TO REPEAL IT!

rottweiler:  "....Of corse there something like "Death Pannels" in the Obamacare fiasco.Where death pannel might be a harsh if discriptive term, there would have to be some kind of limiting care due to cost. Anything else would be even more ripe with fraud." -- beautifully stated

Gibbsdithers:  They are absolutely in ObamaCare.  They HAVE to be for it to work.  Ask Moo' Obama about her past  'patient dumping' efforts in Chicago.  'Patient dumping' is just one aspect of trying to 'show a profit' at the expense of the victim.  We now hear that disabled Vets medical funding is 6 years from being insolvent.  It's all falling apart because of the thievery...mostly Dem thievery.  And ObamaCare needs a whole lotta big time cash from the 'people' real quick here because old people ARE A BALL AND CHAIN to socialized medicine.  They have to be sent to the 'showers'...if you get my drift.  That's what we can expect.  That shhhit needs to be repealed and Obama should do time on the rock pile for passing it against the will of the people, number one and for the fact that it's unconstitutional, number two and three:  NOBODY Fking READ IT....INCLUDING LEECHES ON THE SYSTEM LIKE MAXINE WATERS AND SHELIA JACKSON LEE.   Can you imagine?  Scaring VETS!!!

If you ask Moo', by the way, wait till she has her mouth full of lobster.

And from the dumb:  gobteabagger...."Insurance companies have been rationing care for years.Try to keep up...."

Gibbsdithers:  "..You are stone Cold dumb.  And you're probably real young.  You have no idea what this President has done to you....you have NO conception of the Scope."</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/etnxnf</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6bwl</id></website><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/karl-rove/2011/08/21/karl-rove-delivers-absolutely-epic-whooping-obamas-bill-burton</link><postedTime>2011-08-21T19:07:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-08-22T03:00:20+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5irot1</id><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/karl-rove/2011/08/21/karl-rove-delivers-absolutely-epic-whooping-obamas-bill-burton#comment-292803324</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8nldh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-08-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>