<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m09slw/update/2012-04-02T01:49:44/d3d7c52fed1ab45c9a8bf16bf746973cd0509b2be931c2a7c7144e49f768c195</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I so enjoyed reading the truth as Quek explains it in the very first comment. The USA can be far ahead of every other nation on earth. 
The first form of wealth creation is in finding food as it grows from the ground or in catching animals supported by the earth. The next most important wealth creation comes from fuel for Burning. Coal, tar, oil, and gas are the best fuels and are basic wealth wherever they are available. Production of all goods and services requires energy; for anything to happen first something gets Burned. Abundant and available energy leads to income and wealth for a society.Energy independence is a big comparative advantage for the US over the rest of the world. Historically the energy that  America was privately owned, not owned by king or government. Energy on or under lands owned by the federal government should be considered as owned by us, the citizens. Due to the transportation infrastructure of oil and gas pipelines versus shipping by sea, the local domestic energy cost will likely be less than equivalent world prices. This is anti-inflationary, and desperately helpful given our current monetary mess.The fuels produced in an energy-independent USA will generate unimaginable wealth and spread it throughout society. The income, royalties and taxes on it can balance the central budget and even pay down the national debt. Paying Off the debt is enormously beneficial.The strengthened dollar will remain as the world's reserve currency, another benefit to us. Unemployment will shrink and living standards rise. There's much to say on this, especially about private ownership being superior to government control of energy. But goodnight all, for now.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6vsuf2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/egg0</id></website><link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2012/04/02/energy_independence_after_all_113689-comments.html</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T04:06:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T05:49:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m09slw</id><link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2012/04/02/energy_independence_after_all_113689-comments.html#comment-483304786</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6qa23</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>