<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6gtq/post/2012-03-30T11:15:02</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwdu9h</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>" I respect Jason to the utmost and enjoy his written commentary. 
BUT....He is being a little contradictory here. He states "First ,it 
seems there are still a lot of facts we don't know". Then he proceeds to
 condemn Martin! How about we wait till we get ALL the facts and then we
 can make comments as to what did or did not happen."
"You are NOT the police. You are neighborhood watch! You have know 
right to pursue,detain or take any action against a stranger except to 
make the call to 911. "
"Concealed carry is a privilege and a protection. Not the right to be a
 loose cannon etc. Such as being a neighborhood watch guy thinking he is
 in the wild wild west."

You contradict yourself!   Just like many others you are making "judgment calls."  saying Zimmerman "pursued" "detained" and took "action" against Martin.  You say he behaved like he was a "loose cannon" in the "wild, wild west."   

See how easy it is to leap to a conclusion and to pass judgment?

Zimmerman had the right to follow someone he didn't recognize and found suspicious.  He was Acting as a responsible citizen and a neighborhood watch member.  He wasn't out there as a cowboy from the wild, wild west.  He was part of a group of citizens that were proactive in stopping ongoing crime in their neighborhood!
Who knows, maybe he did stop a crime from taking place, or maybe just doing his job things went wrong!  When the evidence is in, it may be the shooting was uncalled for, maybe not.  However, his action in following a suspicious individual was Spot on right!If we don't like the "suspicion" part or the "following" part, then we best move to a place where crime doesn't exist or close our doors and hide from it until we have to deal with it on our own doorstep and to heck with our neighbors!...but ...knock, knock, chances are good it will come to your door sooner or later!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h7l7v</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/h0e3</id></website><link>http://www.usacarry.com/trayvon-martin-killing/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T14:46:21+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:15:02+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6gtq</id><link>http://www.usacarry.com/trayvon-martin-killing/#comment-480843847</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>