<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/264319/post/126848280/comment/329177603</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>94.                 Reply        // .           2011.07.17 at 1:38 pm                            .        You wrote “I felt bad… I felt a little less shame.”  Why do you have to feel guilty? There is an agreement between you and Costco, where Costco describes their return policy with all exclusions (if they want to add other exclusions, they can, but they didn’t). You think, some customers return not appropriate items or too many items…??? Why do you insult such customers calling them abuses?  Costco can prevent ”abuse”.  Look, Costco can easily change its policy, make it FULL, CLEAR AND UNDERSTANDABLE for everybody, sets the limits (for example, number of items, amounts or % of returns, period of time for returns, items that can’t be returned (for example, food unless it’s bad,… and so on)). .. Why should customers guess?  I feel Costco cheats customers by not providing them with full information regarding their return policy. Customers believe that they can return items according to the written policy, come to Costco and get a Headache, insulting and guilty feelings.  Nobody wants to ague, feel shame, guilty, … to shop and to live in such atmosphere.  Sometimes returns Depend on Costco employees, how much he/she likes you, in such case it is not equal to everybody. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:264319:126848280</id><idPostId>126848280</idPostId><idBlogId>264319</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:264319</id><idBlogId>264319</idBlogId><link>http://miamiinternetadvertising.net/articles</link><displayName>Miami Internet Advertising | Rent A Local Mobile &amp;amp; SEO Ready Business</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://miamiinternetadvertising.net/articles/2012/03/20/advertising-course-internet-marketing-for-the-savvy-entrepreneur/</link><displayName>Advertising Course - Internet Marketing For The Savvy Entrepreneur</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-01T11:35:17.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:264319:126848280:329177603</id><link>http://miamiinternetadvertising.net/articles/2012/03/20/advertising-course-internet-marketing-for-the-savvy-entrepreneur/#IDComment329177603</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T11:35:17.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Advertising Course - Internet Marketing For The Savvy Entrepreneur by walutomat opinie</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://jakikantor.pl</link><idEmailMd5>1fed02aa750888323d4d022f71b2ce8f</idEmailMd5><displayName>walutomat opinie</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://jakikantor.pl"&gt;walutomat opinie&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://miamiinternetadvertising.net/articles/2012/03/20/advertising-course-internet-marketing-for-the-savvy-entrepreneur/"&gt;Advertising Course - Internet Marketing For The Savvy Entrepreneur&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>