<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mxmez4/update/2012-03-07T11:15:24/64f85ff0f606dca097fddf9640dd9e1233127d9f3d4a778f72964148bd69461b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I am at a complete loss and feel so betrayed by the very people who  to help me. I was told, just as the person below me described, that Suboxone was a non-narcotic treatment for opiod dependency. I was treated with opiod therapy on and Off for a total of three years. Unfortunately, I was allergic to a few of the more commonly used medications and then over time became resistant to the rest, to the point where it caused me double the pain I was already in, within minutes after taking it. This too, is something that occurs after long-term use of opiod pain medications. The brain receptors start turning against it and attacking because it thinks it is a poison, and well... it is!! But this was never addressed with me by the physician prior to my beginning the treatment. I hated the way they made me feel. I never had the "euphoric" sensation that has been described. I never had relief from my pain either...never. The doctors just kept going up on the medication or adding another, each time making it worse. The day I walked into the hospital to detox, I was so against any kind of narcotic pain medication that I could have been the poster child for the anti-drug war and prescription pain pill epidemic. I didn't want it in me if it had anything to do with a narcotic. It is why I steered clear of Methodone clinics. They started me on Suboxone, advising me that it was non-narcotic and nonhabit forming. Correction...only habit forming if taken for long periods of time. What I do know is, after being administered it for the first time I was pain free for the very first time in nearly four years. I also felt no side effects such as Dizziness or Drowsiness. The doctor told me that it can be used in low doses for pain management in people who have very real chronic pain issues, but are opiod intolerant like me. It has been working beautifully and I do not abuse it. But, what I have thought to have been my miracle, I am discovering that it is ust another narcotic and I have yet again been lied to. Why? That's not fair! I have tried Neurontin (because I have severe peripheral neuropathy) and in my opinion it should be controlled. That stuff is awful! It causes my head to spin and doesn't touch my pain. So now what? I hail from the great state of Florida if that gives anyone any insight to why my doctors have been so dishonest. I am quickly learning that I am going to have to be my own best advocate, do my own research and be weary of any information given to me from now on.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/go74xk</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/qmjk</id></website><link>http://www.choosehelp.com/news/addiction-treatment/getting-high-on-suboxone-the-fda-says-its-happening-ex-nida-director-blames-doctors.html</link><postedTime>2008-02-24T20:13:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-07T16:15:24+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mxmez4</id><link>http://www.choosehelp.com/news/addiction-treatment/getting-high-on-suboxone-the-fda-says-its-happening-ex-nida-director-blames-doctors.html#comment-458870058</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2008-02-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>