<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5r21fc/update/2011-07-21T23:16:16/a03d3f78a4ed53d48db5b26c679debb87e4db39996a5bc8760b274c9f2bc5b04</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Want You to know, we're here just so hot,Heat wave alert is on nationwide. So far there're closes to 30 human life had been lost due to this hot summer Heat wave. Mostly are elderly people, who they colap at home where there are no one around. This kind of phenomenon do come around every summer at this time. It may will last for may be one to two week extremely hot then after that will cool down in the evening, in the month of September fall season slowly moving in temperature will drop to very cooling in day times and cooler in the night. In the South &amp; Western part of the US you do see most of the creature of what you had showed above but except the Parrot. the cute little monkey and the pig nose turtle, Plus the most cuties one human is who got the kissed by the white Cockatoo huh. Now the Northern and Eastern part of the US and Canada we don't get to see any of these creature, except in the Zoo or the Aquarium like the one you showed. Well,will share more of the different zone and region in climate and creature next time. It can make very interesting to know the habitat of creature in Cold and warm climate. I like your Ray-Ban sunglasses make your eyes cooling,but make you look hot, it does make a different compare to those are non genuine glasses. Non genuine glasses can harm your eyes because it contained pvc material in it when you placed it in the car under the hot sun. The price of $18 for two including a kisses from you,common guys let go milk yourself a one of a life time deal. see ya.        </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/e2oa3s</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/djla</id></website><link>http://www.linoralow.com/2011/events/fun-stuff/true-discovery-in-i-city</link><postedTime>2011-07-21T08:44:09+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-07-22T03:16:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5r21fc</id><link>http://www.linoralow.com/2011/events/fun-stuff/true-discovery-in-i-city#comment-260372487</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-07-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>