<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk96qi/update/2012-03-26T13:23:46/55a001fe9b9f7e4a6fa977d068e72c289002cfc614e30b9449ae597ed10bd95b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Yet another "Different versions of SCAF"


Jihad el-Khazen  Tue, 28 February 2012  &lt;b&gt;Pleasing All People Is Impossible&lt;/b&gt;
  http://www. daralhayat. com/portalarticlendah/368387

Some extracts from article:
I found that the potential candidates[presidential] prefer to attack one another, instead of discussing their political programs with the voters. Some of the contenders did present proposals and views, but they did not amount to a clear program for any of the contenders. 

Behind all the contenders there is the military council. Its popularity has declined greatly since the time that immediately followed the revolution. Perhaps its main mistake was that it has tried to please everyone, but pleasing all people is impossible. In the process, the military council angered everyone. Yet, the Egyptian army remains the first and foremost guarantor of the political process and the transition of power. The army will restore much of its credibility when it hands over power to civilians shortly before the end of June.

In the end, I saw a slogan that said: The army and the people are one hand. But I did not ask where the other hand was.



Shana Marshall  Feb 10 2012 &lt;b&gt;Egypts other revolution: modernizing the military industrial complex&lt;/b&gt;
 http://www. jadaliyya. com/pages/index/4311/egypts-other-revolution_modernizing-the-military-i

Some extracts from article:
The Egyptian military produces a staggering array of manufactured goods: kitchen cutlery, flat-screen televisions, agricultural and household chemicals, refrigerators, industrial machinery, railway cars, and election booths. 

gets the feeling that the production of air conditioners and gas stoves has superseded the production of guns and ammo

remnants of agreements[large production] originally signed in the mid-1980s and early-1990s,

reputation for poor quality, the Egyptian military lacks a robust export market for its defense products continue to roll out weapons systems that exceed what even a bloated military can absorb

Egypt is now home to more tanks than all of Sub-Saharan Africa and Latin America combined.

The military’s economic planners know that a revival of their defense industrial complex will not be achieved through an expansion of these aging operations, but rather through cultivating new smaller scale projects that partner the Egyptian armed forces with a diverse portfolio of second- and third-tier foreign defense manufacturers willing to transfer modern technologies in exchange for lucrative sales contracts with Cairo.

intensification of technology and development collaboration with foreign defense manufacturers, including firms from the United States, Russia, the United Kingdom, China, South Africa, France, and Italy, which necessitated the construction of new facilities for research, manufacturing, and testing. Many of these partner countries are also home to international shipping conglomerates and petroleum companies that have recently launched joint ventures with Egyptian state-owned firms in which the military owns substantial shares. 

Far from slowing down in the face of economic uncertainty or concerns over political stability on the part of arms exporters, co-production agreements and technology transfers may be intensifying under the leadership of the interim military government.

Continuing these high-profile production activities in parallel with more middle-range projects also increases the likelihood that Egypt’s military factories may be able to secure a Spot in the increasingly globalized defense industry supply chain.

construction of new factory infrastructure, research and training facilities, and testing labs to enhance foreign collaboration;

Other production targets included the development of longer-range artillery and ammunition and a collaborative radar development project with an unnamed foreign partner.

Egypt’s military rulers are seizing the opportunity to expand their technological toolbox while they hold the formal reins of government—regardless of the additional cost.

There are signs of growing collaboration with non-Western suppliers as well.... co-produce 120 Chinese K-8E trainer/light attack aircraft... negotiations with an unnamed foreign partner were underway to produce Egypt’s first fighter drone. 

The Egyptian military’s current expansion plans reveal a few general policy trajectories: the construction of new factory infrastructure, research and training facilities, and testing labs to enhance foreign collaboration; an effort to Gain access to defense technologies by seeking out projects with smaller defense firms; efforts to expand weapons maintenance facilities to break into defense industry supply chains; and renewed attempts to boost Egypt’s meager record of arms exports.

One successful case in Egypt's arms export record has been its sale of military-grade jeeps...  

advantages in labor costs...  and proximity to the Middle Eastern and European markets could make it a very attractive option."

“states of the Arab Spring” represented a new opportunity for Egypt to export some of its M1A1 tank arsenal

If SCAF is able to use its executive power to engineer a post-transition system that protects the military’s economic perquisites, the latter will use the tactics described above to augment the share of the economy already under military control. This is only likely to increase the longer SCAF remains in control of the political system, allowing the military to shape electoral outcomes and legal frameworks.

Foreign arms manufacturers have long demonstrated a remarkable willingness to violate international laws and legal norms to enhance their influence with Egypt’s officer corps. This, in turn, only increases the power of the officer corps itself


&lt;b&gt;My Comments&lt;/b&gt;: I am thinking about historical references here like Nasserism where Egypt is the pivot of the Arab world and the military is the true vanguard of the Egyptian state.

Egypts geographical isolation is another part of history that is related to a "pharaonic" rule that now seems to be broken 

Egypt must strive to find its place in the global world and perhaps SCAF is doing that by globalizing their military-industrial complex. Like most of Egypts other state-controlled industry they must find new owners other than the oligarks in future. 

SCAFs (mis)management in other areas is quite poor and when it comes to political decisions I think their original idea was to get consensus in all political fractions first, which ended up in almost no decisions at all.

 </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/d0ly7b</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cjnq</id></website><link>http://blogs.aljazeera.net/africa/2012/01/17/re-building-our-country</link><postedTime>2012-01-17T22:03:47+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:23:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk96qi</id><link>http://blogs.aljazeera.net/africa/2012/01/17/re-building-our-country#comment-476558058</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ckera</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-01-17</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>