<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mflj0q/update/2012-03-15T05:52:45/c0881d7486797d5b74430b17ca8e9cb254480af6d711b18b472545a3d5516148</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Very fair write-up Noel. 

Taken as a result on a page only, this was a tanking, for sure. If folks watched the whole uncomfortable match, they would be less inclined to snipe about The Academy's quality or progression by default.  

As in the Spurs match, the kids had enough of the play in the first half to have been comfortably ahead and conceded virtually EVERY chance that  created. The club-wide malaise afflicting our players ability to finish is bordering on the comic at this point. That it's extended as far as the penalty-Spot is more unsettling. I make that 9 pens I have seen a Redman miss in regulation time this season across the levels. 

It's tempting to pour scorn on our much-vaunted 'second-only-to-La Masia' Academy but in Sterling, Adorjan, McLaughlin, Wisdom, Suso et al we have some real prospects for first team duty. 

Ajax were clinical and wonderfully organised, with several eye-catching youngsters. The final margin of defeat was cruel but not unfair because it was LFC's own failings that meant they were not in contention. 

A chastening experience for Rodolfo's band of talented kids....</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6cwaf0</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/y675</id></website><link>http://liverpool.theoffside.com/miscellaneous/liverpool-0-ajax-6-finishing-lessons.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-14T22:16:50+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-15T09:52:45+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mflj0q</id><link>http://liverpool.theoffside.com/miscellaneous/liverpool-0-ajax-6-finishing-lessons.html#comment-465849775</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c2ikt</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-14</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>