<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mfiynj/update/2012-03-16T01:32:03/0b499795b3b568e04ad34ad41d0c52acdec3e671160a7fcd5ee6283e032d0ee0</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body> Is Karen Stintz, a criminal or racist? Is she mentally fit? ------------------------------------Karen Stintz is a member of the Ontario and Federal Conservative parties. Here are some disturbing concerns I have about this woman and like to share it with you all:1. She entered politics to derail the Minto Condo project. She was actually financed by a group to push their agenda vs what is good for the development of the city. In other words the Jews in that area brought in this woman who had no previous experience in the politics and was living in that area for only 3 years. THIS SHOWS HERE WILLINGNESS TO SELL HERSELF FOR THE HIGHEST BIDDER TO ACHIEVE PERSONAL GOALS AT THE EXPENSE OF THE PUBLIC AND HER WILLINGNESS TO  ON BEHALF OF LOBBY GROUPS WITH OUT CONSIDERING THE LONG TERM GOALS OF THE CITY AS A COMMUNITY.2. She used 4,500 dollars of the public money to pay for vocal training and when caught defended her action. THIS SHOWS HOW MUCH SHE CARES ABOUT THE PUBLIC MONEY AND HER WILLINGNESS TO USE IT FOR PERSONAL .3. She wanted to run for mayor along with Rob Ford in 2010 October. But then she decided not to. The reason she gave was that she does not have the finances to compete with heavy weights who are well known. The statement made on October 19th is as follows: “It's a challenge to raise money and it's a challenge to get your name out.... When bigger names with bigger profiles come into the picture, it makes it that much harder for everybody else.” THIS SHOWS THAT SHE NEEDS SOME WAG THE TAIL INCIDENTS AT THE CITY  TO GET HER NAME OUT FOR FREE. WHAT OTHER WAY TO DO IT THAN JUST CREATE A COMMOTION WITH THE TTC FILE AND  AS IF SHE IS STANDING UP AGAINST A MONSTER ROB FORD FOR THE SAKE OF THE PEOPLE. IT GIVES HER FREE PUBLICITY MAKING TO POSSIBLE TO GET HER NAME OUT IN TIME FOR THE NEXT MAYORAL RACE. AND SHE IS ONLY BURNING NON - JEWISH CAUCASIAN AND OTHER MINORITIES WITH THIS AGENDA WHILE SERVING HER PREDOMINATELY JEWISH NEIGBOURHOOD WITH THE UNDERGROUND LRT SO SHE WOULD NOT ANGER THEM. ==================So how McGuinty and his administration are willing to support this woman in such a scandalous behavior with criminal intent for personal ? Is it because both Dalton and Stintz have the same personality or is it because she has agreed to change sides and become a Liberal from the conservative side? McGuinty government is raising more than one quarter of a trillion dollars in debt over the next 5 years. That is 250 billion dollars from around the world. In the prospectus that is being handed out to the rich and elite, Finance Minister is claiming that most of the funds will be going to infrastructure development. They raised 39 billion dollars for last year. This year another 40 billion dollars being raised. So if this money is being predominately raised for infrastructure as the Prospectus claims, then why McGuinty government can not or will not fund the difference between building an above ground system from Laird to Kennedy station, Keele to Black Creek, Finch West and in the future the completion of the Sheppard Ave line. To my understanding no one has so far asked him for them funds. SO WHY KAREN STINTZ AND HER GOONS KEEP MISLEADING THE PUBLIC SAYING THERE IS NO MONEY TO BURY THE LRT UNDERGROUND IN EVERY AREA., AND ONLY IN THE JEWISH AREA WHERE SHE IS REPRESENTING FROM? 
Metrolinx has allocated and prepared itself to spend the funds available on building the Cross Town LRT which will run underground from Black Creek to Kennedy station. And then it will run on the existing Scarborough LRT line completely away from the traffic. Metrolinx, which was created to address the transit needs with in the GTA clearly understands the importance of its agenda since it will save 25% of travel time and increase the ridership by 30%. The Sheppard ave subway extension and the Finch Ave West underground LRT are considered premature moves based on the existing demand for such services in these areas. 
How ever Metrolinx has never rejected such ideas in the future when the demand increases as the population of the city and the surrounding areas increases. And when that happens, either the city or the province will be in a position to finance such expansions. Especially in terms of the provincial government and its infrastructure agenda, the funds are there for such projects. And Karen Stintz claiming that the funds are not there, is nothing but a total lie to mislead the public like the Weapons of Mass Destruction scam the Bush Jr administration pulled on the world when they invaded Iraq. The province can issue a debt issuance aimed at such expansion plans anytime the demand is justified. ===========
At the end of the day Karen Stintz is a criminal who is using 8.4 billion dollars of ONTARIO TAX PAYER FUNDS as her OWN CAMPAIGN FUND making everyone in Ontario as suckers. When you fill up the gas and pay HST on it, this is one of the reason you are paying for it. She is carefully using the following to commit this crime:
Dividing the city Council based on political beliefs / partisan politics. Any such agenda should have been made clear to the voters before the election so that they could decide who they want to vote for. In other words, since non of these Councilors declared to the public about their political believes, the last election would be called null based on the divison that is being shown in the Council lately. Except for Mr. Rob Ford who ran for Mayor, non of the candidates spoke of this issue or disclosed to the voters.Karen Stintz is using the so called “experts” who got paid from the tax payer thru Mr. David Miller to study the Lrt advantage to promote his agenda. And most of them have ties to TTC and its union. But it is important to mention that Mr. Miller is a staunch environmentalist and this LRT expansion plan study was approved under his Clean Air strategy. Not under any strategy about what is best for the city and the dollar spent. Now Ms. Stintz is using the same experts (who can not speak in favor of an underground system after getting paid to promote the above ground LRT system) to lie to the public about a one sided story in favor of the above ground LRT. The residents of Malvern area also felt this one-sided agenda during a meeting organized by a group called Respect Scarborough which is actually Karen Stintz new found sympathizers who has political  and ties with her. This tactic is similar to that used by the Bush Jr administration to justify their agenda. And it is illegal lobbying since they are not at these meetings to support the agenda of the former Mayor but to aid Ms. Stintz to promote and  herself into Gaining the free publicity and establish that “heavy weight” image she believes that is needed to run for Mayor in the GTA. Last month (February 2012) a whistle blower by the name of Cecilia Leung told to the media, that Karen Stintz intimidated her and treated the whistle blower as if she was wasting her time when approached about issues where tax payer money was being Burnt by TTC employees. As an elected official on the TTC board and above all as the chairperson, this individual had a mandate to protect the interest of the those constituents which she failed to do so and above all failed to exhibit any interest in such responsibilities. So obviously she has been bought out by someone with in TTC. It is rumored that David Miller used to take bribes in envelopes, while he was at the office. So who is bribing Ms. Stintz and how much is being paid to this criminal? </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/65808j</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rdvv</id></website><link>http://www.nowtoronto.com/news/story.cfm?content=185740</link><postedTime>2012-03-15T03:01:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-16T05:32:03+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mfiynj</id><link>http://www.nowtoronto.com/news/story.cfm?content=185740#comment-466665723</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h0j6h</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-15</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>