<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrw5u/post/2012-03-30T12:35:44</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3jjpb</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>That's a great question Ryan S. I have attempted correcting bikers either when driving a car, and even when on my bike, and I've discovered by and large that if you are a jerk and think you are "entitled" you will continue to  entitled and  as a jerk. We have bike lanes in Boise, not ideal ones, but there are some none the less. I live in the part of town (North Boise) where there are more bike riders. I ride a bike. I drive a car. I am annoyed at bikers who do indeed ride as though they are in a peloton on streets with out bike lanes, when there is a street one block over that has a bike lane. It's just general selfishness and Acting entitled. Every time I see a bike rider without a helmet I cringe, and every time I see a bike rider california coast through stop lights and stop signs, I cringe. I'd like to see all bike lines curbed so riders are in their lane and cars are in theirs. It does often mean no street parking, and in urban areas that would cause Heartburn for most folks as there is often no other parking available.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zhgla</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/thxi</id></website><link>http://grist.org/biking/the-a-biker-problem-why-its-hard-to-share-the-road/?postpost=v2</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:13:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:35:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrw5u</id><link>http://grist.org/biking/the-a-biker-problem-why-its-hard-to-share-the-road/?postpost=v2#comment-480927623</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>