<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/anb0ht/update/2010-11-08T13:42:23/e7519a1f9cda6d58ad96c06c8a2fa3e6a1d30159bd02cd185dfa146a1396ee01</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Ok, So first I have to say that I hate the fairy. He's ridiculous! And Rob Pattison (or whatever his name is) is not attractive in the least.

However, I have watched both recently and facts only...Edward wins. If he were any other manly superhero, you guys would think he was awesome. But because he is portrayed as a gay sparkly lover boy, you guys think he's an idiot. 

Anyways, like I said, facts only. Blade kicks ass it his world because the vampires are different. They are weaker than the vampires in twilight. Why? Well first  they can't stand daylight, garlic kills them, same with silver, UV rays and also that chemical they use in the first movie. Blade get his ass handed to him in the first movie. It's the girl that saves him and them he then gets Frost. Not to mention that he kills Frost with that chemical stuff. Even with his super strength he would not have been able to kill Frost. let's face it, Blade would have just continued to hack away until he got killed if it wasn't for that chick. His ass would have been toast in the first movie. None of his weapons would work on Edward or the other vampires in Twilight. Their skin as hard as marble. Most of the Vampires that Blade kills he's does rather quickly with his sword or other random weapons made of silver he carries along with him. None of those weapons would work on Edward or other of his kind. SO bye bye weapons. Also, someone mentioned above about flame throwers... FIRST you have to rip the vampire to pieces and THEN Burn them. Flame throwers are useless unless you do that first. 

I could go on and debate Edwards whole mind reading thing. I'm just going to mark it up as a slight advantage because Blade doesn't have it. Some people mention that Blade has his martial arts as an advantage. Really? If you look at the speed factor, Edward moves at a much faster speed than Blade. Before Blade could get half a karate kick in, he would be dead. As far as I'm concerned, Edward needs one good shot at Blade and Blade is Toast.  Some guy above mentioned "well, if Blade brought a really big hammer to the fight" blah blah blah...Stop grasping for straws buddy, it's a little sad.

All super heroes could be taken apart piece by piece and categorized as Gay. Superman runs around with his underwear on top of his pants and a cape. But he's not gay. Spiderman wears a unitard and the actor talks slow and looks like a turtle. Oh, but he's cool!!! Iron Man is just some rich a$$ that built himself a robot. He doesn't even have any super abilities. The Hulk...don't even get me started on him. You guys are Always doing the same thing, anything that girls like, you guys just feel the need to categorize as Gay and bash over and over again. You even do it with actor that they like. over and over you hear, oh, he's gay. Let's face it, if someone with the same abilities as Edward would come along in a Superhero movie where he is ripping people in half over and over again, you guys would think that he is awesome. 



</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/19t7h</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5q4p</id></website><link>http://whowouldwininabrawl.com/blade-vs-edward-cullen/</link><postedTime>2009-10-24T12:02:03+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2010-11-08T18:42:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/anb0ht</id><link>http://whowouldwininabrawl.com/blade-vs-edward-cullen/#comment-95130773</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2009-10-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>