<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/migvgf/post/2012-03-22T16:17:12</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>

Alright, here are the details.


I’m 19 years old, and I started the oil cleansing method
almost three weeks ago (March 3) because Proactiv isn’t working too well and it’s
expensive. I started  with equal parts castor and extra virgin olive oil
(1/2 tsp. to ½ tsp. and I used Kirkland signature organic extra virgin olive
oil. It was on the list of good olive oils on this site and it’s Cold pressed,
so I suppose it’s okay) and three drops of tea tree oil. 


For two weeks it was fine, and my skin has really improved
in texture, but perhaps around last Saturday my forehead (especially near my temples) broke out very badly.
I think it’s just my skin purging and getting used to the new regime? I’m
hoping that is the case. I don’t know if it’s my monthly gift either, since it’s
been nonexistent since January… a doctor’s visit is required here, I believe. 


I began wiping Off the oil in the shower on Sunday because I
read that the steam helps, and I started using the ACV toner morning and night,
and yesterday I began doing the honey wash in the morning with raw honey in hopes of clearing
up my skin (I’m not allergic to honey, thank goodness)--tonight I’m going to try
adding a more castor oil to the regime as well, because I'm starting to think I have oily skin. For the past two days I’ve
increased the tea tree oil to ten drops too.


Is anyone willing to share how long it took for their skin
to grow used to the OCM? And if anyone has any helpful tips or advice, I’d be
very grateful.


</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/m76yen</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yc54</id></website><link>http://www.crunchybetty.com/nitty-gritty-on-the-oil-cleansing-method</link><postedTime>2011-10-20T19:40:49+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T20:17:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/migvgf</id><link>http://www.crunchybetty.com/nitty-gritty-on-the-oil-cleansing-method#comment-473905933</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-10-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>