<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xlmq/update/2012-03-29T13:42:06/6dd91c11f65639c4216f31174c8145f7617eb711867b10a9b512b1fab1b19162</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I've had very good experiences at Best Buy. Sad to hear others haven't on this news forum (although we don't Always hear all the good since people love to complain and share the pain). I recently purchased a laptop (Lenovo) and it was already setup by the Geek Squad. I knew I could do it myself and that extra $100 was a bit steep and I wasn't quite sure I wanted to pay....so after thinking it over I made an offer to the sales person to reduce the cost of the extra $100 and they accepted. After I got the laptop home I realized that they did an excellent job setting it up. Even if I paid the $100 it would have been worth it. All I had to do was turn the machine on. No final setup or initial setup ..... and wait.... The DVD restore cd's were already setup (and since I don't Burn DVD's often I would have had to purchase DVD's and then spend the time doing it myself - more time away from being productive. I've been to two different stores in Minnesota - Minnetonka (near Ridgdale Mall - where I purchased the Lenovo) and Maple Grove. Both stores have provided excellent customer service. I've asked for a product and they immediately start talking on their headsets to find it for me or bring me to it. I hope these stores are not the ones closing. I do agree that the movies can be overpriced....but if you catch a sale :-) Either way, I'm not bothered helping my local stores stay in business. It keeps the local economy going and people working. And that is a good thing.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zzcav</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rvx5</id></website><link>http://money.cnn.com/2012/03/29/markets/best_buy/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:53:53+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:42:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xlmq</id><link>http://money.cnn.com/2012/03/29/markets/best_buy/#comment-479686159</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zz6od</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>