<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwkg4a/post/2012-03-31T09:20:17</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwi1zb</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hq1nu</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>John - I will take your evasion of my statements as confirmation that your thesis is defeated.

I'm sorry - I never use capitals - but I simply must below in order to highlight facts you seem to have a knack of dodging.

Your first sentence "every statement you have made it yet from another website or claim as is mine"What? In a very long and detailed reply, I referred to just a SINGLE URL...!!  And you claim that "every statement is YET ANOTHER website".  
Huh?
I do appreciate that you would not like the content of my email which does utterly debunk the claims you're swallowing and passing  to others as 'fact' - but your response that I only offered websites does further destroy your credibility.
Did you actually read what I wrote?Carbon is not a poison - yes - this is not a discussion about poison (did you miss that?) it is a discussion about Heat; they're entirely different things.Have you heard of the Carbon Cycle? Given your comments, I would wager that you haven't  - or at least, you don't understand it.Yes - per the carbon cycle, carbon returns back into the atmosphere in various ways (though not nearly in the exaggerated volumes you are claiming) - but we are talking here about imbalance of that delicate balance.

For the record - I was totally opposed to the notion of the ozone hole (though, back then, I didn't have the necessary information). I appreciate that the 'loudness' of the response was driven by Du Pont for economic reasons.
The ozone hole is indeed a naturally occurring magnetically driven cycle. As such, solar activity Acting on the magnetosphere in 11 year cycles will impact.
This is a quite different issue that has its roots in the mid 1800s
I will absolutely concede that taxes and Gore play right into the hands of a very experienced petrochemical PR machine.

The facts, let me conclude, are this - vast expenditure by petrochemical industry on PR (none, zero, zilch on research) to smear the findings of over 1,000 peer reviewed scientific papers identifying human activity as to blame for global warming - and not a single (sorry... I must capitalize this: NOT A SINGLE) peer reviewed paper opposing it.

Natural climatic change is one thing; but the pace and cause of this particular cycle is avoidable and potentially more catastrophic than any before.
You may also appreciate that we have a lot more people and infrastructure at stake in 2012 than the Neanderthals of circa 80,000 to 30,000 years ago.

If you're prepared to see most of the species on earth go extinct in record numbers, that is one thing, I'm not prepared to do so.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67m9r5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/jn2h</id></website><link>http://www.iol.co.za/scitech/science/environment/the-irony-of-earth-hour-1.1267644</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:04:46+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T13:20:17+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwkg4a</id><link>http://www.iol.co.za/scitech/science/environment/the-irony-of-earth-hour-1.1267644#comment-481823641</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hqxok</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>