<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmejr/post/2012-03-30T08:52:29</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Hi Christine, thank you so much for sharing your story, it is just like readu=ing my own...I am 32 years old, a mother of 2 young children
and living with cancer for the past four years. I hated the look on people’s
face when I told them; I hated the phone calls, the pity looks, the flowers the
cards... I wanted to be healthy not sick. I thought that if I let myself believe
I was sick then I would not make it. I chose to  just like you and I still
am. I use tanning creams; I dye my hair, cut it short... I choose the people I
tell how I feel and I only go places when I feel up for it. It works for me; at
least it has for the past 4 years. But recently my workplace has asked me to go
for a medical. They said they couldn’t hold on to my job indefinitely. I don't
know if I feel sad, mad or just think it's my fault for not telling people how
I really feel. Cancer is so much part of my daily life; I don't want it to take
over. Hiding it is my way of coping. I try so hard to LIVE that I don't want to
talk about anything that would remind me that I am on reprieve. Why should I be
penalized for trying to get my life back? For enjoying myself when I feel good?
I have lost so much already... I just don't know how to handle the idea of
loosing my job just yet. I have lost so much already. I understand they need to
move on, but I wish they would just leave me alone. Cancer is not Flu. It is so
hard, it takes so much from you, physically emotionally and yet you can't
complain because you survived. I am thankful, I wake everyday thinking how
lucky I am, I have 2 adorable children, a loving husband and great friends and
family. I am a positive person and I try hard to concentrate on what I have, on
what I can do rather than what I can't do. I think that's why I Act healthy and
hide at home when I'm not. I feel I have won a little battle each time I
accomplish something, and I don't think I should hide it then... I wish I had a
friend who was as sick as me to laugh about it sometimes, but I don't. I don't
feel sick but I am...

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ysku6l</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/oys5</id></website><link>http://www.butyoudontlooksick.com/articles/written-by-christine/chronic_illness_feelings/</link><postedTime>2012-03-05T14:30:23+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T12:52:29+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmejr</id><link>http://www.butyoudontlooksick.com/articles/written-by-christine/chronic_illness_feelings/#comment-480705527</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-05</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>