<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/8jmpb4/update/2011-03-16T11:43:33/7ed1cb0cd3aa159d05392b4bf48ee1d18a1fdb23e6b441f79b3f1aad15ab7d5f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Modern medicine tries to explain this as some sort of neurological condition. I have not noticed anyone talk about this from a modern physics or eastern spiritual standpoint so I would like to share my observations in the hopes that it may assist or Comfort others:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Reality is not confined to the physical world or the five senses. &lt;br&gt;2. There is a spiritual realm/dimension to our existence of which many are not aware of - this is referred by many eastern religion/philosophies as being caught in the 5 sense illusion. &lt;br&gt;3. Many eastern religious/philosophies (Buddhism, Sant Mat Meditation, ECKANKAR, Qyan Yin Method of meditation, Inner light and Sound Meditation) talk about the spiritual world in detail. &lt;br&gt;4. With regard to modern science, physicists now believe that the universe is vibrating. They talk about about parallel universes, how many worlds represent reality and that we have decohered from these other planes of existence. Some have even admitted that they don't like to teach this to chemistry students because people would get upset. This branch of physics is called the modern interpretation of the quantum theory. One top physicist who had spoken openly about this is Michio Kaku (co-founder of the super string theory).  &lt;br&gt;5.According to Einsteins theory, matter and energy are one. Physicists believe all systems in nature have their own particular way of vibrating. Each oscillate at its own unique rate. Rocks vibrate very slowly at speeds that are imperceptible to us. Living things like plants, animals and man vibrate faster and appear to be alive. The same hold for thoughts, feelings, events and words spoken - each carries its own vibration. If all in the universe is taken down to its simplest form, it is just energy. (I got this point five from Dr Rita Louise's radio show on &lt;a href="http://BlogTalkRadio.com" rel="nofollow"&gt;BlogTalkRadio.com&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br&gt;6. Often in these so called "sleep Paralysis" episodes, many people experience/hear sound, buzzing, vibration. This experience of sound, buzzing or vibration is the vibration mentioned in point 4 &amp; 5. &lt;br&gt;7. If you hear sound, buzzing or vibration, then you are experiencing the audible vibration. Some people see light. When this occurs, then they are experiencing the visible vibration. This vibration is also referred to as the inner sound or silent sound.&lt;br&gt;8. This sound, buzzing or vibration is also referred to as "The Heavenly Music" in all holy scriptures of different religions such as the "word" in christianity, the "shabd" in hinduism, the "heavenly music" in buddhism, the "tao" in taoism.&lt;br&gt;9. Many spiritual/meditation groups, like the ones above, meditate on on this inner vibration. &lt;br&gt;These groups often advocate a "purification" of speech, actions and thoughts as these all affect our personal vibration. By "purifying" your speech, actions and thoughts, individuals are able to raise their vibration and protect themselves or escape/avoid encountering these beings with an evil presence. (Generally speaking, physics theory behind this is that we are cohered to notice or experience things within a similar vibrational range to ourselves).&lt;br&gt;10. These unpleasant beings vibrate at a lower/coarser frequency, which is why many people feel uncomfortable in their presence. These beings are also spoken of eastern religious/philosophies for those who are interested in doing research.  &lt;br&gt;11. Typical examples of purifying speech, actions and thoughts include refrain from harming any living being, speaking what is not true, stealing, sexual misconduct and using intoxicants. Generally speaking, it means being a good/loving person with good intentions/thoughts.&lt;br&gt;12. Another way to protect themselves or escape/avoid encountering these beings with an evil presence is to remember, think of and/or want to know about God or what some call the True Self.  This is one of the reasons why when many people following an eastern or western religion ask for help from God, Jesus, Quan Yin Bodhisvatta, Amitaba Buddha, Krishna, their True Self or some other Fully Enlightened Spiritual Guru they are immediately assisted in their experience (just like it is stated in the Bible "Matthew 7:7 Ask, and it shall be given you; seek, and ye shall find; knock, and it shall be opened unto you:"). From a physics viewpoint, focusing on God helps to raise an individual's vibrational frequency.&lt;br&gt;13. Apart from having a physical body we also have what is called a astral body. This is why an individual can clearly see another being present even when they cannot physically open their eyes or may be very short-sighted. This is also why people can leave their bodies and walk around the house or do other kinds of astral travel. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's a lot more I'd like to share but I'm out of time.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/clkquv</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lj1l</id></website><link>http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2009/08/sleep_paralysis/</link><postedTime>2011-01-05T04:05:27+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-03-16T15:43:33+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/8jmpb4</id><link>http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2009/08/sleep_paralysis/#comment-166646970</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-01-05</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>