<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/312236/post/127937490/comment/328562443</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Wake up to this immune-boosting antioxidant cocktail that supplies all your vitamin A for the day and more than half your requirement for vitamin C. 
 
#1 ___CARROT- ORANGE JUICE 
 
11/2 cups fresh or bottled carrot juice, chilled 
2/3 cup fresh-squeezed orange juice ( 3 oranges) 
1/2-inch-thick  peeled fresh ginger 
 
In bowl, mix carrot juice and orange juice. Crush ginger in garlic press to fill 1/2 tsp. Stir crushed ginger into juice mixture and serve. ( If making ahead, stir before serving.) 
 
#2___ITALIAN SPINACH PIE 
Perp: 10 min / Cook: 38 min 
 
Eat plenty of spinach to help keep your heart in tip-top shape with vitamins A and C and folate. 
 
1 tbsp olive oil 
2 medium leeks, white part only, halved lengthwise, thinly , and rinsed 
1 box (10 ounces) chopped spinach, thawed and squeezed dry 
1 cup cooked long-grain white rice 
3 large eggs 
1 cup grated Parmesan cheese 
1/2 tsp dried marjoram, crumbled 
1/2 tsp salt 
1/4 tsp black pepper 
 
1. In medium nonstick skillet over medium Heat, Heat oil. Add leeks. Saute until softened, about 8 minutes. Set aside. 
2. Preheat oven to 375 deg F. Lightly coat 9-inch glass pie plate with nonstick cooking spray. 
3. In medium bowl, combine leeks, spinach, rice, eggs, 3/4 cup Parmesan, marjoram, salt, and pepper. Spoon into prepared plate and smooth top. Sprinkle with remaining 1/4 cup Parmesan. 
4. Bake until firm and browned, about 30 minutes. Serve warm or at room temperature, cut into wedges. 
 
#3___He's a chocoholic that you can't stop him right now...... :-p 
Here an....  
Old-Fashioned Secret-Ingredient Chocolate Cake-low in CALORIES.... 
Prep: 20 min / Cook: 30 min 
 
3/4 cup tomato juice 
1/4 cup water 
2/3 cup unsweetened cocoa powder 
21/4 cups all-purpose flour 
1 tsp baking soda 
1/2 tsp baking powder 
1/4 tsp salt 
11/2 cups sugar 
1/2 cup vegetable oil 
3 large eggs 
11/2 tsp vanilla extract 
 
For Icing 
1 ounce unsweetened chocolate 
2 tbsp low-fat (1%) milk 
1 tbsp unsweetened cocoa powder 
4 ounces 1/3-less-fat cream cheese 
21/2 cups confectioners'sugar, sifted 
1/2 cup seedless raspberry jam 
 
1. Preheat oven to 350 deg F. Coat two 9-inch-round cake pans with nonstick cooking spray. 
2. In small saucepan, bring tomato juice and water to a boil. Whisk in cocoa powder until smooth. Remove from Heat. 
3. In medium bowl, stir together flour, baking soda, baking powder, and salt. 
4. In large bowl, beat together sugar, oil, eggs, and 1 tsp vanilla extract until combined. Beat in cocoa mixture. Beat in flour mixture just until evenly moistened. Divide batter between prepared pans. 
5. Bake until toothpick inserted in centers of cakes come out clean, 25 to 30 minutes. Transfer pans to wire rack. Let cool 10 minutes. Turn cakes out onto rack. Let cool completely. 
6. Prepare icing: In medium microwave-saft bowl, microwave together chocolate and milk on high powder 1 minute. Stir until smooth. Whisk in cocoa powder until smooth. Whisk in cream cheese and 1/2 tsp vanilla extract. Stir in confectioners'sugar until combined. 
7. Place one cake layer on flat plate or platter. Spread top of this layer with jam. Place remaining layer over layer with jam on it. Spread icing over side and top of cake.   
 
Have fun..... Enjoy! _;-)</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:312236:127937490</id><idPostId>127937490</idPostId><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:312236</id><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><link>http://www.denpdf.com</link><displayName>denpdf.com</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.denpdf.com/healthy-dessert-recipes-healthy-snack-and-dessert-recipes/</link><displayName>healthy dessert recipes- Healthy snack and dessert recipes?</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T17:29:43.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:312236:127937490:328562443</id><link>http://www.denpdf.com/healthy-dessert-recipes-healthy-snack-and-dessert-recipes/#IDComment328562443</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T17:29:43.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on healthy dessert recipes- Healthy snack and dessert recipes? by Ng W</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>a099491620ea6b096987ce2769284cfd</idEmailMd5><displayName>Ng W</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>Ng W commented on &lt;a href="http://www.denpdf.com/healthy-dessert-recipes-healthy-snack-and-dessert-recipes/"&gt;healthy dessert recipes- Healthy snack and dessert recipes?&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>