<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkuj4u/post/2012-03-26T10:43:54</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I voted "Yes" on your mediating but I don't believe they are due a full refund - as you stated, they DID take the cruise and enjoy the benefits.

What I believe you should mediate is their getting that $1,000.  Not in Monopoly money, as the cruise line has offered, but in a refund.  The OP paid them them in Cold, hard cash, not in paycheck vouchers, and this is what they should get back.

To offer them a credit like this is a slap in the face because it really doesn't cost them anything to do this.  This is them saying, "We really are sorry about the recent misadventures on your cruise and if you spend another $4500 (or whatever the price is, less $1,000) with us, we'll show you just how sorry we really are."

And I felt this should be said - I'm sure there will be a number of people feeling no refund at all simply because they don't understand why having kids on a cruise would ruin it.  

I love kids and I have four (grown or nearly grown) kids of my own.  I love my grandchildren, when I get to see them due to their being overseas with their military father and I enjoy having them around.  However, there are times I DON'T enjoy having kids around and if I have the expectation of the quiet of no kids, it's jarring when it happens.  When I was the mother of younger kids, we didn't take vacations that would Ensure our travel partners were nothing but adults sans kids.  

This might be difficult to understand if you are the parent of younger children but...  Kids can really ruin a good day and if they have the kind of parents who simply smile and go back to their Long Island Iced Tea while their child rips the toilet from the wall, I just want to commit Seppuku...</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r1zby</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/vhd7</id></website><link>http://www.elliott.org/blog/our-adults-only-cruise-had-a-minor-problem/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T05:11:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T14:43:54+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkuj4u</id><link>http://www.elliott.org/blog/our-adults-only-cruise-had-a-minor-problem/#comment-476440079</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zd6rf</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>