<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msoq87/delete/2012-03-28T09:12:44</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Where are the tears and press on the following?
 Wednesday, Jun. 22, 2011
America's new racists
Today all that has changed. Most racist assaults are committed by blacks. What's worse is there're blacks, still alive, who lived through the times of lynching, Jim Crow laws and open racism who remain silent in the face of it.
Last year, four black Skidmore College students yelled racial slurs while they beat up a white man because he was dining with a black man. Skidmore College's first response was to offer counseling to one of the black students charged with the crime. In 2009, a black Columbia University professor assaulted a white woman during a Heated argument about race relations. According to interviews and court records obtained and reported by Denver's ABC affiliate (12/4/2009), black gangs roamed downtown Denver verbally venting their hatred for white victims before assaulting and robbing them during a four-month crime wave. Earlier this year, four black girls beat a white girl at a McDonald's, and the victim suffered a seizure. Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel ordered an emergency shutdown of the beaches in Chicago because mobs of blacks were terrorizing families. According to the NBC affiliate there (6/8/2011), a gang of black teens stormed a city bus, attacked white victims and ran Off with their belongings.
At Philly's South Philadelphia High School, Asian students report that black students routinely pelt them with food and beat, punch and kick them in school hallways and bathrooms as they hurl racial epithets such as "Hey, Chinese!" and "Yo, Dragon Ball!" The Asian American Legal Defense and Education Fund charged the School District of Philadelphia with "deliberate indifference" toward black victimization of Asian students.

Eight suspects in the savage beating of an 18-year-old Columbia man turned themselves into Columbia police Thursday night after surveillance video appeared to connect them to the crime, the Columbia Police Department said.
8 Blacks jump one lone jogger
   Tonight, around 11 p.m., a group of at least 60-70 African American youth marched down one of the side streets (W. Thrush) to the 4 lane main drag (Sheridan). They were yelling threats to white residents. Things such as we need to kill alll the white people around here. They were physically intimidating anyone calling for help from the police. They were surrounding cars. Cars on the main drag had to slam on their brakes to either avoid the youth blocking not only all four lanes, but a large section of the side street as well. fights were breaking out among them. They were rushing residents who looked out their doors, going on to porches, yelling threats to people calling the police for help.

Submitted by Mark Berman Opposing Views on Dec 23, 2010
A black man from New York, who was convicted of killing a white teenager, is free Thursday, after Gov. David Paterson pardoned him and commuted his sentence.
John White served just five months on a sentence of two-to-four years for his manslaughter conviction for the shooting death of 17-year-old Daniel Cicciaro, Jr.
If you want to see real Racial Hatred look into the Wichita and Knoxville Murders.
</body><verb>delete</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66xv77</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dndh</id></website><link>http://www.myrtlebeachonline.com/2012/03/24/2734596/issac-j-bailey-uncomfortable-truths.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-24T04:05:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T13:12:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msoq87</id><link>http://www.myrtlebeachonline.com/2012/03/24/2734596/issac-j-bailey-uncomfortable-truths.html#comment-478342023</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8959a</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>killed</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>