<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/266648/post/101560918/comment/329470401</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I agree with Rob&amp;#039;s thoughts and am Glad he has expressed them here to open up the discussion.  His entry here has helped me to better understand the feelings of parents with children all across the spectrum.  We do need to pull together as a group to provide the best resources and acceptance for ALL of our children. 
 
I do have one question, though I am merely speaking from my experience.  Do any of you ever feel that being High Functioning is difficult as well, in that there is often an increased awareness of your differences and possibly more Anxiety?  I have a son with Asperger&amp;#039;s who is high functioning academically, yet cannot comprehend the social aspects of others at all.  He has high levels of Anxiety and has tried college (he quit when it came to forced group projects), and is now trying to work part time.  But it is a continuous roller coaster ride.  He is overwhelmed by the social interactions involved, feels badly about himself when he sees those who knew him from high school and expected so much more of him, and misunderstands others statements or instructions.  It is heart breaking to witness. 
 
Thank you for the opportunity to share in this discussion.  And I am in no way implying our struggles are any greater than any other family with a child on the spectrum. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:266648:101560918</id><idPostId>101560918</idPostId><idBlogId>266648</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:266648</id><idBlogId>266648</idBlogId><link>http://lostandtired.com</link><displayName>Lost and Tired</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://lostandtired.com/2011/07/24/why-autism-awareness-is-broken/</link><displayName>Why Autism Awareness is broken</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-01T20:25:05.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:266648:101560918:329470401</id><link>http://lostandtired.com/2011/07/24/why-autism-awareness-is-broken/#IDComment329470401</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T20:25:05.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Why Autism Awareness is broken by Sue</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>bfe379f7af68e83c83f1f64aa1a32ad3</idEmailMd5><displayName>Sue</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>Sue commented on &lt;a href="http://lostandtired.com/2011/07/24/why-autism-awareness-is-broken/"&gt;Why Autism Awareness is broken&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>