<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m1aj5x/update/2012-03-12T16:34:50/67141740d7b37ea9a197369128a15d731b8ee288e8f74602ae6a6638822b4b0d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>It sounds like good sense, at first Blush, to see the argument made that if ANY tax is put on a corporation it will pass that tax expense along to customers.  Let's do away with all taxes and regulatory fines then.  After all, if a corporation pollutes the air illegally, and thousands of asthmatics and babies and elderly people die from that illegal pollution, and the government fines the polluting corporation, this is not a deterrent because the corporation will just pass along the expense of that fine to its customers.  

The seventeen (plus) banking corporations that committed flagrant, blatant mortgage fraud -- resulting in running up the U. S. housing market by 75% or more, under the G. W. Bush administration, and collapsed it (under G. W. Bush), and led thence to the crash of the entire economy (under G. W. Bush)
was a terrible thing.  Don't you agree.  (If you do not believe that this is what brought about the Great Recession, read the best-seller by Gretchen Morgenson (Reckless Endangerment)

It's all totally verfified, and no one can deny it with a straight face.

However, here's where things get REALLY interesting:  No criminal charges were brought against any principal officer of any of those corporations, despite overwhelming, prima facie evidence.  INSTEAD, under the current administration, lawsuits were brought, and one-by-one these corporations have been allowed to settle out of court.  One settlement was for two-billion.  Does that sound like a lot of money?  Check it out in Morgenson's book.  It's mere PENNIES  ON  THE  DOLLAR  of the trillions... yes, with a "t" that corporation Gained through fraud.

So, what happens when a corporation gets taxed, fined, or in any other manner is caused to have to pay out any amount of money?  

It gets passed along to customers -- or comes out of profits and therefore decreases what drives stock prices (profits), and hence penalizes, in the case of a public corporation, its STOCKHOLDERS.

Are you beginning to get the picture.  There are those who would have you and me believe that no corporation should be fined, taxed, sued by any regulatory agency of the government BECAUSE it will just pass along the resultant expense to its customers and/or its shareholders.

See what the gist of that argument is:  It is that the people and their political electees, appointees, and hirelings ARE  POWERLESS  TO  ENFORCE  any rule against any corporation.  

Once you have let that soak in, you may wonder, "Why, then, even HAVE any laws, and regulations or any fines or any taxes on corporations.  The corporate execs will LOVE  YOU  for making that argument on their behalf.  It's tantamount to saying, "There ARE no laws that will impact corporations."

At this point you may be wondering, "Okay, then, why haven't any of those corporate EXECUTIVES been charged under the existing laws... yes, existing laws... against fraud (which Gretchen's book will explain to your total understanding."

Answer:  "Because THOSE  CORPORATE  EXECS  FUNNEL  MILLIONS  OF  DOLLARS  TO  THE  ELECTED  OFFICIALS  WHO  APPOINT  THE  HEADS  OF  THE  SO-CALLED "LAW-ENFORCEMENT AGENCIES" OF THE U. S. GOVERNMENT AND THE  STATE  GOVERNMENTS!"

Those politicians you elect in what you perceive to be a "democratic" way are inundated with campaign contributions, favors or all imaginable kinds (and some unimaginable, unless you have a very dark and correct view of the morals and ethics of todays politicians, and how they get immensely richer than the piddling little salaries they are paid for their jobs).

Get the picture now?  Those corporate execs hire people to pretend to enter comments in blogs just like this one, and muddy the water, to convince you that the corporations should not be controlled in any way, because they will pass the resultant cost on to their customers and shareholders.  So, don't you get it?  The smart thing is to let them do anything and everything they want to, legal or otherwise, because you are wasting your time.  Those corporate execs have friends in high places, and YOU  DO NOT.  You do not have millions to spend on lobbyists and campaign donations.  So your power, and your complaints, are futile and pointless and will just come back on you and other powerless citizens.

You've been hearing certain platitudes that right wing nuts have been repeating to you for decades now, to convince you that corporations are your friends, and the mean old bad old laws and taxes and regulations are hurting those friends of yours... the corporations that bribe, and your politicians who accept those bribes, an sell out on you.

But, hey, I understand.  To dig in and study and discover for yourself the whole picture -- the picture the corporation's hired journalists and cartoonists, and the politicians they turn into multi-millionaires provided they speak the narrative as they are PAID to speak it -- that's the picture you will get, and hear repeated and repeated and repeated and repeated,.. if you do not dig in and find out the facts for yourself.

And when you've heard something repeated a million times, and you never hear the REAL story told, it's only understandable that you don't get it when sometells you you are being scammed.

It's not your fault.  Or, at least, not if being too lazy to dig and find out the truth is asking too much of you.  It's hard work digging out the truth behind all the hype and sound bites and political b------t.  Maybe you should not be expected to question any of that.  To do so requires thinking and questioning what you hear.  It's much, much easier to just repeat what you hear, and have others who do likewise agree with you.

That's what most people do, you know.  And who doesn't want to be repeating what "everybody's" saying, instead of something that might cast doubt on it.  
.  
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/y0v3o1</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/y3mp</id></website><link>http://www.instituteforenergyresearch.org/2012/03/09/bill-oreilly-exporting-nonsense-on-gas-prices/</link><postedTime>2012-03-08T21:08:51+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-12T20:34:50+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m1aj5x</id><link>http://www.instituteforenergyresearch.org/2012/03/09/bill-oreilly-exporting-nonsense-on-gas-prices/#comment-463655829</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6qfs2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-08</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>