<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/cwrwmp/update/2011-06-30T16:27:44/de5cbb12abeb12389f9779100cf0b4e130bbb3cbeb61742cedd6e2ed36a8ed62</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/c3b015</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ep0un</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>you seem to think that opiate addicts can 'just stop' if they try hard enough, but i'd wager you've never been through opiate withdrawals.  every time you move, you get small tears in your muscles, but your natural endorphins stop you from feeling those tears as pain.  in opiate withdrawal your system is completely emptied of endorphins.  every slight movement is painful, it's impossible to sleep for more than about 2 hours per day, you constantly have incredibly strong Flu-like symptoms, every muscle, every bone in your body aches.  i am a recovered heroin addict and i would rather have my leg broken again than go through heroin withdrawal again.  not to mention the fact that if it is severe enough, heroin withdrawal can sometimes kill you, and methadone withdrawal is easily capable of killing people.


Cold turkey simply doesn't work for the majority of people, the survival instinct kicks in, and all they want to do is stop feeling like they have just been hit by a truck.  all rationality goes out the window and all but the most strong willed will cave in, just as most people would cave in to torture.  even if you make it through Cold turkey, you generally haven't been given enough time to adjust to sober life, by the time you're finished, and cravings often get the better of people.  a slow taper  heroin on a methadone program (although methadone is even harder to get ) or preferably on legal heroin or buprenorphine, gives people time to adjust and try to establish a normal life before they quit.  it gives people the opportunity to work and fix the part of themselves that causes them to become an addict in the first place.  Cold turkey simply doesnt work in the majority of cases.  most long term heroin addicts take the drug just to feel normal, they dont feel any real rush or enjoyment from it, they just need it to keep the unbearable pain of withdrawals away.

And as for paying for someone else's drugs habit, i will happily do so if it keeps them from stealing and driving up insurance for everybody, or going to prison and costing a huge amount of money to keep them there.  in any case the swiss guy pays for his OWN habit.  he works and pays taxes.  i would also gladly pay for someone else's habit if they are getting their heroin at a proper clinic and using clean needles and not contributing to the spread of HIV/Hepatitis C.  You can't just ignore those less fortunate and allow them to die or fester, because these things have a habit of filtering up the social classes and costing taxpayers a lot of money.  heroin is not particularly expensive to manufacture and it is much cheaper in the long run for addicts to be treated and gradually weaned Off heroin than to just leave them to rot.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/gxuwwf</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/mxvm</id></website><link>http://prod.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/krokodil-the-drug-that-eats-junkies-2300787.html</link><postedTime>2011-06-21T23:00:47+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-06-30T20:27:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/cwrwmp</id><link>http://prod.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/krokodil-the-drug-that-eats-junkies-2300787.html#comment-239063033</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/meckj</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-06-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>