<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jms9/update/2012-04-02T02:48:25/ad0385594bd0fe366dd9c8f9514cad67406806020af42cf15d2d571eb866077f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m09bv4</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Nikkoh, as far as I can see, the reason we go around and around on this is because no amount of evidence, logic, or discussion will prevent you from continuing to post the same rhetoric post after post without any real evidence to back it up.  You have a gut feeling, and I respect that.  But it's illogical to continue to raise issues which have already been addressed.

Here is what I AM sure of.  Without intervention, the private sector (especially energy) will continue to do what it has Always done, which is to continue generating emissions without considering the long term effects in order to maximise profits.  So when hit with the expense of paying for their emissions , of course they will pass the cost on the consumer, that is the purpose of the compensation package.  The point is that the companies will go wherever the profit is greatest, and you know this is true.  The price on carbon simply adjusts the lay of the land so that doing what we want them to do is also the most profitable route for them to take.

So, if the cost for them is Co2 intensive energy + price on carbon versus renewable energy without any extra costs, and the latter works out cheaper, then the latter will be the obvious choice.

There are numerous causes for price rises in the electricity sector, with ever increasing consumption, installation of infrastructure and maintenance of same along with ever increasing use density and delivery distance, all alongside with the increases in costs of staff, newer technology, not to mention the cost of the materials they consume to produce energy.  Keep in mind that we use quite a high grade of coal in our power stations, so it's not the cheapest commodity in itself, and the coal industry is going to ask for as much as they can get, knowing full well that it is a captive market.  You think these coal companies are rolling in cash because they are subsidising the cost of coal in Australia?  We could then go on to look at the long relatively static cost of power and the inevitability of a price increase to match the cost of production in order to maintain and grow profits.  There are many MANY factors, of which these are just a few of the more obvious.

The notion that the power companies would ramp up prices for a carbon price they did not know about in order to reduce the apparent impact of the cost they do not want to pay is an interesting one.  Suffice it to say, I don't see it.  Why would they help the government out?  If anything, I would suspect the more recent price rises were in order to increase Anxiety over the added cost in order to have it scuttled.  Believe me, these businesses do not want to change, they do not want to have their profits threatened, and I'm sure they would not go out of their way to assist the current government.

The Barrier Reef issue is a distressing one, and I share the opinion that it should be stopped, but given that the current government is at least somewhat able to enter into a dialogue, I feel that we have a chance to stop it from happening.  What we don't need is an Abbott government which will do whatever Tony says, regardless of how much sense it makes.
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zcm8o</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/mk07</id></website><link>http://blog.getup.org.au/2012/03/29/latest-campaign-dont-let-clive-get-away-with-this/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T05:51:30+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T06:48:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jms9</id><link>http://blog.getup.org.au/2012/03/29/latest-campaign-dont-let-clive-get-away-with-this/#comment-483319754</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5dihk</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>