<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp613e/update/2012-03-21T12:02:08/e76fac6184c538fdf8bc1e16bdd8d8f574be98a02174ba41e87adca430e96025</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>White people don't think everything is racist because they aren't discriminated against, most of the time. They are born into a world where they receive special treatment just because of their skin color so when any black person mentions racism, they think it's blown up because they don't experience what we go through. They usually say, like Matt Lauer is implying, everything isn't racist or it's not because you are black. He didn't necessarily say this but that's what many white men and white women azzume. Really? Well, if what black men and women go through isn't because we are black, why do many of us who are law abiding citizens still get mistreated during the workplace, in our cars, in stores, etc.?.... Trayvon's murder was done in Cold blood, but they can't fathom that because they aren't victims of many race-related murders, police brutality, DWB, being followed in stores just because they think you will steal something, being asked why you are in a particular neighborhood, even though you live there yourself, etc.  Or, succeeding in life, then being asked did you go to a particular school because of an athletic scholarship or due to affirmative action. They don't believe black people are smart enough to get into an institution based on their intellect alone..... Everything I mentioned is what many black men and black women go through but most white people don't deal with this so they don't and will never understand. Hell, even if whites don't have a degree, some of them can still make more money than blacks folks with degrees.....White people can be in a relationship with blacks, or blacks can have good friends that are white, have the white co-worker they eat lunch with, and if something racist happens, they still won't be able to relate to what we go through, because they don't experience it. No matter how much we try to explain, they won't get it. 

If Trayvon would have killed someone, he would have been arrested. That young brother would have been in the jail house in less than not even an hour after he fired the shot. But since Trayvon is dead, everyone wants to give Zimmerman the benefit of the doubt, but no one would give Trayvon the same benefit if the situation were reversed. And people want to Act like because a black family is in the White House, racism no longer exist. Three words: Got Damn Lie.
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6djv95</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/45f2</id></website><link>http://bossip.com/559935/trayvon-martins-parents-speak-out-we-want-an-arrest-to-be-made-video69691/</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T13:06:08+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-21T16:02:08+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp613e</id><link>http://bossip.com/559935/trayvon-martins-parents-speak-out-we-want-an-arrest-to-be-made-video69691/#comment-472470954</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>