<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/234352/post/86320894/comment/329353027</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>A lot like high-quality music, the TX has such needs, find a tutorial online and share with you! learning needs, contact the APE TO the CD aspects of knowledge, help after a lot of students, and finally learn, dare not exclusive, so time to make this tutorial to share with everyone, I hope to be able to help acridine of the classmates and friends. first introduced the APE is an audio file format, APE is an audio CD lossless compression format. APE format audio image file compression and download to get by ripping. APE format audio use foobar2000 to play,Hermes Kelly, but also allows WINAMP by installing plug-ins to play the APE for winamp plug-ins included in the Annex. Please need a friend to download it into the relevant directory, and do not know the path can refer to the tarball comment :),Hermes Kelly handbags, APE Burn can use foobar2000 or Nero Burning ROM Burning software to install the plug directly in There may be friends doubt, since these two software can be used to Burn APE format audio, you need to write this tutorial to do it, the answer is this, foobar directly onto CD, the first sound is not very good. The second is to Burn that CD shelf life is greatly shortened. After all, not a professional CD Burning software, do not use these features included. This is like compared to the effect of the popular mobile phone with digital camera and professional digital camera. A lot of people use NERO to Burn through the installation of the plug-APE violent tone of the phenomenon. after a preliminary test of the specialized software, the other a professional CD Burning software Exact Audio Copy (referred to as EAC) (only Burn music) to Burn music CD quality is much better, if the image file to do good, EAC engraved out of the CD is almost like genuine original. So even this focuses on the knowledge of this EAC software and not through the use NERO plug-Burn APE. Well, ado, now start our tutorial: 1.Monkey \'s Audio V3.99f Freeware 2.Foobar2000 V0.8.3.408 finished enhance Edition (full installation) 3.Exact Audio Copy V0.95 the Beta 3 4.Nero Burning ROM v6.6.0.18 downloaded from the Internet APE generally in two forms, The A. a great CDImage.ape CDImage.cue file B. The several small *. the ape and a cue file (or no cue file) composition which ape is a compressed audio file, the cue is the mirror image information file before Burn the first thing we need to do is to extract the ape format into wav format, wav APE Go through two pieces of software to complete. I who first introduced the first software: Monkey\'s Audio V3.99f normal download from the Internet to install the original and Freeware, after 1. Run Monkey\'s Audio V3.99f 2. Select menu - Select hardware and software environment, the extraction process can be canceled at any time decompression, the speed in the demo picture only reference, when the progress bar  100% you can find under the folder of the APE WAV file of the same name. At this point, the extraction is complete. 2, the software can be used to decompress after Foobar2000 V0.8.3.408 finished enhanced version Download Remember completely The installation . Generally contains a CUE file we downloaded APE audio files, directly from the APE file, APE files converted output as a single WAV files, this method is generally used scattered APE files converted to WAV. 1 run Foobar2000, 2. target APE files, right to and then right in the target APE file &amp;gt; APE audio contains CUE menu file, that is, we may need to songs we need to be extracted from the CUE inside a single WAV audio files, this time on CUE file conversion. 1 run Foobar2000, audio track file 2. can make use of the CTRL key to multiple choice For isolated, right above the same start the conversion after the conversion of either of these two software will get what we need WAV audio files, and now we start,Hermes Birkin, please Burn the protagonist Exact Audio Copy software, referred to the EAC,Hermes Birkin bags, almost grab any CD tracks without losing the really converted to WAV, support ATAPI and SCSI CD-ROM drive can play CD, also connected to the Internet to play the CDDB. The highest official version of Exact Audio Copy V0.95 Beta 3, because no Freeware to keep up with, so Oujiu broke a Simplified Chinese language pack, after the above link to download and install EAC, the floor attachment download solution pressure get SChinese.txt, which is the Simplified Chinese language pack, Please SChinese.txt into the Exact Audio Copy installation directory Languages &amp;#8203;&amp;#8203;folder, and now we begin setting up the Chinese interface of the software. 1. run the Exact Audio Copy V0.95, select the Simplified Chinese Save this file and another named for the new CUE file. 6F, , 2006-1-1 22:03 The -------- -------------------------------------------------- ---------------------- 6. begins to load the CUE file we just modified 1. run EAC software, the point on the left below that WRI icon,financial aid, or use the shortcut key the file . audition about the song if there are problems 7. start using EAC to Burn our CD CD the CD-R - 2. 3 increase in the start Burning, thus completing the Burning process. in a very small number of burners and EAC are not compatible will the Dials error can not be read, so we introduced an alternative to Burn CD Software: Nero Burning ROM software, I believe we more familiar with the Nero Burning ROM Enterprise Edition running after installation, open the CUE file saved in the revised,Hermes Handbags, it is recommended to install the 6.6.0.18 version, because some of the early version is not supported by default CUE file, the CUE type must be selected from the file type after can be elected, otherwise you can not see the CUE file, select the appropriate low speed after start Burning. PS: To facilitate research, even in the attachment APE plugin for Nero Burning ROM 1.0.0.37 English to this plugin after installation allows the NERO direct support for Burning APE files, but is not recommended research, only to be used with caution. Download 
 
[WORDPRESS HASHCASH] The poster sent us \'0 which is not a hashcash value. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:234352:86320894</id><idPostId>86320894</idPostId><idBlogId>234352</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:234352</id><idBlogId>234352</idBlogId><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog</link><displayName>Wanton Wordsmith</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/</link><displayName>The day he went away</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-01T16:56:15.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:234352:86320894:329353027</id><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/#IDComment329353027</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T16:56:15.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The day he went away by bj9fw5ft</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://hermeshandbags-sale.com/</link><idEmailMd5>d5822e0c2ffaaba5fe4f7fc4b792d912</idEmailMd5><displayName>bj9fw5ft</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://hermeshandbags-sale.com/"&gt;bj9fw5ft&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/"&gt;The day he went away&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>