<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/amfo1y/update/2007-07-31T21:08:00/ec9c5ba798f99d013676fd84a2e196346e3299e2a1e60de1a960748091f35f5b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>ADDvs NLD : WHEN I THOUGHT THAT I'D COVERED ALL CONDITIONS OF THE "MENTAL" KIND, UP POPS MORE! THIS JUST CONFIRMS WHAT I'D BEEN SAYING TO OTHERS ALL ALONG.  CHILDREN CARRY THE BURDEN OF HAVING A PIECE OF EACH DISORDER, AND THIS MAKES IT "EXTREMELY" DIFFICULT TO DIAGNOS AND TREAT IN A REASONABLE TIME FRAME.  IN THE MEANTIME, THE CHILDREN ARE BEING PUT ON THE "BACK BURNER"  AWAITING MUCH NEEDED MEDICATION UNTIL SOMEONE CAN DETERMINE WHERE THE SPINNING BOTTLE WILL STOP.  HOPEFULLY, IT WILL STOP ON THE ONE THAT SHOWS THE MOST SYMPTOMS THE CHILD IS DISPLAYING.  THIS IS WHERE MY DAUGHTER-IN-LAW IS WITH MY ALMOST SEVEN YEAR OLD GRANDCHILD.  MORE EVALUATIONS AND NEVER A DEFINITE DIAGNOSIS.  THIS IS THE PART THAT IS MOST ANNOYING, FRUSTRATING, AND REDICULOUS FOR THE MOST PART.  IF THE CHILD WAS "ALREADY" DIAGNOSED WITH ADHD, ANXIETY, AND SLEEPING DISORDER, WHY NOT PRESCRIBE SOMETHING FOR THESE SO THAT THE CHILD CAN HAVE "SOME STABILITY".  THE "SCRIPT" CAN  BE "FLIPPED" AT ANY GIVEN TIME TO OTHER FINDINGS. I'M NOT SAYING TO "OVER DOSE" THE CHILD, HOWEVER GIVING SOMETHING TO THE CHILD SO THAT HE OR SHE CAN BETTER "FUNCTION" WITHIN THEMSELVES, AS WELL AS IN SCHOOL AND AT HOME.  WHILE I AM OVER JOYED FOR THE "MEDICAL" WORLD AND ALL THE WONDERFUL THINGS THAT HAVE COME ABOUT BECAUSE OF IT, THE WORLD OF "MENTAL HEALTH" COULD USE A BETTER METHOD OF SPEEDING UP THE DIAGNOSIS PROCESS. GOD BLESS US ALL, AND I'M OUT!! </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/8dj3cq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/deo8</id></website><link>http://www.additudemag.com/adhd/article/1640.html</link><postedTime>2010-08-31T08:59:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2007-08-01T01:08:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/amfo1y</id><link>http://www.additudemag.com/adhd/article/1640.html#comment-73427049</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2010-08-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>