<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwwnf8/post/2012-03-31T12:43:33</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body> These  in France are a very good sign that the existing Government is finally waking up to the real dangers of Islam. These French people are such a fun loving, wine drinking, party all day type of people that they sometimes ignore warnings &amp; permit themselves quite the 
pestiferous situation a wee bit too late. I use the word “pestiferous” in the sense that Islam is a disease that spreads its insanity unless stifled by the Crusader mentality that must be prevalent as times of old. In old France, the Crusaders sent the Knight Templar to push back the heathen Muslims and were quite successful. Certainly, France need only look at the history of its own esoteric societies along these lines to recognize this movement. After all, any freethinker who has enjoyed several weeks in Paris knows how glorious the people are. Wonderful red wine, excellent culinary delights, midnight romances, and of course some of the most beautiful women on earth. Good for France to begin these Raids against those evil heathen before they are overrun by Jihad. As for the Crusaders, We told you an age ago that nothing good would ever come out of Mecca, and that the false prophet Mohammad would be lost in the dust of  Simoon. As for the merchants of the black grease that would finance world terrorism they will know the weight of Our displeasure, and let them know that the Holy Grail &amp; its Holy Water is both the Cup of the Holiness on High, and yet for the heathen these are the waters of death – the Cup of Abominations that Burnt the flesh of the demon Caliph who have set up their Thrones in the lands of iniquity. So shall it be as it was in the Middle Ages whereof the Lance of Knight Templar was dipped in pigs blood so shall We met your Jihad with the Power of the God Awakening within.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zwhjw</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/world/europe/france-arrests/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T08:02:33+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T16:43:33+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwwnf8</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/world/europe/france-arrests/index.html#comment-481983302</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/anf4i</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>