<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3b321/post/2012-03-29T14:55:34</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xin0</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/m2ax7</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Indeed.  It is easier to believe that somehow everything is going to be OK ... that we can eat ourselves sick and spend, spend, spend, have, have, have ... more and more and more.  For those who are just fine being very stupid, very fat and deluded into thinking they have a measure of happiness it is indeed much easier to buy the lies that are being spun by the likes of the Koch brothers who exploit quasi-historical (Cold war Era) propaganda of "rugged individualism"  combined with the wacky positive thought fundamentalism that also grips America.  Wall Street has an all too easy time of exploiting willfully, wantonly ignorant middle Americans who can't be bothered to open a book, or pay attention long enough to anything other than reality TV to figure things out for themselves.

Yet probably 50% of Americans really do mostly know what is going on, they just feel completely helpless against the likes of Wall Street, massive immortal corporations like Walmart, and the masses of fools who continually support them.  Then there is the probably 5% (as opposed to the 1% that gets bandied about) that are part of the corrupt financial system in one way or another (mostly just due to high income) ... that 5% makes up the ruling class.  

No matter how enlightened one is in America it seems that anything that is done, from rioting in the streets to hunger strikes to self immolation ... nothing ... ever gets listened to.  The ruling 5% does what it wants.  The only hope would be the stupid 45% collectively waking up somehow and voting independent of the wishes of the Koch brothers, the Wall Street Plutocrats and the ruling elite.  That hasn't happened since the early 20th century.  It likely won't ever happen again ... sadly I think humanity is doomed.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/m4qqba</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/h8a5</id></website><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/programmes/peopleandpower/2011/10/2011102683719370179.html</link><postedTime>2011-10-27T10:46:03+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:55:34+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3b321</id><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/programmes/peopleandpower/2011/10/2011102683719370179.html#comment-479759784</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/m91bw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-10-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>