<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39s3t/post/2012-03-29T18:00:42</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I just came across this site and this article in particular and although it says it was posted in 2009 i still wanted to add my thoughts. 

I myself wanted to be a "skinny" girl my whole life and through exercise and a very restrcitive calorie diet (1200 cal a day) i finally managed to get there. I went from approximately 60 kg (132 pounds) to 52 kg (114.4 pounds) in 6 months and at 156 cm (5 f 4") for the first time in my life i was fitting into an Aus size 6! I thought it was wonderful. Until..

a few months passed and maintaining this weight became increasingly more difficult. My metabolism had slowed and every time i had an occasional 'slip' and ate something i shouldn't have (well that wasn't tuna or celery) i would INSTANTLY put on weight. MY BODY HAD TURNED INTO A FAT STORING MACHINE! On top of that my hair started to fall out and i stopped getting my period (if that wasn't a big enough sign)

I reaslied that the whole irony of being 'skinny' is that your body is prone to actually store more FAT that if you were 'fit'. This realisation changed my focus.

Rather than being a fat storing machine i wanted to become a FAT BURNING MACHINE! So I decided..

I would now eat MORE and exercise MORE (still creating a deficit) rather than eating virtually nothing and being hungry all the time. By exercising more i would incorporate a lot more weights into my routine. With this new goal came acceptance of the fact that i may put on weight IN LEAN MUSCLE TISSUE, NOT FAT and decided that I would rather weight 55 kg's with a lower fat percentage than 52 kg's with a higher fat percentage. 

My new goal is now FAT loss not Weight loss. The tape measure not the scales. 6 pack abs, not hip bones and to look good in jeans but look even better naked ;)   

Cheers!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/8ime5v</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rcq8</id></website><link>http://www.bodyrock.tv/2009/10/07/being-fit-vs-being-skinny/</link><postedTime>2010-11-12T22:47:03+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:00:42+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39s3t</id><link>http://www.bodyrock.tv/2009/10/07/being-fit-vs-being-skinny/#comment-479946293</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2010-11-12</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>