<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi5waw/update/2012-03-22T15:45:54/2e661241afe54b4ba7edc1f35953cc65a6f0c076e37cfad589f6e73786fa34a4</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Dear Foster,
I honestly don't understand why you allow comments from the so called "debunkers" and other close-minded hypocrites on your blog. You are an intelligent person, I am sure you know they are undercover disinformation agents working for the government - and it's just a day at work for them. Do you really think that a sane person would spend so much effort putting together an entire blog (in such a short time!) about how Thrive is a scam?

The internet is something that they cannot control yet, therefore they cannot censor whoever they want. But they have big budgets and a lot of employees working to divide and conquer us.

Disinformation agents are "masters of ridicule", a feature prominent in their comments - therefore, it's easy to Spot them. By allowing their comments, you are actually disrupting the harmonic energy flow on your blog. By allowing their negativity, you are dimming positivity. Those reading your articles are mostly positive people with positive intentions, who come here looking for solutions for a better tomorrow. And instead of finding that wonderful community, they stumble across dark-driven puppets of the elites. They are only disrupting harmony in order to make your positive community disband and wander away from your project.

The main stream media channels and websites Always censored my comments because they have the power to widely open sleepy eyes and the coherence and evidence that I bring, to crumble their empire (built on blood and deception). So why are you allowing the "dark" agents to ridicule your work?

Those who don't like the Thrive community or ideas can simply move along, instead of creeping around to promote their websites that are bashing your work.

I hope you will take the right decision and filter the negative &amp; nonconstructive comments.

Love and Friendship,
Alexander</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/dunkqv</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/17xq</id></website><link>http://www.thrivemovement.com/FG-Kelly-Response.blog</link><postedTime>2012-01-02T00:50:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T19:45:54+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi5waw</id><link>http://www.thrivemovement.com/FG-Kelly-Response.blog#comment-473882470</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zd4bt</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-01-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>