<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkprff/update/2012-03-26T16:10:01/fdae4fd9ea0b705c9f11e3743e079d92843ce751e2709af5577aad19ae9cbe81</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>ATTENTION POSTERS!!!I will keep posting POSTERS!!  If you had half a brain you would let it pass as your just bringing it up to the top every time you flag it ya big babies!!!!I NEVER WROTE A REVIEW until i seen this movie. I cannot believe the praise and hype this awful movie is getting. I am sincerely blown away form critics like Peter Travis (Rolling Stone) and Roger Ebert. Even a Commentator on CNN raved about this movie. My only guess why is that.....they are so easily pleased, lost touch with good film making or perhaps been paid  in some way because this movie down right STINKS! Every thing was completely predictable. Nothing to the imagination and if anything fell way short of what you think should have happened. The love story was not moving whatsoever and that of a bad 80's  job. I would not even bother writing a review on this garbage if it were not for the people raving about it. People going to spend their money on this need to know the truth. I lost respect for every critic that gave this movie more than 2 stars out of 5. Go back to film school because you are way out of touch with good film. I am a white guy and i still can't believe that they kill Off the black people every time in these movies. if you watched this you know what i am talking about. If you did not yet and you do....you will laugh remembering what i just wrote. But the commercial world still has a nice variety.....1 asian, 1 white, 1 black, 1 hispanic. hahahaha. But the movie industry puts them in, but they are sure to be killed. Anyway the film sucks! In every category...Drama...sucked...Romance....Really sucked! Special Effects...sucked! Ending......I want to Vomit !!!!!! Every turn in the movie was a complete let down I know people are saying.."My the violence...maybe i should not take my kids" Well folks...The violence SUCKED!!! but don't let this be the reason not to take your kids. Don't take them because the WHOLE MOVIE SUCKS!!! And what the heck is Lenny kravitz doing in that film. Just a crappy film!!!!!!! Wait....there was one thing i enjoyed. The film was 2:20 min It felt like about 1 hr 45 min.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rq9em</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/25/showbiz/hunger-games-box-office/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-25T22:57:27+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T20:10:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkprff</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/25/showbiz/hunger-games-box-office/index.html#comment-476699533</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zrlde</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>