<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/midbj6/post/2012-03-22T19:25:09</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Coincidence?   In normal times, coincedences happen, and they also happen in extrordinary times like these.  How do you know if a thing is planned or random?  Random events are exactly that...without a pattern.  When a clear pattern can be derived from the facts, a plan may be responsible.  It's all about points-on-a-line.  Two points seldom hold significance...unless they are two points along a longer more or less straight line or repeating patterm of events.  

Time will tell.  The truth has a way of finding it's way out...at least until it is erased and buried below the victor's heel.

Proverbs 10:19
The more talk, the less truth;  the wise measure their words.

Proverbs 12:17
Truthful witness by a good person clears the air,  but liars lay down a smoke screen of deceit.Proverbs 14:25
Souls are saved by truthful witness  and betrayed by the spread of lies.Proverbs 16:13Good leaders cultivate honest speech;  they love advisors who tell them the truth.Caution should prevail.  We must not make the facts fit our "truth" but seek the truth from the facts.  We must be calm, and cool....steady.  We must do our duty, but not be incited to riot, for in that, we become that which we hate. Consider this warning...and admonishment2 Timothy 4:3-5  (AMP)3For the time is coming when [people] will not tolerate (endure) sound and wholesome instruction, but, having ears Itching [for something pleasing and gratifying], they will gather to themselves one teacher after another to a considerable number, chosen to satisfy their own liking and to foster the errors they hold,     4And will turn aside from hearing the truth and wander Off into myths and man-made fictions.     5As for you, be calm and cool and steady, accept and suffer unflinchingly every hardship, do the work of an evangelist, fully perform all the duties of your ministry.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6mr015</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/o2bq</id></website><link>http://patriotupdate.com/20035/was-andrew-breitbart-murdered</link><postedTime>2012-03-19T20:25:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T23:25:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/midbj6</id><link>http://patriotupdate.com/20035/was-andrew-breitbart-murdered#comment-474054454</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-19</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>