<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwc9dy/post/2012-03-30T05:10:46</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>"...for I am not the one setting the rule here.  The pre-requisites for qualification was set by the Buddha himself and not by me or this or that monk."

The Buddha did not set a rule regarding sexual orientation either. The question at the time of ordination is regarding one's gender ("purisosi?" or, "are you a man (or male gender)?", not of the objects of one's sexual desire. To assume sexual orientation is implied or automatically linked is a rather arbitrary bias. While the majority of men are indeed heterosexual, at the time of the Buddha, the majority of men were also Indian, so should that question also imply ethnicity? If so, you and I would both be out of luck :-)As for the specifics of sexual behaviours and their prohibitions in the Vinaya, ALL sexual behaviour is prohibited for bhikkhus. As we know, the rules were promulgated as offences occurred, not in anticipation of them happening. Therefore, it is probably safe to assume that one's sexual orientation was not a barrier to ordination, as the rules regarding homosexual  were only issued after the bhikkhu was ordained and he engaged in such activity, much like the heterosexual rules. Further, the language used for the various Acts is identical, suggesting that no matter what was done with whom or with what (monkeys and corpses - yeah, yuck!), it was unwholesome; there was no sliding scale of ickyness, as it were.

There was also one more comment that I found rather disconcerting: "The Bhante further reiterated that it will spell trouble if a gay ( who likes man) is admitted into the same sleeping quarters with other monks.". Trouble for whom? Is he suggesting that the gay monk is like an animal in Heat and unable to control his actions? Or for the fellow monks who are so full of themselves that they have an abnormal fear that said gay monk will molest him? He's not being very understanding and compassionate towards his fellow human beings.

One final thought Bhante: I recognise that you and I are following different traditions, and while our respective Canons are virtually identical, there may be some additions in yours* that address this issue (homosexuality in general). If you would please be so kind as to point out those passages, it would be greatly appreciated.

Although this is a rather old topic, I hope that Suling will still receive notifications on this continuing thread. It was important enough for him to ask, perhaps he might find some more food for thought.

*canonical, commentarial, etc.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/8kbo49</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/r7ji</id></website><link>http://buddhavacana.net/2010/10/17/can-a-gay-person-be-ordained-as-a-monknun/</link><postedTime>2010-11-17T05:29:18+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T09:10:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwc9dy</id><link>http://buddhavacana.net/2010/10/17/can-a-gay-person-be-ordained-as-a-monknun/#comment-480544137</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2010-11-17</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>