<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwf6r3/post/2012-03-31T01:03:10</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>So do your own laundry.  It isn't rocket science and the directions about how much detergent to use are printed on the bottle and if you have a washer and , you should also have the directions that came with them somewhere.  Read them.  There, that problem should be solved but if you can't find the directions anywhere, you could Always look up the brand on the internet and find directions there.  Many children, both boys and girls start to do their own laundry when they are anywhere from around 8 to 12 years of age.  They also are sometimes doing dishes by hand or learning to load the dishwasher around those same ages.  Again it's not rocket science.  Do you live in an apartment or a home with lawn to mow, a garden to tend, a garage to keep neat and clean, and an area that needs the snow shovelled?  In many households, the wife takes care of the thngs inside the house and the husband is in charge of everything outside, including all the other things I mentioned and also the siding and the porch and window and door frames and trim.  Since his wife is planning on retiring soon, I do understand her reluctance to give up her territory but if they live in an apartment, he is kind of reduced to no territory of his own so they do need to come to some kind of a more equal sharing of chores.  Wonder who controls the check book and writes the checks to pay the bills?  And who takes care of the appliances, puts new light bulbs in the overhead fixtures, takes care of the Heating and air conditioning equiptment, computers and other electronics and vehicles?  He may really be doing more chores than he thinks he is.  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67xiih</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/4lgx</id></website><link>http://www.arcamax.com/lifeadvice/anniesmailbox/s-1117287</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:35:59+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T05:03:10+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwf6r3</id><link>http://www.arcamax.com/lifeadvice/anniesmailbox/s-1117287#comment-481549965</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mn8ct</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>