<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mktfj8/update/2012-03-25T21:49:10/1d32c351a74daef51b63beb0d8e8ef4d1b3780c3f3ca6ba2e96b43d6a691768e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Okay so this is  topic, but I don't think Alex will mind. I just came out to my brother today in a completely unintentional slightly embarrassing way. Andrew  seemed homophobic and is one of the people who uses "gay" as a synonym for "stupid". Joining the Army seems to have increased that. I had been avoiding telling him that I like guys because we have a really strong bond and the thought of losing it terrified me. It still does.
Anyway, Andrew recently came back from Afghanistan on leave and we've been hanging out. He, his girlfriend, and I were going to see The Hunger Games today and Andrew forgot his jacket at their hotel. So Andrew and I were looking for one of my spare hoodies in my room. He found my porn stash. Andrew didn't actually see anything, thank God, because I caught him in time and told him not to go through it. It didn't take him long to figure out why I cared if he saw my porn or not.
He asked me if I was joking a few times (to be fair that is probably something I'd pull if I were straight. I like messing with him.). Then he asked how (I said I knew since I was about ten and it wasn't a choice). Then he said "no" a bunch of times, seemingly out of surprise; he didn't seem like he was angry or in denial anything. He seemed to still think it was all a joke. Then his expression turned serious.
I'm normally a very calm, rational person. I don't say anything without thinking it through first and I usually have a hundred thoughts in my head at once in any given moment. But in that moment my mind was completely blank. I realized that the entire future of my relationship with Andrew was based on how he handled this, on whether or not he could deal.
He took a deep breath and said that we were still brothers. I honestly felt like I shed a two hundred pound burden. Andrew asked if I ever kissed a guy and I said no (which is true, I've done other stuff but I kept quiet about that detail). He told me he didn't want to know if I did, which confused me because I already answered him but I realized he was probably confused himself. Andrew told me he might be able to talk to me about all this later, but not today. I thought it was just as well because his girlfriend was still waiting outside by the car. She was probably getting Cold.
So the three of us saw The Hunger Games and Andrew was still  like himself all night. We joked and talked and bonded like nothing was different. Things still feel natural between us and I think (tentatively) it's going to stay that way.
I'm posting this for a few reasons. Firstly, for support. I've never before been apart of an online community where the members are obviously pro LGBT. I mean, why else are we here, right? Second, I want others to know that coming out isn't Always a scary thing. If someone truly loves and cares about you, your sexuality isn't going to change that. You need to trust that person, even though it may be hard. Lastly, I'm curious about other coming out stories. Feel free to share if you want.

EDIT: I just realized that people may be curious about our ages. I'm 21 (I'll be 22 in May) and Andrew just turned 23.
PS: It might be worth noting that Andrew wasn't the first person, or even the first family member I came out to. That particular scarring memory is a story for another time.
PPS: Alex have you thought of making a forum? I know Artifice isn't the first comic you've done and you're doing the Young Protectors after this. I think this site could benefit from a place where things like this could be discussed.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66ul2n</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/772v</id></website><link>http://webcomics.yaoi911.com/archive/artifice-page-87/</link><postedTime>2012-03-24T07:02:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T01:49:10+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mktfj8</id><link>http://webcomics.yaoi911.com/archive/artifice-page-87/#comment-476157854</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lj4p4</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>