<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mimbdb/update/2012-03-22T18:11:13/264c96d197b37ed15dd518d5b1b9dd5337c4e57c9e5cca60a195044e5e41433a</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mieeya</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lzvps</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>A big "government socialist" who made real &amp; significant spending cuts and actually balanced the budget of a state teetering on bankruptcy.  Some how the Mitt-haters Always forget that part of his history.  

And as for Romneycare - the state's previous healthcare scheme was Bleeding money fast enough that it was going to fail in a year or two. Mitt worked with the state legislature - 85% Dems - and got a compromised bill passed that added significant free-market characteristics to a mandate that everyone had to buy insurance.  the plan was - and still is - very popular with MA voters, and without question saved the medical system of the state for 5 or 6 years that it wouldn't have had under the system they had in place.

Now it's clear that there were some flaws in the law, but sometimes you have to take some chances to avoid sure destruction.  Romneycare did just that.  It's not a perfect program, but it's not an embarrassment either.  Anyone who says otherwise doesn't understand the situation in which Romneycare was passed (medical system was falling apart), the political finesse with which it was crafted (The opposiition controlled 85% of the legislature!), or that it was wildly popular with the liberal denizens of Romney's state...</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ycr4q</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f047</id></website><link>http://thehill.com/opinion/columnists/ab-stoddard/217429-santorums-lost-message</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T22:30:03+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T22:11:13+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mimbdb</id><link>http://thehill.com/opinion/columnists/ab-stoddard/217429-santorums-lost-message#comment-474007126</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zmtpc</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>