<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwe6nn/update/2012-03-30T08:01:31/526b2c8c30849d098b8e6e5a3c48c0eeedc02d9f080c10ad4ae13b58efcff04c</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3x5z3</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zh700</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Yes, do picture that, YOU calling anyone wicked...Beck calls attention to things that are amiss and intelligent people research ANYWHERE and EVERYWHERE they can in the news, online, in the papers, with others in their community, by reading history, etc., not just following Beck, and they make their own decisions;  BECK doesn't DO the bad deeds and HE doesn't put words in Farrakan's mouth, those "wicked", "frothing at the mouth" people do what they do and they spew untruths and hate and do it publicly and THEY ALONE are responsible for what they say and do, not Beck !!!!  If they don't want anyone to critique them, then they should just shut up and stop making fools of themselves in the public eye.  These people are EXTREME.  Doesn't that raise a warning flag in your mind ?  It should.  Fanatics have influenced gullible people down through the ages (Hitler) who think they have nothing to lose and everything to Gain by following people like this.   People like this think they they are getting away with something because nowadays certain people in power seem to be going boldly and openly against the law/constitution and  getting away with it ...first you need to have at least some brainpower and moral strength to distinguish good from evil in order to protect yourself from it; apparently, you met evil at a young age and are sadly confused...when I read your comments, I see YOUR racism and bigotry, plain as day.  We don't belong in the caves, we earned what we have by hard work - most blue collar Americans didn't inherit, steal, kill for it or weasel our way into getting freebies from the government...we live, we pray, we learn, we love, we walk and talk and Bleed red, JUST LIKE YOU.   We just don't fall over and play deaf like you when some over the top fanatic SPEWS !!!!!!!!!!!  Say a prayer before you write any more comments, be quiet long enough to hear God talk to you in your heart, THEN maybe you'll make some sense !</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hvfef</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rb19</id></website><link>/2012/03/28/spooky-louis-farrakhan-audio-you-will-not-believe/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T15:44:58+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T12:01:31+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwe6nn</id><link>/2012/03/28/spooky-louis-farrakhan-audio-you-will-not-believe/#comment-480663812</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zrtkd</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>