<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nfos/update/2012-03-29T13:06:28/b0ac48b94229d7199ef9334b168f83326956e5beb4c69aeaac6604762fe7fc1b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I STARTED  EBAY TEN YEARS AGO. WHEN I FIRST STARTED IT WAS   HARD FOR A BUYER TO EVEN HAVE A VOICE. NOW   SELLERS ARE ACTUALLY CLOSED OUT OF EVERYTHING. IT REVOLVES TOTALLY AROUND THE BUYERS WANTS. I HAVE SPOKEN TO EBAY BUT THEIR EXCUSES IS THEY KEEP BUYERS HAPPY TO HELP ME GET MORE BUYERS?   HOW THE HECK CAN    DISCRIMINATING AGAINST SELLERS DO ANYTHING BUT  GIVE   BUYERS THE KNOWLEDGE THAT WE HAVE TO TAKE     ANYTHING THEY WANT TO THROW AT US.    THE   FEEDBACK IS  A SAMPLE OF THAT.   WHY  EBAY??   WHEN   HAD IT NOT BEEN FOR SELLERS THERE WOULD BE NO CUSTOMERS, NO EBAY. SO HOW CAN YOU ALLOW  THEM TO LEAVE NEGATIVE  AND   AS A SELLER I  CAN ONLY LEAVE A POSITIVE OR NOTHING.  YOU HAD COME A LONG WAY BABY, BUT IF YOU ARE NOT CAREFUL  WE ARE GOING TO ALL BE LOOKING FOR OTHER SELLING SOURCES. WHERE WE ARE TREATED AS EQUALS.    
I RECENTLY  SOLD A   525 DOLLAR  ON EBAY, GOT PAID THRU PAYPAL. GOT  RIPPED   BY THE BUYER AND  EBAY YOU DID NOTHING  BUT SAY OH WELL   YOU JUST LOST IT. I MEAN I SOLD   ON YOUR SITE, YOU STATE YOU PROTECT US    ,  BUT   I COULDNT EVEN LEAVE THIS LADY A NEGATIVE TO TELL OTHERS SHE WAS A SCAMMER.   WHERE HAS YOUR LOYALTY TO SELLERS GONE?
   ITS GOING TO BE LIKE THE DAM BROKE WHEN    WE START GETTING ALL THESE RETURNS.   SOMEBODY CAN BUY A NORTHFACE FROM ME    IN THE WINTER AND SEND IT BACK IN THE SUMMER FOR A FULL REFUND.    AINT GOING TO HAPPEN. I WILL JUST REFUSE TO ACCEPT ANY RETURNS.   THEN YOU CAN DEAL WITH  ALL THEIR COMPLAININGS.

THANKS, LITERALLY FOR NOTHING.
I PAY YOU TO SERVE ME, BUT YOU HAVE BECOME INCAPABLE OF DOING YOUR JOB. MAYBE ITS TIME SELLERS BAN TOGETHER AND ESTABLISH A NEW     SELLING SPOT. I WOULD  PROBABLY BE FIRST TO SIGN ON.  I LOVE EBAY  CUSTOMERS, I HAVE MET SOME GREAT PEOPLE BUT HONESTLY I HAVE COME TO HATE EBAY        . </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ljqqr</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/jyy8</id></website><link>http://www.theonlineseller.com/2012/03/27/upcoming-ebay-return-policy-change-causes-uproar/</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T17:33:41+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:06:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nfos</id><link>http://www.theonlineseller.com/2012/03/27/upcoming-ebay-return-policy-change-causes-uproar/#comment-479657120</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>