<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/117677/post/127289384/comment/324963852</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>&lt;i&gt;We must intensify our drone campaign throughout the &amp;ldquo;Af-Pak&amp;rdquo; theater&amp;mdash;and talk about it openly, too.  Predator drones work.  They have killed thousands of top-tier terrorists  &lt;/i&gt; 
 
Here is one of your biggest miscalculations. We are not fighting terrorists. We are fighting jihadists, as in stark contrast to terrorism, jihad is holy fighting in the cause of Allah against non-Muslim unbeliever to make Islam supreme and constitutes total warfare that employs both violent and non-violent means of jihad.  
 
Further, covert and deceptive non-violent jihad is employed by the Islamic world against the West and un-Islamic world astronomically far more prevalently and in fact constitutes an exponentially far greater threat to the peace, prosperity, and security of the West and un-Islamic world relative to violent jihad.  
 
In fact, the covert and deceptive non-violent jihadists that have hijacked, co-opted, and usurped our colleges and universities, our news medias, our political elites on both sides of the political aisles, and our federal government represent an astronomically far greater threat to America than all the violent jihadists in Pakistan, Afghanistan, and the entire Islamic world put together.  
 
Indeed, just one well placed covert and deceptive non-violent jihadists can wreck more damage than one hundred 9/11 violent jihad attacks. As a matter of fact, the 9/11 violent jihad attacks never would have ever been possible if not for covert and deceptive non-violent jihadists that plowed the ground and planted the seeds first for it to happen. 
 
Per the dictates of PC multiculturalism, you guys have for years been conflating what is really jihad, which constitutes total warfare that employs both violent and non-violent means of jihad, with being terrorism, which as its name implies can only be violent. Nevertheless, the threat emanating from covert and deceptive non-violent jihad, such as mass Muslim immigration to the West for the purpose of mass infiltration and stealth demographic conquest, that is completely ignored today thanks to PC multiculturalism, actually constitutes the primary threat today.  
 
Meanwhile, this enormous error in perception &amp;ndash; thanks to PC multiculturalism &amp;ndash; is analogous to the West completely ignoring the covert war the Soviets waged against the West during the Cold War. Had the West foolishly made that same stupid error during the Cold War, it would be one big gigantic communist gulag today, and if the West doesn&amp;#039;t soon wake up and realize the errors of its ways, it will find itself subjugated dhimmis to 7th century Islamic barbarians and entering a new Dark Age. 
 
&lt;i&gt;and have not hurt our popularity throughout the region (we are already unpopular).  &lt;/i&gt; 
 
Whatever happened to knowing your enemy as well as you know yourself? All Muslims are obligated to maintain nothing but enmity in their hearts for all non-Muslim unbelievers? How could they not hate our guts? 
 
&lt;i&gt;The drones have, however, undermined among the indigenous population the popularity of the Taliban.  &lt;/i&gt; 
 
I could care less about the Taliban. If not for the millions of covert and deceptive jihadists already living in America as a fifth column, the Taliban would not even be a threat today. Hell, the 9/11 violent jihad attacks would have been absolutely impossible as well. The writer obviously doesn&amp;#039;t get it because he is blinded to the hilt by PC multiculturalism, just like most Americans as well. 
 
&lt;i&gt;The conventional wisdom once suggested that the more we bombed, the more we would &amp;ldquo;inflame&amp;rdquo; hatred against us. &lt;/i&gt; 
 
Again, this is a measure of how much our political elites and federal government have been infiltrated by our enemy. Indeed, all Muslims are obligated to Always maintain nothing but hate in their hearts for non-Muslim unbelievers. Bombing them is hardly going to inflame what is already inflamed. Of course, if not for mass Muslim infiltration, our political elites and federal government would have already known this before they ever dropped the first bomb in Afghanistan.  
 
Indeed, because of PC multiculturalism you guys are all focusing on only a minor threat, the primary threat nevertheless emanates from the millions of covert and deceptive non-violent jihadists already living inside America as a fifth column and not from some violent jihadists many thousands of miles away that you guys stupidly conflate as being terrorists. You guys need to wake up and wipe away the PC multiculturalism from your eyes. 
 
&lt;i&gt;The terrorists&amp;rsquo; cause would be greatly damaged should our national leaders use similar tactics on a more consistent basis. &lt;/i&gt; 
 
I highly doubt the writer even knows the terrorist&amp;rsquo;s cause. Hell, he can&amp;#039;t even figure out that they are really violent jihadists and that they represents only a tiny minority of all jihadists in the world, as the vast overwhelming majority of jihadists in the world today are actually covert and deceptive non-violent jihadists, which he is completely oblivious of thanks to institutionalized PC multicultural blindness. 
 
--continued below </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:117677:127289384</id><idPostId>127289384</idPostId><idBlogId>117677</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:117677</id><idBlogId>117677</idBlogId><link>http://frontpagemag.com</link><displayName>&#13;
	Frontpage Magazine&#13;
</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://frontpagemag.com/2012/03/26/psychological-operations-and-the-afghanistan-withdrawal/</link><displayName>Psychological Operations and the Afghanistan Withdrawal</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:51:58.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:117677:127289384:324963852</id><link>http://frontpagemag.com/2012/03/26/psychological-operations-and-the-afghanistan-withdrawal/#IDComment324963852</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:51:58.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Psychological Operations and the Afghanistan Withdrawal by ObamaYoMoma</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://intensedebate.com/people/ObamaYoMoma</link><idEmailMd5>5436d5623d3abda11da234d69117a45a</idEmailMd5><displayName>ObamaYoMoma</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://intensedebate.com/people/ObamaYoMoma"&gt;ObamaYoMoma&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://frontpagemag.com/2012/03/26/psychological-operations-and-the-afghanistan-withdrawal/"&gt;Psychological Operations and the Afghanistan Withdrawal&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>