<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fn69/post/2012-03-29T16:55:31</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nk5j</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mmlmc</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>In 1857, the South successfully rewrote the tariff/tax laws overwhelmingly in the South's favor.  

'Filibusters'- the original term for Raiding parties- had been Burning towns in Ohio for a decade, as they had been doing in Central America and the Caribbean.  

SCOTUS Cheif Thale was determined to expand slavery west, north, and south. 

 Davis and co. were writing letters to Lincoln explaining their desire to create a new Spanish-style slave empire if the North would only leave them alone.

Lincon's father could no longer bear to watch the oppression of the 'law' on the side of monsters, and fled Kentucky.  Abe learned of Christian Abolition at his pappy's knee.

When apprised of the intent of the Empire of the South, Lincoln tried every compromise possible.  His number one job is to defend the Constitutional rights of all born on our soil.   The 1858 SCOTUS decision stripping those natural rights from children born here, unlike kidnappees from Africa, was the final straw.   

The Constitution was created to prevent illegal governments that crush the rights we are born with.  States do not have rights, they have powers that can be abused.  To defend the Constitution is to defend the individual.

The revolution occurred because the colonists refused to be the last British colony selling human beings.  That trade was to end in 1788, but the South and their New England relatives kept demanding extensions. Slave trade was made illegal in 1807.

The progressives today came from the Klan resurrection in 1894, 
when the propaganda campaign of "Lincoln didn't care about slaves, it was a tariff issue" was launched.  

The Democrats are revisionist plantation slave raiders today, as they were then.  

The children of the Confederates dreamed of recreating the lost Empire they had heard from grandad, because they were wathching Empires in real time- British, Russian, Spanish, Ottoman, Austro-Hungarian.  

The old allies of Boston and Raleigh evaded taxes and put their money into eugenics to justify the militant imperialism and illegal drafts for Democrat family 'unlimited corporations'.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zcqqy</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yv37</id></website><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/2012/03/m-the_republic_if_we_can_keep_it.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T06:13:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:55:31+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fn69</id><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/2012/03/m-the_republic_if_we_can_keep_it.html#comment-479883266</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hfexe</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>