<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwyhaz/post/2012-03-30T10:39:27</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Once upon a time, most people looked at the poor and said, "There but for the grace of God, go I."  I literally can remember hearing this on the street and on TV when I was a child.  The country made an effort to reduce the number of poor and suffering a matter of national policy.  Now, a significant minority look at the poor and say, "They must be bad people.  God is rewarding me (and I am, by definition, good) with more income and possessions (which the govt wants to take away) and punishing them by withholding His blessings."  Which of the following represent the Republican Party today as reflected in Cong. Ryan's budget?  "Blessed are..."the poor in spirit: for theirs is the kingdom of heaven. (5:3)they that mourn: for they shall be Comforted. (5:4)the meek: for they shall inherit the earth. (5:5)they which do hunger and Thirst after righteousness: for they shall be filled. (5:6)the merciful: for they shall obtain mercy. (5:7)the pure in heart: for they shall see God. (5:8)the peacemakers: for they shall be called the children of God. (5:9)they which are persecuted for righteousness' sake: for theirs is the kingdom of heaven. (5:10)
I don't think Jesus said that we should try to help the poor if it happens to be convenient, or only if it we can do it without any monetary sacrifice on our part.  I have a great deal of difficulty reconciling the economic policies of the Republican Party with the brand of Christianity their leaders so brazenly wear on their sleeves when talking about non-economic issues.  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/678hpj</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/egg0</id></website><link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2012/03/30/paul_ryan_irreplaceable_contribution_113672-comments.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T11:50:27+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T14:39:27+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwyhaz</id><link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2012/03/30/paul_ryan_irreplaceable_contribution_113672-comments.html#comment-480806978</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/86ggg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>