<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzc0s/post/2012-03-30T14:13:44</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kkg9</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hfaq6</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> Thanks Michael, it is pretty easy. You see, they want us all to believe that anyone who doubts 0bama is crazy, or racist, or some other excuse. When you look at their story though, it becomes clear that they have a lot of holes, and the holes are too big to fill with BS.
As a former Democrat and one who still has contacts with a lot of Democrats I get a view of their talking points. The things they can't explain they try to turn onto you.
When confronted with the fact that the hospital has no record of 0bama being there, they claim that nobody can know that, they come up with some kooky allegation about a privacy law. No privacy law exists that says you cannot confirm something that is known the world over.
0bama named the hospital on the document he claimed was "proof positive" he was born there. If he had actually been born there that hospital would be proud to tell the world they are the birthplace of a President.
Because he was not born there the document is a fraud and because that fraud was used for personal Gain it makes 0bama a crook.
In fact, any way you look at it, 0bama is a crook.
The fact that honest, hardworking Democrats are leaving the party just shows that they are not fooling many people. Some of the people who write nonsense here already know 0bama was not born where he said and is not who the Democrat Party built him up to be.
He was supposed to be so intelligent, but on his first day he creates an executive order to close Gitmo. The problem is he not smart enough to have a plan, and so the executive order is garbage, worthless space taken up on the White House website.
Now that the highly esteemed and experienced members of the Cold Case posse presented their findings the followers of the guy with more birth certificates than brains try to impugn the character of the posse. Their problem is there's no way they can do it.
For instance, they claim that only Corsi knows that the files are missing from the archive, but, they can't find anyone who says they are still there.
So they slam Corsi some more.
They only know one member of the posse, the spokesman, so they slam him as someone just looking to make a buck.
They are either too lazy or too inept to discover the history of the rest of the members of the posse.
So, take what they write with a grain of salt and then notice how silly their explanations are and laugh. I do. Their explanations are pure nonsense, comedy, jokes, and silly banter.
The posse didn't make up the problems with the selective service registration, the followers of the forger, fraud, and phony did.
There is no way to look at that document and say it is exactly like all of the other registrations.
It isn't
 It stands alone in stark contrast to the others. It is an obvious fake, as is the birth document created about a year ago.
They keep on digging their hole hoping that something will emerge, anything.
So, laugh at them as I do. They are riding a train that is going downhill fast.
When this discussion began four years ago they could get away with calling everyone a racist but now that more than half of American voters disbelieve the fairy tale birth story their attacks are meaningless, a joke, but they don't realize how many of us are laughing at them</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hw1k1</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f7e3</id></website><link>http://wp.wnd.com/2012/03/lord-monckton-convinced-of-obama-fraud-after-sheriff-joe-visit/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T01:04:51+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:13:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzc0s</id><link>http://wp.wnd.com/2012/03/lord-monckton-convinced-of-obama-fraud-after-sheriff-joe-visit/#comment-481028540</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8zpqd</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>