<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m1e6j6/update/2012-03-12T21:13:52/051e1ecbf242d8f0a6b7807c6aa25d6e821057b766099de04dcf2c6098e03aff</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m1g7hu</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/89oo9</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Pardon the length of this- all words are necessary to make you aware.  Most importantly, if you need an ICD it is because your heart goes into what is called "V-tac".  And you need that ICD NOW, not in a year.  V-tac is a scenario where your heart's electical system has a short circuit and is shocking the two lower chambers, or ventricals, before shocking the two upper chambers, which are called atrials.  Atrial fibrillation is uncomfortable, but not lethal 99% of the time.  And that might be what you have.  Ventricular fibrillation is what killed Tim Russert, the TV news personality of Sunday morning fame.  And it is most likely what kills most 16 or so year old athletes that are said to have died of heart failure on the football, or whatever, practice field.  

The heart has its own electrical plant.  It shocks the heart much like milking a cow- from top to bottom.  When it gets out of rhythm, and shocks the lower chambers, the ventricals, first, the resultant muscle contraction, which is supposed to make the heart "squeeze" the blood out into the body, much like milking a cow- and the ventricals have no blood to pump because the chambers are empty because the atrials did not supply the blood to the ventricals because the electrical shock went around the atrials and the blood is still sitting in the atrials- well, what the heart does when it realizes somehow that it hasn't done the job of pumping blood out into the body as it was designed to do, it tries to do so again.  Quickly.  In vain.  And there is still no blood there to pump, so it tries again.  Quicker.  This process will continue, in vain, until the heart Reaches a certain BPM(beats per minute).  And then, when it is nothing but a quivering muscle beating over 2-300 times a minute, it will figure out that it isn't going to ever get to do its job, so it simply quits.  This is called "Sudden Heart Death".  As in the case of a tropical storm's winds being up to 74 mph, and becomes a hurricane at 75 mph, such is the case with the heart and the related medical terms.

I don't recall the bpm level at which ventricular tachycardia (V-tac), which is latin- tachy meaning "fast" and cardia meaning "heart"- becomes ventricular fibrillation.  Fibrillation, if not corrected by an electrical shock, either external by the "paddles" seen in movies, or internal, by the wires that go down into your heart from your ICD, will kill you in less than one minute.  Literally.  There is no pain.  There is no discomfort.  There is only death.  There are no symptoms, save for what the docs call PVC's (Pre Ventricular Contractions), which you can literally feel in your chest.  Feels kinda like your heart "skips a beat", or kind of cavitates.  Any irregular heartbeat is called an arythmia.  That may be a term you have heard.  If not, you will.

The symptoms you will experience during V-tac will be a slight feeling of pressure on the head, much like placing your hands on either side of your head and gently squeezing.  Accompanied by a sense of total Disorientation- your brain isn't getting any oxygen.  And, unlike the movies, when your brain isn't getting oxygen, you will pass out in a few seconds, again, quite literally- not a few minutes, like in the movies.  No pain.  No nothing, save the Dizziness.  And, without help, you will become unconsciuos and most likely die.

The worst thing that can occur is that you pass out.  If that happens and there is no one around you to assess the situation and respond very quickly, you will die.  All state and all government buildings in Texas have portable defibrillators on their walls.  And these devices, even if used incorrectly, can save a life.  If nothing is done, after all, you will shortly have a corpse.

I am not a doctor.  I am a patient, just like you.  BUT, if the physician that you are seeing is not an "EPD", an ElectoPhysiology Doctor, then go to one.  EPD is a branch of cardiology that deals ONLY with the heart's electrical system.  You wouldn't hire a plumber to work on your electrical problem.  Don't use anything but an EPD to deal with issues in your heart's electrical system.

If your current doctor is offended by that- I'd say screw him.  That's up to you.  I'm giving you good advice.

My EPD is at Baylor Medical Center, in the Jack and Jane Something Heart Place building in downtown Dallas- Dr Assar.  He is a saint.  He's also a very fine doctor.  Tops in his field.

The telephone number is 214-841-2080.  Call them ASAP.  Do not wait another day, let alone another year.  These people at the Heart Place are on the leading edge of EP in the Metroplex.  They know who I am by name.  Tell them I told you to call.  They are awesome.

I do not mean to alarm you at all.  But you may not get but one chance to get this right.

BTW- "has it shocked me?"  Yes, 27 times.  Re- "how does it feel?"  Well, everyone wants to know that.

If you can imagine getting kicked in the chest by a mule... and then, 18 seconds later getting kicked again in the exact same place...and then, 18 seconds later...well, I think you might get the picture.  It hurts more than anything that has ever hurt you before.  I've been shot.  I've broken many bones.  Had fights.  Had heart bypass surgery.  Nothing comes anywhere close to hurting that bad.  But, it is literally saving your life when it does it, so I ain't complaining.  And mine hasn't shocked me in 4 years or so, and I've had it since 2003.

I wish I could drive to your house in the morning and load you up and take you to see my doctor.  It is that important to you.  Please call them.

I could never give you better advice.  If I'm wrong, then you went to a different doctor for an hour or so for nothing.  If I'm right, then you will get to see more of your grandchildren.  

Your choice.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ajr50</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnmw</id></website><link>http://www.star-telegram.com/2012/03/11/3801832/three-special-students-inspire.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-12T03:47:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-13T01:13:52+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m1e6j6</id><link>http://www.star-telegram.com/2012/03/11/3801832/three-special-students-inspire.html#comment-463867894</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ld1y3</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-12</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>