<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msas2w/post/2012-03-26T22:35:18</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I noticed the Miami Herald was one of the first newspapers to mention Trayvon Martin's suspension from school, but offered no explanation as to why, or how it was relevant in the story.   A week ago I sent a message to the author questioning her about whose decision it was to include that in the story, hers, her editor etc., and I got no response.

  In their most recent article we see the attempt to attack Martin's character coming full bore from conservatives and Republicans.

Multiple suspensions paint complicated portrait of Trayvon Martin

http://www.miamiherald.com/2012/03/26/2714778/thousands-expected-at-trayvon.html  

My response:

Now the Herald's conservative editorial board, as well as the average racist looking for any excuse to blame the victim, have their smoking gun, as it were.  Of course he was a bad kid, he's black/Black, and y'all know how them Black folks are. Every once in a while you gotta kill one, if they get too uppity, or  if they are foolish enough to wander into the wrong neighborhood. Some of them young ones, they don't know how to show proper respect for the white man, his natural superiority, his property.   Sends a message to the others,  only way to keep them folks in line, right?

 As someone who grew up in South Florida, I know the smell of this all too well,  just as I know how many of the people who run the Miami Herald think.  The fact that Zimmerman is of Hispanic descent makes all the difference in how the people calling the shots at the Herald spin this story.  I asked Ms. Robles in a tweet who edits her stories, I'm not surprised she didn't respond. Officially I'm sure it's her editor and the managing editors, but unofficially, well I imagine there are those upstairs keeping a close eye on every word in these stories. And I imagine they breathed a sigh of relief when these issues came to light.  Or maybe I'm wrong, maybe things have changed at the Herald, it is a new century, right?

Unfortunately I've seen stories like this play too many times, in the form of Hispanic police officers shooting unarmed black folks, and subsequently being cleared of any wrongdoing.  This Orlando incident is just the same old South Florida story with a new wrinkle, Now you don't even need a badge in Florida, now anybody (white or white Hispanic) with a gun, can kill black folks, as long as they take the time to portray their target as 'threatening'.  Say with a 911 call, a call in which you make a series of statements that set the scenario for you to appear to be the innocent neighborhood watch 'good guy' on the lookout or suspicious activity, who Spots an obvious criminal, the Always threatening image of black boy in a hoodie, who's obviously up to no good. 

Then it's open season, you can confront that boy in an aggressive accusatory manner, chase that boy, hell even assault that boy, yeah why not.  And if things don't go your way in the confrontation, if that black boy fights back,  if that black boystands his ground and defends himself,  if you start to get your ass beaten by that black boy, who you outweighed by 100 pounds, if you start to feel humiliated by that black boy, if that black boy makes you feel inferior as a man, inferior in your manhood, well you've still got the option of pulling your concealed semiautomatic pistol and smoking that black boy. You have  that option,   it is now your right,  granted to you under the law,  to shooting that black boy dead, with impunity.  

So what if that black boy was just defending himself, so what if he chose to stand his ground instead of running, it doesn't matter because that 17-year-old boy is dead.  He is no longer around to tell his side of the story.  It's your word (the word of a fine upstanding White Hispanic neighborhood watch, good guy) against the word of a dead (stolen jewelry holding, screwdriver carrying, graffiti writing,  pot smoking suspended from school, obvious troublemaker) Black boy. No jury in the land, or at least not in the land of white suburban Orlando, will ever convict you. So why not pull the trigger, pull the trigger and regained your manhood, pulled the trigger and prove your superiority, pull the trigger and show  all the rest whose boss,  pull the trigger and put em all back in their place, pulled the trigger and rid the world of just another one of 'these f--kin c--ns'?

 I wonder how many of the Heralds upper management keep a gun in their car or have a concealed weapon permit and keep a semi auto pistol on their person. No doubt they feel just a little bit more secure when they're walking down the street, perhaps they even feel emboldened, emboldened when they drive through Little Haiti, Southridge or Overtown. Perhaps they fantasize about what they will do the next time they feel threatened by one of those black boys they see standing on the corner. The ones that make them feel afraid, the ones that make them feel threatened. Now they know the laws on their side, and all they have to do is pick up their cell phone and create a scenario with the 911 operator that grants them virtual immunity from any action they take. Florida, it's a great state, for some. 

This is an old story in the South.



.Police: Zimmerman says Trayvon decked him with one blow then began hammering his head   

http://articles.orlandosentinel.com/2012-03-26/news/os-trayvon-martin-zimmerman-account-20120326_1_miami-schools-punch-unarmed-black-teenager

[With a single punch, Trayvon Martin decked the Neighborhood Watch volunteer who eventually shot and killed the unarmed 17-year-old, then Trayvon climbed on top of George Zimmerman and slammed his head into the sidewalk, leaving him bloody and battered, law-enforcement authorities told the Orlando Sentinel.That is the account Zimmerman gave police, and much of it has been corroborated by witnesses, authorities say. There have been no reports that a witness saw the initial punch Zimmerman told police about.]</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rnix0</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gyz4</id></website><link>http://www.bookerrising.net/2012/03/aaron-laramore-rep-allen-wests.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T00:28:21+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-27T02:35:18+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msas2w</id><link>http://www.bookerrising.net/2012/03/aaron-laramore-rep-allen-wests.html#comment-477099106</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/1bio</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>