<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwyx5j/update/2012-03-30T10:49:34/c5461c212231f4bc75fe7a8e54ab919052f347e96ff5ba8d4e536ebd9cf1feb7</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tb4k</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lv9zw</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>NO I'm not being sensitive. You have made passive aggressive statements before pertaining to this site and so the logical assumption for me is to assume that this comment was one of those things. We don't post every picture that comes out unless there is a story behind it that is relevant. We want to expose lies, not gossip about her shoes. And your tone is  this way even if you don't mean it to be. LOL. I don't think you are a stan and you are welcome to post here because you are civil and we don't exclude people for having a different opinion as long as it is respectful. This is a niche site for like minded people and we are very clear in that so we cater to them and their Comfort and safety. 

So in a way it's my duty to be cautious.And I will have to remove that comment of you calling someone a ho. That is not tolerated on this site. And I will have to ask you in the near future to please refrain from using those kinds of remarks on other members. Disagreements are okay and we know things can get Heated but that is not acceptable and I appreciate your apology.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lpedw</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zdek</id></website><link>http://destinysrehab.com/2012/03/raffles-van-excel-claims-he-cleaned-whitneys-suite/</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T18:49:02+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T14:49:34+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwyx5j</id><link>http://destinysrehab.com/2012/03/raffles-van-excel-claims-he-cleaned-whitneys-suite/#comment-480817467</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dkwgg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>