<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qdg1/post/2012-03-29T11:40:26</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>You can apply all sorts of arguments about who knows what because of their background, but, in theory, we are supposed to elect our politicians to apply their judgement, which we concede they possess in sufficient quality by voting for them. In practice, many voters vote for their team/party, because that's what they've  done and sod what's best for the rest of the country, so who should we have more problem with, irresponsible voters or out of touch politicians?

Cameron may not have shared the life experience of the average voter, but who has? Maybe they haven't had to have a "real" job in the "real" world, but how many senior politicians have? David Davis has, but he lost the leadership in a straight fight with Cameron and hasn't landed a blow of any substance ever since. So having a "real" job doesn't actually make a decisive difference.

If we approach this from the other direction, the party of the downtrodden masses is supposed to be the Labour party, but it was during their watch that the mess the out of touch Cameron and Osborne are addressing occurred. 

You can argue Labour undermined education, ruining not only the prospects for those who might wish to better their lives, but also the country as a whole. The proliferation of higher education may seem well-,meaning, but it is only productive if there is a use for that education upon graduation and there isn't. Perhaps they might have enhanced the prospects of employment elsewhere? Well they certainly enhanced the cost of employing anyone, not only by increasing the minimum wage, but by massively increasing the administrative cost of doing so. 

Never mind, at least they've made sure the ordinary working man will be comfortably-Off in retirement. Well, no they haven't, as a substantial portion of today's workf0rce do not have much in the way of a private pension, if any at all. The stock market hasn't made much progress for years and the tax advantage of pension investment was largely removed when increasing longevity and lower inflation suggested more incentives were required, not fewer.   

Still, at least provision was made for us to stay warm and dry in our own homes, wasn't it? Well, no, again the last government failed to make provision for replacing the obsolescent power plant in sufficient time for it to be online when the existing facilities are supposed to close.  If it's exactly windy enough in the right places at the right time, some of  the country may be able to turn on a lamp, but good luck running electric Heating all day when it's Cold.

Never mind, at least Ed Miliband buys his lunch in Greggs. Aye, right.

If you have to be out of touch, is it better never to have eaten a pasty or not to have the slightest clue how to run a country? Cameron and Osborne may not have much in common with Mondeo man, but if you think Miliband and his motley crew offer any greater insight because they are more grounded, I'd rather you didn't have a vote. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z63l9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ms5i</id></website><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/jamesdelingpole/100148065/what-pastygate-tells-us-about-camerons-conservatives/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T12:22:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:40:26+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qdg1</id><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/jamesdelingpole/100148065/what-pastygate-tells-us-about-camerons-conservatives/#comment-479587596</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a3a3z</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>