<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwovke/post/2012-03-31T05:49:54</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>My old housemate who moved from his hometown in Twente to Utrecht had the same complaints, that it was hard to make new friends, drinks with colleagues could only be made via an advance appointment in the calendar, and felt the general public to be Cold and unwelcoming.  Come most weekends, he went back on the train to his hometown.  I have only lived in Utrecht since emigrating, and found it very hard to make friends in my first two years, although once my language skills improved, and Gained a better knowledge of Dutch society and current affairs, I found the locals a lot more welcoming.  Still, I find when I travel into the countryside, the locals are far more friendly and welcoming (I was shocked at teenagers walking by, smiling and giving me a 'hoi!'), and as with my former housemate's experience, I see the coldness less as a Dutch problem, and more of an urban/rural divide.  I do experience some unforgivable rudeness and bad manners, people seemingly unaware of anybody but themselves, and the way some Dutch will jump to defend this behaviour (as 'directness' or 'honesty') leaves a bad taste in the mouth for anyone who sees that behaviour for what it is.   The situation is also not bettered by certain politicians who's careers are based on pitting natives against non-natives.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/e2n5tc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/qp0m</id></website><link>http://www.dutchdailynews.com/unfriendly-country-expats/</link><postedTime>2011-07-20T21:22:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T09:49:54+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwovke</id><link>http://www.dutchdailynews.com/unfriendly-country-expats/#comment-481698402</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-07-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>