<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwi1hk/update/2012-03-31T08:45:15/519363a1dffcc4aed2350ccadc05b476e1d5d3ca5431d8f9fb0c532401914ff8</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body> There doesn't have to be blood from either on them. He was released to go to jail by the paramedic on scene. There is a patient care report with a signed refusal of transportation (maybe treatment if he refused that as well but it doesn't sound like he did) to the ER that night. The medic looked at and evaluated (maybe treated) his injuries on the scene. There should be a very detailed report written by the paramedic who attended Zimmerman. This report should contain the medics observations of Zimmerman's behavior, his wounds, his words, and any treatment rendered. Any paramedic should have asked Zimmerman how he was injured. I hope the paramedic wrote a good report because he will see it again in court if it goes there. 

According to the police report CPR on Martin was in progress by them when the ambulance arrived. The paramedics had an obligation to continue CPR until ordered to stop by a physician.  That can be done by radio or phone. If Martin's injury was so severe that it was obvious he could not survive (decapitation, massive exsanguination, etc.) then efforts would cease. This may also be the case if Martin were shot through the heart. A lung shot may be treatable but again massive Bleeding and tissue damage (exit wound) can play a factor in the medic's determination.

Paramedics know to evaluate the scene when they are called. They knew they were going to a shooting. When the police got there Martin was on his stomach. The police turned him over to start CPR. Martin had a gunshot entrance wound to the chest according to all reports I have heard. I know nothing about an exit wound if there was one. That  on several factors including the type of gun (9 mm), distance of the shot, and type of ammunition Zimmerman was using. 

It would seem that due to Zimmerman's statements, the initial position of Martin's body, witnesses statements, and the screaming heard before Martin was shot that he was on top of Zimmerman beating him when the shot was fired. After the shot Martin collapsed on top of Zimmerman and he pushed Martin Off or moved from underneath him. 

So where is the blood on Zimmerman? It's not like the movies where blood sprays everywhere when someone is shot. Most of the time there is initially not a lot of blood from an entrance wound.

Who knows? My point is that these reports as well as forensics testing results have not been made public.

</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67fb69</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ju4p</id></website><link>http://www.breitbart.com/Breitbart-TV/2012/03/31/Higher-Definition-Zimmerman-Police-Video</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T08:54:53+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T12:45:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwi1hk</id><link>http://www.breitbart.com/Breitbart-TV/2012/03/31/Higher-Definition-Zimmerman-Police-Video#comment-481801459</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zg5xt</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>