<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m1gluw/update/2012-03-12T19:47:48/a634559f87ce589c3f53bf239d5e9e017f5ac20c855446c96b9140391bc070b6</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I actually know a bit about Kony and he is one nasty character.  He hijacked a legitimate uprising protesting abuses against an oppressed people in norther Uganda that was led by a Christian woman, and claimed the cause as his own.  Legitimate cause, but that's not what he was fighting for.  He simply fights for his own power and has committed far greater atrocities against these same oppressed people.  His group regularly kidnaps young girls walking home from school and forces them to be sex slaves, Burns villages and cannibalizes the villagers... and that's only the start of a very long list of offenses this man has committed.  The man has been cited as a terrorist and criminal by the U.N. and his actions have been condemned by virtually all countries.  There are some U.S. christian leaders who defended him, probably because they were mislead by his fake association with the original movement which is a legitimate christian led movement.  President Obama has sent military advisors to Uganda to help the Ugandan government deal with this man, and some people are simply against anything President Obama does - but the evidence that this man is pure evil and committing terrible Acts against a vulnerable population is very strong.  The only disgrace to humanity is Kony and Alex Jones is very mistaken on the facts if he defending this man.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/68c37f</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t8ad</id></website><link>http://www.gossipcop.com/alex-jones-angelina-jolie-war-crimes-video-kony-2012/</link><postedTime>2012-03-12T14:08:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-12T23:47:48+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m1gluw</id><link>http://www.gossipcop.com/alex-jones-angelina-jolie-war-crimes-video-kony-2012/#comment-463823710</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-12</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>