<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mskv4b/update/2012-03-28T11:51:08/6ecb36faa9b70df5f436b2de41e98d14d1e59b7ea1331a00a44629fd02558877</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body> I do not consider myself either a "denier" or "believer".  What bothers me about this non-debate is the behavior from both sides.  Yes, there are dirty tactics being used by industries at risk, but the "scientists" are no better.  They have gone to great lengths to  like there is no debate.  Born Hippie says below: "But EVERY piece of of credible data PROVES anthropogenic climactic changes"  In the article, Michael says: "Ironically, as these attacks have grown, the scientific facts have 
become ever clearer. Climate scientists know the world is warming and 
human activity -- particularly Burning coal and oil -- is the primary 
driver."  What I was taught about science was that there were laws that have been truly proven and there are theories.  Even the best and most accepted theory is still a theory open for debate until it is proven.  Where is the honest open debate WITHIN the scientific community?  How does Michael consider himself a scientist when he uses words to so go against the scientific method?  Maybe he and other climate scientists are right, but maybe they are not.  Is it too much to ask that they at least Act like scientists and say the truth?  The truth is that based on the evidence they currently have, the best theory right now is...</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hlxz3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/28/opinion/mann-climate-change-email-attacks/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T12:42:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T15:51:08+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mskv4b</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/28/opinion/mann-climate-change-email-attacks/index.html#comment-478478686</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zhmk9</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>