<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkbn6s/update/2012-03-26T09:15:11/b2ee563fb4c5939c72613e5b54187fda187e97ec9b7652f835cbaa01ccea1eaf</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>For the Sanford Police to say that they did not have probable cause to arrest George Zimmerman that is . Probable cause to arrest only requires that a crime be committed and that there be evidence that the accused committed. There is no question whatsoever that Trayvon Martin was shot in the chest and that he is dead. That shooting is either second degree murder or manslaughter; both of which is a crime, which satisfies the first element of probable cause. And there is also no question whatsoever that George Zimmerman is the one that shot Trayvon Martin in the CHEST, which led to Trayvon Martin's death and this satisifes the second element of probable cause to arrest. George Zimmerman should have been arrested and charged with either second degree murder or manslaughter, and if he believe he had any defense to the charge, then that is something that he would be able to raise at trial in his defense. 'Self-Defense' is an affirmative defense, and if Zimmerman believes that he shot Trayvon Martin in 'self-defense', then he is required to put-forth sufficient evidence to support the defense. The same holds true for anyone that is arrested on criminal charges. We hear all the time where people claim that they committed a crime because they were insane. We all know jurors are given instructions that tell them if you find from the evidence that the accussed committed the crime for which he/she is charged because of insanity, then you should find him/her not guilty by reason of insanity.
The same rationale should happen here. Zimmerman should had been arrested, charged with second degree murder or manslaughter, had bond hearing and a trial scheduled. At trial, the state would only be required to prove the elements of the offense. Once the state rests it is then up to Zimmerman to put forth enough evidence to prove to a juror beyond a reasonable doubt that his actions should be excused based on his purported self-defense claim.The State would have an opportunity to rebut his purported self-defense simply by offering any evidence that only raise 'reasonable doubt' that his actions were not self-defense. The self-defense argument is patently frivolous for several reasons. First, we all know that that Zimmerman made a 911 call and reported a 'suspicious' person; that he described the person as a 'black male' in his 'late teens', wearing a pair of jeans and a hoody. We also know that during the course of speaking with the 911 dispatch that Zimmerman stated that the 'suspicious person', who would later turn out to be Trayvon Martin, was walking in the rain and that he later started to run. We also know that Zimmerman started to pursue Trayvon Martin. And we also know that Zimmerman was asked by the 911 dispatch whether he following this 'suspicious' person and that Zimmerman replied, "yes". We also know that the 911 dispatch told Zimmerman, "Ok. WE DO NOT NEED YOU TO DO THAT". We also know that Zimmerman continued to pursue this so-called 'suspicious person'; we know that because Zimmerman, after saying, "These a&amp;&amp;holes. They Always get away." eventually catches upto Trayvon (in the dark on a rainy night) and that apparently an altercation ensues which later resulted in Trayvon's death. Zimmerman's own 911 call to dispatch washes his purported 'self-defense' claim out of the water. First, 'self-defense' is an affirmative defense used only in situations where someone brings about a threat upon you. It does not and has NEVER been used to shield someone from criminal liability where they are the aggressor or the initiator. In this case, Zimmerman was not on the initiator, but also, he was the aggressor because we know that he was armed with a gun and Trayvon Martin, the so-called 'suspicious' person, had only a bag of skittles, an ice-tea and a cell-phone. To accept Zimmerman's purported 'self-defense', the juror would have to believe that Zimmerman was the victim and that Trayvon Martin was the assailant. Under the facts discussed above, any person with common sense could understand that what we really have is a situation where someone has commited 'Cold-blooded' murder and is trying to escape responsibility for their own actions. Zimmerman chose to pursue Trayvon, who was at all times minding his business walking home from a convenience store, when Zimmerman chose to accoust Trayvon. There is no doubt that Trayvon is the victim and that Zimmerman was the assailant. These are all facts. They do not require a lot of contemplation to conclude that had George Zimmerman never pursued Trayvon Martin he would be alive this very day. That is an undisputed fact. It was Zimmerman's very own decision to pursue Trayvon Martin that led to this kid's untimely death. Zimmerman made an unwise decision to pursue Trayvon Martin for his own personal agenda after being told 'WE DO NOT NEED YOU TO DO THAT". It is almost irrelevant what happened after that point because he decided to place himself in whatever situation that ensued thereafter. Common sense: why would I pursue a 'suspicious' person that has his 'hands' in his pocket, or someone that is 'running'. Logic and common sense would have told any reasonable and prudent person not to pursue the person, and that is what George Zimmerman was told but he defied those instructions and chose to do so anyway. Anyone reading this should have a clearer understanding of the facts and the law as it apply here, and can discern that what Zimmerman is really trying to do is keep himself from being sent to prison for his own decision that he himself chose to make that resulted in the unnecessary killing of a 17-year old kid.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yohte</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ydw9</id></website><link>http://motherjones.com/node/168746</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T21:18:51+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T13:15:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkbn6s</id><link>http://motherjones.com/node/168746#comment-476384072</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hio19</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>