<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3b0ex/post/2012-03-29T14:58:12</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Review: Review: The Shins - Port of Morrow

	When I was reading Parasox's review of Port of Morrow while casually turning on the album through 
grooveshark, I immediately knew that the reviewer's experience was completely disjoint from my own callous disregard for the trash  spewed onto my eardrums.  I took issue with the contrived nature of the article, unlike the author, but pressed on with a morbid curiosity.  La vie ne commence même pas à decrire la nature de cet abomination - but  it provides clues as to how un-noteworthy authors can pen reviews like this.  The article is immediately alienating, lukewarm, and I'm pretty sure I'm the only person who bothered to read it all the way through, but somebody has to tread through the obfuscating language to understand the nature of this beast.

	It seems like every time JJG puts out an article (that is this one time), I'm completely disinterested in 
the opposite sex after a lengthy masturbation session.  You could say there was correlation involved, but I would point and laugh at you.  I remember not 10 minutes ago I finished reading this after jerking  to Gianna.  Even though it pains me to admit it, I received no gifts from the concept of wank fodder.  As I sat in a stupor of oxytocin and prolactin, I imagined the disillusioned references to the reviewer's personal life to be proper objective critique.  

	So, oddly, coming into this article I expected the word choice and subject matter to placate me.  In 
hindsight that was probably the lack of sex-rage colouring my cognitive ability.  Upon sobering, I recognized the hateful narcissistic involvement that it takes to liken the tone of an album to one's own sex life and watched my feelings of idolization pervert into a twisted landscape of hate.  I guess the author is two-faced, but "but 'Give 'me your hand, and let's jump out the window!' is a lot darker if you consider that earlier in the song he ruminated on the fact that he was completely unable to fly." is a really shallow observation and just sort of made me feel sad.

	What does this article read like?  I'm not sure there was actually any cohesion to any of this...thing, but 
I'll take a stab:  The first section seems to be a tribute to the death of Myspace circ. 2007 and the self-involved updates of millions of wangsty teenagers, but the second part seems to devolve into a random hodgepodge of references so impenetrable as to be reminiscent of Wikipedia's Citation article's citation section, including the belligerent nature of the editing and the sentences that never end even though they should but could you believe that he actually continues?

	This review, moreso than most, sounds like the product of about one night's work.  While it pretty much treads the small pond that spawned it and breaks less ice than the Titanic (He actually observes that time passes - I almost died of boredom.) there's still a shot that it's just the most brilliant satire ever written.  If that's true, then let me take this time to applaud; The Prince and good ol' Twain have nothing on this rotten bastard of literature.

	I've alluded to the thick bog of mediocrity that JJG delves into when the references start cropping up, but I was dumbfounded by the fact that he just now starts to talk about songs in the album being reviewed.  This is paragraph 6 and he uses throwaway lines like "insanely groovy" to describe songs that an artist spent time crafting. To cap  the insipid description we get the twin observations that one song uses less instruments than average and that another will last longer than some of the band's other songs(Those are fucking tautologies).  Then the paragraph ironically caps  with a criticism of the way the album ends.  Magnificent.

	The article discredits the writer out the gate and it's a shame because we get a line like "arresting immediacy" which was kind of well used. 

	Just kidding.  

	I wouldn't recommend Parasox to anyone without a large wad of cash on hand to force them to read "Review: The Shins - Port of Morrow" because I can't think of another way to convince anyone to invest time in it.  I'd satirize the rest of this paragraph but it would suck because JJG does that thing where his criticisms of the album apply perfectly to his article again.

	Part of the problem with the foundation of the article is that the author seems to be meta-analyzing 
constantly.  This isn't a review about an album; it's a review of a person listening to an album.  This exposes it to all the fallacy, rationalization, idiocy, and ignorance innate to a person.  So rather than the expected 
opinions, the reader is treated to a disquieting view of the author on an uncomfortable level.  The rot of man was never clearer.

	Penultimately, I'm bored.  The article has all the predictability of something damning itself by damning 
something else with Faint praise.  I make such a big deal about it because if I wanted to enact a drunk 
murder-suicide, this would be the eulogy.  There is no main event, no Act, no lines and no play.  The main character is dead and everyone looks on in apathy.  The article is a buzzword hipster trash generic gimmick awful bad horrific cunt-shit terrible wall of cocks fucking lovecraft.

	Ultimately, I'm going to take a piss, like JJG did with this article.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h8xzc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/o0ki</id></website><link>http://parasox.com/?p=9</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T03:42:09+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:58:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3b0ex</id><link>http://parasox.com/?p=9#comment-479762589</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>