<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3vor9/update/2012-03-29T09:06:04/46a1dd74e81bdf8b56073357898c0a7811109e19f4f1932b5fc3da98774de2a1</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Could it be that we have a man (Z) who was, at first, overzealous in his pursuit of a kid and then, because of his own stupidity didn't know how to peacefully Resolve a situation?  (reading my words, don't think I believe this was a simple case of letting things get out of control) Don't carry a gun Z unless you know how to use it to get another person to back down WITHOUT firing it.  Yes, sometimes that is impossible when the other person (no the case here) is carrying a weapon.  Again, not the case here.

And could we have a kid who doesn't know that he should have walked way or called the cops if he felt in danger or being harassed?  His possibly incorrect actions in no possible way in this universe should imply he deserved to be shot or was somehow complicit.

And could it be that nobody on this board, NOBODY, really has the whole picture?  Could it be that the prosecutors didn't charge him because they felt they couldn't get a conviction based upon the facts?  More likely, could it be that the investigation isn't over?  Think about it.  Many of you think this is a Cold blooded case of murder in the first degree.  Honestly it could have been.  But how many of you think that with some of the witnesses who have shown up and who didn't see the actual shot but back up parts of Z's story that it could be murder 1?  Would it be okay with you that he went on trial for murder 1 and then was acquitted because the prosecution couldn't prove that charge (a high hurdle)?  And then he would get away scot free?  Or do you think it would be better that after they fully investigate that he get, say, manslaughter?  Which would you prefer?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zcxr4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T06:16:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:06:04+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3vor9</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html#comment-479473766</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z5bts</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>