<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mggnsx/update/2012-02-07T10:22:41/a0270dc03f053ebfa2675700f5ea3dbc0d406cacbc8166ef6093d1077568c620</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mcpb53</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8cltl</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Spot on Andrewx, we are debt and tax slaves, the welfare dependants are an artificial construct used as an excuse to tax us more and more,  an ever-growing army of state-sponsored nannies to look after them. Similarly there is absolutely no political will to reduce "petty" (increasingly serious) crime, another way of forcing the financially prudent to Burn their disposable income (to repair direct damage as well as purchasing increasingly expensive insurance premiums) the government take a  of all the the action - recycling the individual's wealth back into their pocket. A country whose government spends nearly 50% of its gross product is not engaging in capitalism - this is a controlled economy.

The take of income tax will drop  as traditional workers are out-numbered by the proles, the taxation system will start to focus on consumption not income - it's the only was of "earning" money from the black economy. During the move from income to consumption taxation legitimate working people are being double taxed. Eventually when the country runs out of wealth creators and taxpayers we will be left with a third world country of desperately poor slaves (but all "equal" brothers!) with the political elite living like kings.

The foudations have been laid, Brown smashed the private pensions systems  poverty (and state dependence) for millions
 of prudent hard-workers. He purposefully broke the mechanism which controlled house prices which were allowing ordinary people to accumulate wealth - 
pricing houses out of the Reach of working people and leaving a whole generation with impossible debts.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ylczbn</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/politics/9061328/The-lessons-of-the-fall-of-communism-have-still-not-been-learnt.html</link><postedTime>2012-02-04T21:03:58+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-07T15:22:41+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mggnsx</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/politics/9061328/The-lessons-of-the-fall-of-communism-have-still-not-been-learnt.html#comment-431921685</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a3big</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-04</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>