<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mmgrnx/update/2012-02-10T09:36:13/9f356c896e795f19e48f198da66cf0e09e7fb67d42aee3929ccad67a262f142c</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/meu5ad</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rcudb</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Alright, you've mentioned the Buffy S8 comics. I apologize, but I need to vent now in order to get this out of my system: 

&lt;i&gt;JOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSS!!!&lt;/i&gt;

Okay, much better now. Anyways, yeah, they are goddamn &lt;i&gt;awful.&lt;/i&gt; They are an atrocity against 7 years of lovingly meticulous character development, and I still cannot believe Joss actually let them happen on his watch. We lose intricate, small-scale storylines in favor of ROBOTS! ACTION SLAYERS! SECRET INTERNATIONAL MILITARY BASES! LESBIAN SNAKE MONSTERS! EXPLOSIONS! 

&lt;i&gt;Yuck.&lt;/i&gt;

The ending of S8 alone makes so little sense that...well, you'll see.

I'd strongly advise dropping them like hotcakes and Burning your copies to dispel the bad spirits before it gets further cemented in your mind as "canon", but that's just me.

In my mind, and, I suspect, the minds of many other Buffy fans, S8 is &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; canon; it's a bad dream. I honestly would rather S8-9 had never happened, and Buffy ended with the group in front of the school bus staring at the horizon, than have these abominations thrust upon us. Buffy already had a good ending; it didn't need to be sullied by terrible fanfiction storylines.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ddu6z2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/regional-holiday-music,66270/</link><postedTime>2011-12-09T01:30:33+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-10T14:36:13+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mmgrnx</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/regional-holiday-music,66270/#comment-435268821</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zrhe7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-12-09</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>