<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fgev/update/2012-03-29T16:35:54/7a77753bc1110d20225361619cb1d133d9b48bcad815c7090bb052148f8dd460</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Professor lynch - a word of advice - having a PhD in political science or international relations does not make you qualified to write on all subjects international.  You still have to KNOW about what you are writing about before you put ink to paper or in this case finger to keyboard.



 "They have a
hypersensitivity to double standards, particularly on the Palestinian issue.
Why do all peoples have the right to democracy except Palestinians, they ask,
and why is there a responsibility to protect Libyans but not Gazans?"

Do you really expect us to believe this?  The Arabs have a hypersensitivity to a double standard on the Palestinian issue?  In 1970-1, a one year period, the Jordanian Army killed anywhere from 15,000–20,000 Palestinians in the Black September uprising.  In contrast 4,900 Palestinians were killed in the Second intifada in a NINE YEAR period of time.  In 1991, Kuwait expelled about 450,000 Palestinians from its country.  Today only 40,000 Palestinians are back in Kuwait, less than 3%.    And, in Lebanon, Egypt, and Syria Palestinians are denied rights to hold certain jobs, leave their refugee camps, and attain many rights granted to citizens and even other permanent residents.  The only double standard is that the Arabs expect others (read: Jews, the West) to treat their "Arab brothers" better than they do.  Or there is the double standard that they can kill whomever they want (i.e. Sudanese Arabs killing and displacing black Sudanese) while others cannot even engage in legitimate warfare.  

And...why do people have a right to democracy except the Palestinians?  They Palestinians DID have democracy.  They had elections in 2006, and then refused to hold elections ever since.  Hamas refused to have elections in Gaza, and Fatah would not agree to hold elections in 2010 after it could not agree on a candidate list.  So, if the Arabs want to know why there are no democratic elections with the Palestinians, maybe they should do their research, instead of instinctively blaming Israel and the West.



"The unification of Arab political space and the crystallization of
a new Arab collective narrative has ratcheted up the already real
interconnections among issues in the region. "

----Please.  The Arab political space is no more unified than it was 30 years ago.  Notice the Sunni interests lining up with each other and the Shiite interests lining up with each other.  In the past you had pro-soviet and pro-west arab countries. And, within the Arab countries "unification" is a fantasy.  Lebanon, Syria, Egypt (copts, secular, sunni, salafi), and Iraq, are all countries riddled with sectarian divides that spill into violence. 


"Israel, for its part, is right to worry about the Arab
uprisings. Its policies over the last decade, from the endless neglect of the
peace process to its wars against Lebanon and Gaza, have left it more isolated
than ever in the region, and its leaders have long since abandoned even the
effort to engage Arab publics. The dictators with which it cultivated strong
relations over the last decade are on the run, while the publics it alienated
are ascendant."

-----What kind of ill-thought out nonsense is this?  Israel has "neglected" the peace process as much as the Palestinians have.  Pali-leaks shows that Olmert made real offers to Abbas, who refused to negotiate or make counter offers.  

"The dictators with which it (Israel) cultivated strong relations...are on the run."  "Dictators"? I think you mean "Dictator," ie. Hosni Mubarak.  Other than that Israel had "strong relations" only with one other, King Abdullah of Jordan.  And, King Abdullah is not under significant domestic pressure.  In fact, wikileaks has shown the opposite to be true...that Israel has more friends in the Arab world than originally thought.  Israel has cooperated clandestinely with Saudi Arabi and the Sunni Gulf States regarding Iran and their shared fear of Iranian ascendency.  


"Put bluntly, it has never been more important
to America that Israel solve its Palestine problem, but it has never been less
likely that Israel will be able or willing to do so. The old dodges and
workarounds simply will not work anymore."

-----As if the entire blame for the failure of the peace process is on Israel.  Never mind the fact that the Palestinians are in a sometimes Cold, sometimes hot war with each other (Ala Hamas v Fatah). Should Israel negotiate peace with Hamas? Fatah?  Who is the single entity representing the Palestinians of which to negotiate with?   Is the fact that the Palestinians can't even unite and stop persecuting each others' political factions an "old dodge and work around"?  If it is "less likely" that Israel will be able to negotiate peace, a large reason for that is the Palestinians' inability to get their  together.  So , please, give us all a break.


"It is better for an independent Iraq to find its own
path than for the U.S. to vainly continue to police its streets"

----Not sure you noticed, but we are out of Iraq.  US troops are not policing its' streets.



 "We should
embrace a region moving at last toward what its people Always knew it could be."
----What?  You have no idea wit it's going to be yet.  And neither do they.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z6cyd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/eyjq</id></website><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2012/03/why-the-arab-uprisings-will-force-the-us-to-rethink-israel-palestine/255194/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T11:37:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:35:54+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fgev</id><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2012/03/why-the-arab-uprisings-will-force-the-us-to-rethink-israel-palestine/255194/#comment-479863672</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zgx5y</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>