<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkfld8/update/2012-03-26T12:27:23/1b7a08ba15bdb77db6994d0c9401ba848230e4d52e7e3d912e8de5a0be380a92</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>First, the site launched on Feb 29th, as shown here: 
http://blog.plug.dj/2012/02/join-party-plug.html , if you're going to 
make claims, at least get your facts straight. Second, plug.dj is still 
in beta, and as I recall, Turntable.fm didn't integrate email 
verification until fairly recently. I recently talked with one of the 
site's creators, Steven Sacks, and he openly expressed that email 
verification is in the works. Third, in regards to using YouTube and 
SoundCloud for means of playing music, this was only integrated as a 
means to enhance the music experience. As stated later in the article, 
we managed to stream Ultra Music Festival the entire weekend. It also 
allows a chance for artists to actually SHOW everyone what they are 
capable of, not just playing a mix and letting the audio play. If you've
 ever attended any sort of music event, it's more than just playing 
music, it's about putting on a show and feeling the ebb and flow of the 
crowd. Plug.dj allows you to showcase just how an new artist does that. 
Fourth, the "minor" differences you state between plug.dj and 
Turntable.fm do actually bear some weight. Sure, the WOOT/MEH buttons vs
 Awesome/Lame may be something that can be overlooked, however, with how
 the DJ stands and crowd is set up is not a minor difference. 
Turntable.fm 's setup has it set up so that everyone is clumped together
 in one small basement with 5 djs staring at you from a platform. 
plud.dj 's setup gives you the sense that you are actually giving the 
listeners a show with ONE dj on the decks, while the other 4 wait in a 
line to the side. If you actually paid attention to how the crowd works 
as well, you would understand better. Your avatar is Always front and 
center in the crowd, with your friends and fans close by, while everyone
 else that you don't know are put farther back in the room. It lets you 
be closer to your friends in a slightly more physical manner than 
Turntable.fm , which just randomly throws you in a Spot on the floor. 
Fifth, your claim that the largest rooms only had 7 seven people at most
 shows you obviously did not test the site out well enough. Over the 
past month, I have seen multiple rooms bring in 35+ people to one room; 
and during the livestream we showcased for Ultra Music Festival, he 
managed over 50 users in one room (and they were all active, unlike the 
majority of Turntable.fm rooms where the majority of users are AFK for 
days on end). Don't get me wrong, Turntable.fm was a pioneer in this 
sort of online experience, I used it for over a year religiously. But 
once I saw what plug.dj was capable of (like international streaming and
 doing more than just playing music), I realized its potential was far 
greater than anything Turntable.fm could've hoped for in its current 
state.


</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rwuse</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lcj2</id></website><link>http://evolver.fm/2012/03/26/plug-dj-adds-video-to-the-turntable-fm-concept-but-will-anybody-care/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T15:16:06+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T16:27:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkfld8</id><link>http://evolver.fm/2012/03/26/plug-dj-adds-video-to-the-turntable-fm-concept-but-will-anybody-care/#comment-476513570</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>