<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/momtr3/update/2012-03-20T18:09:58/f9a5c79d979b8042cba9748b135ab9f493f3feef5d319c58e405f7f19164c0b8</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>It's very clear to me that Trayvon was WWBlack in a gated community (that he was invited into) and went out to get some Skittles at a nearby convenience store. Upon returning, the community watchdog, Zimmerman, Spots Martin and instantly assumes he's up to no good. Apparently, if you're black, you CANNOT look at houses, other people or anything accept maybe straight down at the sidewalk, while walking, unless a non-black person tells you it's ok. Zimmerman starts following him and calls police-
GEORGE ZIMMERMAN, Florida: There's a real suspicious guy. This guy looks like he's up to no good or he's on drugs or something.
RAY SUAREZ: Then he pursues the youth, ignoring a dispatcher's warning.
GEORGE ZIMMERMAN: They Always get away.
911 OPERATOR: Are you following him?
GEORGE ZIMMERMAN: Yes.
911 OPERATOR: Okay. We don't need you to do that. I'm sure that a "Stand your Ground" law doesn't mean "chase the black guy" but Zimmerman thinks it does. How is this NOT a racially influenced interpretation of what a "crime figure" is?I've read the rantings of the racist apologist "Flooobs" or "Flop" or "Flash (in the pan)" or whatever on this thread and I outright dismiss him as purely bankrupt individual that MUST make his outburst on a progressive thread because he cannot deal with the fact that this murder was soooo blatantly racist and wrong. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6da5xo</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ant8</id></website><link>http://www.alternet.org/newsandviews/article/864957/trayvon_martin_case_goes_to_grand_jury%2C_fbi_as_devastating_final_phone_call_with_girlfriend_is_revealed/comments/</link><postedTime>2012-03-20T17:25:14+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-20T22:09:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/momtr3</id><link>http://www.alternet.org/newsandviews/article/864957/trayvon_martin_case_goes_to_grand_jury%2C_fbi_as_devastating_final_phone_call_with_girlfriend_is_revealed/comments/#comment-470641533</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l5sdw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>