<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/319679/post/127756041/comment/327453192</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Touhou had no games fanwise or not for a good few years. I don&amp;#039;t think anyone here ever even thought of Touhou when they got into Ponies, I  said it was the Western Equivalent to Touhou in that the unexpected surge of fans it&amp;#039;s sprouted from unlikely source. 
 
ZUN is a huge xenophobe and hated with a passion that his stuff was being leaked outside, his first law was to keep the game series and fanworks STRICTLY within the circle groups! he has/had a huge monopoly on how things got distributed by threatening to not release new games in the series. 
 
He also doesn&amp;#039;t want people to forget his games, it&amp;#039;s his characters from a shooter and doesn&amp;#039;t want any animations to make people especially foreigners that he sees as people who can&amp;#039;t handle his games and will only complain about the difficulties. Which is funny if you ask me because Japanese are usually the first to bitch about a game being too hard :P 
 
 
He killed Off a great fan-made mini series which we&amp;#039;ll likely never get a part two for. And god forbid we could of been graced with a Movie quality showing of Touhou girls in the modern world reeking havoc in all their unbound unrestricted powers. ZUN is just the perfect example of companies trying too hard to control their IP and stop fans from over-shadowing their own works. 
It&amp;#039;s one of the reasons I began to hate the fandom, aside from the growing ceepiness that was spreading like wildfire in the western fandom. 
 
But I digress, Touhou is Touhou and while a few fangames, lots of which I played, are nice only a few are actually worth mentioning as GOLD and the western fanbase of touhou hasn&amp;#039;t relaly created anything noteworthy I see outside of a crazy cross over TouhouxPonies DDR game. 
 
We&amp;#039;re not trying to compete in these two fandoms, and no reason one can&amp;#039;t love both (I still love reading new comics from the conventions when they get released on my favorite site) and while I like to keep the two separate I ain&amp;#039;t ZUN and don&amp;#039;t care if crossovers happen, at least so far they have been fun. Perhaps my experience with the bad side of the fandom left a bad lasting impression but whatever. 
 
 
I personally don&amp;#039;t find Touhou as fun as it used to be, even the canon games have lost it&amp;#039;s luster. The constant silly xenophobic laws ZUN keeps passing to hinder creativity reminds me of how the US government and Religion works to stifle economic growth and progression. Yeah I still see ZUN as a power hungry selfish Cry baby afraid his works will be over shadowed and have more ignorant foreigners consider animations as canon and forget the origins some how. 
 
I&amp;#039;ll cut this rant here and just say Ponies &amp;gt; Touhou for me. The fandom at least so far is much more friendly and it&amp;#039;s the first AMERICAN fandom that has a sense of community and openness than what I could possibly describe at the moment. We come from all walks of life and I&amp;#039;m proud to know the western community is better than I ever gave it credit for. 
 
 
Brony community will only grow as the more they open up and communicate with each other on projects. Long as we can keep the crazy ZUNs from sneaking into such projects and trying to man handle how things can be shared I think we&amp;#039;re pretty much set to go. Games will only come out as fast as the lives of each individual will allow, we&amp;#039;re not japan where most fanworks are creative by shut-ins. No offense, and not really MOST per say but some really amazing stuff like Touhou Apple was :P </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:319679:127756041</id><idPostId>127756041</idPostId><idBlogId>319679</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:319679</id><idBlogId>319679</idBlogId><link>http://www.equestriadaily.com</link><displayName>http://www.equestriadaily.com/</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.equestriadaily.com/2012/03/friendship-is-magic-from-japanese_29.html</link><displayName>Friendship is Magic from the Japanese Perspective Part 2</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:06:56.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:319679:127756041:327453192</id><inReplyTo><link>http://www.equestriadaily.com/2012/03/friendship-is-magic-from-japanese_29.html#IDComment327315937</link></inReplyTo><link>http://www.equestriadaily.com/2012/03/friendship-is-magic-from-japanese_29.html#IDComment327453192</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:06:56.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Friendship is Magic from the Japanese Perspective Part 2 by Telaros</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://intensedebate.com/people/Telaros</link><idEmailMd5>20e510167762759ab6f6c4f9c869c9ae</idEmailMd5><displayName>Telaros</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://intensedebate.com/people/Telaros"&gt;Telaros&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.equestriadaily.com/2012/03/friendship-is-magic-from-japanese_29.html"&gt;Friendship is Magic from the Japanese Perspective Part 2&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>