<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3p1t8/post/2012-03-29T20:37:36</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The Auschwitz 'Gas Chamber' Illusion

By Nicholas Kollerstrom, PhD


5-8-8


 








As surprising as it may sound, the only intentional mass 
extermination program in the concentration camps of WW2 was targeted at Germans. 
From April, 1945 five million Germans were rounded up after surrendering, and 
deliberately starved until well over one million had died, in French and 
American-run concentration camps[1] - an event soon erased from the history 
books. There was, in contrast, never a centrally-coordinated Nazi program of 
exterminating Jews in Germany. Lethal gas chambers did not function in German 
labour-camps, that's just an illusion. The traditional Holocaust story has 
developed out of rumours, misunderstandings, and wartime propaganda. From 
stories pre-dating the Second World War to the Nuremberg Trials which gave 
official sanction to the notion, to subsequent trials, books and films, we have 
had it imprinted on our collective psyche. In most of Europe now, it is a 
thoughtcrime to believe what you have just read, punishable by imprisonment, so 
think carefully before deciding to read on.  
  
The real experts on this subject are - in jail, so maybe you 
will put up with hearing my view instead? Europe needs, more than anything else, 
a truth and reconciliation forum to get to the bottom of these matters, and to 
try and exorcise the demonic hate-images. Ever more nations are passing laws 
that prohibit citizens from expressing doubt - Germany, France, Austria, Poland, 
Romania, Belgium, Switzerland, Canada, Australia and New Zealand. Collectively, 
we need to work trough our despair, rage, and ideas of blame, to try and access 
the real historical record.  
  
Cyanide at Auschwitz  
  
Zyklon-B was used at Auschwitz, as an insecticide. It was 
vital in attempting to maintain hygiene that mattresses be deloused. Cyanide gas 
was adsorbed onto clay-type granules, designed to make the deadly gas as 'safe' 
as it could be. If you go to Auschwitz today, you can't see any authentic gas 
chambers. You see stone huts, and experts have testified that they could not 
have been used to gas people, owing to problems in sealing them up (Zyklon-B 
released its cyanide gas rather slowly[2]).  
  
In 1988 the scientific team of Fred Leuchter (a US 
execution-expert 'Mr Death' in gas-chamber technology) visited Poland, and 
concluded that the Auschwitz 'gas chambers' could not possibly have functioned 
in the alleged manner - i.e., they were not gas chambers[3]. In the following 
years, others would confirm the accuracy of his seminal, 'Leuchter Report'. The 
German chemist Germar Rudolf, who worked at the Max Plank institute for Solid 
State Physics, is now in jail, because he likewise measured the high levels of 
the cyanide in the walls of the de-lousing chambers. It happens that this gas 
bonds permanently with iron, and iron is present in all the cement etc of stone 
walls. Whereas, he found none in the walls of what were supposed to be the 'gas 
chambers' which were mainly shower units. He thereby confirmed the work of 
Leuchter who likewise only found remains of the cyanide gas-insecticide in the 
delousing chambers.[4]  
  
After Rudolf's report was published in 1993, he lost his job 
and was prevented from completing his doctorate, then a few years later he was 
given a jail sentence. He is now in a high-security prison near Stuttgart, for 
the crime of not finding cyanide in the 'gas chambers[5],' echoing Leuchter's 
cyanide residue investigations. [6] When a chemist is put in jail, for 
replicating the result of another - in Germany of all places, the nation which 
invented chemical procedure ­ then the farce cannot continue for much longer[7] 
(The gas chambers were conveniently located east of Germany behind the Iron 
Curtain to make them inaccessible to westerners, which helped the myth to 
flourish).  
  
The Leuchter results were almost too good to be true, with a 
three orders of magnitude difference between the cyanide levels in the delousing 
chamber walls (about one part per thousand) and those in the washing chambers 
(aka 'gas chambers'), around one part per million. They are not published in any 
peer-reviewed chemistry journal, for obvious reasons. The only way to hold a 
debate on this subject appears to be in a courtroom, while being prosecuted! It 
is hard to  the calm condition necessary for replication of chemical 
measurements. Nonetheless people have replicated the fundamental result[8], and 
even folk with no interest in chemistry can appreciate the pretty blue colour on 
the outside of the de-lousing chamber (where the Ferro cyanide has seeped right 
through the wall) and its complete absence around the so-called 'gas chambers.' 
Let's face it, the case is established: the cyanide poison was used where the 
German records state that it was used ­ for delousing mattresses, clothing etc - 
whereas it was not used where the US and UK (at Nuremberg) alleged.  
  
Tourists, thirty million of them, have filed through 'Krema 1' 
at Auschwitz, with its piteous piles of shoes, etc of the dead. This was 
reconstructed after the war in 1946[9], a fact revealed 1992 by Dr. Franciszek 
Piper, the Senior Curator and Director of Archives of the Auschwitz State 
Museum. The historic remains from the camp are such things as shower-unit huts, 
a swimming pool and a morgue. There was a camp orchestra, and quite a collection 
of pictures from the camp art-classes,[10] although these cannot be shown in 
Germany or Poland, on account of laws prohibiting the doubting of the Holocaust. 
Anne Frank of 'Diary' fame came to the camp in 1944 with her father who was ill. 
He was put into the hospital there, and recovered, suggesting that he was 
decently looked after.[11]  
  
The 'gas chambers' at Auschwitz had water pipes in their 
ceilings, indicating that they were designed as shower units. They generally 
lacked tight-seal doors, which would have been essential, even though these were 
easy to install ­ the Leuchter report cited the absence of such seals as one 
reason why the alleged 'gas chambers' would never have functioned.  
  
The Arithmetic of Annihilation  
  
The primary argument put forward by Professor Arthur Butz in 
his classic text, The Hoax of the 20th Century was demographic: the Jews of 
Europe were still there after the war and therefore had not been exterminated. 
They had generally moved eastwards, and once the Iron curtain came down in 1948 
it became difficult to count them. Some two million emigrated from Europe, both 
to Palestine and America. Between 3 12 and 4 million Jews had lived in all the 
lands controlled by Adolf Hitler[12], of which an upper limit of one million 
died in WW2: the figure of a million dead, 'while possible, seems rather high to 
me', concluded Butz[13],[14] - a figure to be contrasted with ten million 
Germans who died during and just after that war[15]. If somewhere around fifty 
million people died during WW2, that Jewish mortality comprised some 2% of this 
total: which is about the average for Europe, i.e. no great excess of Jews died 
in WW2. Almost half a million Jews dwelt in Germany around 1930 (around 1% of 
the population), and by 1939 many had emigrated, some 270,000 
remaining[16].  
  
The figure of six million dead is given in the 'Holocaust' 
section in Wikipedia, with three million having died in Poland. Its high 
'extermination' figures are given in counties well to the East of Germany. East 
Europe was then the epicentre of world Jewry, and in the years around WWII a 
vast diaspora of Jews took place, mainly into what became the Soviet Union, but 
also Palestine and America. Poland had 10% of its total population Jewish in the 
1930s and the Polish premier had 'stated repeatedly that there were a million 
too many Jews in Poland'[17] ­so the pressure on them to emigrate was not solely 
due to German policies. British rule in Palestine disintegrated in 1938, which 
meant that its strict immigration quotas ceased to apply. A very careful 
estimate of East Europe's Jewish population ascertained that there were 2.6 
million in Poland at the outbreak of the war - less than the total Polish 
'deaths' given by Wikipedia. It put total worldwide mortality of Jews through 
WWII at 1 14 million, of which most was due to 'Soviet barbarism' rather than 
German labour-camps[18]. That seems quite comparable to the figure given above. 
Within the Nazi labour-camps, around four hundred and fifty thousand Jews 
died.[19]  
  
Around 500,000 prisoners were registered in the labour-camps 
of Auschwitz in Poland, of which some 130,000 died[20]. Bodies were there 
disposed of by individual cremation, and the records for  fuel consumption 
over the period February 1942 ­ October 1943 for the cremation ovens indicate 
that around five thousand bodies were then Burnt. That accords with the number 
of registered, deceased inmates, viz those who had died from natural causes[21], 
who had to be cremated rather than buried because of the great typhoid 
epidemics. This demonstrates that no mass-incineration of bodies took place. 
Josef Kramer, a supervisor at the Auschwitz camp, gave a statement after the war 
which is recommended by Professor Butz as probably genuine: it had 350-500 
deaths per week happening over May-November 1944, all from natural causes, a 
very high figure because sick prisoners were sent there, and the dead were all 
cremated. He believed the camp held up to 100,000 prisoners, mainly Poles and 
Prussians.[22]  
  
The Final Solution ­ An Export Program  
  
The 'Final Solution' of Adolf Hitler retained a single meaning 
right through WW2, central to the program of 'National socialism,' and signified 
the deportation of Jews, generally eastwards to Poland and Russia[23]. This 
program did not change at any point, e.g. the Wannsee conference of 1942,[24] to 
signify deliberate extermination. If that practice ever happened, it was not a 
centrally-directed policy and did not involve gas chambers: many tons of 
documentation of 'third Reich' policies remains, and no-one has been able to 
find therein any hint of such a meaning ­ of intentional genocide. The 
historical record fails to show any central decision to exterminate Jews by Nazi 
Germany.  
  
The Gestapo and Zionists were collaborating in the late 30s 
because they had in this respect similar aims.[25] But, a German Foreign Office 
circular bulletin of June 22, 1937 stated that: 'In view of the anti-German 
agitation of international Jewry, Germany cannot agree that the formation of a 
Palestine Jewish state would help the peaceful development of the nations of the 
world'.[26] International Jewish organisations twice declared war on Germany, in 
1933 then again in 1939[27]. As the 'final solution' policy[28] was thwarted by 
the Allies, the camps became places of hard labour; then under the impact of 
Allied terror-bombing ravages of disease and famine took place.  
  
No Documents!  
  
At the Auschwitz trial held at Frankfurt in the mid-sixties, 
the court had to conclude that it lacked 'almost all the means or evidence 
available in a normal murder trial' including 'the bodies of the victim, autopsy 
reports, expert reports on the cause of death, evidence as to the criminals, 
murder weapons, etc[29].' Far from leading to doubt, this gave to the mythic gas 
chambers a metaphysical status, doubt of which was forbidden. 'No documents have 
survived, perhaps none ever existed,' concluded the Holocaust historian Léon 
Poliakov.[30]  
  
'In the case of the rush to impute to the Nazis a programme 
for the extermination of millions of people which has implausibly left no 
material traces, all the normal rules of historiography seem not only to have 
been suspended, but to have been violated over and over again. Historians 
routinely cite documents from secondary works like Raul Hilberg's The 
Destruction of the European Jews (1961) or from printed collections of 
documents, such as Robert Wolfe's Holocaust: The Documentary Evidence - but they 
never cite original documents.[31]  
  
The nearest we have to primary-source documents concerning 
what went on within the camps, comes from the bulky, three-volume International 
Red Cross Report published in 1948. This and especially Volume III describes the 
couple of thousand regular, routine inspection-visits that its doctors made 
through the war years to the Polish labour-camps. Their report never hints at 
any gas-chamber, nor any mass-cremations. While maintaining a politically 
neutral position[32], it confirms that mortality in the camps was to a large 
extent caused by the allied terror-bombing.[33] Likewise Winston Churchill's 
bulky, six-volume account of the War gives no allusion to the subject, 
especially volume Six, Triumph and Tragedy where one would expect to have some 
allusion if he believed it had happened.[34]  
  
The head of the SS camp administration office sent a directive 
dated Dec. 28, 1942, to Auschwitz and the other concentration camps. It sharply 
criticised the high death rate of inmates due to disease, and ordered that "camp 
physicians must use all means at their disposal to significantly reduce the 
death rate in the various camps." Furthermore, it ordered: "The camp doctors 
must supervise more often than in the past the nutrition of the prisoners and, 
in cooperation with the administration, submit improvement recommendations to 
the camp commandants ... The camp doctors are to see to it that the working 
conditions at the various labor places are improved as much as possible." The 
directive stressed that "the Reichsfuhrer SS [Heinrich Himmler] has ordered that 
the death rate absolutely must be reduced."[35] A further letter to all 
concentration camp commanders dated 20th January, 1943, reaffirmed that 'every 
means must be used to lower the death rate.' By September 1943 Auschwitz still 
had mortality peaking at 80/day, viewed as 'catastrophic' by the SS 
administration. Thus, from authentic documents concerning the need to reduce 
fatalities at the Auschwitz camp, the world has moved to a belief in genocide, 
with not a single authentic, supporting document[36]. The Auschwitz camp was set 
up as an industrial plant using the giant coalfields of Poland, and located at 
the confluence of rivers; it was essential to the war-effort - it would have 
made no sense to start exterminating its inmates.  
  
The Hamburg judge Wilhelm Staeglich had been positioned near 
Auschwitz during the war and had on various occasions dropped into the camps 
around there. The conditions seemed fairly tolerable, he recalled, and certainly 
nothing resembling an extermination program existed. In particular, he had 
discerned no fear of mistreatment amongst the inmates. He published a testimony 
to this effect in 1973, and in return for his shocking news a German inquisition 
forced him to resign his job, stripped him of his doctoral degree, and  
his book. He was then subjected to police . His book, translated into 
English, is an essential text.[37]  
  
German military radio messages were successfully decrypted at 
Bletchley Park using the 'enigma' codebreaker. Concerning the labour camps, over 
the period Spring 1942-February '43, the following information was obtained: 
'The return from Auschwitz, the largest of the camps with 20,000 prisoners, 
mentioned illness as the main cause of death, but included references to 
shootings and hangings. There were no references in the decrypts to 
gassings.'[38] That seems clear enough - though no-one took any notice of it at 
Nuremberg.  
  
No Photos!  
  
Not only is there no trace of 'Third Reich' documentation[39] 
for what is alleged, but no photographs exist showing anything resembling such a 
group-gassing procedure. Do you believe that Jews both male and female stripped 
then marched into the gas chambers, then were hauled out in piles? If so, are 
you willing to believe that neither the very-thorough Germans nor the clever 
Jews wanted or were able to get a single picture of this ultimate horror? Go to 
Google and search ­ you'll find rows of emaciated bodies, dead of typhus, will 
that do? I don't think so.  
  
US air-photographs taken in 1944 (released in 1978) when the 
'program' was supposed to be in full swing do not show any huge crematoria 
Burning corpses nor queues entering the 'gas chambers: 'The few air photos of 
Auschwitz-Birkenau known to date from the period of December 1943 to February 
1945 show no signs of fuel depots, smoke from chimneys or open fires, Burning 
pits or pyres. The photos were altered: Zyklon B input hatches, groups of 
inmates, and walls around crematoria were retouched onto the photo negatives To 
this day there is no air photo evidence to support the alleged mass murder of 
the Jews at any location in Europe occupied by the Germans during World War 
Two.That the photos in western hands were altered in order to incriminate 
Germany, and were first published by the CIA, is also very significant 
indeed.'[40]  
  
The Fabrication of Untruth  
  
Let's hear a couple of testimonies concerning the dreaded 
gas-chambers. An Austrian woman, Maria Van Herwaarden, testified about her camp 
experiences in a Toronto District Court in March 1988, as she had been interned 
in Auschwitz-Birkenau in 1942 for having sexual relations with a Polish forced 
laborer. On the train trip to the camp, a Gypsy woman told her and the others 
that they would all be gassed at Auschwitz. Upon arrival, Maria and the other 
women were ordered to undress and go into a large concrete room without windows 
to take a shower. The terrified women were sure that they were about to die. But 
then, instead of gas, water came out of the shower heads. Auschwitz was no 
vacation center, Maria confirmed, and she witnessed the death of many fellow 
inmates by disease, particularly typhus, and quite a few committed suicide. But 
she saw no evidence at all of mass killings, gassings, or of any extermination 
program.[41] A Jewish woman named Marika Frank arrived at Auschwitz-Birkenau 
from Hungary in July 1944, when 25,000 Jews were supposedly gassed and cremated 
daily. She likewise testified after the war that she heard and saw nothing of 
"gas chambers" during the time she was interned there. She heard the gassing 
stories only later.[42]  
  
The Allied carpet-bombing destroyed the supply lines for the 
Camps, and so the death-toll mounted from famine and disease. Leaflets were 
dropped from the air, alleging that at Auschwitz a 'final 
solution'/extermination of Jews policy was being conducted, using gas. [43] That 
was the genesis of the story, as those Allied-propaganda leaflets were believed. 
Greeted by the sight, of rows of famished Jews who had died of e.g. typhoid, it 
was not hard to see its confirmation. 'Far from it being common knowledge in 
Germany that people were being gassed the vast majority of Germans were 
horrified by the United Nations accusations and they protested that they had 
never heard of such  until after the cessation of hostilities when they had 
begun listening to United Nations broadcasts . Since the British Broadcasting 
Corporation had been broadcasting these accusations regularly for many months 
before the end of the war, those Germans who had "common knowledge" of the 
gassing before the war's end most likely got this "knowledge" from the BBC!'[44] 
The gas-chamber legend was born in December 1941, when the German author Thomas 
Mann declared on the BBC that, in German hospitals, the severely wounded, the 
old and the feeble were culled with poison gas. This was the 'first appearance 
of gas chambers in propaganda.'[45]  
  
As to how the stories got going, here is a remark by 
Faurisson: 'The Foreign Office saw the new rumors of the Second World War only 
as Jewish inventions, and many in American circles shared that conviction[46]. 
Edward Benes, President of Czechoslovakia (in exile in London), announced in 
November 1942, after inquiry by his staff, that the Germans, contrary to what 
had been reported to him, were not exterminating the Jews. The American Jew, 
 Frankfurter, a Supreme Court judge, stated to Jan Karski on the subject: 
"I can't believe you." In August of 1943, Cordell Hull, Secretary of State, 
warned the U.S. ambassador in Moscow by telegram that in planning a joint Allied 
statement on "the German crimes in Poland", it would be advisable to eliminate 
any mention of the gas chambers, since, as the British pointed out, there was 
"insufficient evidence" in the matter[47]  
  
The Hoax of Nuremberg  
  
A modern inquiry needs to start from the data-fabrication at 
Nuremberg by the US/UK, using systematic assassination and torture of witnesses. 
The Nuremberg trials started in 1946 with the image of six million dead as 
firmly established.[48] This did not emerge as a conclusion from the trials, but 
in its immensity it was presented to the tortured and/or beaten[49] Nazis as a 
fact, and would they confess their part in it? All the main defendants at 
Nuremberg insisted that prior to the trial they had not known of any mass murder 
of Jews: except that Rudolf Höss, the former Commandant of Auschwitz, signed on 
March 15, 1946, a document averring that he had overseen the slaughter of two 
and a half million Jews, and this was read out on 15th April at Nurnberg. That 
day signified the birth of Auschwitz's horror-myth. Two weeks earlier, Höss had 
remarked:  
  
Certainly, I signed a statement that I killed two and half 
million Jews. I could just as well have said it was five million Jews. There are 
certain methods by which any confession can be obtained, whether it is true or 
not."[50]  
  
Decades later, an account was published of how Höss had been 
tortured for three days and nights without sleep by a British army team in order 
to extract that statement.[51] In a letter to his wife, Höss apologised for his 
'confessions' and explains that they had been extracted from him under 
torture[52]. The victorious Allies could not have their 'truth' come out at 
Nuremberg, without the assistance of torture. In 2001, Patricia Meehan discussed 
the network of Secret "Direct Interrogation Centres" the British had set up in 
their occupational zone of Germany[53] - torture chambers, to prepare 'evidence' 
for the upcoming trials. A Zionist influence was noted at the Nuremberg 
trials,[54] not least concerning the figure of six million.[55]  
  
Weighty books are in print as memorials to 'the Holocaust', 
but, let's hear a sceptical view from Down Under:  
  
 
  
  
Revisionist Pioneers: David Irving, Ernst Zündel, and Germar 
Rudolf  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l52ms</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry2d</id></website><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50458</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T19:24:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:37:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3p1t8</id><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50458#comment-480075302</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zd1dw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>