<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwloo5/post/2012-03-30T13:14:32</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body> I would start by buying a small, poor country in the middle of fuck-nowhere. This would probably take the majority of the cash. I would then fill this country with servers and ac units and rebuild my income renting servers to whomever, even TPB. (And of course IHC would have a Spot, rent free. I'll even have the server gold plated with a flashing neon sign of the skull and crossbones.)

After several years of establishing my one country empire, giving money to my new people, giving their children a good education system, everyone a good job, free government healthcare, a chicken in every pot, gaming PCs so I will  have someone to play minecraft with me, all of which I give freely (well, I would not be opposed to having a half dozen or so hot daughters as wives but that is a very loose number. Really it could go either way) I will start investing in private commercial space exploration. 

Once the technology is ready, I will then establish a Moon base. I will appoint Neil deGrasse Tyson as Head-Honcho-Guy-in-Charge-isdent (official title) by I will remain the money behind the scientist. 

I will then commission a giant space-based magnifying lens which I will use, along side a huge solar array, as a source of power generation which I will sell at generous price (and a comfortable profit margin) to the Earth, the Moon, and any aliens that need to top Off their tanks as they past through out solar system. And if anyone get uppity, I will use my magnifying glass (probably not actually made of glass) to Burn them like than ants they are. 

Other things I plan to do along the way:
-Perfect cloning, give Stephen Hawking a new body
-Establish Church of the Phlosoraptor (as a tax shelter)
-Make Taco Thursdays an Earth-wide (and Moon-wide) recognized holiday (yes a weekly holiday)
-Commission a good writer and director to make a really good live-action version of Avatar: The Last Airbender 
-Publish my novel
-legalize marijuana (Moon weed will be very popular, I think)
-Have Michael Bay killed
-Have George Lucas killed
-Have Gene Roddenberry brought back to life
-Have J.J. Abrams maimed but healed after 5 year internship with Gene Roddenberry
-Give Joss  Whedon his own TV channel that he can do with whatever the fuck he wants-Learn to dance</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67c90t</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/v6k</id></website><link>http://www.iheartchaos.com/post/20167978975</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:00:33+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:14:32+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwloo5</id><link>http://www.iheartchaos.com/post/20167978975#comment-480967348</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>