<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nh85/post/2012-03-29T12:45:58</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>More Threat Allegations Surface: The Soros-Funded Media Matters And The Obama Regime Are Threatening The Media Over The Birth Certificate Issue? 
     As evidence mounts that the "birth certificate" released by Team Obama is a "computer-generated forgery,"  EVEN MORE shocking revelations are coming out that Barack Obama's surrogates and far-left power-brokers are engaged in a massive and tyrannical effort to SILENCE the conservative media from reporting on Mr. Obama's eligibility. 

     However, there's some good news to report as well. A few brave souls in the conservative media are finally daring to break the silence. Diana West, who writes for The Washington Times, recently blew the whistle: "Clearly, something has us all on lockdown. That’s much, much scarier than even the amazing possibility that some con artist might be pulling Off the biggest scam in history." 

     And, as we previous reported, Mike Zullo, the lead investigator of Sheriff Joe Arpaio's Cold Case Posse stated; "During our investigation, we actually were told [that media] had been threatened with FTC investigations. Commentators [had been] threatened with their jobs.” And according to WND.com, the "threats were so intimidating that some individuals quit their positions over safety concerns for their families." 

     Of course, there's more (keep reading)... and even more will follow; but for now, one thing is certain. 

     The Obama Regime is not just illegitimate... now that the illegitimacy and tyrannical abuses of the Obama White House are finally starting to see the light of day, the Obama Regime is coming unglued. Like a cornered animal, IT IS OUT OF CONTROL, and if we do not take action, right here and right now, we may very well lose our country. 
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h0hgi</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yjmx</id></website><link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2012/03/28/gop-run-house-easily-rejects-obama-budget/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T01:50:16+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:45:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nh85</id><link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2012/03/28/gop-run-house-easily-rejects-obama-budget/#comment-479640604</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/81s3z</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>