<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkyf18/update/2012-03-25T08:54:19/e9a8d53150b7b320b6d34e444e853087d7bbef58ce0fc15fac2a09872b1de703</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>OK...Here is my .2 Cents. I have a pretty serious medical condition called Marfan Syndrome. Basically it is a genetic in which a mutated gene prevents the persons body for producing a very important glycoprotine called fibrin. The person with this mutation will suffer from (just to name a few) skeletal deformities (curved spine/scoliosis) hyper mobility of the joints, flat feet, bad vision usually nearsightedness the condition also increases risk that the persons retina can detach...gotta keep an eye on the heart (aorta can grow and rupture causing instant death or death with very little warning if you don't keep and eye on it. 

So I don't want to make this too long, but this is why I am forced to seek out heroin or diacetylmorphine, heroins chemical name. Due to a very bad back (curved, messed up discs that cause severe Nerve pain shooting down my lower back into my left leg) My feet are deformed/flat and my ankles buckle when I walk. I would say to a normal person the best way to describe it is imagine if you had to walk upside down on the palms of your hands, with the wrists supporting all that weight. After a short amount of time the pain alone from weak joints taking all that weight would be unbearable. I have had corrective surgery done, but it actually made things worse  pain wise. 

Going back to my curved spine...my neck is a little uneven and I get frequent and severe migraine Headaches if my neck is under very little stress. For example. Sleeping on it wrong, using the computer while sitting instead of laying for a short amount of time. I mean its hard to explain but the smallest thing can set this . Then it is 12 hours of feeling like I have a hot railroad spike in my eye sockets and I am puking in my trashcan cause I don't want to leave my nice dark room with no lights or loud noises. 

I could keep going and I have not really even scratched the surface yet. To sum it up I suffer from chronic pain. However, the pain is based on how active I am. If I stay unemployed and live life at a slow pace the pain....well I am still in a lot of frigging pain! So now I am going to get to my point. 

I was fine most of my life until my early 20's ( I am almost 29 now) then things got rough. So I tried things like hydrocodone and perc's, and was still able to hold a job and have a decent life. Granted most of my money was going towards pills. It was like I was working just so I could afford to work. If that makes sense. 

Eventually people started charging outrageous prices for pills and getting them could be unreliable at best. So I found heroin, or perhaps it found me. 
Pretty cheap compared to pills, and unlike the pills that can come and go quick, the heroin business flows 24/7 365 days a year. 

Looking back, I would not have had to turn to heroin if I had gotten the proper treatment from my doctors. Despite the severity of my condition and how clearly obvious that "something aint right" as far as my body goes...I could not get my own RX for pain control. I am pretty sure it is due to my age, and the fact that Dr's in the US seem to be very afraid of Rx'ing opiate based pain medications. The DEA is riding their asses and it is stupid. Sure there are quacks out there, but these men and women went to school for a long time and studied hard to practice medicine and some "Drug Cop" with a badge and a gun gets to intimidate innocent men and women in the medical profession.  

But here is my biggest complaint of them all. I have seen more pill pushers that admittedly have no chronic pain issues getting fat scripts and selling them all  in days to make a killing. Seems most of these people had something happen to them at some point like and accident and got on disability, and for whatever reason at some point their pain lessened or stopped but they continued to get the scripts. I literally have seen people that get their little check and then turn around and sell x90 30mg Oxycodone pills for $20-25 a pop. They would make roughly and extra 2 grand a month with in a matter of a few days. Those who got more that one script could sometimes make close to 4 grand in a weeks time. Part of me despised these people to the core. They were not in any pain and making a killing  other people that can't seem to get their own script for legit pain and of course the people that just wanna get high as well. Hey, to each his own I  say. 

So anyway back on track. I am having a hard time getting on benefits since I did not have insurance when things started to get bad, so I have very little documentation on my issues. It is kind of ironic. I need to work so I can have insurance, but I need insurance so I can maybe get treated and work. 

Recently I have been having a lot of issues that have left me with no choice to go to the hospital with no insurance. Every time I go and they find out they have a person with Marfan Syndrome in their bed, all the medical students/interns or whatever come around with the main doctors and they want to poke at me and what not.

So they check me out...back, neck, feet, ankles, joints and go "wow you must be in allot of pain" to which I reply yes. They usually ask me about it and I tell them. Then they just finish up and leave. Every time it like "wow that must be painful" then I ask if there is anything that can be done about it. I get some dance around the point answer that is not really an answer and they leave. 

I had one doctor that for about 9 months had me on 60mg time release morphine twice a day and 15mg Oxycodone IR twice a day. During that time I was able to work with complication. I was able to go out in the evening with friends and enjoy myself. Then, because of my age and scrutiny from other doctors at the practice, I was rapidly weened down and cut . My mom was so upset she stormed in there and demanded to know why they were doing this to me. She asked had I done something wrong. She was simply told "no, nothing wrong. I am not an actual pain management doctor so I can't Rx these meds for long periods of time" So it's been close to two years since I was cut  my meds. I have managed not to use heroin. All I do now is bum a few Hydrocodone from my dad every now and again when the pain gets real bad. They don't really work very well anymore, but it's at least better than the Motrin 800mg I get. 

So every thing I try every corner I turn I hit a roadblock. People are pushing  me to get benefits, but I really don't want to do that. I feel (scratch that) I know if I could get proper pain management, I would be able to function well enough to work a job that is not to physically demanding. I would rather work in IT and make 50k a year than get $800 a month from uncle Sam. I have so much potential that is being wasted due to pain issues. 

So I guess the moral of the story is that there are allot of people out there that will end up on heroin for maybe a few years or maybe the rest of their lives. It only going to get harder to get legit pain management as things with doctors and the DEA keeps getting worse. Also, these people getting their scripts and selling them ain't helping. They get caught and the doctor usually has to pay for some ass holes mistake. 

It is getting to the point where things are getting so bad, I am going to really start fighting until I am properly treated. I wan't my life back! I don't want to be a slave to my body and what it decides I can or can not do on any given day. I want to be able to work again, being unemployed and living at home is depressing! 

I am sorry for the long post but I needed to rant. It is a shame that people in severe pain are at the mercy of someone or someone(s) that get to decide their quality of life. Hell I have seen dope dealers with more compassion than  some Dr's.

God forbid a person a person take control of their own life and be able to just get the medication they need without endlessly begging and pleading when the test's/x-rays/mri's all add up! 

N/A</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/cw03jt</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/znv4</id></website><link>http://topdocumentaryfilms.com/heroin-nation/</link><postedTime>2011-02-25T18:31:55+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-25T12:54:19+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkyf18</id><link>http://topdocumentaryfilms.com/heroin-nation/#comment-475784498</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z6v2a</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-02-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>