<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw1pph/update/2012-03-31T00:28:23/2bea7522a332467b5801d9fc491bdc9e3edbf69e53f0a2b52109adf5ad0e4c4f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw1cvc</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7vxv</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>No dipshit. I said Charles Blow has a punchable face based on the fact he's  wearing a shit-eating grin and is an arrogant jackass. What I didn't say, and you would know this if you had a fourth-grader's reading comprehension, was anything about George Zimmerman, which renders your idiotic rant about me defending Zimmerman perfectly nonsensical. As to your point about a possible fight between Blow and I; I suppose anything's possible. However he seems like a rather slight gentleman who works as a "Visual Arts" columnist and I'm a pretty big dude who when he's not responding to douchebags like yourself is a Ranger-qualified infantry officer in the 101st Airborne who got back from Paktika Province 7 1/2 months ago and recently earned an EIB to go along with his CIB (I don't really expect you to know what either of those are). Chances are you've never been in the position I've been, that of having to take a human life from someone trying to take yours or seeing a 25-year-old American soldier who happens to have a wife and two little kids at home shot by insurgents and then Bleed to death so by all means, take your faux-moralizing "you'd need a gun" line and shove it up your ass. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hvum4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tz1k</id></website><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/lawrence-o%e2%80%99donnell-charles-blow-should-be-ashamed-of-their-conduct-in-joe-oliver-interview/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T15:42:27+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:28:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw1pph</id><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/lawrence-o%e2%80%99donnell-charles-blow-should-be-ashamed-of-their-conduct-in-joe-oliver-interview/#comment-481528561</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6uj4t</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>