<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mijxmu/update/2012-03-23T20:47:48/5907d95a03adbd1a5f51c0cdbd5a0b1d15a972b460b4a2f8f7b503d96870bcc6</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mij53g</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/um4b</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Clearly that "Bs detector" person is deeply disturbed and in need of treatment they're not getting (my money would be on schizoid disorders). It's no use to interact with ill people as if they are well, and not fair to comment on them that way, either.

Back to the point of your comment- a friend of mine gets annoyed by homeopathy and thinks it's all placebo effect and should be . I tend to take the middle ground- there are some great natural remedies for certain conditions or symptoms. Slippery elm tea and honey for a Sore throat, aloe for a rash/Burn, or cinnamon to regulate blood sugar/energy, for example. I just think it's become nearly impossible to parse out which products even have the ingredients they claim to, with all the deception in their marketing and labeling. I think a lot of people (not all, of course) might be better  exploring some actual natural fixes, but it's nearly impossible with no rigorous testing and instructions to truly inform people and keep them safe. I think it's a shame.

But, as for the original point of the article- I think that mindset is changing. I feel like everyone my age (30) and younger tends to assume they're being tricked. We grew up with ubiquitous media and marketing, and image manipulation. We Always are looking for the "trick" (well, at least those of us taught to think critically, which generally includes scientists). I wonder if that will change how research, and the scientific mindset, change in the next few decades.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66varw</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lj1l</id></website><link>http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2012/03/opinion-randi-magic-scientists/</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T21:17:21+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-24T00:47:48+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mijxmu</id><link>http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2012/03/opinion-randi-magic-scientists/#comment-474938915</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h3hdq</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>