<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3izcz/update/2012-03-29T21:20:37/8337b79829393d702c3e39002ce5272767fa0fcd24a3273329fec8a3bec849d0</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Nothing has made me give up hope on American society quite like seeing supposed liberals and progressives on liberal websites (DailyKos being one of the big ones)... actually arguing in favor of guns. Good god... WE'RE supposed to be the reality based community, remember?  If you can't look at data regarding gun violence around the world, compare it to America's numbers, and arrive at the conclusion that guns greatly contribute to wrongful death in America... then you're just cognitively impaired.  

I've been living in Japan for the last two years.  Yes, guns are illegal here, and yes, certain individuals still have them (mafia primarily).  And every once in a great while, there will be a shooting.  But in every single instance I've read of, the person killed was the target of a hit put out on him by "business associates."  Not one has been a convenience store clerk, not one was the victim of a mugging, or a jealous boyfriend.  Not one was killed while cleaning their weapon, or because they found it in their dad's closet and thought it was neat.

I don't think very many of you know what it's even like to live somewhere where, frankly... you feel safe.  Where if a shifty-eyed man walks into the 7-11 same time as you, you don't have to worry about getting caught in the crossfire.  Where if you get involved in a spat of road-rage, you don't have to worry about what the other guy might pull out of his glovebox.  Where if I find myself, unavoidably, in an elevator alone with a woman with a severe paranoia of foreigners, I don't have to worry that I might Sneeze and she'll blow my head Off.  (Seriously, to be a black person in America, putting up with stuff like that?  I couldn't do it.)

No, I'm sorry, but if our progressive voters and liberals in America are still supporting gun ownership... if we've laid down arms (figuratively speaking) to that degree in that cultural battle... then I quit.  I'll stay here as long as possible, and try to find somewhere else rationally minded when i have to leave.  America, you can keep playing cowboy, and the rest of the world will continue to laugh at you.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zb883</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5xa</id></website><link>http://www.americablog.com/2012/03/guns-dont-kill-people-hoodies-kill.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:44:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:20:37+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3izcz</id><link>http://www.americablog.com/2012/03/guns-dont-kill-people-hoodies-kill.html#comment-480108506</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/vjh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>