<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3b7dt/update/2012-03-29T14:34:32/925e6e5f3af68395ddb50a315caaf9ea5d78c83b6bb4c63973febe618c397f77</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xs1x</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dx12m</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I was looking for the appropriate place to insert this piece of things I've learned along the way, and your comment seems to fit very well:

I was working for a rather large company doing some low level industrial work for the R&amp;D department.  They sent us down instructions and orders for the day and we created whatever they needed.  Well the chemistry department decided to try working on a new "flavoring agent" as they called it.  Seemed simple enough.  Some part ammonium hydroxide (saturated solution) and some part HFCS.  So wearing the appropriate safety gear we mixed up what was ordered and placed it into an open reactor vessel to basically cook over night.  The next day the chemistry team that placed the request came down to see how things were going.  We opened up the vessel and found (what they expected) something that looked like molasses (and smelled pleasant compared to the eye/lung Burning of the ammonia).  So we emptied it into a container and one of the female chemists was so over Joyed by everything she stuck her pinkie into it and ate it.

At this point all of us non chemistry PhD's just raised an eyebrow as she exclaimed it was exactly what they were looking for....

I realized that day just because what goes in is something that will Burn the inside of your lungs doesn't mean that what comes out isn't something that you might put on your breakfast plate...</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zvynr</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/agg8</id></website><link>http://boingboing.net/2012/03/29/pink-slime-in-the-context-of-h.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:29:24+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:34:32+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3b7dt</id><link>http://boingboing.net/2012/03/29/pink-slime-in-the-context-of-h.html#comment-479736737</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8dix</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>