<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/eus1u9/update/2012-01-06T17:27:23/2bc8375e88820bf5c4b1f3bcde100439bc3e97e62b8314f4cb05efb47aedf763</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/eucblw</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g53ur</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Actually, to me, yet another story-addict who fancies herself as a future failed feature-writer, the core problem remains once and for all the lack of appeal generated by uncharacterized poorly narrated atmosphereless excruciatingly too long for nothing because unbuilt films that  and co Vomit in our viewers' eyes every year.
First instance, the voiceover narration: it's not a book, it's a movie. If you need to tell, it means you don't show. Now I don't mind it occasionally, when it actually adds to the thing whether emotionally or in strengthening the characterization (see In America) but lately it's been abused in oh too many occurrences (you know them when you see them) if not to drag the whole piece down with overweight yet empty artificial narration then only to play the cheap humour card where something visual (yes it does require upscaled writing skills) and more elaborate than basic standup comedy would have brought a tremendously greater pay- (see Septien and that genius shot where the hero peers over kids playing in the park, (mis?)leading the viewer into thinking he's a pedo... yep, trying not to spoil).
Second, under the apparently legitimate pretence of conveying vicarious emotions, they shove down our throats a douchy blend of unchallenging consensuous feely-feely bullshit (sorry, French) as in what they expect us to want to feel. I for one don't watch a movie regardless of its length or make (brand, citizenship, political inspiration, call it what you may) to feel what I want to feel. That's bad marketing, at best. Worse! When they actually leave it to you to decide ( as opposed to interprete) what you want to see (see Inception: if you want the spinning top to wobble and fall, press 1, if you want it to wobble dangerously long enough to give you a thrill and then start spinning again so you've actually seen the movie you paid for, everybody's happy nobody's disappointed we live in Disneyland, press 2... you know what I mean).
Third would be dull lazy visual narrative styles, as in facial (over)reaction shots, (please!) and attention-stirring extreme , when you stop assuming people are too dumb to get it maybe they'll start bothering trying not to be.

Now I do realize I'm not your typical every day viewer in that I hate theaters because my prime goal when I go is to see a film, not execute foreplays or bear with the miscellaneous indiscretions of pigs raised by wolves who think the world is their living-room (phones, food and whatnot you wouldn't expect anywhere near a person's mouth, and yet...). 
With the crazy increase in price I've been led to checking my movies out first (as in test-riding them at home and making the sacrifice only when I know it's worth it), so  needless to say I'd be a big fan of re-releasing if only they would re-release whatever actually is worth it (as in not Titanic, I haven't seen it and I won't, don't bother, I'm not prejudiced here I know myself that's all. James Cameron being one of my most widely used examples of way too long for nothing among other disparaging things). And I don't mind length when it works (It's a mad mad mad mad world to name but one, 192 min original version, not a split second to cut, I don't wanna see the edit I honestly can't even begin to think how they did it). What I mind is making movies longer without adding any substance whatsoever just so people feel like it was worth the rip-, paradoxically when the viewer's attention-span seems to zoom out of shot (why else ads every ten minutes and the spike in very short programs? )

Naturally to find that substance I've been one to turn to whatchacallem serials, and observing the same crucially selective scrutiny as regarding full-length features, believe it or not the good-to-bad ratio (as in what's not a matter of taste) is just about alike, maybe a little more write-as-you-shoot latence there, but the good direction makes up for it, or is it that I'm more inclined towards indulgence because they're not so pompous with their "director's cut" and all? Generally when a tv show's not as good as expected you tend to not mind it as much because you didn't have to  lift your lazy ass out of the couch and pay a fortune (so you think coz you don't Cough it out on the Spot), and mostly because you just zap and you're on to the next low-level brain-removal program brought to you by people who mean you well.

So with all the competition that watching home for free (albeit in lessened quality) provides, my mind definitely bends towards stepping up the plate and as ever quality over quantity and the highest common denominator possible but I highly doubt that's a lesson humanity will in time feel partial to.  You know, like with food, eat less but better, create legitimate quality labels that people can actually trust (hell, let Tarantino or Brad Pitt do it, as ineluctably in times of crisis, charisma's the word, give 'em the face) and why not actually advertise raising talents instead of flooding the market with knock-offs of knock-offs of knock-offs (Fast and Furious 5, really?).

Of course the solution lies in the alternative, be it short, independent, different, or just good, for a change, that would be refreshing. The solution lies in not letting the market direct your conduct but your conduct (theirs, really, as in the decision-makers, as in the wallet-holders) actually making the market. Panicking and freezing won't help things get better, as previously seen with the banks. But here again, knowing that it's not the easiest and most immediate tactical answer to the matter at hand, they will wait for someone else to provide the required critical response and just benefit from it. But judging by the path we're headed down on socially on a global scale, people are going to need escape routes more than ever. They're not just about to stop watching, maybe Hollywood has to accept they shouldn't make such indecent amounts of money out of it.(yeah, like hell!)</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/dfyh7l</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/4iyw</id></website><link>http://www.shortoftheweek.com/2012/01/05/has-hollywood-lost-its-way/</link><postedTime>2012-01-04T09:34:40+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-01-06T22:27:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/eus1u9</id><link>http://www.shortoftheweek.com/2012/01/05/has-hollywood-lost-its-way/#comment-402953174</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-01-04</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>