<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fepm/post/2012-03-29T16:38:06</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Boy, there sure are a lot of armchair scouts in this state!  I think all of these guys have at least a very good chance to be excellent pros.  Barnes especially because he's so good  of one dribble, making him a perfect pick and roll scorer in the NBA.  Don't let a shooting slump fool you into thinking he has no talent!  Henson needs to work on his strength, but he's improved by leaps and bounds in that area over the last couple years, and he will continue to fill out.  Remember, Dean Smith  said that big men don't really grow into their bodies until they're about 28.  Marshall might suffer from a lack of foot speed, but with his vision I just can't see him being anything less than effective, and maybe a star.  Imagine him on the Heat right now, passing to LeBron and Wade; how many assists would he average per game?  And finally, Zeller might just be the best of them all. He got so much tougher as the season wore on, and he's much faster and more athletic than he gets credit for.  He also needs to work on his strength, but I bet he starts for somebody within three years!  I hate to see these guys go, but everyone writing them Off as NBA busts already are either piling on UNC or just don't know what they're talking about!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6znh1x</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnei</id></website><link>http://www.charlotteobserver.com/2012/03/29/3136895/uncs-barnes-henson-marshall-enter.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:30:53+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:38:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fepm</id><link>http://www.charlotteobserver.com/2012/03/29/3136895/uncs-barnes-henson-marshall-enter.html#comment-479865787</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8i6h0</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>