<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/234352/post/86320894/comment/329711130</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Aviation Unit performance, low-flying next year? devaluation of the renminbi is expected to be a recent hot topic as of December 6, the Spot exchange rate of RMB against the U.S. dollar for the fifth consecutive day contact with the lower limit, a continuous downward trend for the past three years the first . Along with the devaluation of the RMB bad expected, and also led to nearly a week of many airline stocks fell sharply and the four trading days December 2 to December 7,louis vuitton site officiel Experts said the extreme Cold in Europe seven or eig, China Southern Airlines (600 029) shares fell 11 percent,sac vuitton, Air China (601 111) decreased by 7%, China Eastern Airlines (600115) decreased by 8%. devaluation of the Renminbi aviation the dividend empty This year,sacs louis vuitton, the airline\'s operating results to a large extent is benefiting from foreign exchange  arising from the appreciation of the renminbi, the proceeds of this part of the book on airline results of operations have a great impact. because the airlines are generally high debt-oriented enterprises, requires a lot of debt to buy new aircraft, in order to maintain the competitive advantages of scale. Three quarterly reports,sac louis vuitton,moncler donna,louis vuitton site officiel, the liabilities of Air China\'s rate of 70%, while China Southern Airlines\' liabilities was 69%. Due to the civil aircraft market, Boeing and Airbus giant monopoly, you need to pay in euros or U.S. dollars to purchase the Airbus and Boeing aircraft, the airline\'s liability part of the purchase and leasing aircraft,moncler outlet The Jiangshan still pillow Cold - Y,sac vuitton,sac louis vuitton, foreign currency debt each year to pay a certain amount of interest expense and principal. Appreciation of the yuan against the U.S. dollar and the euro,louis vuitton borse,sacs louis vuitton, means that the airline\'s net foreign currency liabilities would reduce the proportion of foreign exchange . simply appreciation of the renminbi, foreign currency relative depreciation of the domestic airlines to earn RMB also foreign debt, relatively speaking,sac vuitton, their external debt is reduced with the appreciation of the renminbi, and thus the formation of the carrying amount of the income is foreign exchange . But the devaluation of the yuan is expected,sacs louis vuitton, will become the airline\'s good. Market have expected devaluation of the RMB will reduce the airline\'s future foreign exchange Gains and net profit to reduce. expect next year\'s results were affected by macro ,sac vuitton,sac louis vuitton Yancheng Yancheng game center ga, China Southern Airlines recently held in Guangzhou City, China Southern Airlines Pearl Hotel 2011 First Extraordinary General Assembly. In the Southern chairman Si Xian Min\'s speech the next year China\'s civil aviation market outlook and Southern business planning is very worthy of attention from investors. chairman mentioned that from the current macroeconomic situation, the international community, Europe and the United States the situation is getting worse, especially the European debt crisis on the real economy will be a step-by-step expansion,sac louis vuitton sacs louis vuitton Louis Vuitton 2010 gold and dia,woolrich outlet, will result in global international trade show downturn. The domestic front, the growth rate of China\'s economic slowdown. Comprehensive domestic and international economic environment,sacs louis vuitton, due to the airline\'s business passengers and air cargo business and macroeconomic environment is closely related to the chairman of the Division is expected to next year\'s civil aviation industry business in general will be slightly worse than 2011,giubbini moncler, but does not have much gap . In addition, with the advance of industrialization and urbanization in China,sac vuitton, China Southern Airlines continue to favor the booming market of domestic small and medium-sized cities, the first-line market has been saturated,sacs louis vuitton, China Southern Airlines will adjust flight routes matching a large number of narrow-body aircraft is put into domestic The second and third tier markets. The next year the capacity of or oversupply of put on next year\'s industry capacity, chairman of the Division, said: possible trend of oversupply, the industry-wide this year nearly 230 aircraft, the introduction of this part of the supply in the second half of the year has been a gradual shift, the situation of the industry as a whole from the balance between supply and demand changes to the oversupply,louis vuitton site officiel, China Southern Airlines 2012 a net increase of 55 aircraft, but some models may not be delivered on schedule,sacs louis vuitton, another Southern in 2011 eliminated a number of old aircraft, delayed delivery and out of the models largely offset by the additional 55 aircraft. opinion from 2011 and 2012,woolrich parka The current Cold spell in Europe ha, the Southern actual capacity growth is not obvious, it is estimated that next year China Southern Airlines passenger traffic growth may be slightly lower than the growth rate of the whole civil aviation. quote from a media partner and co-operation agencies, does not mean that Sohu securities of their own ideas and positions,sac louis vuitton,louis vuitton site officiel woolrich artic parka Mobile games mobile games do, we recommend investors it prudent judgment, pursuant to which the stock market at your own risk. 
 
[WORDPRESS HASHCASH] The poster sent us \'0 which is not a hashcash value. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:234352:86320894</id><idPostId>86320894</idPostId><idBlogId>234352</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:234352</id><idBlogId>234352</idBlogId><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog</link><displayName>Wanton Wordsmith</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/</link><displayName>The day he went away</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T04:29:50.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:234352:86320894:329711130</id><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/#IDComment329711130</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T04:29:50.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The day he went away by 334tdn8192</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://sacsmagasinfrance1.com</link><idEmailMd5>ad571259dd232409e22630dc7408f48b</idEmailMd5><displayName>334tdn8192</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://sacsmagasinfrance1.com"&gt;334tdn8192&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/"&gt;The day he went away&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>