<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwiv7w/post/2012-03-31T08:30:01</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>SAN FRANCISCO (AP)--The Giants' final cuts are in, and they are shockers. Few will be able to argue anytime soon that the Giants aren't willing to cut their losses, if that's what it takes to win. 

After the overnight Twitter leak and then the announcement early this morning, fans started gathering outside ATT Park. A festive atmosphere prevailed. "It's almost like when we won the World Series," said one fan. "Now we are all set to win it again," added another.

Already some media analysts are referring to The Twitter Quake.

"Well, cutting Rowand and Tejada last year should have showed us that the Giants are capable of moves like this," one reveler remarked. Another recalled the decision in 2010 to drop Barry Zito from the playoff roster.

With this morning's Zito, Huff, Whiteside, and Theriot moves, the Giants complete a youthful overhaul that, at first Blush, seems to break radically with the veteran model employed by GM Brian Sabean in the past. "Not so," Sabean himself countered; "we've still got the veteran leadership we need. And it's not just on the pitching staff. Elsewhere on the field, the time had simply arrived for our younger veterans to take over those leadership roles. This is simply our vote of confidence in them."

Gregor Blanco's roster Spot seemed secured long before today's moves, but the decision to keep Joaquin Arias and to carry three catchers took most observers by surprise. 

In effect, the Giants traded Huff's role on the roster for those of Brett Pill and Hector Sanchez. Pill and Brandon Belt will now share first base with Buster Posey, with each available for pinch-hitting when the others are in the game. Posey will get the catching relief he needs, and the Giants will be able to keep his bat in the lineup with greater consistency. But it was Sanchez whose spring can be said to have forced these moves. He now seems slated to add another bat to Bruce Bochy's mix-and-match arsenal. Chris Stewart's presence not only rests Posey, but makes pinch-hitting by Sanchez a possibility. 

The Giants may not be done. At a time when most teams are cutting rather than adding, either Theriot or Fontenot may still wind up accepting a Spot in Fresno, and the Giants are reportedly willing to make the necessary monetary accommodation. Meanwhile, all eyes now turn to the pitching staff. With Zito gone, much will be expected of Clay Hensley and Danny Otero. And down the road, much may  on when Eric Surkamp or Dan Runzler is ready to come Off the Disabled List. 

But one thing is certain: The Friday Night Shocker will reverberate in Giants' lore, forevermore. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67lwe5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lz6q</id></website><link>http://sanfrancisco.giants.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120330%26content_id=27760004%26vkey=news_sf%26c_id=sf</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T20:13:15+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T12:30:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwiv7w</id><link>http://sanfrancisco.giants.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120330%26content_id=27760004%26vkey=news_sf%26c_id=sf#comment-481791166</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/51uha</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>