<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mczxls/update/2012-02-03T18:30:08/fb3d9d5391c4529d44402c6b7bc2071a044c019fbed9288615ddb1c1da5e8b93</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Publishing this rubbish confirms that the Telegraph continues  to drift down market and swallows the untruths promoted by vested interests.

A few well known facts:-

1. Wind is intermittent and therefore conventional back-up is required AT ALL TIMES - turbines cannot be switched  / on at will and still use considerable amounts of power even when idling

2. Power demand has significant peaks and troughs and it is impossible to switch / transfer power from the North to peak demand in say, the South-East - ever tried emptying a watering can down a straw ?

3.  Another unfortunate fact is that Cold spells coincide with periods of  very low wind.  Last winter I read [ in the DT actually] that certain large wind-farms were generating laughably low capacity percentages  and I quote  '.......As I write the 1588MW Scottish farm Fleet is actually delivering  25 MW while Denmark's much vaunted 3300MW installation is producing  300MW...... '

4...... and it gets worse, when there is wind and low demand then the taxpapyer still has to pay for all the unwanted electricity produced.  

5. The only reason there are such large numbers [ or any ] wind turbines in the UK is that the whole business is heavily subsidised by the tax payer because of legislation produced by the unelected ie the EU Commission.

6. Is it not true that relatives / associates of Cameron , Huhne and Clegg are lobbyists and / or have professional vested interests in promoting this folly ?

7. Given that wind-turbines are expensive to manufacture and require millions of MW to smelt the aluminium required, are expensive to install and maintain with a limited life   ie their carbon footprint is huge  AND average 10 -20 % capacity then the key question is 

HOW MUCH ' EFFING CARBON HAS BEEN SAVED ?

I WOULD SAY PRACTICALLY F-ALL

Currently there is only one answer - Nuclear.  Let's hope that Thorium reactor technology is better promoted.

No, I don't have any vested interests or shares etc. etc.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yrl44y</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/earth/earthnews/9060086/Could-2012-be-year-of-the-wind-turbine.html</link><postedTime>2012-02-03T17:59:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-03T23:30:08+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mczxls</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/earth/earthnews/9060086/Could-2012-be-year-of-the-wind-turbine.html#comment-428982944</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5d8ng</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-03</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>