<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwk1ok/update/2012-03-31T09:56:51/b668fd331785c9fa67abb1500cf786099cd3cfb3acecd62aaf552027dba63f84</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Let me get this shit straight: The Republic has survived for over two hundred years, with our Constitution whole, unmolested, &amp; in place... Our Civil Liberties Intact...  Through not just one, but TWO World Wars, Invasions by Great Britain, a THERMAL NUCLEAR COLD WAR WITH A SUPERPOWER RIVAL (and one that almost went "hot", several times)... She's come through STOLEN ELECTIONS-TWICE in the last twenty years (haha, it's  the GOP stealing them. Now their stealing them from THEMSELVES? That'd be fine, but get your disgusting fuckin Rat Claws Off MY CANDIDATE!)... We've survived attempted Fascist Coups (in the 1930s)...  The Stock Market Crashe(S)...  The Kennedy Assassination, IMMEDIATELY FOLLOWED BY THE RFK ASSASSINATION (to name only TWO)... All of this...  And yet somehow, America did so without EVER having a piece of dog shit president seize Dictatorial Powers like Adolf Hitler did after the Reichstag Fire... But OBAMA needs them? Huh. So... Abraham fuckin LINCOLN didn't need them, during the GREATEST CONSTITUTIONAL CRISES THE REPUBLIC EVER FACED (before this)... but OBAMA does... Oh. So.. Abraham Lincoln got us through a CIVIL FUCKING WAR WITHOUT THEM, but OBAMA FUHER NEEDS THEM. Jawohl, Mein Obama Fuher! When's he going to declare himself "Supreme Judge and Protector of the American People" and "First Soldier in the German Reic--I'm sorry, AMERICAN... haha. Um... Yeah, if you don't think this is truly fucking "HOLY SHIT" time, then you don't know your constitution, or world history. This is SCARY &amp; this is NUTS. Everyone whose been paying attention even a LITTLE, realizes two things: 1.) Obama is Americas fucking NEMESIS and needs to be ARRESTED. 2.) Ron Paul is one of the only ones in CONGRESS, not to MENTION amongst the pathetic DOUCHE BAGS running against him that has the creds to handle this crises. We are in our darkest hour and thank GOD Ron Paul is here. But we need to get pissed and stop accepting this shit. I was a Green Party voter before, so I know when I woke up to George Bush I &amp; II I realized what threats they were (hahaha, little did I know Clinton was a mere Bush Obama CLONE), I saw the Gore Election stolen, then the Kerry  Election stolen, and I will NOT STAND DOWN AND LET THE RON PAUL REVOLUTION BE IGNORED INTO ACCEPTING THE DESTRUCTION OF MY COUNTRY AND CONSTITUTION ANY LONGER. PERIOD. Unless you've got a  Corporate Media Whore TOOL lodged SO FAR up your bum that your brains seeped out your nose, you KNOW Dr. Paul's been SWEEPING. Even when he hasn't won and had it stolen from him, he's done really well. The media is complicit in this whole fucking Coup d' fucking État, as is CONGRESS, the PENTAGON, the JOINT CHIEFS and DEFINITELY the other GOP Candidates. Its time to WTFU America, and fellow patriots. Time to get serious and take out the trash for real. It's time for the Joint Chiefs or the Pentagon to move to Arrest &amp; Deport Obama or they are going to have to be added to a growing list of Treasonous fucking PIGS that we need to get back to ASAP. Because if all of these people don't know the Constitution, or their freaking DUTIES TO UPHOLD AND PROTECT IT, then they absolutely at the VERY least, they're in the wrong fucking line of work and need to be fuckin fired. If I was a Sheriff I'd try to arrest him even if it would get me killed by the CIA fucking praetorian nazi guard (who should be the FIRST to take him down), but obviously are Rockefeller/CFR/Globalist douche bags. The entire Network and Cable News Media is a HUGE THREAT TO THE COUNTRY as is this Illegal Immigrant, Vagrant Squatter in Ron Paul's White House. He says he needs these powers "in case of a Terrorist Threat or National Emergency", well HE'S THE TERRORIST and HE &amp; The PEOPLE BEHIND HIM AND THE OTHER GOP CANDIDATES AND RUBBER STAMP CONGRESS ARE THE EMERGENCY. Arrest them fucking NOW.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6cw5gj</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/obl6</id></website><link>http://www.ronpaulitic.com/Home.aspx</link><postedTime>2012-03-14T22:20:15+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T13:56:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwk1ok</id><link>http://www.ronpaulitic.com/Home.aspx#comment-481848655</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lfcgo</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-14</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>