<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3siwz/update/2012-03-30T00:00:03/603be6fcbf1737c544894facf6e77cd92788ae49d884ca931882d34e37b47d32</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kiss</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/y7b1n</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Um, Blackberries can run  Exchange, too..they've been doing it for years.  Nonetheless, ignoring the iPhone was just another mistake brought on by a culture that eventually started to imitate the markets it dominated - the notoriously insular government  and enterprise sectors, who both abhor change unless it benefits the executives.  If Hines had any sense at all, he would immediately reorg the company into consumer, enterprise and cloud divisions.  Collaboration between the three would utilize the new optimized processes he speaks about.  Workers would no longer be punished for offering new ideas or pointing out weaknesses in any facet of the business.  Software-wise, RIM's biggest opportunity has been staring it in the face and somehow they don't see it.  BES could be retooled into a framework for building all-in-one cloud messaging, storage and collaboration solutions.  Services could be implemented by BES customers or RIM could provide cloud services itself (with a nice revenue stream to show for it).  Providing a full migration path for customers of Exchange and other such products would be a top priority.  As for the gadgets, the corporate devices would be able to take advantage of RIM's full complement of security and groupware options while the &lt;i&gt;consumer&lt;/i&gt; line would focus on multimedia and all the fluff that's selling smartphones right now.  The consumer devices would be able to access the "non-hardened" portions of the Blackberry cloud ecosystem.  These phones would also be cheaper than their gov-biz cousins.  Sure, the whole "dual mode" Blackberry thing (can't remember what their marketing term is) was kind of neat, but its not the best answer IMO.  The users personal and work lives need to be separate but it should be handled transparently.  I shouldn't have to switch my phone to "work mode"..it should be smart enough to know what I want from it and how it should handle everything.  By taking this approach, the secure BB's could become the most capable smartphones on the market.  They could have all the fun n' games but also a wing-tipped layer of dedicated and secure productivity just beneath the surface, ready to kick in as required.  These "super" Blackberries would ideally be of absolute top-level build quality, with no compromises.  History shows that those who need such a device WILL pay for it, esp. when someone elses' money is involved.  Who knows - maybe these uberphones could even make Blackberry a status symbol once again.  Meanwhile, the rest of the market could enjoy cheaper phones and tablets that would be on par with Android devices of similar price range.  Without all of the security and other hard-core requirements, their software  could be updated more often, keeping pace with the competition.  This also opens the door to running a non-centralized (and of course, less secure) BBM on other platforms, or at least making it interoperable with some existing chat standards like Gtalk/AIM, WIM/Yahoo, whatever).  This also eliminates many of the Headaches associated with countries who demand access to BBM for security or political reasons: if the mass market "funberries" are readily hackable by governments, they can simply Ban the secure types from sale in their territories rather than demanding the key to RIM's local servers.  I have no doubt that half the reason despotic regimes require this is because it lets them read private messages coming &lt;b&gt;into&lt;/b&gt; their nations as well as those sent by citizens.  Of course, the overriding concern in the short term is developer interest.  If the Android player for Blackberry works out well, there's no reason that RIM could not only survive but actually prosper as a trinity of interdependent divisions.  They should already be moving beyond an emulator and working on a true Android compatibility layer for QNX.  The native environment underneath could be the domain of hardened BB apps.

Hines is right: you can't be all things to all people, at least not with a single product.  However, the consumer line can be a subset of the professional series.  It &lt;b&gt;could&lt;/b&gt; work, and it would definitely be a huge distinction for a company who's relied on a nice keyboard and trackpad for a bit too long.  Oh, and a pet peeve that other QWERTY users might understand: BBs need an ALT key on both sides, just like the shift key is.  It would make typing so much nicer.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zoqw1</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/nw4s</id></website><link>http://betanews.com/2012/03/29/lifelines-for-a-dying-blackberry-integrating-re-branding-licensing/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:50:55+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T04:00:03+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3siwz</id><link>http://betanews.com/2012/03/29/lifelines-for-a-dying-blackberry-integrating-re-branding-licensing/#comment-480223670</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8zmz9</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>