<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/152345/post/127953127/comment/329448468</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>No one makes a move to stop him in our government, not our senate or our congress, this black ape shits on the Constitution and our Bill of Rights every day! Even the judges are all bought , This corruption is because the American people will not stand and say this is enough! We write comments here, maybe even as I have wrote countless letters to our Congress Men and Senators, which in this state is a joke as ours drop to there knees to give this Criminal Illegal President head every time he comes into the state to commits more crimes and treason against the American People. The government builds massive concentration camps ran by there FEAMA agency which should be illegal to operate any way, Home land security is a joke, a against the American people agency set up to kill the people, I for one fully believe there FEAMA camps are provided with killing gas chambers from masses of people and furnaces to Burn the bodies and our Government fully intends to use them and NATO troops now stationed in the United States in our now Closed and Open military bases awaiting orders to begin there 4:00 AM  against Americans now on there so called Red lists who are to be taken and killed. those resisting killed by these foreign NATO and Hired Blackwater mercenaries on the Spot!  The corruption is to the very core of this  government, big money and business, foreign and domestic is at its root, We have been sold out, Yes I too believe about 50 years ago it started, You will be a slave, maybe with the right thinking you all ready are, you have no real say in any thing, the dollar you work for is worthless, you slave to earn a living and they tell you what that dollar will buy, Since Obummer the Traitor came to office our Dollar has dropped in value by half, so now you spend twice what you did for food, power, fuel and TAXES they just doubled your Taxes and you did not say a word!!!!! they gave trillions away to foreign country&amp;#039;s many who don&amp;#039;t like us Look at all the Muslim Mosque we are paying for being built around the world for one small percent of the money this Communist supporting Muslim illegal President has given to other nations and foreign people, He works with our hiding it that he is giving away our nation to any who will inter threw our open southern border and we say and do nothing! yet unlike our grand parents who had to pay for there kids and lively hood, these Illegal Invaders you pay for threw your taxes and social services which are financed by your taxes and we welcome them in with open arms as they have 13 children pre family which then join the criminal American down thrown organisations now allowed to operate in America, such as SM13 and the NEW Black Panthers, and just how many other white hating groups that sprout up, And they tell us we owe them something, I think not!      Writing our senators and congress bought  men and women does nothing, it is time to Act! or die! your choice slave.  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:152345:127953127</id><idPostId>127953127</idPostId><idBlogId>152345</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:152345</id><idBlogId>152345</idBlogId><link>http://www.impeachobamacampaign.com</link><displayName>Impeach Obama Campaign</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.impeachobamacampaign.com/careless-whispers-reveal-obamas-true-intentions-to-destroy-america/</link><displayName>Careless Whispers Reveal Obama’s True Intentions To Destroy America</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-01T19:49:32.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:152345:127953127:329448468</id><link>http://www.impeachobamacampaign.com/careless-whispers-reveal-obamas-true-intentions-to-destroy-america/#IDComment329448468</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T19:49:32.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Careless Whispers Reveal Obama’s True Intentions To Destroy America by Guest</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>d41d8cd98f00b204e9800998ecf8427e</idEmailMd5><displayName>Guest</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>Guest commented on &lt;a href="http://www.impeachobamacampaign.com/careless-whispers-reveal-obamas-true-intentions-to-destroy-america/"&gt;Careless Whispers Reveal Obama’s True Intentions To Destroy America&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>