<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/minngq/update/2012-03-23T13:02:18/5e65a11b80049ee3c8dfecf68029c7d49ffb4c7860602a192f959a6835dfd705</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Wow. This is so real.  I have played online games with the "leerers" for a few years, and I can tell you they think you are supposed to enjoy their leering. They have no idea how it feels to be on the receiving end.  They are obsessing on sex and enjoying it, regardless of the effect on you.

My experience as a young woman was similar, though not as intense, because I did not live in the urban environment that you do. But I remember every leer, every pinch, every unwelcome comment.  The dehumanization aspect of it is wounding for an intelligent and ambitious woman. It made me "sexually Cold" towards the men I worked with, in a male dominated profession, for 25 years. But it also made me successful and a great teammate. 

The lingering resentment I have about it, is that I had to lock away my sexiness. I wanted to be taken seriously, so flirting was out of the question. I feel like I missed something there. But the tradeoff was well worth it.  Professional and intelligent men are generally good at self control. They will try to make you feel comfortable. I enjoy the company of men greatly, but I am  "one of the guys" to some extent.

We are still animals, with animal instincts and desires. At the same time, we have our complex intellects and cultures. The mix is not Always a comfortable one. 

I hope you use the energy from this to fuel your ambition to prove your worth. Try not to resent the men. They are just responding to their own desires and have poor social self control. I think letting them know it is unwelcome restores your sense of control.  So I would encourage you to do that whenever the situation allows it.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6d3dh2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/oisu</id></website><link>http://mystreetmybodymyright.tumblr.com/post/19651731625</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T17:31:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T17:02:18+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/minngq</id><link>http://mystreetmybodymyright.tumblr.com/post/19651731625#comment-474610951</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>