<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3uybz/post/2012-03-29T15:11:14</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3bsyz</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l2fal</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>You were there? No. You have no idea what happened to to state he is innocent of murder is ludicrous on your part. Your racist attitude by comparing this to Rodney King is disgusting.

Zimmerman has an arrest history of violence and assault, including assault on a police officer. He should never have been in any neighborhood watch position. 

He was told to stop following Trayvon by the police dispatcher and continued to do so anyway.

The video does not show any blood on his clothing. He claims he had a broken nose, he claims his head was smashed on the sidewalk, he claims Trayvon was on top of him pummeling him in the face, and he claims he shot him in self defense.

He has absolutely NO blood showing on the video. It is not possible to shoot at the range he claims he shot without blood spatter, even matter. I've never seen a broken nose that didn't Bleed profusely and swell, no blood on his face, or clothing, no black eyes, no swelling on his face. You can clearly see his head and there is no damage showing from the alleged battering against a sidewalk and almost need stitches.

There are audio tapes that do not match Zimmerman's account.

The mortician stated there are NO signs of scrapes, bruising or injuries to Trayvon's hands, which would not be the case if those hands had just committed Battery of the type Zimmerman claims.

One of the original officers wanted him charged with manslaughter, there were, oddly, some high ranking officials who responded when it was learned Zimmerman was in custody. Was that because his father is a former Judge in the area? 

If Zimmerman isn't arrested there may be riots but you need to watch something besides Fox because there are marches going on nationally and they are not black marches, people of all colors are marching. If Zimmerman is not arrested there will be a miscarriage of justice that is for sure. 

Your attitude and the manner in which you address this is a disgusting display of racism.

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z7l7e</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dneq</id></website><link>http://www.adn.com/2012/03/29/2397026/injuries-not-obvious-in-police.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:48:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:11:14+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3uybz</id><link>http://www.adn.com/2012/03/29/2397026/injuries-not-obvious-in-police.html#comment-479776118</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/814r8</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>