<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwp61l/update/2012-03-31T06:59:32/c25370e15a297800bd47aabbc270def5ad5cccb80f99cc6a0c3fe489cd3c374a</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I have a # of ideas that have been  around in my head guys/girls

1. A minecraft/tower defense style 4 player coop zombie mode similar, but different than epics upcoming Fortnite.

2. Guns that feature interchangeable barrels for variable long to short ranges

3. Removal of the Health Regen in favor of a light to near critical damage modeling system that effects player performance  on wound location.

4. Integration of a weapon condition meter that slowly drops round over round until the player, using points assessed by kills, reconditions the weapon in between rounds for superior performance 

5. A team based "Campaign" mode that compiles all team based objective modes onto areas of control on a 60's style Red vs. Blue Cold war map.

6. A new class based "Professional" multiplayer mode that locks a player permanently onto a single chosen class that can be upgraded into a branching system of abilities and skills 

7. Certain Killsteaks that feature a "Feint" command that would show the players attacking aircraft pass over the enemy without dropping any bombs or firing any guns. The aircraft would then quickly circle back and drop their munitions at the same, or a different location.

8. A new melee system that allows the player to opt out of using the knife in favor of hand to hand combat moves, that, Depending on the angle of attack, would either disable, disarm, or outright kill the player's enemy. Humilation bonuses would be added to the players score tally.

9. An intelligent match making system that analyses a players strong points and matches them up to a team with strong points that the player is weak in. This,theoretically,  would achieve a balancing effect allowing for better game play.

10. And lastly, for the sports minded, the football like "Trench" mode. This mode would allow two players to assemble, or buy, a set number of different troop types and strategically place them on opposite sides of a football sized trench filled field. Once a round starts, the players, back in their first person shoes, will simply be tasked to carry a suit case size nuke with their team to the enemies side and toss the nuke into a giant scoring bunker where it will explode for one point. The game will end once five nukes are tossed into the enemies bunker. Any team member carrying the nuke cannot fire back so they  must be protected. The nuke can also be passed forward but not back. If the enemy touches the players nuke, the nuke is out of play and therefore must be reset back to the players starting side. If players are killed in game, they will respawn after a set time; AI, once killed, are "downed" until the player moves next to them and revives their health. Nukes passes can also be shot out of the air by the opposing team thereby achieving a block effect and can cause the suitcase fly out of the sideline and out of play.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/674ld9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7d9s</id></website><link>http://games.ign.com/articles/122/1222065p1.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T01:13:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T10:59:32+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwp61l</id><link>http://games.ign.com/articles/122/1222065p1.html#comment-481737036</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/emlbm</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>