<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mko9fi/post/2012-03-26T15:39:36</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Kind of  topic, but worth a read to see what the snake Obama is planning to do to our country:

SEOUL, March 26 (Reuters) - President Barack Obama was  caught on camera
 on Monday assuring outgoing Russian President  Dmitry Medvedev he will 
have "more flexibility" to deal with  contentious issues like missile 
defense after the U.S.  presidential election.
                
Obama,
 during talks in Seoul, urged Moscow to give him  "space" until after 
the November ballot, and Medvedev said he  would relay the message to 
incoming Russian president Vladimir  Putin.
                
The 
unusually frank exchange came as Obama and Medvedev  huddled together on
 the eve of a global nuclear security summit  in the South Korean 
capital, unaware their words were being  picked up by microphones as 
reporters were led into the room.
                
U.S. plans for 
an anti-missile shield have bedeviled  relations between Washington and 
Moscow despite Obama's "reset"  in ties between the two former Cold War 
foes. Obama's Republican  opponents have accused him of being too open 
to concessions to  Russia on the issue.
                
Leaning 
toward Medvedev, Obama was overheard asking for time  - "particularly 
with missile defense" - until he is in a better  position politically to
  such issues.
                
"I understand your message about space," replied Medvedev,  who will hand over the presidency to Putin in May.
                
"This
 is my last election ... After my election I have more  flexibility," 
Obama said, expressing confidence he will win a  second term.
                
"I
 will transmit this information to Vladimir," said  Medvedev, Putin's 
protege and long considered number two in  Moscow's power structure.
                
The
 exchange, parts of it inaudible, was monitored by a  White House pool 
of television journalists as well as Russian  reporters listening live 
from their press center.
                
Russia strongly opposes the U.S.-engineered bulwark being  built in and around Europe against ballistic missiles.
                
The
 United States insists it is intended as protection  against a missile 
attack by countries such as Iran, but Russia   says it fears the system 
could weaken its nuclear deterrent.
                
The White 
House, initially caught Off-guard by  about the leaders' exchange, later
 released a statement  recommitting to implementing missile defense 
"which we've  repeatedly said is not aimed at Russia" but also 
acknowledging  election-year obstacles on the issue.
                
"Since
 2012 is an election year in both countries, with an  election and 
leadership transition in Russia and an election in  the United States, 
it is clearly not a year in which we are  going to achieve a 
breakthrough," U.S. deputy national security  adviser Ben Rhodes said.
                
"Therefore,
 President Obama and President Medvedev agreed  that it was best to 
instruct our technical experts to do the  work of better understanding 
our respective positions, providing  space for continued discussions on 
missile defense cooperation  going forward," he said.  	  	   (Reporting
 By Matt Spetalnick; Editing by Robert Birsel) </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r7c2r</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnm5</id></website><link>http://www.idahostatesman.com/2012/03/25/2050136/battle-over-obama-health-law-reaches.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-25T17:56:34+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T19:39:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mko9fi</id><link>http://www.idahostatesman.com/2012/03/25/2050136/battle-over-obama-health-law-reaches.html#comment-476672322</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/81cbg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>