<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3jl1q/update/2012-03-29T18:23:59/7e26ebabeb4e34abe3a19eb81b0dc734cd3b778a895c97477d553e9c04c37f0b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>To Mr. Zimmerman (and anyone else reading this) I would like to begin by saying, “I know."  If I could  out to anyone right now, I'd actually Reach out to Mr. Zimmerman with those same words and a mountain of empathy.  "I know" is my qualifying statement and it's because I know what it is like to serve a minority community (black, African American, Nubian, WHATEVER...)  "I know" what it is like to go unappreciated for my commitment to their service.

Did I say unappreciated?  I meant hated.
 
"I know" what it is like to serve a minority community (black) with a last name on my name tag which never showed up on their minority approved list.
 
"I know" because I am half "Hispanic" (brown, Mexican, Latino, WHATEVER....) and my last name is German.  (OK white people, leave the room now.)
 I know what reverse racism is all about.  It's uglier than racism.  Racism leads people to profile or label, but reverse racism is actually a bit more insidious.  It layers itself and makes everybody responsible.  

Reverse racism causes other "non-minorities" to turn their backs on you when the Heat is on, Mr. Zimmerman.  
Reverse racism also allows minorities to stand ground against an established society until everyone in that society suffers.  By the way, did you serve in a minority community Mr. Zimmerman?
 
My point is this:
EVERYBODY falls back on LABELING, (OR PROFILING) and EVERYBODY gets Burned when they stand too close to the fire.  Case in point:  the article is by Mallory Simon (hot) and backing writer John Couwels (mmmm.... not-so-hot.).  

Mallory, you used Soledad O'Brien's piece like a doormat then walked in a Burning room, but that is something between you, your editor and your readers.  John, you are too busy primping at Starbucks and sharing your accolades, when you should be busy helping the youngsters get it right.
 
Now, with that said, SANFORD FLORIDA (and her reputation) can stand on her own merit. The fact of the matter is Sanford is predominantly white and "George Bush just don't care".  
 
Oh, wait a minute.  That was an entirely different news segment.
 
But what about CNN and the people it so willingly lends itself to?  LOOK and pay attention to the point you are trying to solicit.  A death didn't divide the town.  (Even I know that.)  People divide the town.  That's right; I said it because "I know".  Sanford is predominantly white but "white is bad" so we lean on the resources of the black community to straighten this out because we all know white people are bloodthirsty, right?

So, I ask you Mallory, and you CNN and all of the readers out there?  Do Mr. Zimmerman and guys like us get the "double whammy" from people like you, just because we're half Hispanic?  See, the funny thing about a label (in this case)  is not the label itself, but how media can be manipulated so easily by minority groups and their leaders (Al Sharpton).  In order to place a label on a guy like Zimmerman, Sharpton and participants sweep Zimmerman through the media kitchen, past the Judge and jury oven and serve him on millions of plates throughout America and the world.  Anybody in the CNN corner taking the time to read up through the 3rd sentence of this article has to admit that Zimmerman was labeled "HISPANIC", but why?  "I know" his last name screams WHITE, yet he isn't "HISPANIC" and he isn't "WHITE" so, what is he?  

Any thoughts on this matter?

I am sincerely sorry about Trayvon and I would like to offer my condolence to his family.  He was a beautiful young man but we will never know his future and it is for that reason we should all acknowledge OUR loss.  His death shouldn't equate to a point/counterpoint battle between minorities and "the powers that be".  It should be an opportunity to heal, not divide, the scar tissues of this country.

Will disorder and misconduct (RIOT) solve anything?  Is that what social justice is all about?
 
In a truly democratic society, the decision of this matter would remain in the hands of the jury until the Judge reads the verdict.  But in THIS matter, the decision has already bypassed the jury and the people get to decide, THANKS to CNN and all other media conglomerates that choose to spread fuel and fan the fire.  

The news media should take 3 steps back from the fire and slap each other for bringing society closer to discord.  Then you ALL should slit your wrists and take a "blood oath" together, promising each other to report factual news responsibly.  You are the real threat.  (OK, white people come back.)
 </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ztxr5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/us/florida-teen-shooting-sanford-divided/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:29:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:23:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3jl1q</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/us/florida-teen-shooting-sanford-divided/index.html#comment-479966707</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zz7ro</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>