<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7f1q/post/2012-03-30T15:27:29</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3k0xa</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a21x9</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I thought of either doing the same or buying an entire mountain in Colorado or New Mexico, at least in the Rocky mountains. The problem with an island is a bad tsunami wiping it out. Imagine buildiing a nice spacious home on top of a mountain and not having any means of getting to it outside of a helipad. All self maintaine with at least a couple back up power supplies including a wind turbin and solar panels on the roof.  You could just sit up there sipping on a cool one by your Heated pool and shoot the world the birdie. The ATF would probably accuse you of being a "suspected home grown terrorist" though and send in an apache helicopter to blast you Off the mountain. You know, like they did to Randy Weaver at Rubyridge and at Mount Carmel with the Branch Davidians. Can't have anybody being self sufficient in this great democracy..duhh!!! Now if you have more than a two week supply of food, you're a suspected terrorist. God help you if you have more than two guns and six boxes of ammo for each. I still think the mountain top hideaway is a fun idea. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zub2h</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/8nmt</id></website><link>http://ksat.preview.ib-prod.com/pns/servlet/page/view/pns-ant/lifestyle/-/477938/9765956/-/jpcnlg/-/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T21:57:15+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:27:29+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7f1q</id><link>http://ksat.preview.ib-prod.com/pns/servlet/page/view/pns-ant/lifestyle/-/477938/9765956/-/jpcnlg/-/index.html#comment-481103299</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gro05</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>