<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwc82p/post/2012-03-30T04:22:12</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kd70</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Thanks for the thoughtful comment! Regarding your opinion of the doctor, "hindsight is  20/20" so it's  a bit unfair to judge when we weren't there: but I personally think their steps seemed appropriate. Firstly, the baby in the first doctor visit sounded like she had what 99% of babies have on these common visits: a very slight Cold, almost Always caused by a virus. The issue is later when the baby was admitted -- but there still isn't an automatic need to give a child antibiotics on admission, because many times it's a viral infection and the child simply needs supportive care as an inpatient. I assume (but don't know) that the doctors did a CBC on admit which didn't show any raging bacterial infection (no high neutrophils), so antibiotics would not be indicated.

But let's try to get back to the main issue, that this child got pertussis from someone else: it didn't have to be from an unvaccinated person, by the way. The pertussis vaccine fades away after a few years which is why a Tdap booster is now recommended for adults (please, everyone, get a Tdap if you haven't gotten one and you have infants at home!)

And I disagree a bit with your conclusion that "Parents also have the choice not to vaccinate, appearently only as long as their kids do not catch these diseases. If they end up ill, families are punished, the hard way", because you leave out a crucial component: it's not so much their own kids that are punished, it's the tiny infants that we worry about -- because they get sick from unvaccinated others! This is the major issue: there many documented cases of infants, too young to be vaccinated, who got sick from hanging out in a doctor's office and catching an infection from a sick unvaccinated kid next to them. THIS is why some peds doctors are really scared and now firing patients, because they worry about these nightmare stories happening in their own waiting room.

If you look at this issue from a community-level "it takes a village" approach, I'm sorry if this sounds harsh but it is selfish for parents not to fully vaccinate their children -- because they are relying on the other 90% of the population to be vaccinated; in other words, they are assuming their own kids are protected because "everyone else" has the vaccine so the chance of getting infection is rare. For any vaccine to really work, "herd immunity" is needed where &gt;90% of the population is vaccinated. 

I seriously doubt we'd be having these debates if something like polio made a raging comeback. Only a few decades ago Drs Salk and Sabin were international heroes because they developed vaccines against this devastating disease. Now we have some parents thinking a new doctor hero is Dr Andrew Wakefield, who for years was the #1 quoted doctor for anti-vaccine groups and yet whose research not only has been completely discredited and recused from the journal, but who lost his license to practice medicine last year in the UK -- and yet now runs around America preaching the same message. Very sad. What happened to the American love of science and progress?</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zhsma</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/o5vj</id></website><link>http://www.myhealthbeijing.com/2012/03/should-doctors-fire-parents-who-refuse-vaccines-for-their-children/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:45:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T08:22:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwc82p</id><link>http://www.myhealthbeijing.com/2012/03/should-doctors-fire-parents-who-refuse-vaccines-for-their-children/#comment-480512765</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/m3qz7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>