<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m02pa3/post/2012-03-31T14:44:28</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Race arsonist Sharpton is getting old and probably looking at the Martin case as his last real so called opportunity to create positive change.  The problem is that he doesn't create positive change but adds fuel to the fire with his prideful race filled speeches that embellish on the facts.  His most recent speech is directed at African American mothers and is laced with fear and Anxiety.  It's sad how black mothers will soak this fear filled speech up and believe every last word as if it were true.  Why does Sharpton only come out of the woodwork on cases that Gain national attention?  It's sad that we now have a guy who has a mob of people literally out to create chaos!  His title as a minister is a complete joke.  Did Jesus teach anything remotely close to what Sharpton preaches?  This case is the absolute worst case possible to bring up the race problems in America.  A Hispanic Democrat gets attacks and makes a bad decision to use a weapon in a situation that  may or may not have been necessary?  I can't think of a worse case to use!!!!!!  At least pick a case where the majority of America agrees with you!  I hope this backfires in his face so bad that we never hear from this idiot ever again!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67tcrx</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rlyt</id></website><link>http://visiontoamerica.org/8973/al-sharpton-encourages-increased-civil-disobedience/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T23:53:15+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T18:44:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m02pa3</id><link>http://visiontoamerica.org/8973/al-sharpton-encourages-increased-civil-disobedience/#comment-482087445</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>