<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ewilci/update/2012-01-26T07:56:16/fdee23891d721399cb69ae7a38008f6ee7851bec92c1ed14abebd631b7b01fe2</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Clearly some supporters of the EDL are racist football fans.  However, hey also have gay, Jewish and black suporters.  

You can see black people at their demos, but you can also see guys that look like football fans. Are football fans a group that should be excluded from the political process?  Does being a football fan make one racist?

There is a video,on Youtube, of the EDL Burning a Nazi flag.  A black bloke sets fire to it.  Some anti-facist made an edited version that makes it look like the EDL is waving the flag.  So, it is difficult to say what the EDL really are.

Part of this problem is class.  What are white working class people doing having a political opinion?  Why are black people and gays supporting them?  This is not supposed to happen.  Some educated liberals may even find it offensive.

We alll know the working class was abolished by the welfare state, and anyway there is New Labour to think and Act for them.  While in Denmark we have Gucci socialism and experts.

We need to the left to take on issues that have been left to groups like the EDL and the DDL.  When protesting aganinst the EDL/DDL carry gay flags, stop chants calling for the killing of Jews, say no sharia here and address the fears of peolpe who feel threatened by Islamification.

Obviously Muslims and all others should be free to follow their religion.  And the rest of us free from following others' religions.  Danish culture comes first, but does not have to be at the expense of one's private life.  Living in Denmark I drive on the wrong side of the road and I expect others to do the same.

No to all racism
No to all homophobia
Equal rights for all

</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yaz74w</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/bx7u</id></website><link>http://cphpost.dk/news/international/racist-network-hold-rally-aarhus</link><postedTime>2012-01-20T13:26:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-01-26T12:56:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ewilci</id><link>http://cphpost.dk/news/international/racist-network-hold-rally-aarhus#comment-421319370</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lkgwj</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-01-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>