<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3iid0/update/2012-03-29T21:48:24/616b453a7c825f6fe6e37805ea3e5c5bd76886c6559b4eb0872a744e6af97f4b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Some of us have honestly looked at something called "facts" and what appears to be "logical conclusions" based on those "facts"......while others (like Jesse Jackson) appear to respond by "emotions" that are not entirely based on the "facts" and the "logical conclusions."
 
For instance, some people see an Armed White/Latino Dude and an Unarmed Dead Black Kid.....and may have made up a wild tale that is not based on Reality, Facts, or Logical Conclusions at all.
 
Where does Jesse Jackson get the idea that the Armed White/Latino Dude simply shot the kid in Cold blood with No Justification at all? Did Jesse Jackson WITNESS the event? No. Is Jesse Jackson relying on the "facts" and "evidence" the Police observed.....or is Jesse Jackson just Making Stuff Up???
 
The POLICE responded to the incident, NOT Jesse Jackson. It was the POLICE that conducted the initial investigation and follow-up investigation....and the POLICE apparently came up with a different chain of events that lead to the shooting and death than Jesse Jackson did.
 
This is the chain of events that was reported....the chain of events that the police looked into....the chain of events that lead the police to determine that NO Probable Cause Exists -at this point - to arrest Zimmerman and charge him with a CRIME: 
 
Zimmerman saw a "suspicious" person and called the police while following him. Apparently the police told Zimmerman to NOT continue to follow the "suspicious" person.....and either Zimmerman complied and/or lost track of the person anyway. Zimmerman was walking back to his vehicle when the "suspicious" person approached Zimmerman, confronted Zimmerman, and (according to Zimmerman) punched Zimmerman, knocking Zimmerman to the ground, at which time (according to Zimmerman) the "suspicious" person jumped on top of him(Zimmerman) and began to BEAT Zimmerman.
 
If - IF - what Zimmerman says is true, at that time the "suspicious" person was no longer just a "suspicious" person.....but was a Criminal actively engaged in a Criminal : Assault and Battery.
 
If - IF - what Zimmerman says is true, neither Zimmerman or any Victim MUST "take a beating" from a Criminal. Zimmerman had every RIGHT to use whatever FORCE was NECESSARY to IMMEDIATELY Protect His Life from Further Injuries and/or Death.
 
Keep in mind that it was the POLICE that responded to investigate the incident....NOT Jesse Jackson or any Racist Black Power Militant Organization.....nor any of those who later wore "hoodies" in a show of support for an apparent hoodlum. 
 
Apparently the POLICE Investigation lead the POLICE to conclude that the chain of events as described by Zimmerman....likely did occur.....and, as a result, the Police do not arrest Victims of a Crime "just beause" arresting Zimmerman makes Racist Bigots happy.
 
Obviously there are a few "facts" - along with answers to many questions - that hopefully will come out in due time.......that "we" should have the patience to wait for instead of simply jumping to what could be, or may not be, erroneous allegations.
 
(1) Were there any Injuries on Zimmerman that were consistent with his story of being jumped?
 
(2) Were any photographs taken that day.....and a few days later (bruises take a day of so to "fully develop)?
 
(3) Were there any scrapes, injuries, marks on the fists or hands of the...deceased....that would be consistent with Zimerman's story of the...deceased....punching him and beating him? Were any photographs taken of any such indicators?
 
(4) Were the CLOTHING of both persons consistent with the allegations of being punched, knocked to the ground, and being beaten while on the ground? Did the....deceased's....knees or tops of the shoes show indication of contact and rubbing on the ground? Did Zimmerman's back show signs of wear consistent with being on his back and struggling with an assailant????
 
(5) Were there any witnesses that might have seen even a glimpse of any alleged "fight"????
 
(6) The report indicates that at least one "witness" heard someone yelling for help.....and the police concluded that it was ZIMMERMAN who did that....and NOT the....deceased.
 
If there is one thing that more than one Civil Rights Activist MUST be FULLY AWARE OF....its is NOT to, in the Name of Civil Rights, VIOLATE the Civil Rights of another by jumping to conclusions and railroading a lynch mob attitude to demand an arrest when no arrest may actually be warranted.
 
I...remember....something.....years ago.....about a young black girl crying "rape"....in New York, wasn't it?....and some of these Same Civil Rights Leaders....railroaded a lynch mob attitude over a accusation that, it turned out, was.....made up....a falsehood....an untruth....a lie.
 
They had better.....pray to God....that they are not making the same mistake....yet again.
 
 </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zfnq0</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/55w0</id></website><link>http://blogs.denverpost.com/eletters/2012/03/29/florida-shooting-raises-specter-racism/17211/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T23:49:01+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:48:24+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3iid0</id><link>http://blogs.denverpost.com/eletters/2012/03/29/florida-shooting-raises-specter-racism/17211/#comment-480129443</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>