<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tptq/post/2012-03-29T10:18:21</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Seems the "sagacious" David Brooks forgot the other, more prevalent thought with which successful people begin: "I want to make a lot of money."  And politicians as "arbiters of justice"?!  What country are you living in?  Talk about Orwellian...do you  trust your betters to make all the tough decisions for you?

It would be great if goofy liberal women would figure out that they're totally entitled to shriek about keeping eeeeevil Republican men away from their uteri provided that they stop demanding that the same Republican men pay for what goes on in their uteri.  News flash: when you demand that everyone around you pay for your "most private decision," IT IS NO LONGER A PRIVATE DECISION.

Why don't these women nag their sundry sex partners to pony up the dough to facilitate their "most private decisions"?  I know: because it's so much easier to crawl over to government begging for (or in the case of these harpies, having the gall to demand) a handout.  After all, better to force people you don't know to subsidize your sex life, right?  That way you don't have to look anyone in the eye!

P.S. The female voters who ushered in the Republican takeover in the House LIKE what Republicans are doing.  These women understand that birth control is a private responsibility, and they don't want hordes of unknown men (and women) Reaching into hordes of unknown wallets to take part unwillingly in such oh-so-sacred "most private decisions."

P.P.S. Rush Limbaugh is doing just fine.  (http://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/style/limbaugh-sees-Heat-over-comments-turn-down-to-a-simmer/2012/03/28/gIQAspEKhS_print.html)</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hgxq6</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/z6bb</id></website><link>http://nyunews.com/opinion/2012/03/28/28michalos/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T06:38:28+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:18:21+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tptq</id><link>http://nyunews.com/opinion/2012/03/28/28michalos/#comment-479521927</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>