<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xnii/post/2012-03-29T13:56:01</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>"...but the president has invited this criticism by elevating several local controversies to national scandals for political ."- Noah 

The Gates controversy first addressed by the President in a news conference focused on the push for healthcare reform.
http://www.nytimes.com/2009/07/23/us/politics/23obama.html?pagewanted=all
Obama answering a question from Lynn Sweet at the end of that conference.
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w-e549qdS8Y
Both the Fluke and the Martin incidents very public, hot and Heated before the President demonstrated leadership. 
As Limbaugh said about the call to  Fluke, “The president called her to make sure she’s okay. What is she, 30 years old? Thirty years old, a student at Georgetown law who admits to having so much sex that she can’t afford it anymore.”
Tommy reported on the Daily Caller's assertion, "Obama and the White House have previously refrained from commenting on the case thus far. Following demands by the New Black Panthers and others on scene in Sanford, Fla. that the White House get involved, Obama jumped into the fight. When first asked about the case, White House press secretary Jay Carney essentially declined comment, offering a boilerplate statement of condolence to Martin’s family."
The President lacks the ability to launch the media storm de jour. They are media created "national scandals".  When he answers questions or calls a publicly assaulted women or sympathizes with the family of a dead boy he is not "elevating local controversies" for "political Gain". To assert as much is rotten. As rotten as the misdirection and spite that come from Limbaugh and the Daily Caller. Horrible stuff.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zt7oi</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tz1k</id></website><link>http://www.mediaite.com/online/families-of-british-teens-murdered-in-u-s-lash-out-at-obama-white-house-for-ignoring-them/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:22:18+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:56:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xnii</id><link>http://www.mediaite.com/online/families-of-british-teens-murdered-in-u-s-lash-out-at-obama-white-house-for-ignoring-them/#comment-479697366</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dhq1x</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>