<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/migeer/post/2012-03-22T15:59:55</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Soul Coughing remains one of the bands I listen and re-listen to with no shame while many others of that time have sunk to the bottom of the 90s sea. I was able to see them before they broke up (at one of those college shows that also featured Everclear and a pre-Fergie Black Eyed Peas) and later saw Mike Doughty solo a number of times, once even calling out my favorite song from the SC- - "Janine" which to my amazement and delight he actually played(!!!)

He  came Off as a pretty likable character when onstage but I have heard stories of backstage snobbery that jive with facts spilled on the pages of this book.  Co-workers of mine  (Borders Books, RIP) returned from the Newport Folk Fest with horror stories about how he refused to sign anything SC related and demanded they only sell his CD-Rs for Skittish.

Like my own signed copy of Skittish, my interest in his "small rock" has been lost.  Too many slicked up re-workings of those rough diamonds for me to stand... That having been said, I'll be pouring over the pages of this memior, embracing my inner 14 year old and remembering when.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yti2l</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/agg8</id></website><link>http://boingboing.net/2012/03/22/mike-doughty-indie-rocker-re.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T13:01:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T19:59:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/migeer</id><link>http://boingboing.net/2012/03/22/mike-doughty-indie-rocker-re.html#comment-473892995</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zdq8j</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>