<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mztu7q/update/2012-02-24T00:06:28/23cada3a27074bb0ab44b3b392a8dfc01e7be26bf0e8ac70fc82c19cbbcc257c</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I need to waste a little time with a prologue/monologue on size. Why is it for reviewers to find a concept so hard to grasp. Do you buy an SUV, then complain that it is bigger than a car ? Or a Ford truck, then complain it is not as easy to park as a corolla ? A corolla and an SUV and a Ford truck will all fit inside a garage. So will the Note in a pocket or in your hand. If you are a male about 6ft +/- a few, for eg with normal sized hands and use a size L shirt, the note will fit in your shirt pocket without coming out. It will flush with your pocket and someone wont be able to see the top of the phone. Unless it is a tiny/small shirt pocket. It will not fit in skinny jeans or spandex. 

Have any of you clueless bashers realized that the device is NOT a phone alone. I would fully agree that it would be stupid to hold a  plain "phone" with that size in today's world. But this is a SMARTPHONE. So it should be logically acceptable, given that it is not really that big as its being made out. 

I think all reviewers need to review this device for what it is. A large phone. It should be a review with that AS A GIVEN. And move on from there. There is just the Dell Streak (failed), Note (market success in international markets; US remains to be seen) &amp; the upcoming LG Vu (4:3 wider body and more difficult to wield) in this new category.

For people WHO INTENTIONALLY want this kind of a device, you need to rate the device in that category.

I own this phone. I LOVE IT. Now I see why people would say iOS looks boring and dated. I thought they were being excessive and immature till I started adding widgets and saw how useful they were. And my  life has not suffered btw.

How a reviewer must review this device :
1. Review it in its category of device - phablet if you will.
2. Review it then without the bias of comparing it to a non-phablet device. How is the perf, Battery life, display etc.. without talking again and again about the damn size.

Try the device yourself in your own hands and pockets. Don't base it on how it looks on others with your bias filter predetermined. You might be surprised at how easy it is to use than you think it would be. And how gorgeous the display is. Not just colors. Even tiny text is easy to read (the resolution/285 ppi is very good for reading text; you won't care about the 331 ppi) . The first time you see thin white lines like the intro screen of Dolphin HD (which has white line arrows showing tips set against a blurred background) your jaw will drop. It can only be seen in reality. No amt of screen grabs on the internet will show it on your monitor. It is stunning. You can see white text looking gorgeous in many places. But in some, it is just OUTSTANDING. You have to find some egs. like I mentioned above to see it more pronounced. Then you'll know.

Oh, Dolphin HD (with a plug in) with a simple side swipe shows me a tiny switch. I can simply click it and I instantly can switch to the Desktop view for that site. Flip the device in landscape and enjoy. 

S-PEN (Stylus)
This uses EMR (electro magnetic resonance) which means &lt;u&gt;you can use it WITH GLOVES&lt;/u&gt; or in Cold conditions in winter where your Cold fingers would NOT work on an iPhone (where it needs Heat).
You can use the stylus if you are an artist.
You can use the stylus if you just want to have fun
You can use the stylus if you want to annotate a clip and email it
You can use the stylus if you want to precisely cut out a shirt or dress, overlay it and resize in on your picture and see how you look in that shirt for eg.
You can use the stylus where you need precision that a finger does not provide.
It is NOT a throwback to the PDA, morons.  You do NOT HAVE to use it.


Got it ? Moving on.

&lt;b&gt;
Summary : 
If you're a big talker and do not have giant hands or a BT headset, you may not like this phone. If you care about what the uneducated and biased masses think (initially) about this phone, it might not be for you. 
If you are more of a data user than a voice user and want all that you consume on the internet to be enjoyed in a more sane size, this is perfect. If you do not want to spend money on a tablet with an additional data plan and carry the tablet everywhere, this is perfect. If you want VERY good build quality, good performance, a stunning display and go in with the full knowledge about its size, it is perfect. Just know that you won't be able to ONE-HAND TEXT and WALK at the same time without risking dropping the device. That is the only salient point regd size. Not about how it looks. It looks fantastic and it looks practical as long as you understand what the complete situation is. It's an SUV of phones, not a Corolla and not a Ford-350 truck either.

Lastly, let me remind you that the genius aspect of the iPhone was to get rid of WASTED SPACE with the keyboard so that you could have a more PRODUCTIVE (larger) screen. That was 2007. Welcome to 2012. The bar has been raised.
&lt;/b&gt;

If you're a woman, you have an advantage of carrying purses and have a choice of very nice cases to go with it. You can choose trendy or business woman. Guys can choose to go with wallet replacements like the SGP Valentinus leather wallets for eg. They will also carry your credit cards and out you go, independent man/woman. Don't be a lemming. Choose your own path.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yfd1lr</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/g7x</id></website><link>http://venturebeat.com/2012/02/23/samsungs-galaxy-note-is-big-bold-and-hopelessly-dorky-review/</link><postedTime>2012-02-23T14:01:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-24T05:06:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mztu7q</id><link>http://venturebeat.com/2012/02/23/samsungs-galaxy-note-is-big-bold-and-hopelessly-dorky-review/#comment-447601375</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8l3jn</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>