<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwiy7w/update/2012-03-31T08:15:42/a87df6cb38941c99424cf721a4cd6ad7f96752feb76cb456a08b54e46f285359</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>For the sake of brevity, I've only pasted part of the the following article, which, I should point out, relates to second-hand smoke in the workplace, not in the home.

Nevertheless, its claim regarding the fumes produced by family barbecues should alarm those anti-smoking, better-than-thou types, who seem to think that they can do anything they like and be free from blame.

Their general saint-like demeanour should - if they take the trouble to read this - be a little tarnished the next time they expose little Johnny or Mary to the family barbecue, or their fellow humans to the exhaust from their unnecessarily large 4x4. Those wishing to read it in full, can following the link at the end:

&lt;b&gt;Health impact of secondhand smoke on bar staff&lt;/b&gt;

For many, the clinching argument in favour of a Ban on SIPPs [smoking in public places] was the supposed evidence that SHS [second-hand smoke] presented a measurable health risk to those 
exposed to it.

There is an enormous amount of published research on the possible health risks of SHS, showing varying and contradictory 
results.

There is an ongoing epidemiological debate about the risks, if any, of exposure to SHS. Probably the main report affecting public policy on SIPS in the United Kingdom was the Scientific committee on Tobacco and Health (SCOTH) report published in November 2004. 

SCOTH concluded that the increased risk of contracting lung cancer for those exposed to SHS was 24% and for heart disease was 25%.

Even if these numbers are accepted, they are utterly trivial compared to the risks we are willing to accept – or expose others to - in many other areas of our lives.

For example, according to Cancer Research UK, the increased risk of contracting lung cancer if you work in a profession that regularly exposes you to diesel fumes is 47% - twice that of exposure to SHS assumed in SCOTH.

Those living in areas with high levels of nitrogen oxide (usually caused by vehicle emissions) have an increased chance of about 33% of contracting lung cancer.

Workers in the ship-building or construction industry have been estimated to have an increased chance of contracting lung cancer of up to 50% - twice that assumed for workers exposed to SHS by SCOTH.

One study even suggests that women who don’t smoke, but have a wood-Burning fire at home, may have an increased risk of lung disease in excess of 300%.

A French study in 2003 suggested a typical barbecue in one’s garden releases the same number of dioxins that would be emitted from 220,000 cigarettes.

So, even if one accepts the SCOTH report’s numbers on the increased risk suffered by those working in smoke-filled pubs and 
clubs, these risks pale into utter insignificance compared to risks we readily and unquestionably accept elsewhere.

Source: http://www.amendthesmokingban.com/our_case/</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/679wlt</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/health/healthnews/9177856/Government-release-new-hard-hitting-anti-smoking-advert.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T10:23:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T12:15:42+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwiy7w</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/health/healthnews/9177856/Government-release-new-hard-hitting-anti-smoking-advert.html#comment-481782094</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hsax3</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>