<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mfb8ut/update/2012-03-15T16:05:06/877f253b0ee3db591d2405681d5e248a722090fc3026aa890504290f859215dd</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>"Priebus said in a statement sent by e-mail. 'Voters have a clear choice this November: continue down Barack Obama's path... or change direction with new leadership committed to reversing the Obama agenda that has Americans worse  than they were four years ago.'"
Worst  4 years ago??? Is Reince Priebus just lying because he thinks the public has no memory of recent events or is he completely insane?

This were terrible in Oct to Dec of 2008, just before Obama came in. That December alone millions were laid . The country was in a fruitless search for Bin Laden in Afghanistan. The banking system teetered on the brink of meltdown and the largest industries in the country faced extinction.

Obama din not start the bailouts of the bank.  He did not start the bailout of GM and Chrysler, nor did he start the wars in Iraq nor hunt for Osama Bin Laden -- that was George W. Bush.

What Mr. Obama did do was to finish all those things. He took the Heat for it, but he did finish them.

In short summery: GM still alive, Chrysler still alive, Bin Laden very dead, US out of Iraq, banks still around to power world economy.

If the Republican had their STATED way - the world would be in a permanent depression, we'd still be fighting two wars and gearing up for a third in Iran, there be one American automaker (if any), medicare eliminated, social security sold  to the private sector to plunder and Osama bin Laden would be very much alive and making more hate-fulled videos against our country.

No thank you, Mr. Priebus.  This is not the change I'd want. We are better Off than four years ago. We are going into half time and we are finally beginning to win, but only narrowly. You don't come back of the field in the second half with a different team and one that lost the last game at that. We will win this game with the team we have now and by a wide margin.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/65tftz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/15/politics/biden-speech/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-15T16:21:32+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-15T20:05:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mfb8ut</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/15/politics/biden-speech/index.html#comment-466283501</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8805r</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-15</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>