<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkporc/post/2012-03-26T16:34:12</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I find this ridiculous.  Companies are never short on "nay sayers."  Nor "yes men."  They're everywhere.  "Negative reaction to the new IPad would never have happened on Jobs' watch?"  C'mon. The press has hounded Apple since the doors were opened.  As soon as Steve's "reality distortion field" dims after each product announcement, there's all kinds of critical press.  Either a product fails to live up to expectations, or Apple has reportedly gone too far in its rejection of  "standards" like Flash or SCSI or ADB.  The presence of Steve Jobs has never once prevented negative reactions.  I'm sure there are many within Apple who are anxious about the future, as well they should be.  This industry is competitive to the point of being cut-throat, and it will take lots of ingenuity and savvy for Apple to retain its Spot on the pedestal, so concern is appropriate.  Shoot, Apple may make some humdingers for mistakes, but mistakes are part of taking risks, and no one can claim Apple hasn't taken risks or made mistakes in the past.  Just look to Macworld or Maclife for articles on Apple's biggest mistakes.  You'll see just how many goofs Apple has made over time, even on Jobs' watch.  I believe the claims in this article are totally unfounded.   </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rj0rd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ucz0</id></website><link>http://www.tvpredictions.com/apple032612.htm</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T09:16:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T20:34:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkporc</id><link>http://www.tvpredictions.com/apple032612.htm#comment-476721039</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>