<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw46y1/post/2012-03-30T17:31:38</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwtlny</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7l51</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>The killer threw the murder weapon away, maybe in the river as he biked back.the backyard was full of skull, blood and dna evidence. And the bone was absent of blood. As in being washed . The absense of of blood is one you can ask the killer as washing down the site for a day or 2 will get rid of most of it. The only unknown DNA was on the purse strap which the DNA expert admitted on the stand can come from cross contamination  ( someone Sneezing on it, hangin on the handle of the cart @ safeway, etc) . the clothing was never found. Mark is huge now, the crown had pics of him from 2000 when he was  150 lbs lighter. The killer drove 14km, then rode back disposing  articles along the way. (1 yellow glove, 3 others found in attic, wallet with money, watch, etc.) no robbery either. How do you kow it was mins after arriving home he called the brother in law? the timeline where there is no communication between is 830pm - 237 am. he could have been home at 11-12am as many many motorists did see a large cyclist. over 6 hrs to clean up, dispose, come back home, get the story right and start making calls. Not to mention the 8 years before charge to  story is 100%. Neighbours from regina testified he did ride in regina before he moved to wpg, and he did ride before from battlefords sask to kamloops bc in earlier years. so i don't think a casual rider, someone with experience , yes maybe fat back then but not nearly what you seen in the recent pics.   weight for the trail would be advantagous for him as it Ensures people like yourself don't believe the biking story. Remember this is a very smart man. Why would a stranger pick this home, with all the lights on, cars in garage, etc, when there were other nicer homes kitty corner to this one where it has already been said in court that no one was home and would have been an easier break in , whatever. And , why would a killer want to move a dead body? wouldn't they only want to get away? The only person that wouldn't want a body or crime to be discovered on their property is someone with something to hide. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67r6yn</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7m2w</id></website><link>http://www.winnipegsun.com/2012/03/30/rowbothams-sisters-stunned-at-stobbe-verdict</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:53:35+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:31:38+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw46y1</id><link>http://www.winnipegsun.com/2012/03/30/rowbothams-sisters-stunned-at-stobbe-verdict#comment-481223292</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lzbyu</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>