<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m937xc/update/2012-03-18T15:11:12/53863ccbe17870b7ba00d8013b0f3b461489c29efef5c81fe07fbdd2ccb1c75a</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9sr44</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l72cl</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>SeperatePeacenik
You like to chery pick my replies and edit them for your own use.The facts are these.You have badmouthed me at other blogs at the Atlantc site before[i believeit was Derek Thompsons. thats fine. I didnt lose much sleep over that.But when you  started calling me "lazy" and "racist" in Friday's thread, and when you left  41 replies to me[almost all that were insulting in tone]  then i percieved you as being insulting  to me

It should be noted that you are not the only liberal  at this blog. Most commenters here are liberal.And its very rare for me to get into a Heated exchange with anyone here. And ive left over 6,000 comments here at this blog.And the very few times i have gotten caught up in a Heated arguement here, both i  and the other commenter ended up apologising to each other .

I will not apologise to you however.Since the nastiness has been one way. To leave over  40 insulting comments to someone , on one single thread is  a very disturbing thing to do. If you want to do it, thats your choice. but it should be noted that about 4 different commenters yesterday and Friday called you out on it.And a couple more have done so today. 

I myself dont like to focus on getting "likes".But havent you noticed that not many people here are "liking " your comments.Its not because they dont agree with you politcally.Its because you are leaving angry comments that  add absolutly nothing to the conversation.  

Goodness knows, im no Saint.And have never claimed to be one.But i have Always tried my best to have good and polite debates and conversations here.Andi have generally been successful in doing so.Despite the fact that i am  often in disagreement with the vast majority of commenters here. Generally most of the conversations here lead me and other commenters to realise that there are areas where we agree on.And both i, and other comenters , try to at least try to understand the opinions that we disagree on.

You ,on the other hand, are not trying to find common ground with me.Nor are you trying to understand my opinions.Nor are you even trying to debate me. You are just trying to be arguementative for its own sake. 

Once again , you have left over 40comments  to me[ and counting] And i just saw that you left two more comments to me on  Friday's thread in the past 3 minutes. Your obsession with me is very disturbing</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6eahhy</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/eyjq</id></website><link>http://m.theatlantic.com/national/archive/2012/03/alexandra-pelosis-inane-attempt-to-offend-both-sides/254669/</link><postedTime>2012-03-17T23:02:55+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-18T19:11:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m937xc</id><link>http://m.theatlantic.com/national/archive/2012/03/alexandra-pelosis-inane-attempt-to-offend-both-sides/254669/#comment-468493095</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/amqoc</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-17</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>