<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ovoz/post/2012-03-29T19:25:27</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m32h2k</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5xhnv</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>one of JEFFERY DAHMER's last victims, a teenage boy, escaped, told police what dahmer had already done to him. DAHMER WHO WAS WHITE told police the teen was lieing. POLICE BELIEVED DAHMER, GAVE THE TEEN BACK TO DAHMER, DAHMER SEXUALLY ABUSED HIM, KILLED HIM, &amp; ATE HIM!
original police reports said nothing about a broken nose or head injuries. anyone familiar with a broken nose knows there is a whole lot of Bleeding. yet the murderer is not Bleeding, does not look hurt or like he's been in a life or death struggle as he and daddy judge claims!
this is how some of white america operates! this murderer's father, daddy judge, is clearly lieing for him &amp; is participating in this cover-up. seems daddy judge has been covering for his son for a long time. perhaps if he lets his violent murdering son grow up and take responsibility for his actions, this young man would be alive!"But there's so much hate that I - I've never been involved in hate, and George hasn't, and it's really unbelievable," said Zimmerman, who did not expose his face in the interview. "I just hope at one point everyone will go beyond the hate that they have." BECAUSE YOU ALL ARE USE TO GETTING AWAY WITH YOUR LIES AND COVER UPS! AND PEOPLE ALL ACROSS THE WORLD ARE SAYING NOT THIS TIME! NO MORE!COVER-UP!  RACIAL PROFILING!  it has Always been clear, but IT CAN NO LONGER BE DENIED!  CELEBRITIES AND PEOPLE IN OTHER COUNTRIES SEE THE LIES, COVER-UP AND INJUSTICE!  AND WE WILL CONTINUE TO DEMAND JUSTICE FOR TRAYVON!  HE AND HIS PARENTS DESERVE IT!
AND THEY WILL HAVE IT IN THIS LIFE OR AFTER!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hapd2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tz1k</id></website><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/lawrence-odonnell-and-charles-blow-give-george-zimmerman-pal-joe-oliver-epic-grilling/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T02:54:25+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T23:25:27+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ovoz</id><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/lawrence-odonnell-and-charles-blow-give-george-zimmerman-pal-joe-oliver-epic-grilling/#comment-480018686</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l3jxx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>