<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpoapl/update/2012-03-22T01:17:50/5c24ef8b23f7013384e7d839029e4e6a97030daa1aeaa826525df5a3e4d1a585</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpbqml</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lytz5</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Dear Anomymous5386,

This drama is still running with 9 more episodes to go. Thus might be a really good news for you since you don't really have to wait for the next episode to show the following day or writing impatiently for Monday to come since this is a weekdays drama, running 1 episode per day, every Monday to Friday each week.

The bad news if you live outside Taiwan, is that there is a copyright issue that arise recently. Thus, some sites that upload this drama are quickly blocked. Making us the foreign fans have to look real hard to find ways to watch the drama before the sites are blocked. Therefore, making it a really bad idea to post site address for this drama in public forum.

However, if you don't mind, you could read some of the episodes recaps in other discussion forum such as asianfanatics and teadramatime. From those two forums, you could get the main ideas of the dramas without watching all the episodes, even though watching it yourself is of course what you actually wanted.

Hope this could quench your Thirst to follow the whole story of this drama. Since I personally also love this drama, been following it faithfully since it started airing last year.

Cheers!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/dlz22b</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lt9u</id></website><link>http://sugoideas.com/drama-2011/inborn-pair/</link><postedTime>2011-12-14T18:58:18+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T05:17:50+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpoapl</id><link>http://sugoideas.com/drama-2011/inborn-pair/#comment-473280816</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-12-14</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>