<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/133995/post/99572680/comment/329720165</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>court the after a few encounters, Zhang Xue clean about their own emotional experience. Back to Lanzhou soon end up with marriage, as well as his son. Disturbed but his wife the day of the bread and water, and soon had an affair, for which they parted ways. Soon after, he took his son came to Beijing battles with dreams of becoming a professional painter, rented in the basement. Even so, he did not give up. Later, to his son to school, his switch to engage the housing design. Xue Jie returned to Beijing to take the money, but the bank staff told her: Upon inquiry, the two bank card only a few dollars left. stunned and Xue Jie in a Cold sweat. The staff told her that 152 million were taken away from in Gaobeidian Sub-branch of Industrial and Commercial Bank of China, Chaoyang District, and an AMT machine withdrawals is Zhang, her passport. Xue Jie understood all of a sudden, bank cards and passports are placed on a bookshelf at home, Zhang key to her home with her to pick up the money, knowing that the bank cards. , Xue Jie does not appear in court, her lawyers learned that Zhang in court for fraud experience is quite proud of, sadly silent. Yes, people do not understand, an extremely intelligent and talented doctoral students, how will the defeat at the hand of a junior high school education rogue. This bombshell lost 2.86 million Xue Jie was born in 1974 in an ethnic minority family, born intelligent, she admitted to the capital of a elite from Hubei mountains, all the way to read Dr. and smooth entry into the national research institutions. She is not only a unit of the youngest female Director, and completed post-doctoral research. However, compared with the smooth sailing school and work, the emotional world of the Xue Jie is a blank. Zhang got the money, suddenly like a changed individual. Xue Jie to call him, Zhang  quibble that busy, two can not be said to hang up the phone; about to meet him, he alleges that they\'re not Beijing. the the next day, Xue Jie called an advertising company boss Peng eagle Tel: Peng, I need one million yuan to buy a house, to Ensure that within a year returned to you, can you help me? Peng eagle is a longtime friend of the Xue Jie, Xue Jie\'s character and ability have no doubt that he hesitated a moment and said: 1 million all of a sudden get out, but 600 000 is no problem. Xue Jie borrowed 600,000 yuan and 1 million handed over with Zhang. The last, Zhang get the money after he heard from. Xue Jie seems to have become accustomed to this way, she told herself, Zhang temporarily neglected their own, is better for the future reunion. combing all of the plot together with Zhang Xue Jie suddenly wake up: into a peach trap. She commissioned a friend in Beijing and Gansu about Zhang\'s information. Soon, the information summarized in the Xue Jie here: Zhang simply is not Dongyirisheng the design director, he just had a little job took Dongyirisheng decorative small contractors; he does not is a brilliant student of the Central Academy of Fine Arts just go to school education through college courses. Zhang use the money cheat from the Xue Jie first to buy a house in Chaoyang District, bought a Mondeo car. Xue Jie, Zhang\'s marital status but also tears; he did divorce, but cohabitation with the working woman Xu Fang in October 2006, and married after more than a year, the time of registration in Lanzhou in 2008 July 28. Zhang would like the next day to go house to measure the design size, Xue Jie something can not go, she assured that the key to him. A few days later, Zhang phone is about to meet Xue Jie said to be also the key to her. The head when he came in her hand, holding a bouquet of colorful roses. Over the years, Xue Jie is the first time that the roses, she was excited about the lips, thrill: p&amp;gt; to take advantage of when the shaking of the Xue Jie Xin Jing, Zhang Minato whispered in her ear, said: Zhang took out her house key, said with deep feeling: there, anyway you want decoration, at any time in the past. I am willing. The two began to discuss Xue Jie, the decoration is their wedding rooms. In January 2008,louboutin soldes, Zhang some difficulties Xue Jie said the house all decorated down to fifty or sixty million, to buy building materials, he is suddenly unable to so much money, prepaid first part of the decoration section. Xue Jie without hesitation: in advance how much? January 12, Xue Jie 30 million transfer to the name of the bank card Zhang. Money credited, Zhang wrote a receipt. (text In addition to Zhang, other is a pseudonym) in November 2007, the 33-year-old Xue Jie Haidian District Huangzhuang, bought a two-bedroom new homes. Looking for decoration company, a chance to know his girlfriend to her company\'s design director Zhang of the Beijing Dongyirisheng decoration. they became familiar, Zhang told Xue Jie, Gansu, and graduated from the Central Academy of Fine Arts. After graduating from the first as a teacher at the Lanzhou Institute of Education, resigned after came to Beijing, the Dongyirisheng decoration company work, entrusted with the task due to the excellent performance,Abercrombie france, the current design director with overall responsibility for the company\'s interior design business. Sure enough, in September 2008, Zhang reappeared before the SIT cleansing. Zhang told Xue Jie said: is coming soon. She immediately launched almost all relatives,abercrombie and fitch, friends and classmates, to borrow money. Friends and family all know the cause of the Xue Jie heyday, no one challenged her to borrow money, credit, and have generously. Xue Jie raised over 100 million deposited into Zhang\'s bank card. Zhang told Xue Jie, get 30 million in renovation costs, he traveled all over the country study the art market, signed a contract agent with a lot of the famous painter, his vision is in Beijing Songzhuang The painters\' village opened a large gallery. In the process of inspection, he spent $ 30 million renovation costs of the Xue Jie. Xue Jie have not had time to blame him, Zhang grabbed her arm Lei Yu be torrential said: life, even the house should live your you can understand my embarrassment as men? get the decoration section, I carry a fixed idea: they must succeed, so as to deserve you. this time I do not take your call, is the fear of you to stop me, I feel bad that I worked hard, pulled me back ... after the incident,Polo Ralph Lauren Pas Cher, people marvel at: Xue Jie has a high IQ, high capacity, how to fall into the only junior high school education, Zhang carefully woven learned, Xue Jie first thought is to alarm, but take into account the face, she thought as long as the get back the money to remain silent. But Zhang is still neither answer the phone, not returning to the SMS. Director of encounter design director of Recently, the Beijing Haidian District People\'s Court in this sensational in two years, claiming to be is Beijing Dongyirisheng decoration company design director Zhang was promoted to vice mayor of a southern city after 33-year-old female Director of a national research institutions, women Dr. Xue Jie to get along in a romantic relationship, and the name of an art gallery, from the Xue Jie extort nearly 300 million yuan RMB. in October 2008, Xue Jie, the organization sent a southern prefecture-level cities attachment served as vice mayor. Xue Jie wanted a year\'s time is not long, and her return to Beijing, Zhang Wei\'s art gallery is certainly also began to profit, then they hand set foot on the red carpet of marriage, her Mayor bride, proud to declared: She called Zhang Wei, want him helping to repay some. Zhang said he is busy, hang up the phone Xue Jie often impatiently. Helpless, Xue Jie had to sell the set not spare some time to the decoration of the house. She let the buyer will be 1.52 million yuan of paying back the principal hit her two ICBC bank card. Xue Jie, two cards away, stay at home in Beijing, together with the passport. November 23, 2009, Xue Jie about to meet with Zhang. Zhang figure is not high, cut fresh, flat head, black-rimmed glasses, it is refined and prudent. He explained to the Xue Jie design concept of the decoration of this house: Ethical Zhaobi beauty. Xue Jie is very satisfactory. Especially learned that Zhang Wei to take care of her bedtime habit of reading the big bed in the master bedroom, designed a small bookshelf with lamp, so that she was prepared to feel the warmth: Zhang laughed: the female Xue Jie like crazy, to Zhang Wei, send text messages, but he seemed generally disappeared. Bitter experience, Xue clean doubts Dunsheng. But she was unwilling to believe that Zhang would be so cruel to treat yourself, I think he had said that the gallery Songzhuang group of painters, no one had heard of the end, Zhang told Xue Jie: temporarily on the bottom of my heart the dream to earn enough money, I\'ll open a gallery. this world there are three kinds of people, men, women and doctoral students, I did not expect half-hard, hit is classified as an alternative. Xue Jie suddenly felt his heart was not just this man touching a bit warm and moved. confirm the final payment credited into account, Xue Jie told Zhang to sell the house. Zhang anxious to sell the house to ask where is the money. Xue Jie told Zhang said: Xue Li, Jie sister at birth, Taizhou, Zhejiang, unexpected accidents due to caesarean section, He died dead in the middle bed. Xue Jie portion of the money of their own to sell the house to help brother-in-law home to ride out the storm. March 4, 2009, Zhang missing for nearly two months suddenly to teach before Xue cleansing. Xue Jie was angry, anxious: few months, where have you been? My money? Xue Jie can not accept all of a sudden: Zhang added: Look, in the near future,Abercrombie Fitch Pas Cher, the \'concrete\' gallery will become a well-known galleries in Beijing, earn at least 300 million a year! looked sadly up. Xue Jie distressed and asked: pay the deposit to the painter, but also requires a lot of input, at least hundreds of million! Zhang conceal his disappointment and said: Jie have a strange melancholy. She stayed up all night, decided to spare no effort to support Zhang. Xue Jie then came to realize that the so-called love of the past two years, all a fantasy out of a dream. That keeps the October 10, 2009, Xue clean up the courage into the Haidian Public Security Bureau report. November 19 Zhang Haidian Police arrested and brought to justice. October 21, 2010, the Beijing Haidian District People\'s Court held a public hearing the case of Zhang\'s alleged fraud. Recently, Zhang was sentenced to 15 years for fraud. Story behind &amp;#30456;&amp;#20851;&amp;#30340;&amp;#20027;&amp;#39064;&amp;#25991;&amp;#31456;&amp;#65306; polo big pony The remarriage man lost the wish to divorce be </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:133995:99572680</id><idPostId>99572680</idPostId><idBlogId>133995</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:133995</id><idBlogId>133995</idBlogId><link>http://camera-letterstotheeditor.pmpblogs.com</link><displayName>Daily Camera: Letters to the Editor</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://camera-letterstotheeditor.pmpblogs.com/2011/07/06/mike-jaeger-who-are-republicans-representing/</link><displayName>Mike Jaeger: Who are Republicans representing?</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T04:48:51.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:133995:99572680:329720165</id><link>http://camera-letterstotheeditor.pmpblogs.com/2011/07/06/mike-jaeger-who-are-republicans-representing/#IDComment329720165</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T04:48:51.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Mike Jaeger: Who are Republicans representing? by dgfrqqu88</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://www.abercrombiefitchh-fr.biz/</link><idEmailMd5>3c381675644fca59c8b0ca3032de47e3</idEmailMd5><displayName>dgfrqqu88</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://www.abercrombiefitchh-fr.biz/"&gt;dgfrqqu88&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://camera-letterstotheeditor.pmpblogs.com/2011/07/06/mike-jaeger-who-are-republicans-representing/"&gt;Mike Jaeger: Who are Republicans representing?&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>