<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/c2qkrl/update/2011-04-11T04:47:10/0f5dcaf28b7e3f0c30de33dfe766b2e9723f342c9b1c0229c57c9af87d21bc26</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>So called ‘birthers’ are in fact Obama Citizenship Deniers.

The press should have been calling them such all along, relegating the existence of the slang term to a single mention per article.

The term ‘birthers’ would not be hidden nor censored; it would be known because the press obviously would quote people using it. 

But otherwise, the press as adult professionals of a country run by adults or insisting on it, would speak the way adults speak about serious matters; and the press would adhere to the decades-old precident, little honored nowadays, that a serious journalist contributing to ‘the journal of our times’ speak soberly ‘for the record.’

I am not insisting on my personal choice of words; I am pointing out that the press has an obligation to speak in its own clear, precise, descriptive language based upon dictionary definition.

‘Birthers’ described by this criteria cannot be described in any other way.

The subject is President Obama and his citizenship status or legitimacy.

It has been proven, to those who value and respect empirical evidence, Barrack Obama was born in Hawaii.

Those who deny the evidence are ‘deniers.’

Perhaps there is a better word or phrase, more accurate, but the point stands.

We out here in America-land can speak like yuk-yukking high school kids if we care to; the press cannot; that is if they have some self respect and mean to truly serve the country.

Most of us do not know an Obama Citizenship Denier, but it matters that many fellow Americans have chosen an absolutely intractable contrary political stance beyond sense and reason.

The ‘birthers’ are indeed as David Plouffe says in the article.
 
"There may be a small part of the country that believes these things, but mainstream Americans think it's a sideshow."

But there are two ways to arrive at that meaning, “sideshow,” two ways to present it and to understand it.

To brand these people with the term ‘birthers’ does not exactly pin down the fact of them, does not ‘close the loop’ of understanding that these people deny a significant fact, and therefore are deeply and stubbornly irrational.

The term ‘birthers’ merely tags them for their ‘sideshow’ aspect and leaves the construction of the meaning of them to the reader.

That is not enough.

Multiplied thousands of times over throughout the national dialog are slang, tags and allusions, terms and phrases one needs to be ‘in on’ or they cannot be readily apprehended.

Multiplied thousands of times over on top of that are people discussing and debating in these ‘Off’ terms, managing multiple layers of superfluous meaning to get at a specific thing.

It is quite difficult enough to ‘say what you mean and mean what you say,’ to understand the intricacies of matters and make a considered judgment.

We do not need our press pitching to us in silly teen slang language.

No one should have to have seen a movie to understand a term in a political news piece; they should be able to arrive from ten years on a desert island and read the news and understand it.

We need a press intelligently parsing meaning and presenting it clear indisputable terms.

It adds up trillions of times over every day, people jumping through entirely unnecessary language hoops to decipher happenings and what they mean, stalling for that one moment to hash through the parsing of a term like ‘birther.’

The term Obama Citizenship Denier causes no pause, no parsing, no dissonance between the cute word and the stark, disturbing fact: No matter what evidence is presented to them, Obama Citizenship Deniers have drawn an imaginary line in the sand at the day of our president’s inauguration and frozen themselves in political time.

And some know better, are shrewd, conniving, aware that anyone bent upon believing a conspiracy about President Obama will follow along, and thus are undermining the president in Carl Rove manner, adding a pregnant negativity to people’s conception of Obama.

Whatever is going on, it is enough in itself to figure out without Burning time and mind on a Donald Trump assertion about whether the press denigrated the denigrating phrase they picked up from denigrating politicos and gave to their readership before the readership ever encountered the fact of Obama Citizenship Deniers.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/5nl1o3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cusm</id></website><link>http://www.rawstory.com/rs/2011/04/10/donald-trump-media-made-birther-a-negative-word/</link><postedTime>2011-04-10T15:35:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-04-11T08:47:10+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/c2qkrl</id><link>http://www.rawstory.com/rs/2011/04/10/donald-trump-media-made-birther-a-negative-word/#comment-182325576</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-04-10</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>