<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwd5w4/post/2012-03-30T09:40:49</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>How in the world can anybody think they're being attacked by an armed man when they are being asked  to identify themselves by a neighborhood watch volunteer.

That is ludicrous!

Being attacked by a possibly armed and dangerous stranger who could possibly end your life that night is exactly what Zimmerman's reality was (not what he was thinking) .

George never ever thought he might be attacked. HE WAS ATTACKED!!!!

There is a big difference between perception and reality and it takes an honest person with some intelligence to understand. It's too bad that everybody thinks that it's OK to lie and cheat just to get the result they want out of life. This is the way our country has gone...Only see things the way it fits your agenda. Sad indeed.

This is all about promoting racism and doing everything possible to fan the flames while doing absolutely nothing to try and bring all people together for a common good.

Just think about it....if all people in this country black ,white, asian,  hispanic etc. all got along peacefully and shared the same values and morals there would be no need for politicians or two different political parties because everybody would soon vote for the same party/candidate. This is why they want to keep the people divided! It benefits them!!

If we could get all people to love and help each other in this country and  like Americans we wouldn't have all these problems or politicans. We should stop  like a bunch of foreigners/nationalities (african-american, asian-american, latin-american etc.) all living on the same Spot of ground and start Acting like americans.

The </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z3b9t</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T07:25:56+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:40:49+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwd5w4</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html#comment-480749850</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zz0vy</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>