<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mklfb0/post/2012-03-25T13:48:46</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>My scores were not much better. I tried doing it yesterday, and got 32 squat jumps, 14 pushups and 6 burpees in before I had to stop. I had gotten maybe 3 hours of sleep in the past two days and had ran a mile that morning, and my body was just...done in. Here are my scores for my second attempt compared to the most recent of my older scores: 

(Old/New)
(1) 32 vs 32/27
(2) 20 vs 14/10
(3) 10 vs 6/11
(4) 160 vs 132
(5) 12 vs 12
(6) 9 vs 12
(7) n/a vs 12
(8) 16 vs 18 

I would have thought that my scores would be much better than this - but I do have a lot of stress in my life right now, so that may be playing a role. Also, my diet has not been clean. Any time I hang out with friends, my diet ends up going to shit. So, I am starting a food diary today, and I have to have a clean diet because I am working my ass  and not losing weight, and it's really starting to piss me Off - and 70% of Weight loss is diet, and I am failing on that front. So, hopefully I can keep my diet super clean for at least a few weeks. I want to see my muscles!!! Oh, but I did find this thing on Pinterest that said, "Don't treat yourself with food, you're not a dog!" I love that, so I figured I'd share. :D

Thanks guys! </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yu70br</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rcq8</id></website><link>http://www.bodyrock.tv/2012/02/20/naked-ambition-fit-test-2-of-the-february-30-day-challenge/</link><postedTime>2012-02-21T01:37:47+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-25T17:48:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mklfb0</id><link>http://www.bodyrock.tv/2012/02/20/naked-ambition-fit-test-2-of-the-february-30-day-challenge/#comment-475924427</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6e405</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>