<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3usfg/update/2012-03-29T15:40:31/1e92439184e38f7d0eea39ccf4b595d1c8e798d0e3430d99ae027db271f1f8c6</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Yea guys this is a tragic situation,tragic indeed. Could you imagine what it feels like to have your dream crumbled before your very eyes. George had dreams of becoming a cop and a Mighty Morphin Power Ranger.


George thought when he killed the kid, he had a sure winner. He thought he would be deemed a hero. George even went out his way to write a letter to the Sanford PD on a brown paper bag at the crime scene stating "HAHA Sanford PD, I know you guys deeply regret rejecting my application to join you guys"

Then when George learned he shot an innocent teen, visiting his pops, armed with skittles and a ice Cold beverage. George world crumbled before his feet. George pleaded "Those were no ordinary bag of skittles, they were magical he insisted. "Those skittles once belonged to the devil. In the right sequence of events, Trayvon could summon a deadly Leprechaun, I seen this happened once on Reading Rainbow". Oh and the tea, don't get me started on the tea.

So all is all. The Sanford place bought his story an stated "George was Acting under the stand your ground law" police wannabe's have a right to deal with supernatural forces and the powers that may be".</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ztxr5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/us/florida-teen-shooting-sanford-divided/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:29:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:40:31+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3usfg</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/us/florida-teen-shooting-sanford-divided/index.html#comment-479806025</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hbh12</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>