<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwpdj5/delete/2012-03-31T06:54:52</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwpgg8</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hwvsb</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Well being fat isn't very much fun, sorry but it is true.  I quit smoking and had a pretty bad knee injury and was laid up for almost 3 months.  It was the greatest three months of my life, all I did was sit in a recliner, eat, and play video games.  I also Gained 40 pounds.

The health problems were numerous.  I couldn't breath, especially at night, and especially when sleeping on my back which I had to do because of my knee.  I had terrible heart Burn all the time and couldn't eat any of the stuff I used to be able to eat, especially spicy foods which I love.

Then I noticed I started to slow down.  I'd be going up or down stairs and I couldn't move my legs like I used to be able to.  Not due to the injury either, I just couldn't move like I wanted to, or like I was able to in the past.

My resting heart rate was up near 100 and I had high blood pressure.  For the first time in my life I had started to feel pretty bad about myself and my self esteem was in the tank, which virtually affected every single part of my life.

Thankfully I had the willpower to turn it all around, I've lost the extra 40 pounds and am now working on the last 20 to get back down to my college weight.  I feel better, my health is better, my blood pressure is back to normal, my resting heart rate is back in the 70s,  I can run again, I can breath now and taste foods since I quit smoking, I don't drink much anymore which improved my life also.

There is a reason to be healthy, other than the shallow reasons that many point out, like beauty or what have you.

I do reject that fat is beautiful, because it simply isn't, eye of the beholder or otherwise.</body><verb>delete</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67xhtd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/31/living/fatshion-beauty-bloggers/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:07:43+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T10:54:52+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwpdj5</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/31/living/fatshion-beauty-bloggers/index.html#comment-481734544</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ho8n5</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>killed</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>