<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fi7x/post/2012-03-29T17:08:34</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Personal branding, what a load of bollocks. People are not commodities, they are living, breathing, thinking, feeling individuals. With this in mind, one of my intelligence colleagues said it best a few weeks ago, "All this ludicrous emphasis on personal branding is a phenomenal waste, spend your time doing the actual work rather than focusing on the appearance of doing the work/talking about it, and the rest will take care of itself." Precisely right. 

Further, all this dependence on Social Media to me indicates HR departments have fully consumed the SM Kool Aid and  that marketing/PR  is now taking precedence over substance and capability. Just because somebody blogs incessantly, makes a lot of noise, shows up on every SM site, has lots of followers, or posits themselves as a supposed expert on the internet -how does this really correlate to their actual ability to perform in a specific role? This is certainly not established in this article.

That said, I'd like to focus on a few of the points made in the article:

1) "In a world where too many job seekers fabricate parts of their resumes, 
the Internet can provide valuable third-party verification that you are 
who you say you are."

INTELRPO:  Really? Reference sockpuppeteering the personal equivalent of corporate astroturfing. 

2) "If you're invisible you are a fraud. Employers are looking not for words, but for demonstrated knowledge and results. If you've got a strong online personal brand, you're in."

INTELRPO: 

Oh, how to even get into what's wrong with the above. Let's start with "if you are invisible you are a fraud."  From a position of logical argumentation, this is  known as begging the question/circular logic. This sort of "reasoning" is fallacious because simply
assuming that the conclusion is true (directly or indirectly) in the
premises does not constitute evidence for that conclusion. So, where's the evidence that SM invisibility means someone is a fraud? Malarkey. Some folks chose to not broadcast their every thought and personal details out of concern for their privacy, this does not make them a fraud. Others may be busy actually doing something that behooves the firm they are working for and not constantly updating LinkedIn or blogging; this does not make them a fraud.As to the assumption that a strong online brand=knowledge and results;  no evidence is presented for the causal link. I want to see some statistical research validating this claim. Its highly specious.3) "You've spent the past few years developing new skills and capabilities —
 yet your employer and colleagues are oblivious. The only way you can 
demonstrate your new expertise to a broad audience — one that might want
 to hire you, in fact — is to brand yourself as a public expert, just 
like a candidate for office would. Online, create a stream of valuable 
content by tweeting, blogging, and being quoted by media outlets."

INTELPRO: 

Well, if your employer is oblivious to your expanding capabilities, obviously they don't have a good talent management program. Shame on them.

Further, just because somebody goes and brands themselves as a public expert does not make it so. Note, that the media isnt exactly selective in spewing whatever BS serves a particular agenda often regardless of where it comes from and candidates for office are typically the most full of BS. The game for a politician is  say whatever it takes to get elected- the truth is irrelevant. All PR all the time as it were.

I  cant tell you how many times I've watched executives at the highest levels of the Fortune 10/Global 400  hire some of these supposed experts who blather about in the public domain incessantly. Thinking noise=knowledge. Yet, when these charlatans get put on the Spot, all too frequently their cluelessness is instantaneously exposed.  Hence, in my view as a respected intelligence analyst and SME on various technologies/markets and adviser to C level executives who by the way doesn't go give press  quotes or tweet  because I would be fired if I did- what the internet has really enabled is superficially informed folks to spout buzzwords and posit themselves as experts.  So, in actuality I think this ends up requiring a new level of vigilance from HR departments who are woefully unequipped to test all this professed expertise. 

In closing, in my experience the folks who really have deep expertise and that do drive strategy and decision making (real experts), are not the same folks out  from the rooftops allover the web. Frankly, I've guided multibillion dollar decisons on major M/A, influenced strategic partnerships, and influenced at least $2.5B in long range technology investments and I could care less about tweeting and being quoted by media outlets. How many of the folks who are constantly quoted and tweeting and professing themselves as experts in my industry on the web can say the same? I happen to know some of  those folks, and what their impact was when my company was stupid enough to bring  them in thinking they would offer valuable insight. What they got was a swift kick in the ass right on out the door for spouting conventional wisdom... which is almost Always entirely wrong....



</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ho9fl</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/mft1</id></website><link>http://blogs.hbr.org/cs/2012/03/its_not_a_job_search_-_its_a_p.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T19:58:08+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T21:08:34+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fi7x</id><link>http://blogs.hbr.org/cs/2012/03/its_not_a_job_search_-_its_a_p.html#comment-479896401</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>