<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9pwc7/update/2012-03-18T09:32:58/b5f4fd66b58de1a361d1ee4c365bf08dd0854248e9b1d3ce6c3818604ececead</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9jy66</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yxbg</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I  find it funny when someone says this because they are usually people who have never been in the industry in any serious role.  Beatmatching on 1200s is the same as using a midi controller like the S4. In fact it's harder on the midi controller because of the reduced platter surface and the lack of hardware pitch control.

Many International DJ's used CDJ's in the past because it was easier to travel with and easier to Burn new unreleased tracks to a CD to play. I never liked them and I think they're pointless now with all these new midi controllers and Serato digital setups. I also never understood why newbs  say you have to use vinyl not Serato. There's no difference, in fact spinning old vinyl is as easy as riding a bike. 
The DJ traditionalists get left behind as new setups demand more from the DJ. Now you have people with an APC40 triggering all sorts of insane things in Ableton live, and believe me it's not just as easy as pressing buttons. Old DJ's get left behind playing weddings explaining to drunk people how awesome vinyl is compared to this new fangled technology. That's why A-Trak doesn't do his old DMC stuff anymore and instead is one of the leading DJ's in dance music because of his ability to stay on top of new music and to mix in an interesting style, not worrying about how much street cred his setup has.

But besides all that, everyone knows it's the production that matters most. You can spin wheels around all you want but fresh sounds will Always come first.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6gypv9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/y2ru</id></website><link>http://www.engadget.com/2012/03/16/pioneer-launches-rmx1000/</link><postedTime>2012-03-16T18:32:08+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-18T13:32:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9pwc7</id><link>http://www.engadget.com/2012/03/16/pioneer-launches-rmx1000/#comment-468330459</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8zii7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-16</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>