<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0afrl/post/2012-03-31T15:34:16</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwsai4</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zc091</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>This is a rant that probably will only make sense to me but you should still read it for kicks to know that there are people crazier than you out in the world,or maybe even smarter?


I blame Disney. Name one thing decent they have done for the television world(or just the world in general,those evil bastards) in the last decade. Actually don't name because I really don't care(Phineas and Ferb or Kingdom Hearts are drops in a bucket the size of the Grand Canyon),anything you say is easily negated with two words-Hanna Montana. That's the show that undid everything Sesame Street worked so hard to accomplish and is a culprit in the creation of the cult of Bieber heads we have today. Now because of that all you have to do as a show to be successful is have the main character sing the main song,sing the title to the crappy straight to broadcast movies you put out every week(they don't even have to be in the crappy movie just the fact that they sing will get you millions of views),and work them to death until their very image is Burned to the back of the retinas of viewers,then you release them to be forever forgotten;usually this happens within 4-5 years. Why you say? Simple,because the 7-8 year old's whose brain cells you have destroyed are in high school now,and it'll be far viler to attack the next generation with even dumber  and scripts than the ones you already have set up because they're programmed to eat what ever you feed them at this point,and there's Always the slight chance that the younger siblings of said generation are smarter than the older. If you don't believe me do this. If you have a younger sibling,cousin,niece/nephew etc... ask them,did they ever outgrow their favorite disney show? Then ask them the age when they realized they were too old for the show. Now with this information think to yourself and research when they became zombies to the point where they snapped out of it. I guarantee you they never got the chance to outgrow the show,the show ended before they got the chance to do make that decision for themselves. You do not outgrow Disney,Disney outgrows you-hahahahahahahahahaha(evil Mickey Mouse voice)hahahahahahahahahaha.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67933j</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7d9s</id></website><link>http://tv.ign.com/articles/122/1222062p1.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T10:23:01+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T19:34:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0afrl</id><link>http://tv.ign.com/articles/122/1222062p1.html#comment-482129256</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/da2ji</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>