<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3n4c6/update/2012-03-29T12:54:05/f4becfa50dc587f0984b5b7d9e78871c082588c3fca933fd0b4e82e6055ac63d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tq81</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>In response to Bobb:  A teacher with a Master's Degree and 30 years of experience in upstate NY would be thrilled to earn 100K for 180 days of work.  Sadly, that is not the case here or in most other areas.  Rarely do teachers RETIRE at the 70-75K a year mark (that's after over 30 years working and having a Master's Degree).  Teachers put in far more than 180 days as well.  They work  the clock at night, on weekends, and during the summer so that curriculum can be improved and kept to current core standards.  Teachers do not get paid past their contract hours, so most of the grading and parent/student conferences, emails, Back to School Night, etc., happen for free.  The brave souls who go into teaching know that their business world peers will out-earn them within a year or two.   Starting teacher salaries in the upstate NY area?  35-40K a year.  We are not talking big money here.  It is insulting and frustrating when people say derogatory things about teachers and their professionalism.  I have taught for over 21 years--I love what I do and I don't expect to get paid for the actual amount of work I put into my job to Ensure that the students can master the state standards.  I spend my own money on tissues, pencils, and basic classroom supplies for my students because there is no longer a budget for that from the school and because so many of my students cannot afford supplies.  It's no wonder that teacher Burn out is so high when there is a general lack of respect from people like Bobb.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zgera</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ml2k</id></website><link>http://thedailystar.com/archive/x1361427158/Letters-to-the-Editor-March-29-2012</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T07:40:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:54:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3n4c6</id><link>http://thedailystar.com/archive/x1361427158/Letters-to-the-Editor-March-29-2012#comment-479647126</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>