<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/234352/post/86320894/comment/328265352</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Yesterday, technology counterfeiting fundraising team legal website shows donations. Website screenshot yesterday, Haidian Public Security Bureau outdoor the reception room of economic cases, Overheating exhibit Report instructions. The newspaper the reporters Qin Binshe WASHINGTON for that Haidian Economic Investigation whether to adopt a few days recovery land tax Chaoyang has formally adopted the civilian affairs division said that the jurisdiction of the individual to rise money, and did never adopt police did not officially accepted ,mulberry uk, yesterday , Overheating their friends and fans, accompanied forward representatives of, came to the Haidian Branch of economic cases the anteroom reported Fang and his attorney Peng Jian, in connection with IMPACT asset and Technology crackdown Shi-security wealth afterward Overheating came to Chaoyang Local Taxation Bureau to report impose evasion afterward Fang and his attorney Peng Jian,on suspicion of Overheating indoor and out from the relevant Division,hermes handbag, said after the complete record the plenary movie and gave the invoice of duly authorized management. 14:00, Overheating came to civilian society organizations below the Ministry of Civil Affairs Authority to report Fang and Peng Jian connection without authorization, which claims to have the public ecology of the fundraising. The staff involved in its Report, Department of the fund raising Fang and Peng Jian, as an individual fund-raising,mulberry uk, which is not surrounded the jurisdiction. yesterday, Overheating of the reporting process microblogging live. Starting from yesterday morning begin Overheating namely Always microblogging to the fans real-time announce Fang said to be discrediting said. Fang said he had exposed in early the Overheating illegal school and false advertising. Fang said the initial set up namely anti-counterfeiting fundraising troop when he Chuan-Guo Xiao accident Later some of the crackdown Technology crackdown fundraising crew set up in his own appoint the money they raised is used principally to finance namely absolutely conducive to anti-technology deceit and to curb knowledgeable misconduct Litigation happenings After he was attacked Peng Jian fired his own name-raising plays to rise the money as the expenses of Technology crackdown \'personal security. March 20,hermes kelly bags, Overheating in to upload a withdrawal documents, the sender Peng Jian, the aggregate of 2500 yuan,appendix marked an thousand five hundred yuan postmarked March 17. Fang said Peng Jian call Overheating of 2500 yuan, 1000 yuan namely Overheating donated the money. yesterday, reporters cry Peng Jian,mulberry bags, the phone incapable to connect. Fang said &amp;#9632; Interrupted donations publicity without costing details Technology crackdown fundraising crew allowable yesterday the publicity, the IMPACT project has received 267,537.27 yuan donations,hermes, science and technology the crackdown person personal security project has received $ 728,488.32 yuan and 985. The official website announced the disbursement for security projects as of March 13, 2012,additive expenditures 590,239.87 yuan,merely the IMPACT project disburse column shows the disburse of asset audit &amp;#9632; respond yesterday for Overheating of some of the issues involved in reporting, Fang were to respond. security funding why never publish the details? Fang: If published,mulberry bags, others to know what security measures we have taken, you longing know how to respond. Money so characteristic flowers to where you are,tin not be proclaimed on the Internet. Peng Jian initiated security asset has been stated in the announcement according the inner monitoring team to supervise the use of wealth security. two faking main expenditures Why namely displayed as Fang: IMPACT funding is the reason why no announcement,hermes bag,for the past few years namely never how to cost money is especially adapt to fund the minority rights activist. Peng Jian,whether the money saved to a determined amount to the registration of private non-enterprise fund,mulberry outlet,or want to do a public service agencies. Because it first fired we wanted to set up for the Fund, and later base namely the relatively lofty threshold to set up a fund there ought be several million of starting central so to raise asset to disburse tax Fang: it is the public good such as a newborn namely sick, and we donate money to him, do never must disburse taxes? This is never illegal fund-raising,unlawful fund-raising to dissemination return on investment. But I do never have the money and in variety,equitable to get a security service,hermes handbag, and not country namely enjoy such a service is essential to disburse impose In addition, our anti-counterfeiting investigation and prove collection costs are expenditure for their own,as I do never deficiency people to enumerate namely I was to spend money aboard anti-counterfeiting,mulberry, independence aspiration be affected. 4 Technology counterfeiting money or technology IMPACT Fund? Fang: Technology IMPACT Fund in 2006 changed the Technology IMPACT things the initial establishment wanted to enrol as the Fund,yet a few months later Peng Jian pedestal to be made of the fund namely also difficult put the funds into money. Peng Jian (microblogging content): as a main project managers, I never said namely (technology crackdown king namely a fund phoned Fang Luo event one,along to middle reports, in 2006, Overheating has donated 1000 yuan as the counterfeiting chief However, the same annual Overheating establishment of Bullog,hermes bag, the two forged grievances. 2,2011,mulberry handbags, the two sides afresh in the online argue The Overheating said his wife Fang Fang uncover illegal Overheating schools, and pretended advertising. three,2012 March 22,hermes birkin handbags, Fang Luo spat upgrade Overheating of the division of civil affairs public security divisions impose ministries to report and questioned IMPACT things and technology crackdown Shi-insurance funds &amp;#9632; experts say personal award of money impose namely not apparently defined yesterday, Tsinghua University, Director of the Centre of Innovation and Social Responsibility tightness said,along to China\'s new the relevant regulations of the public philanthropy charitable institutions provided,merely individuals never eligible to do fundraising and does not necessitate tightness think to adopt the donation,mulberry handbags,mulberry outlet, the appoint of the individual namely a personal acceptance of the award action Personal acceptance of the gift the judgment does never necessitate the public, donors accountable under the contract aboard the line,yet whether we adopt the reward is a public service to adopt a reward in the appoint of the moral or the public. as the individual to adopt cash reward should disburse taxes, Beijing King &amp;amp; Bond Law Firm lawyers Jianghua namely individual in housing grants to disburse taxes,hermes kelly bags,but taxation of the People\'s Republic of China on Individual Income Tax Law and other income taxable along the State Council financial ministries did not comprise cash gift among individuals. Ganghwa,hermes birkin handbags,levy laws and regulations,earnings derived according individuals,namely complicated to define Which of the taxable items of proceeds onward the impose authorities review identified. Primary Discussions Wang, edition have written the reporter Kara Share: Welcome to the comment I lack to microblogging suggested | hot microblogging todayRelated articles&amp;#65306; Related articles&amp;#65306; even if the children Thus 
 
[WORDPRESS HASHCASH] The poster sent us \'0 which is not a hashcash value. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:234352:86320894</id><idPostId>86320894</idPostId><idBlogId>234352</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:234352</id><idBlogId>234352</idBlogId><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog</link><displayName>Wanton Wordsmith</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/</link><displayName>The day he went away</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:41:16.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:234352:86320894:328265352</id><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/#IDComment328265352</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:41:16.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The day he went away by pjexuhhzu</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://mulberrybag-handbags.com</link><idEmailMd5>af88a91b8e4a8bfcd273673471bacef8</idEmailMd5><displayName>pjexuhhzu</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://mulberrybag-handbags.com"&gt;pjexuhhzu&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/"&gt;The day he went away&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>