<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mimwyx/update/2012-03-22T18:33:12/a77091f33e3d806a530531954bb195a5532fbe334ab3fb9aabedea089e703600</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>If the festival happens, who would choose the ? Miami is full of  that merit a Spot at this festival. Would Perdomo's band Dreaming In Stereo headline? Would all Forward Motion artist have first dibs? I understand the argument that Miami is known more for being a party town than being a town for live music, however, I'm a true believer that the people should decide if you're good enough! Let the people vote!

You can't force people to like your band or your music. If people are speaking during your performances, like they do during many unknown  performances, maybe it just means they don't deem it good enough to listen to. People will listen if you're good. If they connect.

I have personally been to venues where Dreaming In Stereo has performed and although there are some beautiful melodies and great songs, Perdomo is no Brad Pitt and at certain venues the music is not appropriate for the crowd. It is coffee house music, they are not a Top 40  where masses of people sing along to their songs. 

Perdomo however is a dreamer and like many other dreamers his ideas and visions sometimes blur reality. In respect to his idea, Perdomo is a local innovator, and a SXSE would indeed be a step in the right direction for our city. He will be surely be remembered as someone who broke barriers and was a pioneer for live music within South Florida.

It will surely take an Act to break out of our city and make it big and later speak up about the masses of talent and open the minds of the world to a much bigger picture than just dance music, latin and hip hop bands.I just hope Fernando Perdomo doesn't think he is that person.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yfzbi</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rinx</id></website><link>http://blogs.browardpalmbeach.com/countygrind/2012/03/fernando_perdomo_south_by_southeast.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T19:01:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T22:33:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mimwyx</id><link>http://blogs.browardpalmbeach.com/countygrind/2012/03/fernando_perdomo_south_by_southeast.php#comment-474022713</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>