<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3k631/post/2012-03-29T22:18:23</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>TJ - Good discussion topic.

I think we all are going through the 'growing pains' of having to re-think everything - offense, defense and draft - that is affected by the signing of Manning and the addition of Del Rio (I like the addition of Del Rio).

For instance, before, I thought a draft of someone like Martin, or even Ganaway, to be expected (even if one had to move up in the draft). Now, I'm not especially unhappy with what we have at RB. Moreno, if healthy, should do well with Manning. Ball, if I'm not mistaken, started in the NFL with the Colts and knows something of Manning's system. McGahee and Fanin can get the 'tough' yards as well as Martin.Even Johnson might do well. I don't expect as much injury among RBs simply because their use will be altered significantly.  I also, like you, do not see a RB pick early (though they may bite on Martin if he falls to #25, which I'm not expecting). 

Manning also has changed my way of thinking about WRs, TEs, and OL. With the FA siginings, and the fact that Davis (if I remember correctly) was  regarded as a three position guy, with C as an especially good Spot for him, I'm not especially nervous about the OL. On offense, I think they may select another lineman, and perhaps a QB in the later rounds (Osweiler?), but not much more.

More difficult to predice IMO is what happens on defense. I liked Allen. I like Del Rio more, I think, largely because I have the feeling that he thinks more in terms of "amoeba". He does both 4-3 and 3-4. He especially uses LBs creatively. And he salivates over the possibilities of DBs.
IMO, if Del Rio gets to influence the draft (and I think he might), he'll not be as concerned as I might be. He'll see a DL that has Ayers, Beal, McBEan, Warren, Siliga, Unrein, Vickekrson, Jarmon &amp; Dumervil (maybe even Garland) and not be especially dismayed by its prospects. Likewise, at LB he'll see Von, Mays, Irving, Woodard, and DJ and feel OK with what he has. The same for DB where Champ, Harris, Vaughn, Goodman, Porter Thompson, Adams, Moore, Bruton and the two Carters are not without Comforting potential and, the predictable conclusions is that, in the draft - he'll look for the best available player. 

And I expect this year's draft to have some surprises. If one of the more elite DB's fall to #25 (Claiborne, Kirkpatrick, Denard, Gilmore, Barron, maybe Jenkins) they'll probably bite. Likewise, if Kuechly or Hightower fall to #25, they'll probably bite.

After that, IMO, it's DL, at least in the early rounds, but perhaps even further into the draft. And, given what little I know of Del Rio, I think everything is in play - NT, DT, DE, maybe even DE/OLB. And it see intriguing picks here, from the earliest to the later rounds  - i.e. Brockers, Still, Worthy, etc to Jean-Baptiste, Chapman, etc.

Anyway, I'm becoming increasingly curious as to what will become the tact taken.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6znvn1</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ui6h</id></website><link>http://www.itsalloverfatman.com/broncos/entry/some-speculation-on-how-defensive-tackle-could-play-itself-out</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:34:29+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:18:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3k631</id><link>http://www.itsalloverfatman.com/broncos/entry/some-speculation-on-how-defensive-tackle-could-play-itself-out#comment-480151068</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lv3be</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>