<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3zoeu/update/2012-03-29T05:58:00/d3e6a0c0cc6d238c8b9f6544bcbc8d2ab4c99612743efb16856fa1c8f3d01d34</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3d963</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/e3vvy</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>your semi-coherent rant is so full of misconceptions, one hardly knows where to begin:

 "surveillance footage" CANNOT show that Zimmerman was "wholly uninjured after the shooting"; only a thorough medical examination could do so. The police report states that he was Bleeding.

the reasons why so many whites are disgusted with the orgy of breastbeating over the Martin/Zimmerman shooting are straightforward:

1) Zimmerman is a mestizo, but was converted by the media into a white person so that white Americans could engage in yet another masochistic orgy of self-condemnation for our imaginary racism.

2) white Americans are tired of being preyed upon by feral blacks in cities and towns from coast-to-coast; 85% of violent incidents involving blacks and whites are black-on-white.

3) we are also tired of budding thugs like Martin being transformed by media magic into choirboys. While I wish Martin were still alive, and that instead of being coddled by a dysfunctional educational and legal system, and that he might have faced the kind of stern discipline which might have turned him from a sleazy thug into a decent human being, we all know that in all likelihood, he would have continued to burgle people's homes, punch people for no particular reason, sell drugs, and be a general nuisance to society. 

4) the vast majority of whites approve of laws allowing us to defend ourselves against feral blacks, and the attack on Zimmerman is felt to be an attack on that right. whether secretly or openly, almost all whites wish that their neighborhoods were being controlled by people like Zimmerman.

5) through a dizzying range of programs, including jobs programs, what America pays trillions of dollars to placate, appease, and coddle blacks without receiving anything in return (as just one example among hundreds, have a look at the articles on this site about the way in which transit authorities coast-to-coast have been transformed into welfare programs for incompetent, lazy, illiterate blacks, who earn salaries in six figures for doing practically nothing and refused to hire qualified nonblacks)

6) this protection money doesn't even work: black on white crime is as bad as ever. what Americans are owed a clear objective accounting of the sacrifices we have made on behalf of blacks. The noisy, arrogant ingratitude of blacks is hardly an inducement to make a sacrifice even more!!!!

7) whites are simply tired of being terrified of saying anything politically incorrect for fear of losing their jobs, terrified of blacks because of the ever present threat of physical assault, terrified of being shut out of employment opportunities by Black mafia outfits like the infinitely corrupt transit authorities.

8) Personally, I hope this latest attempt at blackmail backfires and galvanizes white Americans, convincing them that it's time to say: ENOUGH!

9) the equality mafia that has wrecked most of America's institutions represents the true racism in America: That of holding blacks to a LOWER STANDARD than whites. 

incidentally: no DNA evidence links Thomas Jefferson to Sally Hemmings; the evidence. Instead, it clearly links a male Jefferson (conceivably Thomas; he had several brothers, and God knows how many male cousins) to her children; there is no evidence whatsoever linking Thomas specifically to her children.

this is another case of white masochism and black blackmail: white historians who know better – who are trained to handle evidence objectively – go along with this fiction of Thomas Jefferson being a child molester, blah blah in order to placate blacks who they secretly hold in contempt as superstitious, irrational, and childish.

I have two brothers. If DNA evidence suggested that ONE OF THE THREE of us had fathered a certain child, and a lawyer argued in court that this "proved" that I was the father, not only would the case be thrown out instantly, his colleagues might recommend psychological counseling, because he would be clearly insane, deluded, and incompetent.

speaking as a former Kool-Aid drinking race hypocrite, I will state categorically for the record that ABSOLUTELY ALL of the white enablers of black pathology in the media, academia, politics, etc. secretly regard blacks as inferior, childish, ridiculous, and incompetent.

they are the real racists. If only more blacks were smart enough to realize that fact.
 
the race relation house of cards in the United States is based on pure, unadulterated hypocrisy, mendacity, and lies.

Every single one of these white hypocrites knows well that blacks have been accommodated and enabled to a preposterous degree, and that continuing black failure must be traced to causes other than discrimination and racism.

We all know, whether we are willing to admit it or not, that blacks on their own worst enemies.

the failure of blacks to take advantage of the opportunities offered them in America is a tragic reality that cannot be papered over with more lies.

the reason for their continued failure is clear, has Always been clear: low average cognitive ability, and glaringly obvious psychological deficits.
Whether these are problems to be solved, or realities to be accepted and adapted to, only time will tell.

only by facing challenges with courage and determination (not having their incredible narcissism and arrogance indulged by the usual warm bath of liberal fantasy) might blacks have any chance at all of bettering themselves.

by accommodating black pathology and repressing scientific fact in favor of politically correct fairytales, we have lost at least half century, during which we might have addressed these issues and realistic objective manner.

I hope white patience with this insane flight from reality is at an and. I know mine is.


</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hcrc6</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f9vj</id></website><link>http://amren.com/features/2012/03/the-trayvon-shooting-fact-versus-fantasy/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T04:24:29+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T09:58:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3zoeu</id><link>http://amren.com/features/2012/03/the-trayvon-shooting-fact-versus-fantasy/#comment-479380271</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>