<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ofua/post/2012-03-29T19:39:05</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>'&lt;i&gt;Outside endemic corruption, uncertain or wholly absent rule of law, and relatively low per capita income....'&lt;/i&gt;

If we're going to talk about corruption can we at least be honest Jeremy?  The EUSSR and its collective assortment of verminous mafiosi is probably the most corrupt institution the world has ever known.  With financial warfare and the connivance of our own Cameron they are bulldozing the sovereignty of European nations.  Their lastest Act of mendacity was to steal, from private bank accounts, the funds of hospitals and universities in Greece leaving them bereft of money and likely closure.  You cannot get much more corrupt than that and our own 'free' media declines to report it.  Vomit inducing really.  

Just for the record Saddam was trading Iraq's oil in euros for three years before the US decided to put a stop to it.  Coincidentally, or not, Gadaffi was setting up deals with African nations to trade Libya's oil for gold.  Hosni Mubarak we know vehemently opposed the Washington plan of a nuclear defense umbrella to arm Iran's neigbours (Al-Gumhoria - a Cairo newspaper), so Mubarak had to go. 

Between the controlled western media and the lying scumbags in government, we in the west are so deeply covered in layers of decomposing animal manure we don't even notice we're being robbed blind and buried in debt to keep the banks afloat, but thanks to the BBC we haven't the remotest clue even what's going on in the rest of the world in our name courtesy of the CIA, M16, Washington and London.  

Despite all the globalist's NWO covert violations I'll eat all my Tesco carrier bags if the US dollar is still the reserve currency this time next year.        
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zqiaw</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/finance/financialcrisis/9173668/Why-a-Brics-built-bank-to-rival-the-IMF-is-doomed-to-fail.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:07:20+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T23:39:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ofua</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/finance/financialcrisis/9173668/Why-a-Brics-built-bank-to-rival-the-IMF-is-doomed-to-fail.html#comment-480030157</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hrilp</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>