<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tzsj/update/2012-03-29T09:51:04/f6ef3c6c469776c74ce61fefb58ebb967ccbf97774cacd5636e42d37fce82bda</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Alright folks, a job well done here. Now that we've got to the bottom of this case we can all get on with our day.

Just to recap: George Zimmerman, the hispanic, whose name sounds Jewish and everyone refers to as white, who just called 911 for the 47th time and carries a 9mm for neighborhood watch in a gated community confronts Trayvon Martin. Martin, the 17 year old black male who weighs 100+ pounds lees than Zimmerman and is enjoying himself a snack of Skittles and Ice Tea while on his way to a family members house while wear a hoodie (cue dramatic music) is confronted. Even though Zimmerman was told he doesn't need to do that by Police, he does anyways (has anyone said what the actual threat was? and at what point was the community in so much danger that Zimmerman couldn't walk away?). Something happens, and the guy with the gun shoots the guy without the gun. Guy without gun dies.

Hispanics are mad because Zimmerman keeps being called white (hint: be happy you aren't taking the Heat for this; you know, because according to most people on here it's the entire race's fault for the  of one)

Blacks are mad because they feel a young man was unfairly profiled, assaulted and ultimately murdered. Feels like racism, but either way it's a disgusting Act.

Whites are mad...wait why are whites mad? 

I prefer to classify myself as a human being. I'm a little upset because my big neighbor to the south of me (America) is swirling down the toilet at alarming speeds. I have never seen or read so much hate as I have on this board today. Your politics are a disaster, your economy is crumbling, your people are so angry, intolerance is rampant and the media is vile. Anyone who thinks this case is a tragedy and disgusting is welcome to come live up here with us, it can get a little chilly but at least the economy is awesome, healthcare is friggin' sweet, we're nearly completely secular, weed is decriminalized as well as brothels (if that's your thing), we have less polution, less obesity, we can change our government as soon as they start to suck, we have the 2nd largest oil supply in the world (you guys love that stuff), our education system although not perfect is pretty good, we get all your TV channels (big selling point!) and our dollar stronger then yours right now. Come on up reasonable people!

Your friendly neighbor to the North. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zcxr4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T06:16:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:51:04+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tzsj</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html#comment-479503035</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6ofwq</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>