<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3zgs3/delete/2012-03-29T05:02:11</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3l0zs</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8ok3l</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> The Old Testament God of Abraham constantly depicts God to be angry, jealous, wrathful and possessive.

Genesis 19:1-26 God destroyed the cities of Sodom and Gomorrah. He murdered all the people, including all the innocent children. Lot’s wife turned to look at the carnage. God murdered her by turning her into a pillar of salt.
Genesis 38:9-10 Onan, when he had sex with his brother’s widow, would waste his seed on the ground. What he did offended God. God murdered him.
Exodus 9:23-25 God murdered by hail every man that was outdoors.
Exodus 12:29 God murdered all of Egypt’s firstborn. 
Exodus 14:6-28 God forced the Pharaoh and his army to chase the Jews. God parted The Red Sea for Moses’ people. God collapsed the sea and murdered the Pharaoh's Army who had followed the Jews into the sea.
Leviticus 10:1-2 Aaron’s sons Nadab and Abihu offered incense to God, by unauthorized fire. God murdered them both, by fire.
Leviticus 20:9 God commands: Anyone who curses his father or mother shall be put to death.
Leviticus 20:10 God commands: If you commit adultery, you shall be put to death.
Leviticus 20:12 God commanded: If a man has sex with his daughter-in-law, murder them both.
Leviticus 20:13 God commands to murder gay men
Leviticus 20:27 God commanded: If a man or woman Acts as a fortuneteller, murder them.
Judges 1:4 God delivered Judah the Canaanites and the Perizzites into their hand and they slew 10,000 men.
 Hosea 13:16 (KJV) or Hosea 14:1 (Catholic): Samaria, who rebelled against God, will fall by the sword. The little ones shall be dashed to pieces, expectant mothers shall be ripped open
Joshua 24:5 God boasted: Then I, God, sent Moses and Aaron and murdered Egypt..
Judges 11:30-39 God had Jephthah murder 20 cities for Him. Then, God had Jephthah’s 13-year-old daughter first to come through his door, to happily welcome her father home. Jephthah gave his virgin daughter 2 months to mourn her virginity in that she couldn’t live long enough to bear children. Jephthah then sacrificed his only child by Burnt-offering to the Biblical God</body><verb>delete</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h3ze8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dneq</id></website><link>http://community.adn.com/?q=adn/node/160531</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T23:37:34+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T09:02:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3zgs3</id><link>http://community.adn.com/?q=adn/node/160531#comment-479351409</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/k5kr</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>killed</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>