<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/312236/post/127908437/comment/328343310</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>here it is.. 
 
Caramel Apples  
 
8 small apples, such as, Granny Smith or macoun  
2 cups light brown sugar  
1 cup maple syrup  
1/3 cup light corn syrup  
1/2 cup heavy cream  
4 tablespoons unsalted butter  
Toppings of choice, optional, recipes follow  
 
 
Remove the stems from the apples and scrub them under warm water and dry them. Insert a chopstick through the top of the apple all the way to the top and line a baking sheet with waxed paper, set aside.  
Put the sugar, maple syrup, corn syrup, and cream in a saucepan. Bring to a boil over medium-high Heat and cook, swirling the pan but not stirring, until the mixture Reaches 250 degrees F (firm ball stage) on a candy thermometer. Pull pan from the Heat and stir in the butter. Tilt the saucepan and dip and spin each apple into the caramel, covering about 3/4 of the apple. Place on the prepared baking sheet until set.  
 
If using a topping spread the topping out on a sheet pan or wax paper and immediately roll the caramel coated apples in the topping. Transfer to the prepared baking sheet until set.  
 
 
Topping 1:  
2 cups chocolate wafers, graham crackers, or vanilla wafers  
 
Put the wafers or cracker of choice in a plastic storage bag and smash until coarse.  
 
 
Topping 2:  
2 cups walnuts or pecans, toasted  
1/3 cup dried cranberries  
1 tablespoon finely chopped crystallized ginger  
 
Preheat the oven to 350 degrees F.  
 
Spread the nuts on a baking sheet and toast until fragrant and brown, about 8 minutes. Pulse the nuts, cranberries, and ginger in a food processor until mixture resembles very coarse sand. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:312236:127908437</id><idPostId>127908437</idPostId><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:312236</id><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><link>http://www.denpdf.com</link><displayName>denpdf.com</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.denpdf.com/mrs-prindables-does-anyone-know-of-a-recipe-for-making-caramel-apples-like-mrs-prindables-from-qvc/</link><displayName>mrs prindables- does anyone know of a recipe for making caramel apples? like mrs. prindables from QV</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T08:58:30.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:312236:127908437:328343310</id><link>http://www.denpdf.com/mrs-prindables-does-anyone-know-of-a-recipe-for-making-caramel-apples-like-mrs-prindables-from-qvc/#IDComment328343310</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T08:58:30.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on mrs prindables- does anyone know of a recipe for making caramel apples? like mrs. prindables from QV by Asawa</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>544cde82c5e99e167f7273d633d559d1</idEmailMd5><displayName>Asawa</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>Asawa commented on &lt;a href="http://www.denpdf.com/mrs-prindables-does-anyone-know-of-a-recipe-for-making-caramel-apples-like-mrs-prindables-from-qvc/"&gt;mrs prindables- does anyone know of a recipe for making caramel apples? like mrs. prindables from QV&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>