<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3n67e/post/2012-03-29T12:41:45</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This school started Off well, but now is a joke. The loving and nurturing environment they display in the beginning is a thing of the past or I should say a lure. Once in in middle school the kids are emotionally abused and cannot Sneeze, burp, Hiccup, feel sick, talk or use the bathroom. When horrible things such as a student in a headlock that required medical attention, kids showing signs of Anxiety attacks due to the school's treatment. Students who are pushed to the limit and try to Burn the school down and yet no parents are notified of a single event, but they sweep everything under the rug to maintain face. The dean screaming at 7th graders using inappropriate language and deeming the girls are too coddled and need to be released and talked down to (or as they say their working method) so they don't wind up pregnant or in jail.  Teachers who literally scream in the student's faces (kids can still smell the breakfast or lunch on the teachers breath)is denied time after time when confronted with parents.  Kids are made to march up and down the school with all their books in tow as punishment because they are not quiet.  This school is out of control and doing a good job at keeping the parents quiet. If you want a well rounded child - this is not the school for your child unless your child is unruly to the point of needing professional intervention, your child will suffer - this is for juvenile delinquents. The school even keeps pertinent information for entrance to the best public schools.  Turnover for teachers is climbing and the students leaving as late as March is at an alarming rate - a total of about 15 students have left since the beginning of the school year. This school is more for the gang banger parents, sad but true.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/gcbch9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/vzq9</id></website><link>http://www.localschooldirectory.com/public-school/3002866/NY</link><postedTime>2011-05-19T22:50:58+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:41:45+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3n67e</id><link>http://www.localschooldirectory.com/public-school/3002866/NY#comment-479637186</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-05-19</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>