<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mhwz6t/update/2012-02-23T02:53:46/4971a8d7b35c0666f9fd8a716ff9cde7b8efd752da07f8908fd4321f5337fa80</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mlstdb</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I spend a lot of time thinking about this show and it occurred to me one day to wonder what most other people in the Downton world actually see of Mary compared to what we as the audience get to see.  She is very reserved and cool most of the time.  She lets Matthew, Carson, Violet, Anna and Sybil see warmer, sweeter and funnier sides of her personality.  She has also been kind to some of the servants (for example, William when she heard that his mother was ill) .  However, she has said throughout the series that people misread her (When Pamuk comes to her room, she says that he makes the same mistake about her that her parents make, thinking that she is more worldly than she is.  Also, she rather derisively comments that everyone knows that she has no heart).  Also, we see from the reactions of other characters (Mrs. Hughes, Lord and Lady Grantham) to her that they find her Cold or calculating or manipulative or intimidating.  We have gotten to see the tremendous changes that have occurred in her in the seven years that have passed (in Downton time) since we were first introduced to her character.  One of the great pleasures of this show, I think, has been watching Michelle Dockery's finely calibrated performance and how all of those incremental changes added up to, for example, the scene with her father where he let her know that he knew about Pamuk and that he was letting her Off the hook.  The warmth and relief that she showed in that scene was in stark contrast to her shockingly Cold reaction to news of Patrick's death at the beginning of the series.  Her character has probably changed more than any other on this show and I think it's really cool that she is still complex and interesting while being a much better person.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yuyk88</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/vh3p</id></website><link>http://tvrecaps.ew.com/recap/downton-abbey-finale-christmas-special/</link><postedTime>2012-02-20T19:48:34+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-23T07:53:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mhwz6t</id><link>http://tvrecaps.ew.com/recap/downton-abbey-finale-christmas-special/#comment-446703065</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>