<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwi5bf/post/2012-03-31T08:05:52</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Lol, you're funny darkseid. There you are complaining about insults then you launch into insults yourself.
 
Hypocrisy doesn't come more brazen, though it's more stupidity in your case. As was your ridiculous childish complaint to Norman that he wasn't treating you properly, what a Cry baby you are, You're good at handing out the nasty stuff, but scream like a baby when someone does it very mildly to you.
 
As to mass immigration, let's put it to a national vote. I'm happy to abide by the result which will be a huge No! echoing back from the hills. Probably bonfires will be lit in celebration. 
 
If the answer is unexpectedly yes, we like mass immigration and we want more of it, then I will just quietly accept the position as the majority view of the Brits must prevail.
 
As to indigenous Brits, they're not mythical at all and again let's ask everyone what they think and whether they want to be obliterated by a tidal wave of foreigners. No! will be the answer of course.
 
Go on, look up the results of opinion polls on mass immigration if you're in such doubt and report back. I await your response saying the Brits love it and want more, haha.
 
Abusive by the way doesn't come much stronger than this, do you remember who wrote these words? ....

''At the risk of being censored, go and stuff your brainless head up a dead bear's bum, you moronic, repetitive and certifiable little twat. I'd happily bring back capital punishment as a one-Off just to see your fart of head rolling down the street and into the nearest gutter, where it - and your innate racism - belong. You're a disgusting little troll and I wish you a painful and lingering death. Don't EVER presume to hijack my words to support your nasty little racist points of view. Drop dead.Yours sincerely,A well-wisher.''

Hypocrisy darkseid, as well as violent bullying, is your speciality.
 
 
 
 
 
 </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rjawu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ms5i</id></website><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/normantebbit/100146822/elections-are-won-and-countries-are-governed-from-the-common-ground-not-the-middle-ground/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T08:22:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T12:05:52+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwi5bf</id><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/normantebbit/100146822/elections-are-won-and-countries-are-governed-from-the-common-ground-not-the-middle-ground/#comment-481775857</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rx3cr</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>