<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4b79/update/2012-03-30T17:49:09/b42a8aef735a9265e0a7e1c5bd78e1e6f33bc1c96957377572078a8e34c670d6</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Why on earth are moronic Mayor Kenoi &amp; our cro-magnon County Environmental Mgmt. section of DPW trying to re-invent the wheel by paying another $200G (ludicrous waste of money but still less than a  third of the rip-Off payroll expense of Mayor Kenoi's gagged co-opted scribes-useless top aides such as Bishop/etc.) for a hole-in-the-head opala of value only to the shil consultant and money trough/special interest  recipient Mayor Kenoi? 
 
Council Chair Dominic Yagong is proposing that the County of Hawaii expand the Hilo landfill and not truck the waste to Kona because 1) the private truck companies will get richer for no good reason (and neither would it be a good idea to hire more county employees as truckers because this needlessly would spike up county expenses) and 2) trucking our waste causes more wear and tear to our cross-island roadways, and increases pollution, &amp; wastes valuable petroleum. Chair Yagong wants to expand the 1) Hilo landfill by 75 more acres from our adjacent rock quarry while 2) also considering an RFP (request for proposal) from the private sector to handle a sort station contract looking into the possibility of the private sector investing in capital improvements to our county property &amp; simultaneously generating badly needed revenue to the county.   Chair Yagong called out Mayor Kenoi's invitation for discussion, to no avail. 




(Stephens Media).  Hawaii County Council Chairman Dominic Yagong has turned up the Heat on Mayor Billy Kenoi’s plans to operate a Hilo garbage sort station.  Yagong, a potential mayoral candidate this year, accused the mayor of bowing to pressure from public-sector unions rather than looking out for the best interests of taxpayers.  In a Tuesday letter to the mayor, Yagong said “that you want to protect and increase county union jobs by keeping this facility under county control…growing government jobs does not help our county employees.  Instead, it puts current employee jobs in jeopardy because our revenue stream cannot sustain a continuing growing labor force.”  





Mayor Kenoi said all council members are welcome to call or visit with him.  At issue is a plan to create a county-run garbage sort station out of a $9.3 million facility that’s been sitting idle near the Hilo landfill since 2010, using four new positions the county added in July.  The county council passed a nonbinding resolution last month asking the mayor to instead put the project out to bid.    http://prgnewshawaii.wordpress.com/2012/01/04/hawaii-island-news-04-january-through-05-january-2012/

http://www.hawaiitribune-herald.com/sections/news/local-news/recycling-measure-postponed.html http://www.hawaiitribune-herald.com/sections/news/local-news/yagong-pay-people-recycle.html http://kona.westhawaiitoday.com/sections/news/local-news/solid-waste-2-3.html




Chair Yagong's proposals  would increase the life span of the Hilo landfill, allow rental income and revenue generated through  private/public partnership (it has worked wonderfully for the County of Maui), and we keep the county expenses to a minimum.  These solutions make the most sense while showing who in elected office is continuing to be the progressive reformer and who clearly thinks outside the box in finding solutions to our island's most complex challenges.   Sincere, Honest, and for the People...Dominic Yagong</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zupqy</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f2ph</id></website><link>http://www.hawaiitribune-herald.com/sections/news/local-news/study-backs-trucking-garbage-west-hawaii.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:08:21+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:49:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4b79</id><link>http://www.hawaiitribune-herald.com/sections/news/local-news/study-backs-trucking-garbage-west-hawaii.html#comment-481239062</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zd1kx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>