<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi5f1h/post/2012-03-22T15:31:21</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpyjgx</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6vxko</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>He has done more than this. He money given through Bill Gates foundation and running several jobs programs in US, Africa and Asia etc then don't ask for one single mill. Below is money he already Coughed up which he didn't deducted through income tax.

Ten million Berkshire Hathaway Inc. Class B shares have been . Each year, 5 percent of the remaining  shares will be transferred to the asset trust.
The first installment of 500,000 shares, or 5 percent of the total 10 million shares , was transferred to the asset trust in August 2006, with a value of about $1.6 billion.
In July 2007, 9.5 million  shares remained, and 5 percent of those shares were transferred to the asset trust, with a value of $1.76 billion.
In July 2008, there were 9 million  shares remaining, and 5 percent of those shares were transferred to the asset trust, with a value of about $1.8 billion.
In July 2009, there were 8.6 million  shares remaining, and 5 percent of those shares were transferred to the asset trust, with a value of about $1.25 billion.
After the Berkshire B stock split in January 2010, there were 407,253,100 million  shares remaining. In July 2010, 5 percent of those shares were transferred to the asset trust, with a value of about $1.6 billion.
In July 2011, there were 386,890,500 Pledged shares remaining, and 5 percent of those shares were transferred to the asset trust, with a value of about $1.5 billion.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6d9ihw</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/u1k5</id></website><link>http://finance.fortune.cnn.com/2012/03/21/warren-buffett-hedge-fund-bet/</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T12:33:02+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T19:31:21+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi5f1h</id><link>http://finance.fortune.cnn.com/2012/03/21/warren-buffett-hedge-fund-bet/#comment-473871613</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mff7r</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>