<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwbvr0/post/2012-03-30T21:44:09</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I've promised to write my traditional new season assessment prior to game one.  Last year I said we we lose Beltran and KROD, sign Reyes and finish 3rd.  Oh well!  The Wright and Ike injuries and lack of funds defined last year and this one.
I'm almost ready to contribute my review but this blog is about Lucas Duda.Duda, Wright, Bay and Davis can in theory hit over 100 home runs and drive in 375.  My issue then is who might score these runs.  Not Murphy or Torres, at least neither has ever scored over 100.  Wright will given health, and perhaps Bay who has and can run the bases.The facts are that Murphy is a natural #3 hitter who strikes out less than Wright and is potentially a better clutch hitter.  Tejada may end up hitting second and scoring 90 plus runs if he hits like last year.  But lets discuss Duda and Davis.  I predict each will hit 30 plus home runs and Duda will get 100 RBIs first.  Both will hit over .275 but not without the protection of Jason Bay, who need to play like, well .... Jason Bay.  If Bay hits, they all hit, if he fails, well Duda and Davis will each get high OBPs without seeing good pitches to hit and not hit the numbers each is capable of.  Duda is great but its a team sport folks.
My lineup though definitely not Terry Collins
Torres   B   Too many SO to stay in leadoff Spot  .250  will hit 7th or 8th before long 
Tejada   R   Will lead   Must draw walks, learn to bunt, steal n then score 100 runs
Murphy  L    Natural #3    .305   45  2B  18 HR  85 RBIs   105 runs
Wright   R    Best Spot for David     .288  40 2B  24 HR  109 RBIs
Davis    L    Hits his Stride     .292  35 2B  31 HR   94 RBIs
Duda     L    Team HR &amp; RBI leader       .278  36 2B  37 HR   117 RBIs 
Bay       R   The key              .272  32 2B  22 HR  86 RBIs 
Thole &amp;Nickeus       Thole can hit .280 with some power.  

If Bay fails early, get him out of there.  Put in Hairston or trade or promote someone

Then this team can win some games if the pitching holds up.


</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67dlzu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lz6q</id></website><link>http://newyork.mets.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120330%26content_id=27755074%26vkey=news_nym%26c_id=nym</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:33:53+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T01:44:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwbvr0</id><link>http://newyork.mets.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120330%26content_id=27755074%26vkey=news_nym%26c_id=nym#comment-481417775</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5aj4b</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>