<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3i3sd/update/2012-03-29T21:55:01/f98df03edce84e65fd4550ed9efbe4b7581e4dd3cfbc3735a1278aa5497aa6d3</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I think this is a real stretch.  The entire Twilight series is about a girl who is so desperate for a boyfriend that she plans to kill herself in order to spend eternity as walking dead.  If I'd done that for MY high school boyfriend, I'd have some pretty deep regrets by now.  Katniss has few dreams because she has nothing to dream OF.  The only "better life" she's seen is the one lived by a society she despises on principle; she becomes aimless in the second book when she no longer has to provide for her family, and she goes back to hunting to fill the void.  She doesn't  passively accept her objectification as the story unfolds, but rather welcomes it willingly as the one thing she can do to contribute to the freedom effort.  It's also a bit unfair to dismiss the fighting she does throughout the final book; she is a brave soldier and actively participates in the final battle of the war.  

What bothers me most about this, though, is the idea that because she chooses to have a family at the end of the story that all of her previous accomplishments are less meaningful because she chose what is a "traditional" path.  Why is becoming a mother a slap in the face to women?  How does that even make sense?!  A woman who enjoys true equality, as far as I'm concerned, is a woman who is NOT LESSENED IN HER OWN EYES, OR THE EYES OF OTHERS because she's a mother.  Are men considered "lesser" because they become fathers?  I'm actually more offended by the statement that motherhood negates any other accomplishment in a woman's life than I am by the vapid nonsense that runs through Bella's head throughout the whole Twilight series (and believe me, if I wasn't busy writing a term paper DESTROYING that wad of toilet paper I would have dropped it after the first chapter and reconsidered my stance on book-Burning).

Also, I really, really doubt that Suzanne Collins was making a statement when she wrote Peeta as light-featured and Gale as dark-featured.  Give her some credit, will you?  If you really must read something into it, I think it makes more sense to assume that earthy, rugged Gale (and Katniss, too, for that matter) seems better suited to deep, dark tones than Pampered, raised-indoors Peeta.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z81el</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/9dn5</id></website><link>http://www.womensmediacenter.com/feature/entry/katniss-and-bellagetting-to-the-heart-of-the-matter</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T05:18:27+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:55:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3i3sd</id><link>http://www.womensmediacenter.com/feature/entry/katniss-and-bellagetting-to-the-heart-of-the-matter#comment-480134168</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>