<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjo0e/post/2012-03-26T14:50:53</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I think it is a falure on the part of Trayvon's parents that their son is dead. At the age of 16 or 17 my son had no business out walking the streets after dark. If he was not working or at a school function in was in his house or yard when the street lights came on, and if at one of these functions I alway made sure that he had a secure way home and not left to walk. For a youth of Trayvon age nothing good can come from being out on the street after dark. I am a firm believer if you want to dress like a thug you will be identified and treated like a thug. The media can paint a rosy picture of Trayvon all they want but, he was where he had no busniess being, and in my opinion, was dressed like a thug. After all what was the point of wearing a hoody it was not Cold out. He was up to no good and wanted to be unidentifiable. And the Black Panter's (a racist militant organization) to put a  on Zimmerman capture has done nothing but open the door for another thug to Act out some form of transgression against Zimmerman and or his family. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r8gyn</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f7e3</id></website><link>http://mobile.wnd.com/2012/03/witness-trayvon-martin-attacked-zimmerman/</link><postedTime>2012-03-25T00:17:57+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:50:53+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjo0e</id><link>http://mobile.wnd.com/2012/03/witness-trayvon-martin-attacked-zimmerman/#comment-476628594</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zrzft</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>