<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miys52/post/2012-03-22T21:12:05</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Weird,didn't hear a damn thing about this:

A woman accused in the death of a 12-year-old boy who disappeared Christmas Eve and whose charred remains were found in a ditch nearly a week later has admitted she dumped the body, according to authorities. 

Mona Yvette Nelson, 44, is charged with capital murder in the slaying of Jonathan Paul Foster, who  from his northwest Houston home about 2 p.m. Friday.

Nelson was arrested Wednesday at her apartment and had been scheduled to appear in a court hearing this morning, but officials said she had a medical issue and was not brought to the courtroom. They didn't release details of her condition.

Authorities detailed evidence against Nelson to allow a hearing officer to determine if prosecutors had enough information to have arrested her. She was ordered held without bond, which is common in capital murder cases.
Prosecutors said Nelson admitted to police that she was the driver of a silver pickup who got out of the truck and discarded Jonathan's body in the ditch in the 9902 East Hardy near Schilder.

Surveillance cameras at a business near the Spot where the body was discovered had recorded her images, prosecutors said.
They also said investigators found Burned carpet at Nelson's home and discovered twine that appeared to match the string that was used to bind Jonathan's hands.

She also was identified by a witness as the woman seen Friday at the Fosters' small cottage near an apartment complex on Oak.
Investigator believe Nelson took Jonathan to her home Off U.S. 59 and Laura Koppe, where she likely killed him and Burned his body, said HPD homicide investigator Mike Miller.

However, they have yet to determine a possible motive for the slaying.
Nelson was friends with Jonathan's mother's roommate, Sharon Ennamorato. who also was Jonathan's frequent babysitter.

In 1984, Nelson was charged with aggravated robbery and later pleaded guilty in exchange for 10 years' probation, court records show. In 1991, her probation was revoked and she was sent to prison. It was unclear from court documents how she violated probation or how long she spent behind bars.
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y11mf</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t33k</id></website><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/pick-a-topic-and-blog-i-have-to-run-up-to-capitol-hill/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T18:25:23+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T01:12:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miys52</id><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/pick-a-topic-and-blog-i-have-to-run-up-to-capitol-hill/#comment-474113232</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/on6k</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>