<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mku415/post/2012-03-26T10:26:33</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I keep hearing the same arguments over and over. But, I don't think people are getting the big picture. Sure, there are some small tweaks they could do to make things easier with a mouse/keyboard (bringing back the start button, but NOT the start menu, would be a start. Also, adding an optional taskbar toolbar to make the charms  visible would be another thing they could do). But, on the whole, there are some great things to like for mouse/keyboard users in windows 8, if you have an open mind.

First of all, I actually LOVE Metro apps more than traditional desktop apps for reading news/content and for web browsing. Mostly, this is because it seems like pretty much every desktop app is not designed for a screen I actually have. Either I'm at work and I have a high-res but relatively small multi-monitor setup, where all the text is tiny and unreadable, or I have a laptop with, again, high res screen but relatively small - all the text is too small. I can try the stupid "scale text 120%" trick, but everyone knows that just breaks most desktop apps, because they're not designed for anything but the default text size, so text is readable but it gets cut . And some dialogs just no longer work, because the UI inside the dialog reflows to fit the text, but the dialog window size stays the same, so the buttons at the bottom are no longer visible. In metro style apps, all of the UI (not just the text)  scales perfectly for your screen resolution and pixel density. I don't have to think about it. Higher res screens are able to display more items at once, but the text is  readable. If you have a high pixel density screen, like a laptop or an HD desktop monitor, the metro UI handles the scaling for you, and the apps are automatically built for this scaling to happen, so nothing gets cut .

And the windows 7 start menu? I can't believe nobody has noticed that this thing is a joke. It ends up taking a tiny corner of your screen, and makes you click four or five times to get at an app you want, unless you happen to pin it to one of the limited Spots. The search box? Doesn't work. Takes 5 seconds just to spin up. It's faster to just click through to all programs and scroll and open the sub-folder to get to the app I want. I'm not even exaggerating. It's no wonder people clutter their desktops and taskbars with shortcuts. The start menu is broken. It's just that it's all people know, so they don't notice it.

In windows 8, the start screen takes up the whole screen, so instead of only being able to pin 6 or 7 apps to the start menu, I can pin 15, 20, as many as I want. You may have seen screenshots of the start screen in action on a tablet with only a few tiles and thought "that sucks, taking up the whole screen and only showing like 9 tiles? pass".  But if you have a high res desktop monitor, a lot more icons and tiles fit on there at once. I can also make my own categories and jump right to the category I want (semantic zoom works with the ctrl + scrollwheel gesture everyone is used to using in other apps). If I don't have something pinned, I just start typing the name of the app (no need to click on a search bar, just start typing) and within two or three letters, the search has INSTANTLY found the app AND highlighted it, so I just hit enter to launch the app. No clicking on a search bar and waiting for it to spin up. It happens instantly. It's amazing, and I hate that people complain about it so much because I bet the IT managers will ask for a way to disable it at the policy level and I'll have to use that stupid start menu again.

Now, that being said, I will admit that there ARE a few issues left in the consumer preview. First of all, hot corners were a bad choice. They don't work that well if you have multiple monitors. It's fine to have them available, they work OK if you have only one screen, but there should  be an option to disable them in favor of  visible clickable UI elements. For example, the start button shouldn't have been removed. It should have been optional, and on by default. Also, the taskbar needs a toolbar with all the charms, so they can stay Always visible. I don't need to pin apps to my taskbar as much anymore in windows 8, so there's more room down there for toolbars like that.

Oh, and just so you know, there's a utility called Start8 that brings the start button back, and even makes it so you can have the start screen not run in full-screen (it has options from full screen and different sizes. I have mine set at "large"). I really like it - and I hope Microsoft makes this an "official" option in the final version. I think most desktop users would be quite satisfied with that setup.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66dfnh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/r7w0</id></website><link>http://preview.pcmag.com/article2/0,2817,2402031,00.asp</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T15:07:41+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T14:26:33+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mku415</id><link>http://preview.pcmag.com/article2/0,2817,2402031,00.asp#comment-476428612</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cxxx2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>