<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mizmo2/update/2012-03-23T04:29:58/04541944713396761ec8220c32b6614a00facc9806d23efa7b556d409561edc9</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Perhaps you truly believe that if you use big words people will give your opinion more credit. You are incredibly far from the truth about The Hunger Games.  From your article it is blatantly obvious that you have not read the Hunger Games and are making vast assumptions which are wildly inaccurate. 
"And when Katniss finds true love with fellow District 12er Peeta Mellark (Josh Hutcherson) in the Heat of the Hunger Games, the development is hobbled by a shocking deficit in chemistry between the stars." 
Read the books and you will know why they did that. Katniss it under the impression the whole games that Peeta and herself are only Acting in love for survival purposes. Peeta truly loves Katniss but she does not become aware of her own feelings for him until book #2. They are not supposed to have a deep and wonderful love connection. They just battled for days on end for their lives it's not happy go lucky. 
Seriously- read the books before reporting such irresponsible journalism. Although I am an avid fan- I wouldn't mind reading well crafted critiques and respecting other's opinions, but this article was awful. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6euqtu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ydw9</id></website><link>http://motherjones.com/node/168156</link><postedTime>2012-03-18T23:57:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T08:29:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mizmo2</id><link>http://motherjones.com/node/168156#comment-474314976</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zd3sr</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-18</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>