<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/312236/post/127936912/comment/328556120</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I've been making this recipe for years and everyone loves it.

2 sticks of softened unsalted butter(If hard just pop the butter in the microwave for 15 odd seconds)

3/4 cup cocoa powder(unsweetened)

6 eggs

1 tablespoon vanilla extract

2 cups sugar(I like to use a cup and a half and taste the batter then add some more if required)

1 1/2 cup + a tablespoon of all purpose flour

1 tsp salt

One large handful of nuts of your choice(I used a mixture of hazelnuts,cashews and almonds)

 Roughly chop the nuts..you want sizable chunks, keep aside. 

Preheat oven to 350 degrees Fahrenheit

In a bowl beat the eggs with the sugar and vanilla

 

In another bowl measure out the flour and salt

 

Melt the butter in a saucepan on the stove(on medium Heat) stir in the chocolate and mix well, then take it  the stove

I take it  the stove prior to adding the eggs and sugar mixture because if the chocolate mixture is Too hot it wills scramble the eggs and somehow chocolate scrambled eggs don't sound very appealing.

 

After taking the saucepan Off the Heat, let it cool for a few minutes

 

Armed with a whisk, throw in the egg,sugar and vanilla mixture and whisk violently until the eggs are fully incorporated, taste it to see if the sugar is ok (and no you are not going to die of salmonella)

 

Next add in the flour and nuts and mix well

 

Pour batter in pan of your choice.

 

Bake for 15 odd minutes if you're using cupcake trays,23-25 minutes if using a cake pan. Personally I like to shove a skewer through the middle of the cake and check if it comes out clean, if it does, your cake's ready. Let it cool completely before taking it out the pan



I like to make it in cupcake tins, comes out easily just grease the tins well</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:312236:127936912</id><idPostId>127936912</idPostId><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:312236</id><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><link>http://www.denpdf.com</link><displayName>denpdf.com</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.denpdf.com/brownies-from-scratch-how-to-make-the-best-brownies-from-scratch/</link><displayName>brownies from scratch- How to make the best brownies from scratch?</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T15:09:09.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:312236:127936912:328556120</id><link>http://www.denpdf.com/brownies-from-scratch-how-to-make-the-best-brownies-from-scratch/#IDComment328556120</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T15:09:09.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on brownies from scratch- How to make the best brownies from scratch? by Ŧãŧěř Ťöţ</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>ab9c45933fc43414b766915e1926fda9</idEmailMd5><displayName>Ŧãŧěř Ťöţ</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>Ŧãŧěř Ťöţ commented on &lt;a href="http://www.denpdf.com/brownies-from-scratch-how-to-make-the-best-brownies-from-scratch/"&gt;brownies from scratch- How to make the best brownies from scratch?&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>