<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkbucr/update/2012-03-26T09:21:39/263742eeaf1bda089ee3e39819f39c6b48bc128c6c4dea0a3c29c6c199a44669</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkbmgv</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lgovi</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I hope so.
Is it possible? For sure. Is it likly to happen? Increasingly so.
In my opinion it all  on de-centralized storage technologies being introduced in the market as soon as possible. 
Many experts call for some kind of incentive for personal stoarage systems. Such incentives are not uncommon in Germany, since there are all sort of tax-credits &amp; cheap loans for modernizing homes, Heating systems and all things energy efficency. 
If this happens cheap home based multi-kWh storages systems could become a reality rather fast, since the technology is already available. If those systems could follow the learning curve of PV-Solar systems in the coming years, the question will be: Who is dump enough NOT to get -grid? 
Since the price of storage technology is all about expanding the  production capacity, I am very optimistic that it will happen untill 2020. Simply because the auto &amp; chemical industry is currently investing billions in expanding their factories &amp; mining operations for multi-kWh lithium-ion Batteries and stuff like that. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rin07</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/68bl</id></website><link>http://cleantechnica.com/2012/03/26/germany-7-5-gw-of-new-solar-power-in-2011-confirmed/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T11:51:00+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T13:21:39+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkbucr</id><link>http://cleantechnica.com/2012/03/26/germany-7-5-gw-of-new-solar-power-in-2011-confirmed/#comment-476387687</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zrg3b</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>