<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tcrp/post/2012-03-29T09:28:51</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>REPOST of a reply previously:
I am not sure of the exact percentages, but I have seen that late-life, and end-of-life expenses account, by far, for the largest chunk of our healthcare expenditures. Baring a kidney transplant or some super-nova of a health problem, we simply don't, as a cross-sectional observation will reveal, spend all that much throughout our lifetimes on healthcare...until we  the late life stages.

As a revelation to support this statement, I offer the weirdest window on this fact that I could find. The GAO did an accounting profile on healthcare expense for US smokers versus US non-smokers just a few years ago. It found that smokers actually drain the health-care funds LESS because once they get sick, they go very quickly, and live a shorter life span anyway. On the flip side, the league of grannies in workout clothes living in grand coffee-klatch retirement, cost the system a bundle. They are healthy, and when they go, it takes a LONG time, and just sucks down the resources. The health care industry would be better controlled if regulators looked at this one main  of the cost schedule. Americans have developed an unnatural fear of death, and I am not sure whether this stems from a diminishing of faith or what, it has been noted that the end-of-life expenses in 'blue staes' trend much higher then in 'red states', and that avowed atheists clamour to be given every life-prolonging technology there is while staring at the ceiling in a hospital ward. (a discussion for another venue) I lean toward no philosophy in my statement, I am only stating the statistical facts. 

Obesity? Diabetes? Americans could avoid a lot of these maladies if they took advantage of education and preventive care, but they don't. Even those with 100% cost coverage don't, but rarely, use them. I have my own theory on THOSE issues that fit a different blog. The health issues here in the US are a direct result of interference by the same people who want to control our treatment of those problems. A vague generality about corporate-government corruption, but unless you want short term, but extremely violent social and political upheavel by removing corporate subsidies and entitlement cutbacks in one swift drop of the , it's not going to happen. And as long as Lindsey's getting naked, or Charlie Sheen is uttering a stream of profoundly frat-boy like commentary, or we continue to cling to the words of wisdom flowing from the font of genius that is Sean Penn, or whatever other flavor of the month we have to take our minds away from the fact that we let Washington loot us blind, WE ARE GOING TO CONTINUE TO SPIRAL DOWN. 

Sidebar: We have become a nation of government dependent whiners. How many of you could survive if the power went  for a year without warning...tomorrow? Some West Asian country manages to get a nuke  both eastern and western shores on a ship and boosts those babies to 100000 feet over the eastern seaboard and over the great basin. EMP wave... Poof. Space Mountain grinds to a halt. Aunt Edna's Airbus A380 flight falls from the sky. The elevators in the Empire State Building get stuck. NYPD can't respond because the electronic ignitions on their trucks are baked. John Travolta's 65K Breitling watch quits working, but he can't call the dealer because cell phones all die. American Idol can't go on the air...because there is no television. No one can blog or be cooler on line because the internet, and their computers (along with the porn collection and the recipe files)...die. Socialized medicine? Ha. After the initial triage, those that can pay will get treated. The rest of you...won't. 
End sidebar.

You will find that in socialized medicine, end-of-life scenarios cost less simply because the committees in charge generally, (and I say generally, because there are  exceptions) deny life-prolonging treatment once it becomes obvious where the patient's health trend is going. Hence the vigorous European traffic to the clinics in Switzerland for the assisted suicide cocktail. Also, the amount of expenditure by the state varies from person to person in socialized medicine. The UK system, for example, has a tiered system of care. Tier 1, Tier 2, etc. Say you are listed to recieve Tier 4 benefits. You receive the exact same care as everyone else in Tier 4. Everyone is equal. Except you have access to more options and higher quality if you are in the next tiers up the chain. And what determines your Tier 'level' qualification? Wait for it....your economic status! Ta-da! The CEO of a British company receives better care then the ale delivery truck driver. And that's a fact. This is a hidden reality that the media doesn't talk about. In France, do you think the cheesemaker in Marseilles has the same access to healthcare as President Sarkozy? Or that Vladimar Putin sits in the waiting room next to a country farmer's wife with 4 children? Or the prima ballerina at the Bolshoi has to wait the same amount of time for an x-ray on her ankle as the steel worker who also took a fall? If you believe the answer is yes, you are living in  or sucking up to Michael Moore. We hear of advances in Italy on the field of transplant surgery or fertility. Do you honestly think these places are part of the socialized medical system? Not a chance! These are corporate-supported research facilities. The Italian governement can't afford trash removal (the mafia stuffs it in old salt mines near Naples...for a fee, lol, true story!), how can they afford the research? And, if socialized medicine is so great, why did Pelosi and her great crusade for equality specifically exempt Congress from having to participate? Why does Congress have its own medical facilities Off limits to even the liberal press? Why were unions exempted? And if that doesn't convince you that all the cards are not on the table, why is it, with the wonderful miracle of socialized medicine being so irrefutably better then the American system of care, that so many wealthy non-Americans and foreign leaders leave their wonderful socialized medical facilities to travel to the US for serious healthcare?

Next. So many of you tout the superiority of the European healthcare system. In fact, you tout their way of life as being better. Yet, I don't see many of you jonesing to emigrate. Why not? Come on. They only take 75-85% of your paycheck in taxes... Put the money where the mouth is....
Truth is, most of you couldn't survive over there. 
Unemployment is higher. Education levels are higher. Prices for everything but basics is higher. Fuel is about 15 bucks a gallon... 
Sure, the life expectancy is higher in some places. We'd ALL live longer if we could retire at age 55 or somesuch nonsense. The Greek people Burned down half of Athens because the government had the unmitigated gall to raise the age of retirement from 50 to 52 or 55. Oh. the humanity! Oh, if only... I'm 55, and I see no day of retirement, because my life is pretty damned entertaining as it is. (As long as Washington DC doesn't encroach any further, I'm happy. BTW, that's why Americans as a nation excelled until recently, because our government, more or less, left us the hell alone to do just that.)(An autocratic or socialist nation is only as intelligient as it's bureaucracy. And ours...isn't.) 
Sure they live longer, but what true quality of life does one have unless you retire WITH MONEY over there? At a 75% tax rate? Let me know how that works out for you. You never hear much about the money families in Europe. Why? Because it wrecks the myth of a socially equal society.

And finally. You CAN'T emigrate and become a citizen in Europe unless you meet certain strict criteria. Unlike here, where everyone who sneaks in gets taken care of, they DO have a national ID and a national healthcare card. And unless you show a liquid asset worth in the mid-six figures AND ARE IN GOOD HEALTH documented by a physical, at this point in EU history, you cannot become a full-fledged citizen. You haven't got snowball's chance in hell. Same with Australia. Try emigratin' to the land down under. Or New Zealand. Or South Africa. Or Morocco. YOU CAN'T EVEN BECOME A CITIZEN OF MEXICO! 

I won't convince all of you that the curtain is only partially open to show you the good side, but, flawed as it is, it sure is a lot better overall then anywhere else. 
(IE: in Acapulco, any treatment in the ER on an American tourist requires pre-approval by credit card of a 6K fee.) 
Can it be improved? Absolutely. 
Is Obamcare the way to do it? Absolutely NOT. 

And that's my 55.5 cents.
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6msvob</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/fzi6</id></website><link>http://www.freeenterprise.com/health-care/truth-comes-out-health-care-0</link><postedTime>2012-03-20T14:03:33+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:28:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tcrp</id><link>http://www.freeenterprise.com/health-care/truth-comes-out-health-care-0#comment-479488025</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hp293</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>