<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3i65e/post/2012-03-29T21:13:52</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This is actually in reply to Drefan, but for some odd reason DBPB won't allow me to respond directly.


My name is Ginny. I am a fifteen year old girl from Georgia. I have two older brothers and a dog. My family lives in an upper middle class neighborhood. My mom teaches English at Chattahoochee Technical Institute and my dad owns a Printing and Design business. My mother was raised as a third generation cotton farmer in the deep southern part of Georgia. My dad was raised by a baptist preacher. My parents met when my dad was a business apprentice for my grandpa. They got married at 19 and 21 and went to the University of Georgia together. almost 15 years later, my oldest brother Rob was born. Then, 6 years later, my brother Zeke was born. Two years later, I was born. My parents baptized all of us at the age of 6 months. We were all baptized in the same Presbyterian church. In 8th grade, we were all confirmed into our church. Once we turned 15, we were given the choice of what church we wanted to go to or if we wanted to go to church at all. Rob chose to stay at our small Presbyterian church and joined a non-denominational church when he went  to college. He joined a Christian Fraternity in the middle of his Sophomore year. He met his girlfriend, Dani, when the sorority sisters to his fraternity visited. They are getting married in late 2012/early 2011. Zeke chose to stop going to church. He is unsure of his beliefs at this moment, but is leaning towards Atheism. I currently go to our small Presbyterian church on sunday mornings and nights. I work in the nursery in the mornings and go to choir and youth group at night. On wednesdays, I go to my best friend's church with her. Currently, I am non denominational. I have many beliefs similar to Atheists. As of right now, I am more similar to an Atheist than a Catholic. I am pro choice. I am for gay marriage. I have a mouth like a sailor and have admitted to hating people. I don't go around screaming my religion at people. The only differences? I believe in a higher power. I am against premarital sex and probably won't drink alcohol. This doesn't mean I go around calling people whores and alcoholics. Both of my parents drink. Rob drinks. Dani would drink, but is really dainty and gets tipsy over a few sips of a cosmo. Now, for all I know, you could be against premarital sex and drinking, but most Atheists I have met are not. They like to live freely and I understand that, I do. The choices most people make like sex and alcohol and drugs are tempting, but I feel the consequences would outweigh any other outcome. We really aren't that different. ***Now, to your questions. I'm afraid that my answers may not be very clear or help anyone's case, but they are what I believe and I suppose that's all you really asked. I don't argue with people over religion, so it's not my problem. I do, however, believe that people who argue over religion will have some consequences, maybe not Hell. I do believe that God is omnipotent and omniscient. And(this may not make as much sense out loud as it does in my mind) I don't believe that God would want to change his future mind. This creates a sort of paradox and if God is omniscient, then he wouldn't create a paradox. After all, is this not the reason why many believe time travel will not work? Interfering with changes in time can cause certain outcomes and parallel universes and all sorts of sloppy universal messes. God being omniscient would realize this. However, it would be possible for Him to do it, in my opinion at least. To your next question. I don't plan on interfering with your life, but let me tell you a quick story. A man was trapped on a desert island waiting for God to rescue him. A helicopter came across the man and landed on the island. The pilot asked the man if he needed help. The man said no and that he was waiting for God to rescue him. The pilot left. Next a passing boat came along. The captain of the boat asked the man is he needed help. The man kindly said no and that he was waiting for God to save him. The captain left. Next, a plane found the man. The pilot of the plane asked the man if he needed help. The man kindly said no and that he was waiting for God to rescue him. The pilot left. Days turned to weeks and weeks turned to months and the man died of starvation and Dehydration. When the man got to Heaven he asked God why he didn't save him. God simply replied, "I sent a helicopter, a boat, and a plane. You did this to yourself." You never know how God helps you because it is never direct. "God works in mysterious ways." To your death toll, I somewhat agree with you. Our God is a cruel God, yes. But, our God is a just God. Those who deserve punishment shall receive it. Being only fifteen, I am not certain of my beliefs, therefore I cannot answer your questions perfectly and with confidence. My views may change and I do not have many answers and a full understanding. However, I don't have many answers and a full understanding of life either. I don't know what it takes to get to Heaven. John 3:16 says "God so loved the world he gave his only begotten Son that whoever believes in Him shall never die but have eternal life." Yet, I have been to several services in which I was told that to go to Heaven, I had to protest sin and hate the Wicked. I believe that Churches have harshly distorted the true meaning of the Holy Bible.     In my opinion, churches confuse us. I have my beliefs and they do not change with what churches tell me. I search for my answers on my own. As of now, I believe in the Theory of Intelligent Design,yet I also believe in the story of The Original Sin. I don't have all of my questions answered, but I'm close. As for people telling you that you're going to Hell, those are the crazy ones. I can promise you, most of us are NOT like that. I can name  the top of my head at least five people that I am very close friends with who are close friends with each other that have very different beliefs. My friend Kelsea is Catholic. My friend Megan is Jewish. My friend Magall is Muslim. My best friend, Joy, is non denominational, though we've both had discussions of being Agnostic and Atheist. Usually we Christians are pretty accepting of all beliefs and faiths. I mean, come on, aren't there crazies from all beliefs?


***The answers to the questions start here, before that is some background of myself, my family, and my beliefs. By the way, sorry for the long post.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/mgs81k</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dxu1</id></website><link>http://dearblankpleaseblank.com/permalink.php?viewid=595768</link><postedTime>2011-10-03T18:35:09+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:13:52+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3i65e</id><link>http://dearblankpleaseblank.com/permalink.php?viewid=595768#comment-480103350</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cndxx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-10-03</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>