<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw1bf2/post/2012-03-31T00:14:41</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>

This is what
has happened to Obamacare. A well thought out scheme is promoted democratically
over a period of two to three years. But the opposition, not accepting the
norms of true democracy and enforcing its extensions, refused to accept it and
kept on agitating against it. The freely available media, which Depends on
creating controversy which increases its viewership and thus revenue, used its
own definition of the extended meaning of democracy, kept the flames of
controversy Burning and here we are almost in square one after about four
years.


This is not
going to be the end. We can expect this to continue for several years till our
nation is really doomed. Is the preservation of party rule so sacrosanct that national
interests have become secondary? Have we all become so blind that we are for
war one day and peace the next day; for increasing taxes one day and just the
opposite the next day; for stricter regulations today and for abolition of any
control tomorrow. When we flip flop so much as a nation, why blame Romney for
swaying to the wind?


This is not
going to last much longer. When words fail, when reasonableness is ignored,
when justice is denied with impunity, when the system is aborted, people
revolt. I am waiting for that day. Because, if nothing else, democracy has
taught us how to successfully agitate and get our reasonable demands conceded.
We may be delayed, but we cannot be stopped. nirmala@sify.com


</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/674ur4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/politics/scotus-health-care-whats-next/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T01:33:24+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:14:41+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw1bf2</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/politics/scotus-health-care-whats-next/index.html#comment-481519332</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gnmu2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>