<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3w43j/post/2012-03-30T01:59:37</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m33kzr</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/w5bj</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Sorry, but I don't know what you're smoking.  Sandy Bridge graphics still sucks, and everybody seems to have an opinion about supposed advances in Ivy Bridge before it's even released, but I can tell you already that AMD will outpace it because of Intel's history in graphics.  Remember the i740?  I do.  And I've used every single Intel graphics chipset since then and compared it to the competition.  Frankly, Intel ISN'T any competition.

AMD had low-power chips for embedded devices.  You're probably thinking about Geode.  Geode was an x86 low-power processor in many variants.  It never scaled that well because it used old architecture.  It was a dead end, but has a few uses in embedded platforms.  It is seen as an x86 alternative to old ARM chips (think ARMv5-6).  It's obsolete now.  I see it as "throwback" chip architecture.  What they did was repurpose the old architecture in a low-power variant which allowed them to get slightly more scaleability out of the old architecture, but it didn't really have a future.  This is what Intel did with the Pentium III architecture, readapting it to create the Pentium M (and early Atom's).

Yes, what you say about Qualcomm is true though.  Microsoft wants baseline specs to be DX9 across the board for all Windows 8 &amp; WOA devices.  They are pushing OEM's to produce more up to date specs on their hardware.  For ARM, this means better chip improvements.  There are other things that they are pushing too, like that system manufacturers can't use switchable graphics like NVIDIA Optimus/Hybrid SLI for power management.  Microsoft says (and I agree with this) that higher-performance GPU's shouldn't rely on a low-power GPU for power savings.  The mainsteam GPU should do its own power savings.  Remember that they are still focussing a lot of efforts on getting  levels in check too, so this isn't just a paper spec that isn't going to benefit the user.  In fact, GPU makers like NVIDIA need to work harder on providing GPU's that offer better power management, and when you're talking about high-end notebook systems with discrete graphics, as powerful as the GPU is, it still shouldn't consume that much power just drawing Aero and doing H.264 decode.  If ARM SoC's can do both without a Heat spreader and active heatsink, then that dual-GPU card should be able to do the same.  All of the ARM manufacturers have to abide by the DX9 target though, not just NVIDIA.  It's a big jump going from mobile graphics to desktop-class 3D though, since the current ARM spec of only having OpenGL ES 2.0 is still several years behind even DX9.  AMD has chips that exceed this spec already (their APU's meet the premium WHQL spec, even in the lowest-end APU's, and they ALL have hardware VT with SLAT and have for a couple years now....try to say that about Intel), and  life is still pretty good (an E-450 notebook typically gets around 6 hours on just a modest ).  Intel needs far better graphics and performance vs. Battery life, and ARM need to work on getting the specs up higher.  AMD is sitting pretty right now, but they aren't sitting still.
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hj82g</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5zaa</id></website><link>http://www.tgdaily.com/node/62387</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T18:42:41+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T05:59:37+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3w43j</id><link>http://www.tgdaily.com/node/62387#comment-480301407</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8zjsy</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>