<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/a2650k/update/2010-07-07T10:57:00/573d6832aa87e8818e9466b75994cb82fe6580e4dbdc8f25309bc9a9fbecce26</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Suppose the thing is built and is a perfectly functioning marvel of technology, a real triumph.

What is it a triumph over? A triumph over nature, sure. It would be a testament to the force of industry. Certainly a triumph of will, enterprise and mind. 

But not of high intelligence, it only takes mind to do it, or, industrious intelligence. After we witness its performance and know, yes, by the will and mind of man a flying underwater torpedo bomber exists, is anyone to feel proud? Whose spirits will soar at an encounter with the truth of this thing; at the idea of zooming , submerging, killing a bunch of people and destroying their ship or whatever, then zooming untouched back to hearth and home?

Maybe many will get a kick out of it; but the ‘kick’ is reliant on omitting any thoughts of the monumental cost, which is not merely money spent, but money removed from the country’s volition elsewhere; or the thousands of acres paved over for bases, which is never to be nature again; or the filthy tons of Burnt fuel it spews, which we all have to breathe, though we might get some interesting sunsets out of it; or the umpteen hours of attention paid to it, years of training and zooming and submerging, yet the thing is never used for its purpose. After all, it is a thing everyone wishes to never use.

Right now, as an idea and a plan, the thing is a dabbling pie-in-the-sky pipe dream slated to become monument, a human embarrassment in every realm save comic books and movies. Certainly a kind of crime to spend on dime on it while millions are out of work.

Once it is real, it will be a summit of irrelevancy. In the Scope of mankind’s endeavors, an accomplishment so singularly tangential as to rival the pyramids in great costly uselessness, except it won’t be around 4000 years from now for anyone to marvel at. At best, it will be a picture in a book causing someone to think, ‘look at just how caught up and fraught they were. They could have done anything, but they chose to spend their time, money and effort, on that?’
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/as8amn</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/7872645/Pentagon-plans-flying-submarine.html</link><postedTime>2010-07-05T12:52:27+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2010-07-07T14:57:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/a2650k</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/7872645/Pentagon-plans-flying-submarine.html#comment-60939211</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2010-07-05</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>