<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwpx7k/post/2012-03-31T07:25:11</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Maybe...just maybe the Flames are starting to realize what the rest of the hockey world knew last year, and that is that this team is in MAJOR need of rebuilding. However to what extent do you rebuild this team? Well there are a lot of things that need changing, and those changes start right at the very top. Feaster has to go. Last year this team finished 10th in the west, and the only change he made was to trade away one of your top D-men, and then ice the same team that missed the playoffs last year. He (Feaster) tied his own hands with terrible contracts that didn't allow him to bring in help, or even trade for it. So instead, he hoped for a miracle, and of course...didn't get it. If he resigns any of the UFA vets this spring, that should be a clear cut sign that he has to go, because it shows just how little he really knows about hockey teams in the NHL. 
  Sutter in my opinion did a pretty good job when you consider the lack of true talent he had to use night in and night out. Of course he will probably loose his job regardless, but he isn't this teams weakest link. They simply have very little talent, he knew it, nothing he could do about it, he had to use what was given to him. 
  Kipper and Iggy in my opinion are the two very best players on this team, and the reason they didn't finish down by Columbus in the standings. Kipper kept this team in games all season long that they had no business being in. When your team gives up 40+ shots on a nightly basis, and you still win...you thank your goaltender, because he is the reason. Kipper may have another 1 or 2 good seasons left in him, and right now there is no one in the system that can come close to his level of play to replace him. 
  Now a lot of people are getting on Iggy, and blaming him for all of this, but you have to remember something. This team does not have consistent secondary scoring. Iginla is by far your best forward, and the only true star on forward. The problem with being the only real constant scoring threat on the ice is that other teams know it too, and its a lot easier to double team one guy on the ice than it it to do it with 2 or 3. Keep Iginla in check and Off the score sheet, and all the teams know there really isn't anyone to pick up the slack. In my opinion, there isn't a single player on that team that can keep up to his level of play, and every team in the NHL knows that.
  Other than Kipper and Iggy, there isn't really any players on this team that I would say had job security. Want further proof of that? A couple weeks ago you had an emergancy call up of that Sven kid...not from the Heat, but from the WHL, and he totally outplayed 90% of the guys on this team...that right there should speak volumes about the true lack of depth and talent the Flames currently have on the roster. Sure this kid has all the ingredients of a future star in the NHL, but he is still playing at the WHL level, and already outplaying your regular NHL players on a nightly basis...if thats not a red flag, I don't know what is. 
  Give Sutter, Iggy, and Kipper some credit for getting this team as close as they did to a playoff Spot, because in all honesty, they have no business being there with the rest of the "talent" (or lack of) that they have on this team.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67x20c</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7mag</id></website><link>http://www.calgarysun.com/2012/03/30/flames-drop-home-tilt-to-avs</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T03:49:37+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T11:25:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwpx7k</id><link>http://www.calgarysun.com/2012/03/30/flames-drop-home-tilt-to-avs#comment-481750987</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l4yf8</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>