<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3khb8/post/2012-03-29T22:23:15</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39t81</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6drqg</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Chill out, man. Everyone is entitled to his opinion.

"Buying British" is never a problem. The problem is buying not so good British. At a premium price. 

Develop Downing? He is 27 and has some 30 caps for England. This is his prime and arguably for all wingers at his age. May be he's a victim of bad chemistry and the pressure under the shadows of Steve McManaman and Steve Heighway. I don't know. But the result said it all. He is part of the mediocrity of this team.

This is the Champions League Era. Money works. You buy players to contribute right away at a 20M price tag, not develop them. C/D had 100M to spend and no 4th Spot. Try to imagine if SAF, Wenger, Redknapp had that kind of money last summer. C/D has blown their chances. 

We root for our team but we don't necessarily have to accept mediocrity the current management brought us. For Fuck sake I jumped out of the couch when Downing smashed that winner against Stoke. Did I care who scored? Fuck, no. All I cared was Liverpool scored.

Finally, what potential do you see in CHAD? Believe it or not, I have not lost hope on Carroll. He just needs 2 wingers who are willing to get their jerseys dirty at the baseline. Downing? Hendo? Their jerseys were never dirtier than Gerrard's. 

Can't agree with your logic.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z8ng3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/y675</id></website><link>http://liverpool.theoffside.com/premier-league/dalglish-and-comolli-need-stewart-downing-to-come-good.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T05:11:49+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:23:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3khb8</id><link>http://liverpool.theoffside.com/premier-league/dalglish-and-comolli-need-stewart-downing-to-come-good.html#comment-480154538</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>