<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ud13/update/2012-03-29T15:10:05/504956ac092d5fc4e8cec70e00c761e380d3603cc69d9408ab872f625e3b550e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nsme</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8bgsg</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>There's no reason to believe that DeRosa or Lombardozzi would be improvements over Desmond.  Lombardozzi only has 31 major league at bats, and he's just 23.  He might be better than Desmond eventually, but there's also a very good chance that he'll struggle to adjust to major league pitching.  DeRosa hasn't hit in 3 years (and for that matter, he's only played 4 innings at 2B since 2008).

They problem isn't necessarily that they lack a lead-Off hitter type, it's that the guys they put in that Spot in the lineup can't get on base.

I don't really understand what you're trying to say about an impact hitter.  There's no one in the Nats lineup who has put up numbers like Fielder or Votto, but Morse's 2011 and Zimmerman's 2010 were comparable with Holliday's 2009-2011 seasons and better than Berkman's. 

Furthermore, I'd argue that your theory on "impact hitters" is just plain wrong.  The Phillies won 102 games last year without an impact hitter other than Hunter Pence, and he didn't show up until game #106 (they played .628 ball before he got there, and .630 ball after).  Teams score runs based on the offensive production of their entire lineup -- and that can be achieved with or without "impact" hitters.

Nobody thinks that the Nats will win a lot of games if they don't get good offensive seasons from Morse, Zimmerman, Werth, Espinosa and Ramos, plus some contribution from Desmond, Lombo, Harper and LaRoche.

Edit:
Morse wOBA in 2011: .387.  Zimmerman wOBA in 2010: .389.

Holliday 3-year average 2009-2011: .393.  Berkman: .378.

2011 Phillies: Howard: .354; Victorino: .372; Mayberry: .369; Utley: .344.

So, yeah, what I wrote was exactly right.  Morse in 2011 and Zimmerman in 2010 were comparable to Holliday over the past 3 years and better than Berkman.  They were also better than any of the Phillies in 2011 until Pence showed up.

The Nationals would have been better served by replacing Desmond and Ankiel with league average players than by replacing Morse with Votto.  Do the math.  And learn to write.

(And not that it matters, but Dunn and Willingham were both better in 2010 than Berkman's average year from 2009-2011, and Dunn's 2009 was better than Holliday's 2009-2011 average year.)</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zlnnt</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gyfc</id></website><link>http://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2012/03/offseason-in-review-washington-nationals.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:46:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:10:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ud13</id><link>http://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2012/03/offseason-in-review-washington-nationals.html#comment-479774913</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ctgy</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>