<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3i17f/post/2012-03-29T21:38:23</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3i7g7</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hase3</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I've had this argument many times. Its  the same. You people give wrestling fans a bad name.

"LMAO and next your going to say cena can wrestle huh ?"

Yes. What else is he doing in the ring? It's not gymnastics, it's not water polo, and it's not Basketball. Must be wrestling.

"Austin is 1 of my idols but technical wise he was'nt that good your obv a kid if you think other wise"

How old are you? I ask because while you call me, a man who has been watching wrestling for decades and actually saw Hogan wrestle in his prime, a "kid" and then you not only write but formulate opinions as a child.
What you call "technical" wrestling is merely heavy offensive wrestling. Using plenty of offensive moves, tons of armbars and dragon screws, and no-selling everything so you can fit in as many Spots as humanly possible doesn't make you good. Generating a crowd reaction in the ring as well as telling a good story makes you a good wrestler. Thus Cena, Austin, and Hogan are the best.

And if you watch Austin from his time as Stunning Steve or as a member of the  Blondes, or throughout most of his career he used a variety of different offensive moves, he merely changed it, like all greats, to suit the audience who he was performing in front of."and shut the hell up hogan was horrible in the ring"

No, he wasn't. Hogan told a story, set up Spots, and got a bigger reaction than anyone in history. He also  used limited offense so the fans would care about his moves more. He actually had a more offensive based repetoir during his time in IGP in Japan however he, being smart, changed his style to suit the American audience, as his style here Gained him much more adulation.

When a man used tons of moves per match he gets little to no reaction. Why is this? Because fans are not emotionally invested in each move, thus they don't care. This is why Hogan, Austin, and Cena are the best.

"wrestlers great 1s well Bret Hart , Y2J , Owen Hart , Eddie Guerrero , Hbk , Cm Punk , Aj Styles , Davey Richards ,Mr Perfect and many many more,"So men who for the most part were and are Midcarders and can't hack it with real Main-Eventers? Tell me, which one of them was a real draw? Bret and HBK got dominated by Hogan. Eddie was never a real draw. Owen was a Midcarder, Davey was a Midcarder. AJ is only good enough to be a midcarder, Hennig was good but he was never main event tier in WWF, or really anywhere else aside from AWA, but they were in the midst of a fall.

And CM Punk isn't yet at the level of Cena, isn't a proven draw, and even then he has changed his style a lot of the years to cater to the audience.

Regardless all of this continues to show you don't understand wrestling.
"Austin made up for his lack of in ring abilty with being a brawler and having a great character plus epic promo work."Those other two parts go into being a wrestler. Even then Austin was great in the ring because he knew how to work an audience and catered to them by changing it. That makes a good wrestlers, not tons of different moves.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z4pf5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cq26</id></website><link>http://www.wrestlezone.com/news/252207-jerry-lawler-reveals-his-favorite-wm-match-to-call</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:24:00+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:38:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3i17f</id><link>http://www.wrestlezone.com/news/252207-jerry-lawler-reveals-his-favorite-wm-match-to-call#comment-480121909</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lqpgm</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>