<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwxeda/post/2012-03-30T20:22:29</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>and ......these people vote for our elected ......this is scarey...

It's time again for the annual 'Stella Awards'! 

For those unfamiliar with these awards, they are named after 
81-year-old Stella Liebeck who spilled hot coffee on herself and 
successfully sued the McDonald's in New Mexico , where she purchased 
coffee. You remember, she took the lid  the coffee and put it 
between her knees while she was driving. Who would ever think one could 
get Burned doing that, right? That's right; these are awards for the 
most outlandish lawsuits and verdicts in the U.S. You know the kind of 
cases that make you scratch your head. So keep your head scratcher handy 

Here are the Stellas for this past year -- 2011 

* SEVENTH PLACE * 


Kathleen Robertson of Austin , Texas was awarded $80,000 by a jury of 
her peers after breaking her ankle tripping over a toddler who was 
running inside a furniture store. The store owners were understandably 
surprised by the verdict, considering the running toddler was her own 
son. 

Start scratching! 


* SIXTH PLACE * 

Carl Truman, 19, of Los Angeles , California won $74,000 plus medical 
expenses when his neighbor ran over his hand with a Honda Accord. 
Truman apparently didn't notice there was someone at the wheel of the 
car when he was trying to steal his neighbor's hubcaps. 


Scratch some more... 


* FIFTH PLACE * 

Terrence Dickson, of Bristol , Pennsylvania , who was leaving a house he 
had just burglarized by way of the garage. Unfortunately for Dickson, 
the automatic garage door opener malfunctioned and he could not get the 
garage door to open. Worse, he couldn't re-enter the house because the 
door connecting the garage to the house locked when Dickson pulled it 
shut. Forced to sit for eight, count 'em, EIGHT days and survive on a case 
of Pepsi and a large bag of dry dog food, he sued the homeowner's 
insurance company claiming undue mental Anguish. What "Mental Anquish?" He didn't have the mind to pull a small rope hanging from the door opener and release the door to be opened manually. Amazingly, the jury said the insurance company must pay Dickson $500,000 for his anguish. 
We should all have this kind of anguish Keep scratching. There are 
more... 


Double hand scratching after this one.. 


* FOURTH PLACE * 

Jerry Williams, of Little Rock , Arkansas , garnered 4th Place in the 
Stella's when he was awarded $14,500 plus medical expenses after being 
bitten on the butt by his next door neighbor's beagle - even though the 
beagle was on a chain in its owner's fenced yard. Williams did not get 
as much as he asked for because the jury believed the beagle might have 
been provoked at the time of the butt bite because Williams had climbed 
over the fence into the yard and repeatedly shot the dog with a pellet 
gun. 

Pick a new Spot to scratch, you're getting a bald Spot.. 


* THIRD PLACE * 

Amber Carson of Lancaster , Pennsylvania because a jury ordered a 
Philadelphia restaurant to pay her $113,500 after she slipped on a 
spilled soft drink and broke her tailbone. The reason the soft drink 
was on the floor: Ms. Carson had thrown it at her boyfriend 30 seconds 
earlier during an argument. What ever happened to people being 
responsible for their own actions? 


Only two more so ease up on the scratching... 

*SECOND PLACE* 

Kara Walton, of Claymont , Delaware sued the owner of a night club in a 
nearby city because she fell from the bathroom window to the floor, 
knocking out her two front teeth. Even though Ms. Walton was trying to 
sneak through the ladies room window to avoid paying the $3.50 cover 
charge, the jury said the night club had to pay her $12,000....oh, 
yeah, plus dental expenses. Go figure. 


Ok. Here we go!! Drum roll .. 


* FIRST PLACE * 

This year's runaway First Place Stella Award winner was: Mrs. Merv 
Grazinski of Oklahoma City , Oklahoma , who purchased new 32-foot 
Winnebago motor home. On her first trip home, from an OU football game, having driven on to the freeway, she set the cruise control at 70 mph and calmly left the 
driver's seat to go to the back of the Winnebago to make herself a 
sandwich not surprisingly, the motor home left the freeway, crashed and 
overturned. Also not surprisingly, Mrs. Grazinski sued Winnebago for 
not putting in the owners manual that she couldn't actually leave the 
driver's seat while the cruise control was set. The Oklahoma jury 
awarded her, are you sitting down? $1,750,000 PLUS a new motor home. 
Winnebago actually changed their manuals as a result of this suit, just 
in case Mrs. Grazinski has any relatives who might also buy a motor 
home. 


If you think the court system is out of control and America has lost 
ALL common sense, be sure to pass this one on!!!
 

Even more shocking is that the people on these jurys vote!!!!
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zpfvu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t33k</id></website><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/thoughts-or-try-this-is-the-media-fair/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T04:00:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T00:22:29+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwxeda</id><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/thoughts-or-try-this-is-the-media-fair/#comment-481358017</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lora4</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>