<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw1hqe/post/2012-03-30T23:56:49</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mse2vo</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Not really germans vehicle only have one  and it's stored in the boot (for effeciency purposes eg. snowy, icy countries "effective starting in Cold climates") and balance and less weight over the front axle or in front of the front axle for better handling and reduced body roll.

And clearly you have no idea why a car has a  it's primary and main purpose for a car  is for starting a car and energy storage for when the engine is not running for accesories after that when the engines running thats where the alternator/generator kicks in and powers "everthing" once started. Cars only have dual  to increase vehicle amperage or voltage  on how the 2  a connected (series or parallel) not both as power runs through them from the alternator increasing amerage or voltage  the above mentioned reason.

And if many light passenger vehicles use this (DUAL ) name them I dislike hearing "MANY CARS" and absolutely not examples of such vehicles.

Car manufactures offer dual  for vehicles that may be equiped with high ammounts of portable equipment, high power equipment added to them or longer power use when vehicle engines are Off eg.4WD's, Trucks, UTES and emergency vehicles.

New cars are designed with an alternator/generator that is designed to supply with enough energy to power all  manufactures standard equipment. (cars are restricted to a 12 volt electronic system for safety reasons).</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ll9z2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/drfv</id></website><link>http://www.carsales.com.au/news/2012/prestige-and-luxury/bmw/5-series/bmw-recalls-15-million-cars-for-electrical-problem-29458</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T03:47:59+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T03:56:49+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw1hqe</id><link>http://www.carsales.com.au/news/2012/prestige-and-luxury/bmw/5-series/bmw-recalls-15-million-cars-for-electrical-problem-29458#comment-481507458</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>