<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk1zrp/post/2012-03-26T11:27:12</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Kind of agree with being Burnt out on WoW.  I've played since BC and ever since the end of Wrath it's all just seemed so...boring.  Not because it's too easy - I'm not of the mind that difficult gameplay = fun gameplay - but just because it all seems like the same thing with a different coat of paint.  

I'm hoping that MoP will revitalize WoW a bit with things like the pet battles and scenarios, but I'm not holding my breath.  At this point the only reason I'm still playing is because one of my best friends IRL still loves the game and the endless (and IMO, insufferable) grind for gear each patch.  If it weren't for him, I would've quit a long time ago.  Still, I agree with you - the fantasy nerd in me likes keeping up with the story regardless.

Oh, and I personally think Sylvanas is awesome - sure, she's raising dead humans, but who wouldn't want to be a badass Forsaken?  And really, it's not like they have a choice in the matter, since Forsaken can't procreate.  Plus, the humans deserve what they get...they've been racist assholes ever since WC3.  That's just my opinion of course; to each their own.  

Still, I'll be Glad to take down Garrosh, since he's not any better.  I hope they put Vol'jin in charge after that, rather than bring back Orc Jesus, er, Thrall.     

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rbb2e</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/v6k</id></website><link>http://www.iheartchaos.com/post/19935358692</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T02:49:23+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T15:27:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk1zrp</id><link>http://www.iheartchaos.com/post/19935358692#comment-476469641</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>