<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qqe7/post/2012-03-29T11:57:41</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>My daughter had brain cancer as a baby and received radiation as part of her treatment. The radiation damaged the hair follicles on her scalp and she has a rather large baldish Spot. She also has autism. About a year ago, she started wearing this one particular coral-pink baby sunhat that we got 3.5 years ago. She wears that hat all the time. Even to bed. She only takes it  for the bath, and she gets extremely anxious when the hat is out of her sight. She only likes *that* hat. No other will do. 

We have scoured the interwebz &amp; ebay looking for a duplicate of that hat in case - Maud Forbid! - anything happens to it, but haven't been able to find it, so there's just been this persistent mild dread about what's going to happen for our girl if the hat gets damaged or lost or she outgrows it. 

One of my best friends is a public relations whiz and she got to thinking about my daughter's famous hat one day and decided she just had to find a duplicate for her. She called the company who made the hat and sweet-talked their PR people and convinced them to look in their storerooms for any extra stock of that exact hat from 4 years ago. They found one - in a larger size - and sent it to us for free. My daughter didn't bat an eye about wearing it and happily switches between both hats. It's a great relief to have a back-up hat.

It was an unexpected gift, a small gift all in all, but also a HUGELY meaningful gift. 

By the way, the company who made the hat is Life is Good; they have a charitable arm that focuses on creating Joy for children dealing with life-threatening illnesses. Very appropo.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lwljj</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ync</id></website><link>http://shakespearessister.blogspot.com/2012/03/question-of-day_27.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T23:01:43+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:57:41+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qqe7</id><link>http://shakespearessister.blogspot.com/2012/03/question-of-day_27.html#comment-479601879</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cqd9s</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>