<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw76tb/post/2012-03-30T15:07:59</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwyips</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lvca1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>First, please do not call us SM delusional fans because,



A) We are Shinhwa fans and Shinhwa is no longer with SM Entertainment and has not been with them for a very long time now. 

B) You have no concrete proof that everyone (or anyone at all, for that 
matter) here who loves Shinhwa IS delusional because a delusion is 
 pathological (the result of an illness or illness process). So if
 you do not have anyone's medical records/history on file, it's 
incredibly presumptuous of you to declare us as such.



If you really feel the need to call us something, just refer to us as Shinhwa fans or Changjos. 



Second, you stated that you "respect" Shinhwa and that you did not come 
here "just" to put them down... and yet, funnily enough, your post is 
worded in a way that you KNOW would incite indignation amongst Shinhwa 
fans. You Cold have just written the first part but the the whole "not 
fair" thing just came across as antagonistic (and whiny, truth to be 
told). 



As someone before me has pointed out, Shinhwa gave credit to the 
writers/producers to whom they bought the music from. If it sounds like 
anything at all, it would be because of that. They're not the first 
Korean  to buy music from an American producer and I highly doubt 
that they will be the last. The number of Kpop  overwhelms the 
number of prolific songwriters in Korea so buying music from foreign 
writers is the easiest way for Kpop  to put out songs. If they wait 
on the Korean writers, the fans would have to wait for a very long time 
for their favorite's comeback since a writer does not cater to just one 
 alone. 



True, there ARE artists who could write the music themselves, but let's 
face it, how many of these  CAN actually write their own songs? 
Writing lyrics is hard enough as it is, but creating the music itself 
takes mad skills and ample time. Can you even imagine how long it would 
take if they're to write ALL the music and lyrics in one album alone? 
Buying music that is copyrighted elsewhere is not illegal and is a 
practice of ALL music labels across the globe.



If they DO win for '', how can it NOT be fair? They own the 
copyright to the song in Korea, it's in their album, they're promoting 
it, they're singing it live on various shows - they're basically doing 
ALL the things the other groups are doing so, again, how can it NOT be 
fair? Did they take a shortcut through the whole process? Did they buy 
the votes? Did they coerce anyone to vote for the song? Have they 
threatened harm to anyone if '' doesn't win? Did they do anything 
illegal AT ALL to Ensure their win? Is it a REQUIREMENT that each and 
every song that each artist promotes should be PERSONALLY written by the
 artist themselves or barring that, be ORIGINALLY and SPECIFICALLY 
written for the promoting artist? If the answer to everything is no, 
then again, I ask, how is it NOT fair?</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67aalg</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lyjc</id></website><link>http://www.allkpop.com/2012/03/legendary-idol-group-shinhwa-returns-with-venus-on-music-bank</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T10:33:42+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:07:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw76tb</id><link>http://www.allkpop.com/2012/03/legendary-idol-group-shinhwa-returns-with-venus-on-music-bank#comment-481083610</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hfnyn</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>