<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/209309/post/128041986/comment/329389223</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This raises some profound theological questions, to be sure. Do posthumous marriages follow the rules currently in place, or the ones in place during the life of the prospective spouses? &amp;#039;Cause the church just &amp;quot;recommends against&amp;quot; interracial marriage, whereas before the big watershed of 1978. But back when Sally and Thomas were making whoopie it was &lt;i&gt;streng verboten&lt;/i&gt;.  
 
Useful reading on the subject, from the prophets: 
 
&amp;ldquo;Had I anything to do with the negro, I would confine them by strict law to their own species...&amp;rdquo; 
(Joseph Smith, Jr., January 2nd, 1845, History of the Church, volume 5, pages 21-218) 
 
&amp;ldquo;Shall I tell you the law of God in regard to the African race? If the white man who belongs to the chosen seed mixes his blood with the seed of Cain, the penalty, under the law of God, is death on the Spot. This will  be so. The nations of the earth have transgressed every law that God has given, they have changed the ordinances and broken every covenant made with the fathers, and they are like a hungry man that dreameth that he eateth, and he awaketh and behold he is empty.&amp;rdquo; 
(Brigham Young, Journal of Discourses, volume 10, page 110) 
 
&amp;ldquo;Your ideas, as we understand them, appear to contemplate the intermarriage of the Negro and white races, a concept which has heretofore been most repugnant to most normal-minded people from the ancient patriarchs until now.... there is a growing tendency, particularly among some educators, as it manifests itself in this area, toward the breaking down of race barriers in the matter of intermarriage between whites and blacks, but it does not have the sanction of the Church and is contrary to Church doctrine.&amp;rdquo; 
(LDS First Presidency (George Albert Smith), letter to Virgil H. Sponberg (critic of the anti-black ), May 5th, 1947, quoted in Lester E. Bush, Mormonism&amp;rsquo;s Negro Doctrine: An Historical Overview, page 42) 
 
 
&amp;ldquo;We must not inter-marry with the Negro. Why? If I were to marry a Negro woman and have children by her, my children would oil be cursed as to the priesthood. Do I want my children cursed as to the priesthood? If there is one drop of Negro blood in my children, as I have read to you, they receive the curse. There isn&amp;rsquo;t any argument, therefore, as to inter-marriage with the Negro, is there?&amp;rdquo; 
(Apostle Mark E. Peterson, &amp;ldquo;Race Problems &amp;ndash; As They Effect the Church,&amp;rdquo; Address given at the Convention of Teachers of Religion on the College Level, delivered at BYU, August 27th, 1954) 
 
&amp;ldquo;However, in a broad general sense, caste systems have their root and origin in the gospel itself, and when they operate according to the divine decree, the resultant restrictions and segregation are right and proper and have the approval of the Lord. To illustrate: Cain, Ham, and the whole negro race have been cursed with a black skin, the mark of Cain, so they can be identified as a caste apart, a people with whom the other descendants of Adam should not intermarry.&amp;rdquo; 
(Bruce R. McConkie, Mormon Doctrine, page 114) 
 
&amp;ldquo;Brigham Young made a very strong statement on this matter when he said, &amp;lsquo;... shall I tell you the law of God in regard to the African race? If the white man who belongs to the chosen seed mixes his blood with the seed of Cain, the penalty under the law of God, is death on the Spot. This will Always be so.&amp;rsquo; God has commanded Israel not to intermarry. To go against this commandment of God would be to sin. Those who willfully sin with their eyes open to this wrong will not be surprised to find that they will be separated from the presence of God in the world to come. This is spiritual death.... It does not matter if they are one-sixth Negro or one-one hundred and sixth, the curse of no Priesthood is still the same.... To intermarry with a Negro is to forfeit a &amp;lsquo;Nation of Priesthood holders.&amp;rsquo;&amp;rdquo; 
(Elder John L. Lund, The Church and the Negro, pages 54-55, 1967) 
 
[Cut and pasted from &lt;a href="http://mormonismexposed.blogspot.com/2008/01/mormon-leaders-condemn-inter-racial.html" target="_blank"&gt;http://mormonismexposed.blogspot.com/2008/01/morm...&lt;/a&gt; ] 
 
 
 </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:209309:128041986</id><idPostId>128041986</idPostId><idBlogId>209309</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:209309</id><idBlogId>209309</idBlogId><link>http://wonkette.com</link><displayName>Wonkette</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://wonkette.com/468744/helpful-mormons-hitched-up-thomas-jefferson-and-sally-hemings-for-all-eternity</link><displayName>Helpful Mormons Hitched Up Thomas Jefferson and Sally Hemings For All Eternity</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-01T18:04:39.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:209309:128041986:329389223</id><link>http://wonkette.com/468744/helpful-mormons-hitched-up-thomas-jefferson-and-sally-hemings-for-all-eternity#IDComment329389223</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T18:04:39.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Helpful Mormons Hitched Up Thomas Jefferson and Sally Hemings For All Eternity by Chichikovovich</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://intensedebate.com/people/Chichikovovich</link><idEmailMd5>b8da4d0f5a7623fd3c34acb2d2309c6d</idEmailMd5><displayName>Chichikovovich</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://intensedebate.com/people/Chichikovovich"&gt;Chichikovovich&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://wonkette.com/468744/helpful-mormons-hitched-up-thomas-jefferson-and-sally-hemings-for-all-eternity"&gt;Helpful Mormons Hitched Up Thomas Jefferson and Sally Hemings For All Eternity&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>