<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3rtdz/update/2012-03-29T03:37:40/6120d2938fb7b0426b5b734f59f3b7ff4a7752b465dcf2b7ab1dd643d91114cd</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3gsd6</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zhfzu</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>TRAYVON WAS PRESUMED GUILTY BEFORE HE COULD PROVE HIS INNOCENCE!   TRAYVON WAS NEVER GUILTY!  AND I ASSURE YOU THERE IS PLENTY OF EVIDENCE THAT PROVE TRAYVON WAS INNOCENT! WHY THE #ELL SHOULD WE CARE ABOUT THIS MURDERER AND HIS CREW OF LIARS!

THIS MURDERER WAS LET GO BECAUSE HIS FATHER IS A JUDGE!  HIS FATHER LIED FOR HIM IN THE BEGINNING NOT KNOWING THE 911 TAPES WERE GOING TO BE RELEASED! THEY HAD NO IDEA THIS WAS GOING TO BLOW UP THE WAY IT DID! 

WHERE IS THE WET SPOT AND GRASS STAIN ON HIS BACK?  I LOOKED HARD AND CLOSE UP FOR A HEAD INJURY, BUT I DIDN'T SEE IT. I'M MAD ABOUT THAT! I WAS HOPING TRAY JACKED HIM UP!

this child's body lay in the medical examiner's office for 3 days WHEN POLICE HAD HIS CELL PHONE &amp; DID NOT CALL ANY OF HIS #s!  as his father called his son's phone looking for his son!  police purposely marked as a john doe when they knew who he was.PROVEN FACT!       WHY WOULD THEY DO THIS?z father made a statement last night full of lies, hose baez claims emt's cleaned him up that's why there's no blood on him in the video. they are going to take their lies as far as they can. then they complain about mad black people. i applaud his parents because i don't know if i could hold it together like they have!

i'd be helping the black panthers plan the revolution!God is on their side!  everyone will get what's coming to them!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hwmgc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yzhx</id></website><link>http://www.miamiherald.com/2012/03/28/2719868/network-broadcasts-surveillance.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T00:30:26+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T07:37:40+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3rtdz</id><link>http://www.miamiherald.com/2012/03/28/2719868/network-broadcasts-surveillance.html#comment-479226110</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l3jxx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>