<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3wngw/post/2012-03-30T02:02:10</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/63x4l</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/4x0m</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Having trouble viewing this email?
Click here http://campaign.r20.constantcontact.com/render?llr=mnsck5bab&amp;v=001o1NWE3yaJ-oQfj61bN1BQ8LnSWepFPYaMBJfy6HaXyEUR8uE02xccJLjipTjY-pI_fFygbyKtBcLXoUGTP7iJutIMaxip-BakrxHj6SdJ6jfGcSbEVVNQtteGGdGpzkT 

How They Won Back Their Teen
by AlethaHinthorn

Carol and her husband helplessly watched their sixteen-year-old daughter who had attended church and week-end witnessing missions change from a happy teen, to a sullen, uncooperative, school-skipping rebel on drugs. She became Cold and hard, rejecting all they stood for. When they came near, she physically avoided their touch.
The rejection began to get to Carol, and she found herself withdrawing from her daughter. After one painful incident, she ran to her hiding place, and poured out her sorrows to God. In time, an inner calmness indicated her petition was heard. Her cry changed to praise and to singing.
Finally, she listened. God spoke to her heart in His still, small voice. First, He  her. Then He told her to open her eyes. Her eyes fell upon a beautiful snowfall. Each  landed with no expectations or preconceived destination on the surprised October grass. "That's how I want you to love your daughter," God told her. "Gently, like my blanket of snow, softly covering her with your love, holding nothing back."
Engulfed in peace, Carol  to trust God. She and her husband avoided preaching,
but in her presence, they cheerfully shared God's faithfulness in their lives. God&#13;
had set Carol free to show her unconditional love again.&#13;
He also gave her insight into how to pray. Hopelessness was replaced with confidence&#13;
in Him for whom nothing is too difficult. Longsuffering overcame self-pity. One &#13;
and a half years later, the world released its hold on their daughter.&#13;
Months after this turnabout, their daughter said, "Mom, if I hadn't known you and&#13;
Dad would welcome me with open arms, I'd never have made it back."&#13;
Thank You, Father, for giving us Your thoughts when we seek You with our whole hearts.&#13;
"Love must be sincere" (Romans 12:9)&#13;
&#13;
Memory Verse for March "May the God of hope fill you with all  and peace as you&#13;
trust in him,  so that you may overflow with hope by the power of the Holy Spirit"&#13;
(Romans 15:13).&#13;
&#13;
Prayer Request&#13;
Please pray for Beth Coppedge, Come to the Fire's much loved speaker, and her husband&#13;
Al, as they minister in Africa.&#13;
Conference Testimonies&#13;
What an incredible conference.  I have been to many conferences but believe that&#13;
 this was one of the best. Why, you might ask? It was so filled with the Holy Spirit&#13;
and the worship was amazing. It was not just fluff, but it was a deep holy experience.&#13;
I so appreciated the opportunities of silence, contemplation, searching and just&#13;
 the beautiful experiences of prayer. I realized I have been living the past year&#13;
in "me" nation. I knew that God was calling me, but I was holding part of my heart&#13;
back from Him because of fear and that led to not trusting and believing in Him.&#13;
 Rondy's talk on Friday night was for me. God spoke through her directly to my heart.&#13;
It was amazing how it fit. I have been looking for rest for the past year, and realized&#13;
why I couldn't find it. I went to the alter and surrendered the remaining parts &#13;
of my heart. I am excited to renew my relationship with Him and to move deeper in&#13;
knowledge and intimacy so that my trust can be strengthened and I can be at rest&#13;
 and ready to do radical things for Him. Thank you so much for all the time that&#13;
 you invest to help others to find the love of our Heavenly Father!!  Lisa&#13;
I think I was crying within five minutes of corporate worship  starting....and that&#13;
seemed to be the pattern the entire conference!  During the music that a.m., I almost&#13;
immediately got this picture and  prayed that God would "hose me down." Just as &#13;
a little girl that has  been playing in the mud needs to be sprayed with water to&#13;
become clean, I  asked God to wash me clean from all the grime and dirt that was&#13;
  covering me like a putrid film because of my environment. And he did,  and I was&#13;
like that little girl delighting in running through the  sprinklers. It was beautiful.&#13;
That was the start of me hearing from God  through EVERY SINGLE SPEAKER and EVERY&#13;
SINGLE WORSHIP SESSION! I  honestly thought to myself, "How could I hear anything&#13;
else from God?!?"  He is knocking my socks  with the goodness of Him speaking&#13;
 to me SO  MUCH!!!&#13;
Danielle&#13;
When I came to the conference I really was expecting just another conference.  However,&#13;
being in ministry myself, I felt that I needed a little refreshing, so I came.  &#13;
I was amazed, humbled, and stripped naked before the Lord.  His Holy Presence was&#13;
so breath-taking that there were times when I could not speak.  I could only breathe&#13;
Him in with my face bowed before Him.  As I breathed Him in, all this "life stuff"&#13;
that I thought had been removed from my heart and mind came to the surface and God&#13;
began a COMPLETE cleansing and healing.  All these years, I thought the closets &#13;
of my heart had been opened, only to find out that although they were open, they&#13;
 were not completely swept clean.  Now they are!  A complete healing!&#13;
Teresa&#13;
&#13;
I have to say the conference was a "more than you can imagine" answered prayer! &#13;
God showed up in every area! I heard a woman say it was the best conference she &#13;
had ever been to because the Holy Spirit was present in all and throughout! [not&#13;
 just a certain "guest" speaker.] To me, that was the true litmus test. When it &#13;
is truly a divine agenda, the presence of Christ Jesus is intensely palatable and&#13;
souls are set ablaze for more of Him!!!  I pray the sparks of this godly conference&#13;
will help set our world on fire and rally the Bride to make herself ready for her&#13;
coming Groom.&#13;
&#13;
Bethany&#13;
&#13;
I don't think I have ever felt the presence of God so strongly in any other type&#13;
 of meeting or conference. I was praying before the conference that God would meet&#13;
me and give me a fresh sense of Himself. I left knowing He had been faithful to &#13;
that prayer.&#13;
&#13;
Each meeting was so Christ-centered, and it felt as if Jesus knew He had been invited&#13;
and was in charge of the time. The message of holiness was presented in an attractive,&#13;
realistic way that conveyed the message that God is big enough to deliver us from&#13;
sin.&#13;
&#13;
This conference gave me a renewed belief in the power of prayer. The results of &#13;
the many hours of prayer for this conference were evident by the atmosphere during&#13;
each day. Nothing but prayer and dependence on God could have produced the same &#13;
result. Thank you for not trying to organize this on your own.&#13;
I feel strongly that that something like this needs to be done for men as well. &#13;
Our husbands and church leaders need something like this that they can come to and&#13;
hear the holiness message presented so clearly. The men need an opportunity to "Come&#13;
to the Fire" just as much as we did.&#13;
&#13;
Anne&#13;
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&#13;
&#13;
A Women's Conference on the Holy Heart&#13;
October 11-13, 2012&#13;
Olivet Nazarene University&#13;
Bourbonnais, IL&#13;
Register Here [http://r20.rs6.net/tn.jsp?et=1109652449568&amp;s=10237&amp;e=001ZNLNjmIHaPdoLSSxTLKu7uhmtBfNitC8DuKz-Vs1KgesueWouTuGoGtLuIxYpKKbwArUVpXALs-M1BNPwin3ka3Q53jmDHfBmVlxIxRXyvG9H0ywmSMBnQ==]&#13;
White  Picket Fence shows how marriage problems can be a springboard for  renewal.&#13;
Discover the treasure of blessings in your marriage.&#13;
*Live  in harmony with an unbelieving spouse&#13;
*Discover how to grow closer  spiritually&#13;
*Learn how to build a healthy blended family&#13;
*You can  get your spouse to listen to you&#13;
*Forgiveness is possible&#13;
*Just  friends? Safeguard against an affair&#13;
*Discover creative dates after  marriage&#13;
*Did you choose the right marriage partner?&#13;
Read More and Order Here [http://r20.rs6.net/tn.jsp?et=1109652449568&amp;s=10237&amp;e=001ZNLNjmIHaPd8eFL1CjuRE0KuQePad5oSJU4PoMd4SpMr858CDHh2yW53486YVzEyLj7YVeAKUhPFLblExF3Ba1wlUq0R-XC4fuY6GRPYMVr3LnVQSlnZnO1abxeaNaTLWvMzPn2ofsSCZwZR1V8iQQ==]&#13;
Titus Women's Discipleship Summit April 19-21&#13;
The Inn at Amish Door&#13;
Wilmot, OH&#13;
Learn More [http://r20.rs6.net/tn.jsp?et=1109652449568&amp;s=10237&amp;e=001ZNLNjmIHaPdz8Ra4LWYFmobB14HLheX6HvGVb0cdOsCYBdFzcFtWHMa-DXkd8LMzYQHrEbUPu9k3kHwOra42MXEoIFEQTGUye7xX-UOKsEMrSv_5u0PgrFFNpvlPx7UXpiQ7K_7aGtffA7xHgoW2iQoVad6rbs-OU70gZjK1kjM=]&#13;
&#13;
Read More and Order  [http://r20.rs6.net/tn.jsp?et=1109652449568&amp;s=10237&amp;e=001ZNLNjmIHaPdF4KthFFLwkXBCOdpnNdVjqbALaCq6aaL87waSZahv0l5lGnLFAAOvDgnz-d8zWw_PlFbyVii6xjSeNuiIusD65xmZOTOQofIhobvO5f6z8LgyzkVK-DJ38pRf5HwYdFc=]&#13;
Order Here [http://r20.rs6.net/tn.jsp?et=1109652449568&amp;s=10237&amp;e=001ZNLNjmIHaPdF4KthFFLwkXBCOdpnNdVjqbALaCq6aaL87waSZahv0l5lGnLFAAOvDgnz-d8zWw_PlFbyVii6xjSeNuiIusD65xmZOTOQofIhobvO5f6z8LgyzkVK-DJ38pRf5HwYdFc=]&#13;
Order Here [http://r20.rs6.net/tn.jsp?et=1109652449568&amp;s=10237&amp;e=001ZNLNjmIHaPdF4KthFFLwkXBCOdpnNdVjqbALaCq6aaL87waSZahv0l5lGnLFAAOvDgnz-d8zWw_PlFbyVii6xjSeNuiIusD65xmZOTOQofIhobvO5f6z8LgyzkVK-DJ38pRf5HwYdFc=]&#13;
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&#13;
&#13;
Quick Links&#13;
&#13;
Did you miss&#13;
Come to the Fire 2011 at Grove City Church of the Nazarene?&#13;
View live streaming.&#13;
Click the&#13;
"other" tab&#13;
after you&#13;
Click Here [http://r20.rs6.net/tn.jsp?et=1109652449568&amp;s=10237&amp;e=001ZNLNjmIHaPe5mYvnnUVyrizoKmEXaxA9MQly_lzz4YNDch8zT0ky67DyYq4VDguPpBrPW3sKJaih21rwpAYW2bU-Lj90PWY9vGL2w90SJc79i0Aqe4zjZrAKP6nPjGmwh3zlhLlg1focFSf9Y9rFO0ev_rfs_xgfV53aG3aNus4=]&#13;
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&#13;
&#13;
Join Our Mailing List! [http://visitor.r20.constantcontact.com/email.jsp?m=1101602572716]&#13;
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&#13;
&#13;
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~&#13;
Forward email&#13;
http://ui.constantcontact.com/sa/fwtf.jsp?llr=mnsck5bab&amp;m=1101602572716&amp;ea=&amp;a=1109652449568&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
This email was sent to  by ahinthorn@gmail.com.&#13;
&#13;
Instant removal with SafeUnsubscribe(TM)&#13;
http://visitor.constantcontact.com/do?p=un&amp;mse=001k6dau0Gb9W81sobTjEbfAdbefnNWNN4Hq9iLO7nbwGk%3D&amp;t=0011GW-NVAeZ40WC11KK4RUpQ%3D%3D&amp;lang=001FCSs65SMrsI%3D&amp;reason=001y5KaVlBn7_Y%3D&amp;llr=mnsck5bab&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Privacy Policy:&#13;
http://ui.constantcontact.com/roving/CCPrivacyPolicy.jsp&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Come to the Fire | P.O. Box 480052 | Kansas City | MO | 64148</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/bhurc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cie9</id></website><link>http://cometothefire.com/page8/page8.php?id=2020690242803356365</link><postedTime>2009-10-03T16:18:24+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T06:02:10+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3wngw</id><link>http://cometothefire.com/page8/page8.php?id=2020690242803356365#comment-480302998</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z077</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2009-10-03</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>