<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tfgk/update/2012-03-29T10:10:30/682829c51f307db0d0a9fd639bfc337a50f2c056c2b6b611f0b3f8e9f0c1d014</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Summary of Events - Day 380: Wednesday, 28 Mar 2012

More than 2000 Syrian refugees flocked into Jordan this past week as a result of the regime’s increased operations in the province of Daraa. 600 refugees flocked to Jordan on Tuesday alone in what has been counted as the biggest exodus of Syrian refugees in one day; most of the refugees came from the towns of Herak and Bosr Harir. Clashes continued in Daraa today, especially in the towns of Tafas and Bosr Harir, while arbitrary sweep and arrest campaigns continued under heavy cover by random machinegun fire.

In the north, regime forces continued to shell the cities of Homs, Qasir and Rastan, and the towns of Khan Subul, Khan Shaykhoun, Kafar Batikh, and Dadikh amid incursions, arbitrary sweeps and arrests, and torching of private property. In Hama, regime forces invaded the towns of Qalat Madiq and Jabal Shahshabo after hours of heavy shelling, while regime’s militiamen Raided the town of Tweeni in Sahl Ghab and Burnt over 100 houses.

Assad’s forces killed at least 27 today; most fell in Homs. Despite all the violence and crimes against humanity, massive peaceful demonstrations continued to go out in most of the disaster-stricken provinces and cities such as Homs, Idlib, and Hama.

In the Capital, regime forces conducted massive arbitrary arrests and house sweeps in the Damascus suburbs of Harasta, Kafarbatna, and Moadamiya, accompanied by random shootings, and increased security checkpoints. As for Aleppo, regime forces opened heavy fire at a night demonstration in the neighbourhood of Salahdin and shelled the town of Atareb.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ylh931</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cjnq</id></website><link>http://blogs.aljazeera.com/middle-east/2012/02/05/fighting-back-against-assads-forces</link><postedTime>2012-02-05T09:27:20+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:10:30+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tfgk</id><link>http://blogs.aljazeera.com/middle-east/2012/02/05/fighting-back-against-assads-forces#comment-479516323</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zlwz2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-05</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>