<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3yi9s/update/2012-03-29T02:30:14/960891753efd4824869a5784562f11cedbe590f19e8aba61c74d7460bc37e980</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mswsid</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5bpxc</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> &lt;blockquote&gt;Why could I not add another adult with whom I don't have any kind of relationship with (like say my sister, or a close friend and his wife?)  &lt;/blockquote&gt;

I'd be fine with you and your sister and whoever else being in a legal union, personally.  It shouldn't be the government's concern whether you guys are actually having sex.

&lt;blockquote&gt;What is the time split of the children if your relationship breaks up?  Do you wind up with three way custody?  Does the biological parent assume custody?&lt;/blockquote&gt;  

That's for the family law court to decide, no?  It's not like they don't face equally complicated cases involving step-parents and grandparents and whatnot.

Offhand, I would think that in a large poly marriage, one or two people would be designated as the child's primary guardians from birth.  (It's generally accepted that a kid needs some parenting continuity; a toddler probably shouldn't be spending 1/87th of its time with each of its 87 poly-parents.)  They'd then have primary custody rights in case of a breakup.

&lt;blockquote&gt;Are the other TWO parents both obligated to child support?  Doesn't that make poly relationships economically advantageous over monogamous ones?&lt;/blockquote&gt;

I don't see why; presumably poly families would be raising more children, so they ought to have more people contributing support.

&lt;blockquote&gt;I've got a problem with that - because I can imagine being "required" to "marry" into the line marriage for economic reasons (our partners are all married, so if you'd like this job...) and then you're basically at a Spot where your job is regulating your sex life.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

Which is a Spot we're at already, and have been for pretty much the entire history of monogamous marriage.  Marry the boss's kid, inherit the family farm/business.  Marry a Hollywood director/producer, star in their movies.  Marry a politician, get a cushy job in a PAC/nonprofit/think tank associated with their pet issue.  Most people are fine with Mom &amp; Pop corner stores, and it was probably just Pop's store before he married Mom.

To the extent that this demands government intervention, I think it can be taken care of with laws against nepotism and sexual harassment and so forth. Any halfway explicit "marry us if you want this job" deal would be quid pro quo harassment.  I don't see that keeping polygamy illegal does anything to help.

&lt;blockquote&gt;One of the reasons polygyny is "bad" is because it creates a sort of permanent underclass of unmarried adult males and exacerbates existing economic inequalities.  &lt;/blockquote&gt;

I don't think women should have their marital options legally constrained for the sake of single men, though.  A big pool of unmarried young men can be a severe social problem, yes, but mostly in societies where marriage is critical to a man's sexual/economic/social success.  In our society, where half the men are already unmarried, not so much.

As for exacerbating economic inequalities, the jury's still out on that.  In societies where the manual labor of women and children is a big factor in a husband's wealth, polygyny contributes to economic inequality among &lt;i&gt;men&lt;/i&gt;, because it helps rich men amass a workforce to make themselves richer.  (That wouldn't work too well in a society which prohibits child labor and allows women to retain control over their own assets, though.)  On the other hand, it reduces economic inequality among &lt;i&gt;women&lt;/i&gt;, because multiple women can benefit from joining a high-status household.  Which is why, historically, laws against polygamy have been most strongly supported by upper-class women and middle-class men.

&lt;blockquote&gt;I'm basically concerned that by having "marriage" at all we're going to be all but requiring  people of one stripe or another to engage in sexual dynamics they'd rather not engage in order to compete economically.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

Well, if you want to make sure people aren't &lt;i&gt;legally&lt;/i&gt; compelled to engage in a particular sexual dynamic, you don't have to erase legal marriage.  Rather, you can eliminate its sexual element.  We're already halfway there; adultery is rarely prosecuted in Western societies, and wives usually aren't legally obligated to have sex with their husbands.  In the eyes of the law, marriage is mostly an assets-sharing, child-rearing, health-care-proxy-having thing.

That doesn't remove extralegal economic pressures on sexual behavior, of course.  But people don't have to be married to face those.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lfla4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/z910</id></website><link>http://www.patheos.com/blogs/slacktivist/2012/03/27/drive-a-wedge-between-gays-and-blacks/</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T15:51:24+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T06:30:14+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3yi9s</id><link>http://www.patheos.com/blogs/slacktivist/2012/03/27/drive-a-wedge-between-gays-and-blacks/#comment-479150312</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5ufde</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>