<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3pv0d/update/2012-03-29T20:24:16/f701891c4c04eafdce9a797dc400977cdadf29fa8824fe30d65fb7cdb4481e0f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I grew up Mennonite &amp; began covering my head when I was 9 years old.  The types of head coverings as well as the age girls begin to cover vary widely.  For me the practice of covering the head was oppressive.  I'll bullet point the teachings (both written &amp; passed on unwritten as tradition) that I was taught that made me feel it was sexist &amp; oppressive.  The "spiritual authority structure" in the Mennonite church is God, Man, Woman.  This plays into head covering beliefs.

- Woman must cover her head to pray.  If she doesn't it dishonors her head which means both her own head &amp; her "spiritual head" (her husband).
- Since one should  be prayerful women must Always cover.
- Men do not need to cover.
- Women must also wear their hair up underneath the head covering.  This is because their hair is their "crowning glory" &amp; must be saved only for their husbands to see.  If it is worn down it will tempt men to have lustful thoughts.  The hair must also be never be cut.
-Style of head covering varied widely &amp; one was under constant evaluation &amp; critique because style/size was linked to spirituality.

Wearing the head covering was oppressive in the teaching &amp; also the implementation.  Coverings the head made normal living uncomfortable.  You couldn't put your head back against a couch, or chair.  You couldn't fall asleep in the car without crushing it.  Many women had daily Headaches &amp; large bald Spots due to wearing their uncut hair up every day.  Everything activity you would want to do was filtered through if &amp; how you could do it while wearing a head covering (and a dress).  One would receive open ridicule or would have to engage in long conversations with strangers about their beliefs.  Men had none of these daily life issues.


That was my experience &amp; because of that, it is very difficult for me to see any head covering practice as not being oppressive.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rz4qb</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/4te3</id></website><link>http://thesocietypages.org/socimages/2012/03/25/head-covering-as-a-common-practice/</link><postedTime>2012-03-25T17:20:23+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:24:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3pv0d</id><link>http://thesocietypages.org/socimages/2012/03/25/head-covering-as-a-common-practice/#comment-480065588</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>