<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31bdl/post/2012-03-29T16:12:06</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>oh my! moments:

 when I realized that every time I sing a particular song I wrote, it rains.

when a white feather fell out of a birdless clear blue sky onto me as I stood in a temple to Zeus in Athens

Coming back to Greece from Crete on an overnight crossing, the ferry I was on ran into a very powerful wind and wave storm. I was wearing a pair of quartz crystal point earrings I'd made, and took them out and put them in the pocket of my skirt because they were in danger of blowing out of my ears, and I was enjoying being on deck. When we went below to eat dinner, we found out one set of stabilizers on the ferry had gone out, which was contributing to the violent motion of the ship, and most of the crew was seasick as well, that's what kind of storm it was. I  into my pocket to put my earrings back on, and found only one. The pocket was deep enough there was no way it could have fallen or blown out, but I went back and looked for it anyway. No luck.  The storm didn't seem quite as severe as it had, and after we ate, we went to bed. We got up the next morning docking in Greece, and heard that a couple of other ferry boats had swamped or gone down in the storm, and I turned to my spouse and said, "I guess Poseidon took an earring as payment for getting through the storm."

sitting in a Samhain circle where the working was to speak of someone who had crossed to make peace with either them or their crossing, and having a dog (whom I trusted completely) ask to speak through me about the loss of his life-mate. I said ok, don't remember all of what he said, but it brought most of the group to tears.

A friend of mine said, sort of tongue-in-cheek but not completely, that since the world has changed so much, many of the jobs of the Old Gods have become irrelevant to modern society, so they've taken on similar, but new, jobs and that Isis is now the God of Parking Spaces.  If you need a place to park, and there isn't one, She will get you one if you ask. Needless to say, I was skeptical and thought it a bit frivolous. She offered to demonstrate one time when I was in her car and we were going somewhere that parking is  a problem. She said out loud, "Isis, I need a parking place, please" and two cars pulled out from in front of the place just as we arrived. I've tried it myself on occasion when I've really needed a Spot, both aloud and silently, and it's never failed me. I also make sure to light a candle or incense to Her when I get home, for politeness.

And then there are the cautionary "be careful" stories:

have an acquaintance who had a friend who got terrible Headaches, and the acquaintance said she could "cure" them. Did energy work, and Headache cleared up. It became a habit for them. 6 months later, the friend died of a brain tumor, found on autopsy. Doctors said it must have caused her terrible pain and wondered why she'd never gotten medical attention. If she had, it could have been removed and she'd probably still be alive today.

large (9-10K) public 2 week camping event with about 500 "weather witches" in attendance. A few days in, scattered thunderstorms are predicted. "witches" decide to do rituals to prevent T-storms, and it doesn't rain. Repeat scenario for 4 days, with T-storms becoming more frequent and stronger, and a squall line actually splitting and one half going one way around the campground, while the other half went the other way. (Saw it myself, and predicted 'Mom' is getting tired of these people) Next day, they tried to divert the T-storm with the tornado, and didn't manage it. 5 people were killed BY THAT TORNADO in a state park downwind. Would there have been a tornado if some people hadn't been pushing so much energy at the storm? Would there have been such a violent series of storms if the first one (or ones) had just been allowed to rain themselves out? And there was some pretty severe damage to campsites and the campground itself where the "witches" were working. Electric power was out for over 24 hours.

In my personal world-view, the 'weather witches" are responsible for those 5 deaths. They might have happened without the interference in the weather of the 'weather witches', but the 'witches' were interfering when the deaths did happen, so they carry at least part of the responsibility, in my opinion. They didn't have adequate information to  they would "do no harm" by not wanting to be inconvenienced by a little, possible, occasional rain. If their lives had been at stake (if it rains the crop will be ruined and we'll starve to death this winter), it would have been a different matter and they'd have been working their tails  to get the crops so the interference would be as minimal as possible since the Gods do sometimes demand their price, but just because they didn't want to get wet? Really?   (stepping Off soapbox now)</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dk5xa</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/n36p</id></website><link>http://www.patheos.com/blogs/bishopinthegrove/archives/warning-call-on-a-god-and-he-just-might-show-up/</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T15:55:59+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:12:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31bdl</id><link>http://www.patheos.com/blogs/bishopinthegrove/archives/warning-call-on-a-god-and-he-just-might-show-up/#comment-479839116</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/y9a82</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>