<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6i4u/update/2012-03-30T11:46:23/fc044ba562a12a4a7de519355f2e66d89ed231b50efce40b88c85100c41cac5b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>It is very possible that Zimmerman's brother broke his nose to give him an alabi after the murder. A fellow Klansman on the Stamford police was the one who made the suggestion. So Zimmerman went home and took a couple of Oxycontin and when he was feeling numb, his brother broke his nose. If the nose was already broken, Zimmerman took the Oxycontin before making his injuries worse by having his brother slam his head on the pavement make the alabi better. The broken nose story falls apart because of Zimmerman's impossible explanation of how it happened. Like most criminals who are foolish enough to open their mouths, they often give either too much information, like Casey Anthony's mom who made up the name of the fictitious kidnapper, or information that convicts with facts that are later established as indisputable. After the murder, Zimmerman had grass stains on his clothes and Trevon's blood, which splattered everywhere because he was executed at short range. Do the Stamford police have those garments in evidence as they would with a black man who might murder a white man? No! The Police force was part of the cover-up. The brother either Burned or dumped the bloody clothes the murderer wore with the grass stains and Terevon's blood on them. A witness to the shooting could not see much except two shadowy figures on a location where the witness new that there was grass and not pavement, but witness did see that the two were wrestling on the grass and not on the pavement, that the shooting took place on the grass and that Zimmerman walked  of the grass. The witness is afraid not form the Zimmerman family or Trevon's Family or from any other people except the Stamford Police, who are working hard running this person so that they can find a friend or relative in trouble with the law so that they can threaten the witness into changing their story. Trevon could have possibly broken Zimmerman's nose, but the abrasons and opther injuries suffered from contact with the pavement, those were done after the fact and after 2 Oxycontin. The Stamford Police have been working very hard to help Zimmerman with his alabi. Every Stamford policeman carries a handgun under the seat of their patrol car that has had the identifying numbers ground Off of it. The gun is wiped clean and ion a zip-lock bag. The guys on the Stamford Police Force call this the "Insurance gun". In the event that they mistakenly or intentionally shoot an unarmed person, they put on a pair of latex gloves and put the loaded "Insurance Gun" in that dead or dying person's hand so that there will be prints on it. If Zimmerman had only called the police immediately, a friendly Klan-Affiliated officer would have don the "White Thing" and taken the Skittles and placed the "Insurance Gun" in Trevon's hands. I guess that I ought not to visit Stamford anytime soon! Sir Arthur Coanan Doyle B.A., J.D., S.P.J.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z3b9t</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T07:25:56+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:46:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6i4u</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html#comment-480876287</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z6p23</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>