<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qs6s/post/2012-03-29T12:18:53</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I'll admit I'm not an MS lover but I have to say that MS really has started getting a bit more concious about the standards issue. The backlash on their Document Format becoming an ISO standard with all their patents encumburing said standard really Burned a lot of engineers and governments. In this case, they're actually going about it the right way by proposing this to the IETF AFAIK Google hasn't done yet with SPDY. The main point that MS has actually addressed that Google hasn't is backwards compatibility. SPDY does not play nicely with older versions of software such as Apache, various FTP products along with IM and Email clients and that's why it's not been accepted as yet by the IETF. No backwards compatibility and it doesn't degrade gracefully. You do have to hand it to MS that they do get Backwards compatibility even though it's beginning to bite them in the ass so I hope the committee really Ensures that this does degrade gracefully for those running systems that simply can't be upgraded (embedded and obsolete closed code). </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hja9j</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rohx</id></website><link>http://www.extremetech.com/computing/124153-sm-vs-spdy-microsoft-and-google-battle-over-the-future-of-http-2-0</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T18:42:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:18:53+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qs6s</id><link>http://www.extremetech.com/computing/124153-sm-vs-spdy-microsoft-and-google-battle-over-the-future-of-http-2-0#comment-479618888</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6tw10</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>