<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3friq/delete/2012-03-29T16:44:40</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ufzl</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zkij</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Or, maybe he was a guy in the way to the grocery store who saw a suspicious character lurking around an area that has had multiple burglaries? I carry concealed so I would have been armed, too. 

I would have called the police and reported him but not followed him I wouldn't want to take a bullet from a petty criminal that is where GZ erred. TM could easily have been a little gangbanger with a Glock. 

Hero complex? He was having his head smashed into the sidewalk I would have shot TM as well. I helped you with your post:



Martin was a black teenager walking home from a store with a
bag of candy - don't forget the iced tea!


Zimmerman is a white, unauthorized' 'self-appointed Community Watch captain, on
patrol' - Zimmerman was on his way to
grocery store when he Spotted TM whom he did not recognize


Zimmerman was armed with a deadly weapon which is against Community Watch
policy - Looks like this saved his life


Zimmerman was patrolling alone, which is also against Community Watch
policy - Was not patrolling, was going to
store


Zimmerman was instructed by police to not follow nor approach Martin, but
did BOTH - Not true. Dispatch said
"You don't need to do that" indicating safer to wait for patrol
officer


Martin knew Zimmerman was following him and tried to avoid him - Motive? GZ may have assumed he was hiding
something


Zimmerman and Martin intersected in some way - Obviously


Martin was killed with Zimmerman's gun -
Obviously


Zimmerman's father is a retired judge in the same community - Relevance?


Zimmerman has multiple police records of violence, each inexplicably non prosecuted - Inexplicably? Tell me are you
privy to facts of "incidents"? I didn't think so.


Martin has no record for violence, as in 'none' - Does have record of drug use and possible theft, two things GZ was
wondering about TM


The Sanford police gathered evidence on and tested Martin - Plus autopsy and toxicology which has not
been released


The Sanford police DID NOT gather evidence on nor test Zimmerman - Took his gun and clothes 

Zimmerman
claims injuries which are unverified since evidence was not collected - Eyewitness and police accounts back up GZ


Zimmerman shows no signs of injuries, grass or blood stains or a struggle
in a police video shot shortly after the event - What? See above


Zimmerman claims protection under Florida's Stand Your Ground law - Self Defense is likely defense if TM was
aggressor


Florida's Stand Your Ground law apparently does not apply on Martin's
behalf - Depends on who was aggressor


The town of Sanford, Florida has a long and sordid history of racial
unfairness - Hearsay; Sanford is a suburb
of Orlando not some Mayberry hick town


The Sanford, Florida Police Department continues to 'leak' smearing
'intelligence' about Martin almost every day - Like the facts

Sorry for long post!


</body><verb>delete</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hvrv5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q2aj</id></website><link>http://www.thenation.com/article/167085/what-its-be-problem</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T15:28:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:44:40+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3friq</id><link>http://www.thenation.com/article/167085/what-its-be-problem#comment-479872315</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/aplw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>killed</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>