<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ekczti/update/2012-01-19T01:21:41/eb8feab8586e901b8de32caf2743442a1beeba5c733f4acf92a25beb5b957cf8</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Normally I construct a mini-essay (that balloons to obscene lengths) for my comment, but I don't really have any strong analysis, just some observations:

-So Ashley overheard Victoria and Conrad's talk, right? Could blackmail be in their future? 

-I feel bad for Jack getting his ass handed to him, but I don't think any reviewer should be making a case for Nolan-as-collateral-damage. He basically pestered Emily week after week after week after week until she let him in on the revenge plot. And while, yes, he was useful to her in those pestering weeks, he still came knocking at the door first. She never sought him out to include him. So Nolan has to accept whatever ass-beatings come his way as a side effect of a) being involved in a complicated revenge plot, and b) not being as well-trained in revenge as Emily, so that he's less able to handle complications as she is.

-So what of Declan? What does Conrad get out of paying for his schooling? I know he claims to have done it for Charlotte, and this was before he got the paternity test results back, but it still seems uncharacteristic for Conrad to have done. It seemed somewhat uncharacteristic for Declan to have accepted it, after the big to-do over Victoria's attempted payoff. I guess he's just past the point of caring how he gets to be with Charlotte.

-Loved the scene between Victoria and Fauxmanda. All this tension and sinister undercurrent. Just two cats trying to pretend that the claws weren't already out. And the quick flashback to Young Amanda in that scene really evidenced for me how much more like Young Amanda the Real Emily Thorne looks, so that one could easily believe she IS Amanda Clarke. Weird casting choices, in that case, since that can't have been what they were going for.

-Interview tape under the bed = Jack gets popped for arson. Then we have ourselves a trial when he's also implicated as Daniel's shooter from the flashforward. That's my prediction. Because the only thing this show needs to be the soap of all soaps is a big showy trial, where personalities from the past (Tyler! Fauxmanda!) make eleventh hour appearances, bursting through the double doors of the very traditional-looking court room, because court rooms these days don't at all look like a monochromatic conference  in a community college.

-Extra prediction, based Off of Carrie's line: &lt;i&gt; I suppose the Hamptons should just be happy they aren’t working together; the sheer force of them would be unstoppable.&lt;/i&gt;

I'm 1000% convinced that's where they're going. Emily eventually gets all the way up to the top, and finds out that Victoria, though despicable in her own right, actually isn't the big wig she should have been after, but Conrad. Thus, they put their differences aside to bring down Conrad.

Not saying it would be good television, but I would hope they aren't paralleling Emily and Victoria so hardcore just to have Emily take out Victoria and &lt;i&gt; become &lt;/i&gt; her.

-While I'm talking about the future, does anyone know when the next new episode airs? I noticed we didn't get a preview for the next episode, so I'm guessing we're on a bit of a hiatus, even if just a one-week break.

-Lastly, gotta give props to Emily VanCamp in this episode, just for the look on her face at the end of the episode, as Daniel recounts how his mother was "raped" by David Clarke. All the emotions playing across her face, this slow drag where her face goes from shock, to disappointment (with Daniel, for believing it), to sadness (upon realizing that, well, what - is he supposed to not believe his mother?), to anger ("I'm going to gut that slanderous c***."). I'd argue it was her finest moment on the show so far. 

But I also have to give a big ups to her for this entire episode. Between the proposal scene, the final talk with Fauxmanda, and the scene with Charlotte, she was really letting us get at the Emily character while reasserting, when necessary, that girlfriend is COLD as ice.

Bring on the rest of the season.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/y2hwzd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/commitment,67832/</link><postedTime>2012-01-19T05:46:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-01-19T06:21:41+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ekczti</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/commitment,67832/#comment-415023906</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dol7v</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-01-19</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>