<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6zcc/post/2012-03-30T11:25:48</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwaslh</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/86evg</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>The same points keep being made by others so I feel obliged to counter the completely unwarranted optimism based on naivety on the part of many.  If you think that is whinging then hard shit - don't read it.  

I do not believe that SL should have won a GS.  That's your fantasy, not mine.  I merely pointed out that he has not been very effective to date: I watched 4 and a half of the games and they were desperate for most of them.    Loudly proclaiming otherwise won't change it.  Lancaster may be a genius but he has shown no signs of it yet.  I'm not a MJ apologist, but did England do better in this 6N than the last?  No, thought not.

Your argument about it being a decision being made and therefore unworthy of debate is fatuous.  If I were unlucky enough to meet you in person and I steal your watch, you apparently think that since that decision was made it does not need to be discussed?   A ludicrous argument.

And what the hell does a 'shattered squad' mean?   I had to smirk at that one: do real people actually use cliches like that in Cold blood?    Broken legs all round?  Nervous breakdowns in the front row?  Admit it, you've been reading that muppet Cleary again haven't you?

Lancaster got the nod because (a) he strokes the press and they love him (for now), (b) he was lucky in this year's 6N, (c) he will be less upsetting for the blazers than Mallet (they Always prefer a yes-man to someone who demands his own way and doesn't Mallett have history of falling out with his employers?), and (d) the selection process involved the use a very patriotic Scot and similarly disposed Irishman (I have yet to see a cogent argument on why even the RFU thought it in the interest of a Scot and Irishman to recommend the best man for the job from an English rather than Scottish or Irish perspective).</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zkcyf</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/sport/rugbyunion/international/england/9174762/England-must-hold-its-nerve-as-Stuart-Lancaster-fashions-a-team-in-his-own-way.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T05:22:30+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:25:48+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6zcc</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/sport/rugbyunion/international/england/9174762/England-must-hold-its-nerve-as-Stuart-Lancaster-fashions-a-team-in-his-own-way.html#comment-480854991</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gx4vy</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>