<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwcnx4/update/2012-03-30T05:00:05/9528a43df206c33030dfa7dd66c458ca5997a2d65013a906f6e73e23ea482b32</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>With all the talk of panic and pasties, the Bradford election had passed me by completely, so Galloway's victory came as a surprise for more than one reason.

Galloway might already have signalled the error that has become increasingly commonplace amongst our politicians, believing electoral victory provides a blanket mandate to  as you think fit until just before the next election. Galloway will have to accept he represents every constituent, not just those who voted for him, for whatever reason. That is why he needs to be aggressively challenged on precisely what he means by "Bradford Spring".   

The message must be clear to those who have taken safe seats for granted, your last vestige of safety remains in general elections, when people consider what government they want. This by-election confirms the standing in the affection of all the major parties and the Burning desire of the electorate for something and someone to vote for. It is not just the party leaders who must note this, it is the parties themselves, who must decide why they exist. If it is simply to Gain power under any circumstances, that is not enough. 

Notice has been served, the parties have to reflect long and hard on what has passed and what must happen in future. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zwo6k</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ms5i</id></website><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/brendanoneill2/100148251/george-galloways-victory-confirms-the-denigration-and-demise-of-the-radical-left-not-its-resurgence/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T08:25:47+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T09:00:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwcnx4</id><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/brendanoneill2/100148251/george-galloways-victory-confirms-the-denigration-and-demise-of-the-radical-left-not-its-resurgence/#comment-480536838</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a3a3z</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>