<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkfzvb/post/2012-03-26T12:31:09</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk1dfh</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a3brs</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I go the other way on assets - you can't eat gold -  33 acres of land in the south west with my own clean private water supply, PV electricity and biomass Heating, a small herd of cows for meat &amp; diary, a small sheep flock &amp; chickens, a polytunnel &amp; veg patch - trout in the stream - oh and a very close relationship with my (very well armed) neighbours in the neighbourhood "FarmWatch"- plus a microbrewery and a cider orchard. The global economy can go to hell in a handcart - we're close to not needing it - all for the price of quite a modest house in London.

Land values have quadrupled - so a cracking investment - and last time I looked, they've stopped making it. 

As fossil fuel runs out, the global food supply is coming under acute pressure and drought will all become  major problems - in the SW countryside the only thing I have to worry about is security.

Energy goes up? I don't buy it. Food more expensive - great: I sell it - water a problem? Not with a 180 ft borehole. Can't afford Heating? We use our own woodchip fuel from coppicing our trees. Can't afford transport? We plan to use an electric car charged by PV electicity. Fancy a drink? We brew it. Supermarket empty? We grow our own food.

Suddenly there's a lot of people trying to do the same thing - and around me, most are refugees from the City - clearly they see the impending meltdown and have concluded that the only option is to get out of the mainstream economy.

Even if there is no financial collapse, we are now so well financially insulated through self-sufficiency that we don't need the cash income which  those who live in cities require just to live - and the subsidies for eco- farming, PV electricity and biomass  renewable Heating provide a nice little earner too - as long as they last.

It reminds me of the way that many of the Irish used to live before it became the "Celtic Tiger". </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rvol9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/finance/comment/rogerbootle/9165893/Ireland-dutifully-gulped-down-the-nasty-medicine-but-is-still-in-pain.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-25T19:41:32+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T16:31:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkfzvb</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/finance/comment/rogerbootle/9165893/Ireland-dutifully-gulped-down-the-nasty-medicine-but-is-still-in-pain.html#comment-476516470</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/d0rmp</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>