<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwhfxt/update/2012-03-30T13:55:31/f57e276eac07402e8e0f9e6bfb9447d8cd05d90c332bd1e0dc072a7e2627eac8</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>So if you don't make it to the Champions League your fans your owners your sponsors they don't want you to win either the League Cup the FA Cup or the Charity Shield none of these people see any of the above as a trophy. The demise of LFC is because of this idiotic way of thinking ,  it's no wonder we are at the bottom of the ladder of the top teams our previous managers have  settled for fourth Spot. Weather the so called LFC fans who show they are no better than the gutter press who have been on our case ever since the man came back one message to you all KENNY DALGLISH will never settle for LFC to be fourth, would he take it right now "yes" we are so far behind even Dalglish with his desire to put us back can not do such a mammoth task overnight. If the new faces that arrive fit in we are not to far away,  had our players hit the net more often this season we would not be down in 7th place. To those who have faith stick with it, to those who don't F..K  OFF to another club as we don't need or want scum like you at LFC...    </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hkvx1</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/sport/football/teams/liverpool/9172490/League-Cup-is-a-good-start-but-league-title-is-an-obsession-for-Liverpool-fans-says-former-manager-Gerard-Houllier.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T21:54:41+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:55:31+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwhfxt</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/sport/football/teams/liverpool/9172490/League-Cup-is-a-good-start-but-league-title-is-an-obsession-for-Liverpool-fans-says-former-manager-Gerard-Houllier.html#comment-481009877</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hbfb0</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>