<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/midwj2/post/2012-03-22T19:51:56</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mimegk</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>[Eminem]
And I would like to introduce myself
Surprise! *beatboxes* Hi, it's Ike
'Bout to get my Ike on, icon, with a life supply
Of wife beaters and my Nikes on
And a white tee over that Iron Mike
Lookin' fly tonight, feel like I might die from a spider bite
Come back as Spiderman, Park my Peter inside her dyke
Bitch actin' like she got fuckin' higher standards than Mya, right
Had to pry her fingers Off with the motherfuckin' pliers
Ice cream/I scream with the pliers, like "AAHHH!"
...
Girl, you got a nice pair/pear, but you're plumb/plum stupid!
So when I pull up in that Benz
Don't try to pretend like you ain't interested to impress your stupid ass friends
And refuse to get in woman, and get slammed on the ground and snap like a pool stick against
Cement, if you suck a dick, pretend it's a musical instrument
You get one shot, do not miss your chance to blow
I can tell at first glance you're a ho, cause your pants are so tight
When you dance with O. Trice, your implants explode
So Cold the dykes, the chance of snow in San Francisco
I'm from Detroit city, you livin' in animosity
That's a fucked up state to be in, such an atrocity
Look the way these random thoughts keep you in senseless mind babble
"What me? Apologize? labrbrr" This is the way the rhyme unravels
And I wouldn't fucking take it back if I time traveled!

For the people who are too slow to understand eminem in his prime</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yu6en</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/9ghv</id></website><link>http://www.defsounds.com/hip-hop-songs/obie-trice-ft-eminem-richard/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T17:16:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T23:51:56+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/midwj2</id><link>http://www.defsounds.com/hip-hop-songs/obie-trice-ft-eminem-richard/#comment-474069996</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lbzjr</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>