<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwehbc/post/2012-03-30T08:06:30</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>whether we like manure or not we have to admire/respect them. they play great football. we need to put man utds chance of future success in our own hands. enough of the bulls*** excuses every week and mediocre signings. enough of this f***ing hype coming out of player's mouths and statements clarifying the need to be consistent and fixing whatever other bull*** arises. liverpool needs a culture change. the first step is to  dalglish. i highly respect the man and i do feel for him, however he's past it. he has no tactical nous. he may be a great man manager but that doesn't solely win you top 4 Spots and leagues. carling cup was good but not great. i know it as our first trophy in 6 years but the euphoria fromt he club was quite embarrasing. liverpool needs a winning mentality expecting only the highest standards. man utd have a mentality which reflects the attitude of Always believing they can still in the game. it explains their knack of winning draws/wins at the death after playing ordinarily. they have belief in their ability. they have cohesion, fluidity, belief, precision and ruthlessness. this is what we claim to have. BUT WE DONT!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6723rk</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gfg</id></website><link>http://www.liverpool-kop.com/2012/03/lawro-admits-16-million-man-united-star.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T10:26:58+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T12:06:30+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwehbc</id><link>http://www.liverpool-kop.com/2012/03/lawro-admits-16-million-man-united-star.html#comment-480667755</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>