<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0pvgk/post/2012-04-02T07:05:46</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Once again hats  for leveraging on both writing style and your HBR credibility.. But hats right back on "ethics" and "lack of integrity". So I am obliged to tell you once again "SHAME ON YOU UMAIR". Following is why:
I will quote the pioneers of the discipline of Evolutionary Psychology, Doctors Leda Cosmides &amp; John Tooby. Principle #3 of this discipline states:
"Consciousness is just the tip of the iceberg; most of what goes on in your mind is hidden from you. As a result, your conscious experience can mislead you into thinking that our circuitry is simpler that it really is. Most problems that you experience as easy to solve are very difficult to solve -- they require very complicated neural circuitry".
This is your second article in a row (after "Overthrow yourself") where I see you hammering on the same topic "work-life balance" and heroically coming forth with solutions to the masses of docile corporate executives...who are unconsciously hungry to swallow any pain killer you will give them to help ease their Anxieties and fears resulting from their meaningless and irrational lives. 
I want to make clear that the method you are using would be “ethical” if used solely in the “work” domain. So it would be perfectly fine on topics like how to produce future General Managers or the next generations of CEOs. However, as soon as you bring the “life” part to the equation...it should become a completely different ball game…one cannot cross-over without a mind shift. One would risk being too childish.
I will now outline in bullet points two"ethical mistakes / logical fallacies" by which you are inevitably (and I am sure unaware) shaping the cognitive behavior of your audience. I will do that hoping to generate a counter-intuitive reaction in your audiences and bring back "integrity" to this sensitive topic of "work-life balance":
-Ethical Mistake / Logical Fallacy #1: MISDIAGNOSING THE PROBLEM
Umair you are not putting enough observation and intelligence into the subject matter and as result you are misdiagnosing the problem. The problem of life, so to speak, is a problem that has troubled humans (at least rational humans) for ages. Surely solving such a complicated problem cannot take be in the form of an “HBR editor figuring it out on behalf of the masses and posting it ready-packaged online for the masses as if it were an over-the-counter pill. One must spend a lot of time observing this significance human problem...and I mean individually observing this problem FIRST-HAND...exploring how it is actually affecting our daily behavior...our daily relationships…be it Inter-personal relationship (which is across groups) or Intra-personal relationship (which is most critical and THE source of conflict as this is the birthplace of the famous Ego). A pre-requisite to genuine happiness is surely genuine individual transformation...it cannot be up for grabs for the masses to effortlessly and automatically adopt...no way….it is not a new habit they should pick up…it can only come individually and after the right effort is put by that individual…and I tell you, the right effort starts by observation. Surely the answers to tough questions lie in the questions themselves…in the problems themselves…and not in the "ideal" or the “dream” of a better tomorrow...that would be too mechanistic to capture something as difficult as happiness...I tell you the mechanical way of manufacturing sets of instructions to be followed and actualized can take you to the moon, but can never make you happy. See it for yourself.
 
-Ethical Mistake / Logical Fallacy #2: FAILING AS A MENTOR
Umair after having misdiagnosed the problem, you went PUBLIC with it. It is as if someone "thought" he discovered something and directly went to "share" the discovery, before validating it...this is a most “Pseudo-scientific” approach. I am sure you are aware of the checklist required before a discovery can be worthy enough to be called a scientific one. And isn’t anything non-scientific just speculation? I am also sure you acknowledge the scientific method in disciplines like  the Natural Sciences or Math or Physics. But you have certainly not shown that you “care” about this matter in the psychological sciences. Surely you have carelessly bypassed this method when writing simply because HBR “expect” you to write about something “relevant” in exchange for a salary. So you go and write something. And who is going to stop you from doing that. Absolutely no one! HBR certainly won’t care as long as the article “looks” ok. 
Some might argue that you are merely stating your opinion and not forcing it on others...that you are merely laying it out...that you are merely being a citizen of the democratic world...but I would argue back that isn’t democracy just another form of manipulating people so that monetary  is achieved by the few…sure a more "overtly" acceptable kind of system, but a "discretely" manipulative, psychologically and mentally, rather than physically. Yes Umair you have prematurely went PUBLIC…”Acting” like a professional mentor...Being an HR professional, I can safely tell you that you would rate F on mentoring…first rule of mentoring: a mentor should not shape the behavior of people…because that would be something "unethical" to do.
 
 </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6gmjn3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/mft1</id></website><link>http://blogs.hbr.org/haque/2012/03/the_economic_roots_of_your_life_crisis.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-16T16:53:21+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T11:05:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0pvgk</id><link>http://blogs.hbr.org/haque/2012/03/the_economic_roots_of_your_life_crisis.html#comment-483423763</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ztaez</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-16</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>