<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m02gkf/update/2012-03-31T14:09:17/6a739cbfb481e8fdd5c9f8b447407b4ece72cec73a27e35379956286d6fc5a60</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>To those who truly believe that all Zimmerman did was ask Martin a question and Martin decided his answer would be to beat Zimmerman's @$$.. . . . . . . . 
Because you were there, and saw exactly what happened. How do you know that all Zimmerman did was ask a question and Martin just started to beat on him?! Really?! So that's how it went down? Forget the facts that Zimmerman (the self appointed "captain") had called 911 over 40 times in the past (the majority to report a "suspicious" black person)... That none of those calls produced an arrest... That he was basically stalking Martin on a dark street (per accounts of the neighborhood) with the thought already Burned into his (Zimmerman) mind that Martin was "suspicious" "up to no good" "on drugs or something" "these a$$h*les Always get away" "F'n ____" . . . . And confronted Martin (in a nice way?) despite being told to wait for the police. Forget about all of that. Obviously (according to you) Zimmerman just said "Hi! How are you tonite? What are you doing?", and Martin just started beating his @$$. If Zimmerman had complied (not followed Martin), Like his "good friend" Mr. Oliver said, and did not continue following Martin, How was he able to ask Martin a question? Of course if Zimmerman had just called 911 and waited for the police, in his vehicle, ... they would have shown up (for the 40th something time) and found there to be NO wrong doing What so Ever!! Again!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67i5gb</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/31/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T13:47:24+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T18:09:17+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m02gkf</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/31/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html#comment-482057413</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8rf0t</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>