<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tmv5/post/2012-03-29T09:36:44</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The question is how does the opposing Defence prepare for Carolina's Offence. Cam, Tolbert, Williams, Stewart, Smith, Olsen.  Defense Secondaries can't hang back because of the Run, Screen and Swing pass out of Back Field by four different weapons. Steve Smith will Burn you on a Blitz if you are not careful. This year i see Gettis breaking out and Edwards improving. In my opinion Edwards has been missed used by a long ways. Just look at what he done at ASU. They need to develop a few plays where he can pass as well as catch the ball. If they can run a trick play where all the Offensive line can stand there and not move and score ( coolest play ever ) then they can use Edwards strengths as a quarterback as well. Then if our Defense is ranked at least Fifth overall i think we have a chance at the Big Show. But I do believe the Defense will be Ranked First or Second. With Beason &amp; Davis coming back i think it will take some pressure Off the secondary, but i would like to see some improvements in that area. Godfrey is Great and Munnerlyn is a good Nickle but we need one more fast shut down corner. All in all i can't wait for the Panther's to pounce.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hjptn</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnei</id></website><link>http://www.charlotteobserver.com/2012/03/28/3133853/seattle-coach-look-out-for-cam.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T19:17:43+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:36:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tmv5</id><link>http://www.charlotteobserver.com/2012/03/28/3133853/seattle-coach-look-out-for-cam.html#comment-479493364</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g24du</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>