<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msmyvl/update/2012-03-27T07:58:59/ba2c5075eb8793d3418587424b3ee718fb937ebb9f84f1bdc0ffc748abfd7047</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I've never been one to dismiss cover art. I'm actually quite proud of my rather immense video game collection. As such, I have so many shelves in my living space that I can't fit a proper bed without having to climb over it so instead I have a futon that I roll up in the morning. Every wall has shelves, with everything from Atari to present packed in them. I still have most of the boxes for all my cart games, and the loose ones all have their own special shelves that I made for them so they don't fall about, especially the N64 games with their very stupid shape. Everything that has come out with proper cases I still have every single one of them. In fact I will not buy games without them. Say I'm purchasing a Dreamcast game on Ebay and it says game disc only, or disc &amp; case no manual, I won't buy it.
 
I also never open a game and immediately start playing it. First, I  look at the cover. Then I read the blurb on the back. I then open it and look through any inserts. Then I read the manual. Finally I'll play the game. I've  been a bookworm, so I Always take the time to fully read and enjoy everything the game has to offer before even turning on the system.
 
Now to the actual article. I really like the choices here. I definitely agree with the GTA covers. They're all great, and instantly recognisable. My favorite is Vice City's cover. The only one I'll go ahead and disagree with is Left 4 Dead. While I like simplicity, I find this is too simple. While Heavy Rain's cover piques your interest, and is actually what first got me to even look at the game, Left 4 Dead's in my opinion seems to just be using the popularity of Zombies to try and sell it's game. 
 
My personal favorites are both from Sega Saturn. Blazing Dragons and NiGHTS into dreams. I was a huge Monty Python fan thanks to my dad, and I remember seeing an advert for Blazing Dragons in the back of one of my Saturn games. I was able to read the words Monty Python but not much else since I couldn't actually read yet, so I got my dad to read it for me. When he told that a guy from Monty Python made the game I instantly fell in love with it, though I have never actually played it. I saw it at my rental shop and the image has forever been Burned into my mind but I have still never bought it. NiGHTS I do have and I think the reason I like the cover so much is because of the nostalgia it inspires. Love that game.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lgxe9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lroj</id></website><link>http://www.cheatcc.com/extra/bestvideogameboxart.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T20:36:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-27T11:58:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msmyvl</id><link>http://www.cheatcc.com/extra/bestvideogameboxart.html#comment-477349788</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>