<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwyy75/update/2012-03-30T10:34:51/734fe4984102b85af385ccbbbd9571826674ba98fb83d99ffd863438d9da2222</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmpqb</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lhdsu</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>From a distance?  What if it's every day?  What if it's several times a day?  What if it's 3 or 4 of these hoodie types in a group walking slowly?  Are you comfortable with that?  Does that make you happy in your home?  You wouldn't feel the lest bit threatened?  You're not going to do anything but let the police handle it?  How many times are you willing to call 911?  How long before they stop taking you seriously?  Who long before somebody in the neighborhood has had just about enough of it?  How long before YOU have had just about enough of it?  

You get it.  It's the theme of countless westerns and 50's crime dramas.  Finally some little guy stands up on his feet and does something about it.  Maybe he's the one folks thought would be the last one to Act.  In the movies, at least the old movies, he's the hero.  But In our times apparently he's Satan incarnate.

Well, rest assured, you're going to get your way.  Zimmerman is being crucified and he will probably be tried and convicted of something.  

Meantime I don't believe you at all.  You really don't think Zimmerman is more dangerous.  You're just spouting.  You know good and well that a 6'-3" unknown black teenager wearing a hoodie approaching you on the sidewalk is a lot more dangerous to you than an overzealous neighborhood watch type.  Because you understand that there's nothing you could say to the hoodie that would stop him if he's up to no good, you are toast.  All you have to tell the watchman is that you live in the neighborhood. Worst case is he may be a bit of a bore and want to chat about the weather and the Tebow trade and you really don't have time.  The result of the one scenario is that you are on the ground robbed and Bleeding.  The result of the other is that you're a couple of minutes late for dinner.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zfs4j</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f7e3</id></website><link>http://www.wnd.com/2012/03/its-all-about-race-now/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:09:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T14:34:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwyy75</id><link>http://www.wnd.com/2012/03/its-all-about-race-now/#comment-480802288</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zdmzg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>