<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mjglo7/update/2012-03-19T06:15:05/faf540e7cb884f249a2cf3df773a8998bbee1ef5a70d1e367d8d154b7975861c</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Here's the weird part: all these lowlifes think progressives are controlling the government. They're mad at US for the mess we're in.

A recent poll has a majority of Americans believing Obama is "too liberal."  on the fringe, where the true Repubs lurk, they think the President is a crazed socialist-radical-communist-pinko. They think the Misery Index is at a 28-year high because Obama is being too liberal!

(Pause while Perry goes mad...)

But there's more. Instead of making it clear that Obama is in no way a liberal or lefty, Democrats are stolidly defending Obama's policies, pretending they really are liberal policies. This means that my colleagues on the left either believe, or are pretending to believe, that Obama is a very progressive fellow. They are, of course, doing this based on the universal fear of another Republican President--a fear which I fully share.

So we've got poverty shooting up faster than ever, Depression-Era levels of unemployment, massive skepticism about government's ability to do anything at all, the banks bigger than ever and still up to their old tricks, the Constitution being further shredded every day, etc., etc.--and everyone is pretending Democrats are in power, doing Democratic things.

Do you see how this is damaging the left and the Dems in a big way? All the crazies--and everyone else, too--think progressive policies are in effect. The only point of national debate is whether those policies are helping or not. The left says yes; the right says nay. But it's all based on the fantasy that any sort of liberal policies are being enacted, anywhere, in any way whatsoever.

The result will be a newly-militant rightward fringe who are insanely mad...at the left, for electing and supporting this crazy leftist radical. And the left's behavior is supporting this delusion. So progressives have no power to speak of, but are going to take the Heat for our ongoing disasters. The Right will argue for decades that progressive polices were tried and failed during the Obama Administration.

&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JYkyZm8MGQE"&gt;Fear of Republicans&lt;/a&gt;</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ekbl5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ant8</id></website><link>http://www.alternet.org/election2012/154578/birthers%2C_racists%2C_sexists_and_homophobes%3A_13_toxic_endorsers_of_gop_presidential_candidates/comments/</link><postedTime>2012-03-19T07:25:46+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-19T10:15:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mjglo7</id><link>http://www.alternet.org/election2012/154578/birthers%2C_racists%2C_sexists_and_homophobes%3A_13_toxic_endorsers_of_gop_presidential_candidates/comments/#comment-468862719</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/duia</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-19</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>