<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk1ob0/post/2012-03-26T11:53:06</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>These movies are no JOKE and sadly like the the lore of Jules Verne and his contemporaries we will not be waiting so long to see the outcome. 
1.)Cash will be a thing of the past and any worth will be installed on a chip the man can turn Off at any minuet he chooses.  
2.) A welfare state is what is wanted. Pregnant teens and low income housing. You become property of the state and will be used as such.
3.) No grocery stores. You will go to the "store" on a given day and be given your aloted amount of food.
4.) Pertussis immunization? Flu Shots? Keep getting them there good for ya. VERY FEW pharmaceutical meds are beneficial to your health.
5. Genetically altered foods, Growth hormones for cattle, NOT GOOD, Cattle can't even reproduce properly. That is why your paying $6 a pound for hamburger.
6.) should be first! APATHY! we have to stop waiting for something to happen. Get up and tell your neighbors. Call your state reps and congressmen, Do something, ANYTHING.
7) Educate yourself and spread the word. Show documenteries at your library. Teach YOUR CHILDREN!
8) Time has already been wasted.
9.) Research MONSANTO. again EDUCATE YOURSELF! Do not buy into the medical sale. Look up cures for your diseases or disorders on line. Something as simple as drinking water can help you. Vitamins save lives. Organic fruits and veggies. Learn how they loose their beneficial aspects once picked, processed and cooked.
10.) UNITE for a greater good. Know your rights. Study the constitution. Demand freedom NOW!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rso3e</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/26/travel/hunger-games-travel/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T13:46:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T15:53:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk1ob0</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/26/travel/hunger-games-travel/index.html#comment-476488187</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/o1g9</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>