<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jasr/update/2012-04-02T02:18:00/f09fad84ec1aaf4e4ecec2b4ce534dcd84f4922c8ea95043bedf01b55fe49566</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Beginning to have a place in my heart for The Hound. Sure, he rides down unarmed butcher's boys and skewers them, and obliterates armed knights with a single blow...but last season he saved Sansa life and gave her his hanky linen for her split lip on the walkway, rescued the Knight of Flowers from the huge evil brother of his, and it opens this season with the Hound backing Sansa again, discretely, by vouching for her dumb lie "It is word!".

Ceirse is one Cold fish. And well  by Lena Heady. Who while evil and Cold - is hot enough in attractiveness that you sort of understand...Jaime's  lust.
Joffrey just adds more each week to the vilest most loathsome child character I can remember. Not superbly Acted by young Jack Gleeson (sometimes he overacts or the emotions look a little forced - but give him a break, he doesn't have 50 years of experience like Helen Mirren) - Still, what young Jack Gleeson is doing overall is superbly done nevertheless in effect on the audience. Because the end result is Gleeson makes the whole audience toss out their "never hurt a child principles" and actively ACHE for any adult near him to bitch-lap the little monster or worse. 

Love the directors are giving sleazy Bronn more sardonic one-liners this season. Jeremy Flynn is awesome!
Like Osha, too! 
.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6vkanr</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/vh3p</id></website><link>http://tvrecaps.ew.com/recap/game-of-thrones-north-remembers/</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T01:55:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T06:18:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jasr</id><link>http://tvrecaps.ew.com/recap/game-of-thrones-north-remembers/#comment-483311963</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ah9i4</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>