<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw3rnl/update/2012-03-31T11:35:23/964a1d6378a96508c73443abcdbc39608681e2a1b034a9e282ebc7495fac8b34</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>237 Years Ago Patrick Henry Said: "Give Me Liberty or Give Me Death.
		
Written by Joe Wolverton, II		
		  
	



	
		





	Lord
 Byron called him the “Forest-born Demosthenes.” Others called him the 
“Lion of Liberty.” Whatever the title, Patrick Henry (left) was never 
one to mince words in the defense of freedom. The silver-tongued orator 
was never at a loss for words, and he spoke with a ready arsenal of 
logic. Biographer William Wirt said of him in 1817, “Tis true he could 
talk — Gods how he could talk!”

	Generations of his countrymen have celebrated Patrick Henry for his rousing calls to arms. First, there was the speech in opposition to the Stamp  when the 29-year-old newly minted delegate rose to address the Virginia House of Burgesses:

	 

	It was in the midst of this magnificent debate, while he was descanting
 on the tyranny of the obnoxious , that he exclaimed, in a voice of 
thunder, and with the look of a god, “Caesar had his Brutus — Charles 
the first, his Cromwell — and George the third — ” (“Treason,” cried the
 Speaker — “treason, treason,” echoed from every part of the House. — It
 was one of those trying moments which is decisive of character. — Henry
 faltered not an instant; but rising to a loftier attitude, and fixing 
on the Speaker an eye of the most determined fire, he finished his 
sentence with the firmest emphasis) “may profit by their example. If 
this be treason, make the most of it.”

	 

	Henry became one of the first of the Founding Fathers to call for 
independence and to face head on the repercussions thereof. He was 
fearless in his defense of the right of man to be self-governing and 
free from the oppression of tyrants.

	 

	One account elegantly describes Henry’s critical role in the American struggle for independence:

	 

	Patrick Henry is all but forgotten as the first of the Founding Fathers
 to call for independence, for revolution against Britain, for a bill of
 rights, and for as much freedom as possible from ­government — American
 as well as British. If Washington was the "Sword of the Revolution" and
 Jefferson "the Pen," Patrick Henry more than earned his epithet as "the
 Trumpet" of the Revolution for rousing Americans to arms in the 
Revolutionary War.

	 

	The second of Patrick Henry’s most remembered bold renunciations of 
English despotism and reminders of the rights of Americans orations was 
delivered 237 years ago. On March 23, 1775, Henry implored his fellow 
Virginians to take up arms not in revolution against a legitimate 
government, but to restore the rights of all Englishmen to have a say in
 the laws made to govern them.

	 

	Arising to address his fellow delegates at the Virginia Convention, 
Patrick Henry stood in St. John’s Church in Richmond aware that 
Virginia’s support for the War against Great Britain was in great part 
dependent on his ability to once again ignite the fire of resistance in 
the Old Dominion.

	 

	Sitting among the assemblage of notable burgesses were the 
aforementioned George Washington and Thomas Jefferson, the latter of 
whom reported that Henry’s declaration “had produced a great effect, and
 I myself had been highly delighted and moved.”

	 

	Patrick Henry began by presenting several resolutions that would put 
the colony of Virginia "into a posture of defense ... embodying, arming,
 and disciplining such a number of men as may be sufficient for that 
purpose." As an earlier measure had passed by a very narrow margin, 
Henry delivered this speech before a vote was taken, imploring his 
colleagues to support the supply of troops and materiel to the fight for
 freedom.

	 

	Speaking without any notes and with a clamorous crescendo in his voice,
 Henry concluded his speech with the words that still swell the hearts 
of those engaged in the war on tyranny.

	 

	There is so much Heat and so much fire in this ardent advocate’s 
defense of freedom and call to arms that no restatement would suffice. 
Therefore, here are substantial selections from the text of that famous 
oration as reported by early Patrick Henry biographer William Wirt in 
1816.

	 

	No man thinks more highly than I do of the patriotism, as well as 
abilities, of the very worthy gentlemen who have just addressed the 
House. But different men often see the same subject in different lights;
 and, therefore, I hope that it will not be thought disrespectful to 
those gentlemen, if, entertaining as I do opinions of a character very 
opposite to theirs, I shall speak forth my sentiments freely and without
 reserve...

	 

	Mr. President, it is natural to man to indulge in the illusions of 
hope. We are apt to shut our eyes against a painful truth, and listen to
 the song of that siren, till she transforms us into beasts. Is this the
 part of wise men, engaged in a great and arduous struggle for liberty? 
Are we disposed to be of the number of those who, having eyes, see not, 
and having ears, hear not, the things which so nearly concern their 
temporal salvation?

	 

	For my part, whatever anguish of spirit it may cost, I am willing to 
know the whole truth — to know the worst and to provide for it. I have 
but one lamp by which my feet are guided; and that is the lamp of 
experience. I know of no way of judging of the future but by the 
past... 

	 

	We have held the subject up in every light of which it is capable; but 
it has been all in vain. Shall we resort to entreaty and humble 
supplication? What terms shall we find which have not been already 
exhausted? Let us not, I beseech you, sir, deceive ourselves longer...

	 

	Our petitions have been slighted; our remonstrances have produced 
additional violence and insult; our supplications have been disregarded;
 and we have been spurned, with contempt, from the foot of the throne. 
In vain, after these things, may we indulge the fond hope of peace and 
reconciliation. There is no longer any room for hope.

	 

	If we wish to be free — if we mean to preserve inviolate those 
inestimable privileges for which we have been so long contending — if we
 mean not basely to abandon the noble struggle in which we have been so 
long engaged, and which we have  ourselves never to abandon until
 the glorious object of our contest shall be obtained, we must fight! I 
repeat it, sir, we must fight! An appeal to arms and to the God of Hosts
 is all that is left us!

	 

	The battle, sir, is not to the strong alone; it is to the vigilant, the
 active, the brave. Besides, sir, we have no election. If we were base 
enough to desire it, it is now too late to retire from the contest. 
There is no retreat but in submission and slavery! Our chains are 
forged! Their clanking may be heard on the plains of Boston! The war is 
inevitable — and let it come! I repeat it, sir, let it come!

	 

	It is in vain, sir, to extenuate the matter. Gentlemen may cry, "Peace!
 Peace!" — but there is no peace. The war is actually begun! The next 
gale that sweeps from the north will bring to our ears the clash of 
resounding arms! Our brethren are already in the field! Why stand we 
here idle? What is it that gentlemen wish? What would they have? Is life
 so dear, or peace so sweet, as to be purchased at the price of chains 
and slavery? Forbid it, Almighty God! I know not what course others may 
take; but as for me, give me liberty, or give me death!

	 

	Where can we find a Patrick Henry for our generation? Where is there a 
man or woman or will Shout “Give me liberty or give me death” rather 
than the more commonly heard “Give me liberty or give me safety”?

	 

	We, as the heirs of such unwavering bravery, must raise the clarion 
call. We must remind our countrymen that security is not the purpose of 
freedom. We must honor Patrick Henry’s memory and not permit our elected
 representatives to demand our liberty in exchange for the illusory 
promise of safety.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67hsio</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7e99</id></website><link>http://conservatives4palin.com/2012/03/holding-out-for-a-hero.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:00:18+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T15:35:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw3rnl</id><link>http://conservatives4palin.com/2012/03/holding-out-for-a-hero.html#comment-481924812</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5r4tx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>