<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms1r3n/update/2012-03-28T02:41:58/6937b5ddb29946d6e4beb48f829e3ade87810ac591b6c938be2ccd384a02cff3</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msqux5</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/chkef</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Sorry, but you are dead wrong on every one of your two "facts."

State education funding began declining about 1981-82 and school districts began laying of teachers for lack of funds for the first time.  This was the immediate aftermath of Prop 13 and the delay from 1979 passage was due to the state running through the huge reserves it had that, in part, led to putting Prop 13 on the ballot in the first place.

Lest you say I make this up, I was one of those laid Off in Pleasanton El (in those days) and did not get recalled until the end of October and didn't go back.  Burn me once....the private sector was much more secure for me and about 3X more financially agreeable...shall we say.

In the 80's, education got some "extra" funding because of another attempt to "reform" education, SB 813, but it was mostly earmarked for programs like longer school day, longer school year, Classroom Teacher Instructional Improvement grants (CTIIP), Mentor Teacher and the like.

Then the next funding crisis was from 1991-1997 when Prop 98 was suspended and the state invented such a thing as a 'deficit factor."  The simple way to explain it was the state withheld part, and then all, of the COLA education was due under prop 98 and promised to restore it to its statutory levels some time in the future.  Notice, I did not say re-pay.  Backfilling previous years' shortages was not on the docket.  It was just to restore the funding level per student, eventually, but only going forward.  It took until  the 2001-2002 school year for education to be brought up to its legal minimum entitlement.  

Education funding was at the legal minimum funding for a little while, until 2007-2008.  Deficit factors were again invented but today's preliminary ruling by the judge makes it possible that the state won't even have to bring education funding up to the legal minimum EVER, despite the agreement to do so.

If a classroom has 32 students, a little under average in the post-CSR days, the school will get $35.11 per student per day for 180 student days instead of $43.33 per student per day which is the legal minimum under California's Constitution and 47th lowest in the nation.  Prior to Prop 13, Student funding in California was 6th highest in the nation.  This money is for supplies, custodians, secretaries, aides, gardening, maintenance equipment, paper, teacher salary, Principal's salary, books and other such fripperies.  So the average class of 32 brings in about $249,600 if fully funded up to the legal minimum level.  Instead, the average class only brings in $202,000.

People have been complaining about to effect of Prop 13 on school funding for 29 years, not starting this year for the first time as you assert.

Other than that, all of your facts are correct.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lwmpp</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnm3</id></website><link>http://blogs.sacbee.com/capitolalertlatest/2012/03/judge-tentatively-rules-for-california-in-school-funding-suit.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T22:53:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T06:41:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms1r3n</id><link>http://blogs.sacbee.com/capitolalertlatest/2012/03/judge-tentatively-rules-for-california-in-school-funding-suit.html#comment-478146152</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7n79</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>