<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miduwm/update/2012-03-22T19:27:48/4b772e4ffd1af1be9eadd0ab48a2635947ecf0f6be3f7562d6cd2c760f8d340d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/migsfu</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ljr4h</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>You have a real talent for blogging nothing at all, dear. 

What do you think of these violations of human rights in Communist Cuba?

2009 Human Rights Report: Cuba
Bureau of Democracy, Human Rights, and Labor
Arrest Procedures and Treatment While in Detention

The law places few formal limits on police discretion to stop or interrogate citizens. Police street surveillance was heavy, and police frequently and randomly stopped cars and pedestrians for questioning. There are no formal protections under the law to protect citizens from these investigative stops, and there were many reports that such stops continued during the year. 

Police have broad detention powers, which they may exercise without a warrant. Under the law, police can detain without a warrant not only persons caught in the  but also someone merely accused of a crime against state security. Police, by law, cannot conduct a search without a warrant, but both the CCDHRN and human rights lawyer Rene Gomez Manzano reported that police Always had available a supply of signed and stamped blank warrants that they merely filled out on the Spot.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y8j9w</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yzhx</id></website><link>http://www.miamiherald.com/2012/03/21/2706473/sen-marco-rubio-internet-access.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T21:59:35+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T23:27:48+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miduwm</id><link>http://www.miamiherald.com/2012/03/21/2706473/sen-marco-rubio-internet-access.html#comment-474055999</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/80afr</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>