<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3pc6b/post/2012-03-29T20:01:09</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>How can you feel Cold to your family, when brought up Cold,
towards myself early life, when you cannot be Cold,
when eventual need called, cannot ignore.

A corner of the mind disturbed, past times compromised,
come back to haunt, a closed corner thought shut,
only to find, unlatched, a jack in a box, with life.


Don't think I need to say anymore, for people who "get" what I just said. Be thankful those that don't, emotional torture when young, day in day out, drip-drip, when nothing was felt good enough, but when looked back it should have. Backed my parents up  when young, but self them was only I experienced.

People in general society just say leave me to God, but I was in a peculiar situation, could write chapters on it. But I survived, in sorts, sorts of what can be seen as I am now. Jesus wept, I wasn't being over-sensitive, I just had two parents, one shouldn't have been with the other, my mother should have left my dad to whoever.

Anyway, I am feeling better these days, got over the dark days when my mother died and everything came to a head in my head of all my life. Never was happier when I was away from them, but something inside me Always dragged me back. It was like a multi-generational form of some sort of abuse, destroying each other, but not in the usual sense, just emotional coldness, and shoving hurdles due to fright in front, that shouldn't be there, for life.
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/emdbu6</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yhv3</id></website><link>http://www.alastaircampbell.org/blog/2011/08/02/a-rare-venture-into-poetry-and-yet-another-outlet-for-my-madness/</link><postedTime>2011-08-02T09:27:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:01:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3pc6b</id><link>http://www.alastaircampbell.org/blog/2011/08/02/a-rare-venture-into-poetry-and-yet-another-outlet-for-my-madness/#comment-480047854</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-08-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>