<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzhsr/update/2012-03-30T14:26:04/00f2314596dde53291dc1a6fb32c70ad4bea29d8d71209ad9c755943e101fb93</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Soundtrack - scene by scene

&lt;b&gt;ASSUME EVERYTHING IN THIS POST IS A SPOILER&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;b&gt;p2&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. APARTMENT - DAY
&lt;/code&gt;
Nice introduction to Ian. I get a clear mental image of Ian even if I don't know his height, hair colour, or eye colour. Works for me.

I'd trim "Is it a eureka moment?" to "A eureka moment?" and "Guess not." to "No."

The fake movie trailer is funny, but do you want to have jokes in your comedy that aren't part of your comedy? The exchange through the wall is a nice introduction to Mrs. Pokorny.

The scene is a nice introduction to Kaitlyn's character, but we don't know her appearance. Ian's character and their relationship come through nicely. There isn't an obvious, "Oh, they're ex-lovers" vibe. I'm good with that. This early it's fine to know something happened between them without knowing what.

&lt;b&gt;p6&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. LIMZICKI’S OFFICE - DAY
&lt;/code&gt;
I like Stuart's description. Stuart's character is clear. Perhaps his lines are a little too funny for funny's sake. Stuart isn't an important enough character for it to glitch the story.

Nice set up of the situation through the two characters arguing.

&lt;b&gt;p10&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. RECORDING STUDIO - DAY
&lt;/code&gt;
Ian isn't in the action. He just starts talking. It's a bit confusing. This scene develops the crisis situation and lays in the setup for a disaster later (the CD).

I like we see the violinist who appears at the end. He (or she) is a very minor character, but seeing him (or her) twice ties things up nicely.

&lt;b&gt;p11&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. CAR - NIGHT
&lt;/code&gt;
Not a scene…

&lt;code&gt;
EXT. HOTEL - CONTINUOUS
&lt;/code&gt;
But it continues here. That's fine.

&lt;b&gt;p12&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. HOTEL - BACK OFFICE - LATER
&lt;/code&gt;
Now it falls apart. For ease of reading, I think this scene should also be marked CONTINUOUS. Taken together they show the continuous action of Ian getting ready for his shift. Strictly speaking, there has to be a time jump between the EXT. and the BACK OFFICE. It's very minor. The previous two scenelettes don't stand on their own and should be cut if they don't blend into this one. All they show is Ian changing &lt;i&gt;while&lt;/i&gt; travelling.  This sequence could start in the BACK OFFICE with Ian changing as he asks Rob for an advance.

I like that Ian simply asks for the advance without explaining. It's enough.

&lt;code&gt;
INT. HOTEL - LOBBY - LATER
&lt;/code&gt;
Can you find a single word to cover "ostentatious ambience"?

The drunk hasn't been noisy at the time he's described as noisy.

With the previous scenes we now have a complete picture of Ian's plight as a struggling composer in need of money who is about to punt his big break and has a soul deadening day job. And another nice set up for a later disaster (the spilled drink).

&lt;b&gt;p13&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. APARTMENT - NIGHT
&lt;/code&gt;
*lots

"Unquestionable hottie but a firecracker" doesn't call up a clear image. Are "hottie" and "firecracker" contrasts?

Tracy's actions define her character nicely. The Ian/Tracy dynamic is clear.

I like the connection to the first scene in the cause of the accident. Well done.

&lt;b&gt;p16&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. WHITE ROOM - NIGHT
&lt;/code&gt;
DISSOLVE TO is unnecessary. And weird. He's knocked out, hard.

Nice introduction to Soundtrack. We are shown how it works, but we don't yet know we've been shown how it works. Ditto for its goal.

&lt;b&gt;p17&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. APARTMENT - DAY
&lt;/code&gt;
Tracy talks, then storms in.

Nice introduction to how Soundtrack works, and what it thinks of Tracy. We learn about Ian's ex-girlfriend. If we're paying &lt;i&gt;close&lt;/i&gt; attention, we know it's Kaitlyn. (And that Soundtrack approves of Kaitlyn.)

Don't need POV here. He sees an empty hallway is fine.

I like Mrs Pokorny. I like the dynamic between her and Ian. More info about how Soundtrack operates.

How can she slam his door? Seems awkward. Unless she pushes him back in and snags the door with her cane.

&lt;b&gt;p21&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
EXT. APARTMENT - CONTINUOUS
&lt;/code&gt;
You mean EXT. APARTMENT BUILDING, yes?

Nice vignette of Ian grappling with Soundtrack. I would suggest cutting something this short, particularly as the next scene opens with the same beat, but this is so short, and somewhat funny, I think the extra example of how Soundtrack works is worth it. At this early stage of our experience with Soundtrack, this scene is not inconsequential.

&lt;code&gt;
INT. CAR - CONTINUOUS
&lt;/code&gt;
I question CONTINUOUS.

The scene lays in more examples of how Soundtrack works. It is aware of things Ian is not aware of. We get Ian into the beer shirt quite reasonably, connecting the setup from earlier to the upcoming disaster. I like this evidence the writer thought things through.

&lt;b&gt;p22&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. STUDIO - HALLWAY - DAY
&lt;/code&gt;
*RECEPTIONIST

&lt;b&gt;p24&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
CONFERENCE ROOM
&lt;/code&gt;
This scene demonstrates my biggest technical concern about the whole conceit of Soundtrack. See my summary post for details.

No description of the Producer or the Sound Editor. Very minor characters, they only have one line between them, it still might be telling to see if they contrast with Gordan. Are they sloppy like him, or dressed in quality suits? The answer changes the room's atmosphere.

Nice payoffs of two setups from two previous scenes into one big disaster. Well done.

Stuart is again a little slapstick. He's not a main character. I think the writer gets away with it.

&lt;b&gt;p28&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. STUDIO - HALLWAY - DAY
&lt;/code&gt;
INT. STUDIO - HALLWAY - DAY to INT. STUDIO - CONFERENCE ROOM - DAY only rates CONFERENCE ROOM, while CONFERENCE ROOM to HALLWAY gets the full INT. STUDIO - HALLWAY - DAY. Either would work, but be consistent. Inconsistency can trip up a reader. Is this a full scene change or not? (It isn't.)

Nice choice to end the scene on Ian simple statement "I don't know." It gives us all we need to know. An actor could make a lot of that simple line in context.

Why does Soundtrack cut out? There is no clear external event to trigger the change. So far Soundtrack has responded to externals. The rules of the game are getting fuzzy.

&lt;b&gt;p29&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. EXAM ROOM - DAY
&lt;/code&gt;
Doesn't move the story forward. It's funny. It's a nice change from the hectic pace of previous scenes. It's not completely extraneous because Ian seeks help for his condition. This is never revisited. Cutting this scene wouldn't effect the plot. Bad sign.

&lt;b&gt;p32&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. HOTEL - LOBBY - NIGHT
&lt;/code&gt;
This is the other scene that begs huge technical questions. How are the duelling soundtracks (Soundtrack and piano) going to be filmed? I don't know. I don't need to know. But any studio reader, producer, or director is going to ask. This needs to be rewritten to show the writer has considered this question and has an answer. Otherwise the screenplay is likely to be binned as unfilmable.

&lt;code&gt;
INT. HOTEL - BACK OFFICE - CONTINUOUS
&lt;/code&gt;
What's Soundtrack doing during this scene? This is the first scene since the accident in which Soundtrack is completely absent. Ian blew his big chance just before this scene. Now he's lost the job that keeps him fed. Surely this is worth a comment by Soundtrack?

Rob doesn't need to storm  (from his own office). End the scene with "Go home."

&lt;b&gt;p34&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
EXT. HOTEL - NIGHT
&lt;/code&gt;
Soundtrack's back. What was the trigger?

Here begins Ian's pursuit of Kaitlyn's Theme. Nice revelation.

&lt;code&gt;
EXT. KAITLYN’S APARTMENT - NIGHT
&lt;/code&gt;
Now Soundtrack won't play because he's trying to force it. That works. But it's muddied by other times it doesn't play simply because the writer didn't bother to include it. The impact is lessened. I like how he tries saying different things to coax Soundtrack out.

&lt;b&gt;p36&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. APARTMENT - NIGHT
&lt;/code&gt;
Soundtrack could be less aggressive and still be uncooperative. This would leave the door open for many more instances of Ian actively opposing Soundtrack rather than being completely passive, allowing it to bully him.

Where'd he get the champagne? Tracy withdrew the offered glass.

Nice conflict between Ian and Soundtrack, but he, a composer, never tries to override it in his head. He just tries to drown it out with exterior noise. What if he tried kissing her while humming The Battle Hymn of the Republic? That would make him more active, and be funnier. Or what if he tried humming the stripper song while she was doing her dance? To him it would be a logical counter to the goofy music, but it wouldn't go over with her any better than his giggling.

How did Mrs Pokorny hear him. It's mildly funny, but doesn't match what we've been shown about her hearing.

Ian's fight with Soundtrack would be stronger if he was fighting it not just with drink, but with drunken singing.

&lt;b&gt;p41&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. APARTMENT - BATHROOM - DAY
&lt;/code&gt;
Lose DISSOLVE TO.

Very short scene. Does advance the story. Ian surrenders to Soundtrack. He is defeated.

&lt;b&gt;p42&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. ELEVATOR - DAY

INT. MALL - DAY

INT. STORE - DAY
&lt;/code&gt;
Earlier, you used CONTINUOUS for scenes much less directly connected than these. For consistency, and to not trip up the reader, use CONTINUOUS here as well, or collapse the whole thing into one scene. The store seems big enough to have its own elevator. Just start with an action block and capitalize ELEVATOR.

The perusal of possible gifts kibitzed by Soundtrack is nice. It flows well and has a couple of chuckles, but Ian is completely reactive in this scene. (Again.) He's allowing himself to be bullied by Soundtrack without complaint. This scene would be another good opportunity for him to try and overpower Soundtrack by humming triumphant tunes when examining a gift he likes but the soundtrack doesn't, or make the sad trombone noise himself when told the price of the bracelet. Or, if you want to play up his surrender, have him actively ask Soundtrack for guidance, maybe putting up a fight when it chooses the bracelet.

&lt;b&gt;p43&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. LIBRARY - DAY
&lt;/code&gt;
Why is Soundtrack absent? Yes, we need to hear the external porn music to be amusingly misdirected. Yes, we need to hear the Faint strains of Kaitlyn's theme. Those are not reasons imbedded in the internal logic of the story. Soundtrack has been routinely kibitzing on much less important matters than this. Now it's about to get what it wants and it's completely quiet? Doesn't make sense under the rules laid out by events so far.

The interchange between Ian and Kaitlyn is very nice. We get lots of backstory without feeling they are telling us backstory. Ian's inability to be clear seems rooted in his character and not convenience.

&lt;b&gt;p49&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. APARTMENT - DAY
&lt;/code&gt;
A montage! Yay! Cut it. Leave montages to hack directors who don't know how to tell a story.

&lt;code&gt;
INT. APARTMENT - MOMENTS LATER
&lt;/code&gt;
This scene only provides an unnecessary set up for the reveal of the score on his arm later. It doesn't need a set up. It's funny even if we don't see him draw it. Cut.

&lt;b&gt;p50&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
EXT. HOUSE - DAY
&lt;/code&gt;
You wouldn't be revealing any twists by naming the house in the slug.

Another scene that I would normally say to cut as nothing happens to move the story forward, but the addition of Soundtrack kibitzing means there is some meat to the scene. Shouldn't there be a frill of happy or sexy music when Kaitlyn answers the door looking divine before Soundtrack drops back into execution music as he crosses the threshold?

&lt;code&gt;
INT. HOUSE - LIVING ROOM - CONTINUOUS
&lt;/code&gt;
Ian meets Cheryl, Kevin, and Tony, has very different interactions with all three, and Soundtrack remains constant? It never fades but renews with vigor when Tony enters. Missed opportunity. Also, Cheryl is way scarier than Tony.

The exchange with Kevin is cute. Is it necessary? No. Does it break the flow of the story? Maybe. It does seem at odds with the soundtrack. If Ian is going to relax this much to tease Kevin, Soundtrack should reflect it.

&lt;b&gt;p53&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. HOUSE - LIVING ROOM - LATER
&lt;/code&gt;
Why later? How much time has passed? This seems to be continuous with the previous scene.

There is a lot of opportunity for Soundtrack to kibitz and…nothing. It isn't mentioned.

Tony's not scary. That's fine. But Ian and Soundtrack both seem more frightened of him than of Cheryl. That's wrong, and misses an opportunity for funny.

Everything after "I must have forgot" is superfluous.

&lt;b&gt;p57&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. HOUSE - DINING ROOM - LATER
&lt;/code&gt;
Silence. Has Soundtrack taken the evening ? Surely it has some comment.

Cut "The brief moment of levity lightens the mood." If it's funny, we'll laugh. Don't tell us to laugh.

&lt;b&gt;p58&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. HOUSE - DINING ROOM - LATER
&lt;/code&gt;
Unnecessary. Cut and start in the bathroom.

&lt;code&gt;
BATHROOM
&lt;/code&gt;
Soundtrack doesn't change when she says she's trying to seduce him? It doesn't change when she threatens him? Soundtrack is lazy.

&lt;b&gt;p59&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
EXT. HOUSE - POOL - NIGHT
&lt;/code&gt;
The bit about her legs is a change of tone for the descriptive writing. How about something simpler like, "…sculling her long legs through the water."

The dialog seems natural. Kaitlyn avoids the direct question, then answers when Ian persists. The whole conversation shows us these two people really work together. They should be a couple. They play  each other where Ian and Tracy just clash, or at best work at cross purposes. You are showing us why this is the couple to root for. Well done.

Nice setup to allow the phone swap. Well done.

*aflush

Soundtrack is quiet for most of a scene that has a lot of up and down, smooth and rough, and changes.

&lt;b&gt;p66&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. HOUSE - CONTINUOUS
&lt;/code&gt;
I like the quick beat in the house. Do we get any Soundtrack?

&lt;code&gt;
EXT. HOUSE - CONTINUOUS
&lt;/code&gt;
No kibitzing from Soundtrack?

&lt;b&gt;p68&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. KAITLYN’S CAR - NIGHT
&lt;/code&gt;
This only sets up Tracy being upset with Ian later. Unnecessary. Cut it. Tracy already explains why she's throwing things, "She answered your phone!" That's all we need.

&lt;code&gt;
INT. APARTMENT - MAILBOX - NIGHT
&lt;/code&gt;
Quibble: you can't really have an INT. MAILBOX. Do you mean INT. LOBBY? Anyway, this can be cut. Have him enter the next scene carrying mail. We'll figure out where he got it.

&lt;code&gt;
INT. APARTMENT - NIGHT
&lt;/code&gt;
The fluttering coffee cup amongst all the heavy items is a nice touch.

When Tracy starts pawing the bracelet, Soundtrack should be furious, not mischievous. It picked that bracelet out for Kaitlyn. It hates Tracy. IT'S NOT FOR HER! This could be an opportunity for Ian to try and re-score Soundtrack.

Nice character note for Tracy. "Are they real? Then I love it!" Material bitch.

&lt;b&gt;p72&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
BEDROOM
&lt;/code&gt;
No need for this scene to take place in the bedroom. Have Tracy (O.S.). It's pitch black, anyway.

&lt;code&gt;
EXT. APARTMENT - CONTINUOUS
&lt;/code&gt;
This slugline is confusing. EXT. APARTMENT suggests to me the street outside the building. I believe you mean INT. APARTMENT BUILDING HALLWAY. Or, as the next scene is a pawn shop, you do mean outside the building, but you don't mean CONTINUOUS as Ian passes through two locations (HALLWAY and LOBBY) to get to the street. Since the purpose of these scenelettes is to show the power is out only in his apartment, you could end the previous scene with him opening the door into a brightly lit hallway while saying, "Must be a power outage in the building. I'll be right back."

&lt;code&gt;
INT. PAWN SHOP - NIGHT
&lt;/code&gt;
Appraised value is retail value. Pawnbrokers don't buy at retail.

&lt;b&gt;p73&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. APARTMENT - BEDROOM - LATER
&lt;/code&gt;
No comment from Soundtrack?

&lt;code&gt;
INT. APARTMENT - DAY
&lt;/code&gt;
What is Soundtrack doing in this scene? There is lots of potential both for it to kibitz and for Ian to try and drown it out.

The power won't be back on yet. Mention daylight coming through the window.

Make it clear Tracy enters from the bedroom. You don't need "suddenly".

&lt;b&gt;p77&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. BOWLING ALLEY - NIGHT
&lt;/code&gt;
The bubbly tune in contrast to Ian's outward look strongly suggests Soundtrack is not Ian's inner heart.

Isn't it messy to skip while carrying a pitcher of beer?

Soundtrack seems to be implying there might be something between Ian and Sean. Is Ian gay? No. Is Sean? Sean being gay leads to some interesting possibilities. It could explain where he came from so quickly after the breakup. He isn't Kaitlyn's boyfriend. He's Kaitlyn's longtime gay friend who she has latched onto in her grief and anger. He doesn't know they're a couple. This means he knows Ian broke Kaitlyn's heart. Great. It adds a level of conflict.

The sexy music is funny. But it doesn't come from anywhere and doesn't go anywhere. Find a way to earn the joke. If Sean is Kaitlyn's longtime friend, Ian probably knows he's gay. Or suspects. He'd be surprised back at the pool to hear they're a couple.

&lt;b&gt;p79&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. BOWLING ALLEY - LATER
&lt;/code&gt;
Why later? Nothing suggests the game has been going on for any length of time. The action that starts this scene could be the first ball of the match.

Why would Kaitlyn momentarily think Ian was calling her "babe". Nothing in the sequence suggests it. Earn your moments.

The bowling scenes are probably weakest for dialog. There are no consequences to the banter. The entire bowling sequence could be cut without weakening the plot. Or, it could be tied in more tightly with the rest of the screenplay and add a dimension.

&lt;b&gt;p82&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
I/E CAR - NIGHT
&lt;/code&gt;
He is reassured by her . What does Soundtrack think?

This is a great time for him to stop fooling himself and dump her. But the actual moment? The direct impetus for him to do it? Weak. She's been way bitchier than this before. Maybe if he wasn't reassured by her touch just before. The last time she tried to put the moves on him, Soundtrack pitched a fit.

Nice active dump. Side of the road.

A missed opportunity as Ian is driving away for him to be humming triumphant music (as we expect Soundtrack to) only to be interrupted by danger music.

Lovely detail of her going by in a cab as he runs out of gas after dumping her.

&lt;b&gt;p87&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
EXT. CAR - NIGHT
&lt;/code&gt;
Why doesn't Soundtrack have any commentary on this scene?

Sean's very casual about leaving a) his girlfriend with her ex, or b) his good friend with the creep that broke her heart. Yes, he has to do it for the plot. Make it more a character moment, less a convenient plot point.

&lt;b&gt;p88&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. CAR - NIGHT
&lt;/code&gt;
Soundtrack only chimes in at the very end of the scene. Another missed opportunity.

The game shows us once again that these two really belong together. Nice move pulling the rug out from under a lovely moment at the very end. Ian's got more work to do.

&lt;b&gt;p92&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
EXT. KAITLYN’S APARTMENT - NIGHT
&lt;/code&gt;
Where's Soundtrack through most of this? Its boy is at the make or break point. Shouldn't it be pitching in?

This is where I really question where these boyfriends and girlfriends came from so quickly after the breakup. There doesn't seem to be enough time for Kaitlyn to be this invested in a new relationship.

His hair thinning is a very small thing to cause all this trouble. I like that. I like small things that cause big problems. It seems real to me.

Again, as we are about to have our beautiful moment, you yank the rug out from under them. I like it. Don't go the simple happy ending. They haven't got to the core yet.

&lt;b&gt;p97&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. STUDIO - CONFERENCE ROOM - DAY
&lt;/code&gt;
Cut DISSOLVE TO.

Here Ian has his epiphany. He commits to what Kaitlyn means to him. I like it.

"I don't care" is perfect. He doesn't care. He's not interested in throwing away his chance in some grand gesture. It doesn't figure in his calculations at all. The only thing he cares about at this moment is Kaitlyn.

&lt;b&gt;p99&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. LIBRARY - DAY
&lt;/code&gt;
I like this little scene. It's unexpected. At this point Ian is supposed to burst into the library and sweep Kaitlyn Off her feet. He doesn't. One final tease.

&lt;b&gt;p100&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
INT. RECORDING STUDIO - CONTINUOUS
&lt;/code&gt;
The other side of the tease.

&lt;b&gt;p101&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;code&gt;
EXT. COUNTRY CLUB - NIGHT
&lt;/code&gt;
Cut. Start with her looking around trying to find some way in.

&lt;code&gt;
EXT. COUNTRY CLUB - COURTYARD - NIGHT
&lt;/code&gt;
The build up is nice. She sees the copy of the first angel. It has a ring box. The ring box doesn't have a ring. Ian makes a nice speech. Kaitlyn's theme begins to play. She gets the slideshow she never saw. Ian appears. He finally speaks his heart. &lt;i&gt;Then&lt;/i&gt; he offers her the ring.

Awww.

And the joke about the pawnshop doesn't clang. It fits the moment and fits his character as does her response.
 </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/676vh6</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cj6q</id></website><link>http://scriptshadow.blogspot.com/2012/03/screenplay-review-soundtrack-amateur.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:12:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:26:04+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzhsr</id><link>http://scriptshadow.blogspot.com/2012/03/screenplay-review-soundtrack-amateur.html#comment-481041371</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hwwl0</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>