<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwszyh/update/2012-03-31T10:42:20/651df0522485184e3e81332df859fdfe7232539f62308fe6ad9a35f21905793e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Many many years ago, a Medicine Man or tribal chief ate a mushroom and saw God.  I am convinced that ALL RELIGION started with the ingestion of a psychedellic substance, mushrooms, peyote, ergot of rye, marijuana (The "Burning bush,") even "Giant Toads" (Hippies called them "Licking Toads")  and ever since then, those guys &amp; their followers have been trying to make their "visions" explain "reality."  (BTW, Joseph Smith, who invented Mormonism, was an Epileptic who had visions during his seizures, and found a Giant Toad guarding those golden plates that became the Book of Mormon. According to Smith, that toad knocked him down 3 times before he could retrieve those golden plates. Total visionary bullshit.

Faith-healing  on the faith of the healee, not the healor; thus may charlatans make miracles.  Prayer is self-talk, that's why it works.  You punish or reward yourself,  on how pleased or displeased you are with yourself, and blame it on God.  If prayer is self-talk, guess who God is -- and Always has been.  It's us.  We have a power to heal ourselves, but no one has taught us how to use it.  The High Priests of all denominations have claimed that power as theirs, coming directly from God.  They lie--for their own benefit.

Greta has it 100% right as far as i'm concerned.

BTW, my own book discussing the Reality behind Religion, will be out in May or June. It is called "It Was Too Soon Before."  My conclusion is that Jesus wasn't preaching Christianity, he was trying to teach Evolution (The Son of Man) "substance abuse," ("Shewbread" aka LSD) and homosexuality (men loving men.)  It was Peter who called him Messiah and as a result, Christianity has misled the world for 2000 years.  Jesus' original message was right, (not necessarily what is reported in the offical Christian Bible) but it got mired down in the pig-pen of Judaism.  He was supposed to "fulfill" the prophets' predictions, but didn't. All he did, according to Saint Peter, was come back to life after being dead three days.  Then, instead of annointing himself King of the World and freeing the Jews from slavery, he floated up to heaven in his burial clothes, promising to come back later to "save" the world. According to Christians, Jesus is still up there above the clouds, with his Dad, the magic old man with a white beard, waiting until it is safe to come back down and send all the sinners to hell and turn the earth into Paradise for the righteous.  Oh, and it's Our Fault that he died in the first place.  Bullshit pure and simple.

Keep it up, Greta!  I for one agree with you!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67xzas</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ant8</id></website><link>http://www.alternet.org/story/154774/the_top_10_reasons_i_dont_believe_in_god/comments/</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:08:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T14:42:20+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwszyh</id><link>http://www.alternet.org/story/154774/the_top_10_reasons_i_dont_believe_in_god/comments/#comment-481881649</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cn3d7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>