<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m33z1q/update/2012-03-30T00:38:05/695b614dcda27a435a3290e98b774dbd99f1e7657e717da20dca44ec209972b6</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I take a less charitable view of these late Romney endorsements.  They reek of a political, &lt;i&gt;please kill me last,&lt;/i&gt; cynicism.  These endorsers have fallen for the "inevitable" concept, and are jumping on the train to appear to be part of the winning team. The idea is to avoid the Cold shoulder of Mr. Inevitable, should he succeed in defeating Obama.

In most elections in my life, I'd look upon this as simple posturing, and wouldn't care 'oo endorsed 'oo.  But this election is every bit as crucial as the decision by some colonists to rebel against England in 1776.  So I view these endorsements of "the inevitable candidate" as a form of constitutional cowardice.  The refusal to  ones life, fortune, and sacred honor to the restoration of this republic.

While I was never a real Paul Ryan fan, I've appreciated some of his hard work for the right-side of the political dumbell. But I've noticed he, like Rubio, sounds more like a guy wanting to be a lifelong member of Congress, and not a leader of conservative thinking. More of a "solutions" guy than a "principles" guy.  We'll Always need the former, but we are desperate for the latter.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zj5cq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/4847</id></website><link>http://www.therightscoop.com/report-paul-ryan-preparing-to-endorse-romney/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:23:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T04:38:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m33z1q</id><link>http://www.therightscoop.com/report-paul-ryan-preparing-to-endorse-romney/#comment-480249235</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/eevaa</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>