<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miuf3b/update/2012-03-23T16:09:59/f834102364efdd0049912cd6faa7123214437299a04f087c5ded3d62df4043d6</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miy7xa</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zdn5k</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>9 out of 10 drug arrests are blacks/minorities, even though the majority of drug use is by whites. During segregation and even during Civil Rights and past that, there were deliberate policies to degrade black people and encourage breaking up of their families and culture. The same thing happened to Native Americans. BOTH are still discriminated against, written Off, not given equal concern and care as human beings by society, and you can now put Hispanics in there as well (and heck, other minorities also). It's not about blacks, it's about poverty. When you don't give a damn about people, try to blame them for their status, and refuse to treat them like human beings, they're GOING to start seeing society as an Enemy, and crime will result, along with depression, Anxiety, hopelessness, and suicide. WE ARE ALL HUMAN BEINGS. WE ALL DESERVE THE SAME RIGHTS, OPPORTUNITIES, AND RESPECT, NO MATTER OUR RACE, RELIGION, GENDER, OR ORIENTATION.


I'm TIRED of seeing my sisters and brothers, and beautiful little children, degraded and told "we don't give a crap about you and it's all your fault anyway." Let us give equal opportunity and equal rights and equal respect to all, and deal with each other as *individuals*, judging each other by how we behave and care or don't care about one another.

And if it matters to you (judging by your comment, it probably does), I'm WHITE. And I'm SICK of this garbage, and sick of seeing human beings treated like DIRT.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yo1cd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ewhe</id></website><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/trayvon-martin/trayvon-martin-black-youth-react-to-tragedy-in-sanford-florida.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T21:33:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T20:09:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miuf3b</id><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/trayvon-martin/trayvon-martin-black-youth-react-to-tragedy-in-sanford-florida.php#comment-474758410</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hw35f</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>