<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwqhb9/post/2012-03-30T18:31:10</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This TH and BBC article is completely devoid of background info and pricing so lets go look for that.

see "Can Scotland afford so much wind"  from feb 12 2012

This isn't Scotlands Wind, it is for the entire UK even if it is mostly in Scotland presumably where the best wind is. All of the UK consumers will be paying for this even if it looks all Scottish. At least 1/3 of the power will be used in Scotland.

This is a mandate from the 2009 EU Renewable Directive for the UK to meet 15% of its entire final (primary?) energy consumption. It says that the UK energy consumer will have to pay up 
£8B/yr to meet this mandate with the total subsidy draw from 2002 to 2010 adding to £55B. 

Going on to 2030, this increases to £130B, presumably their will be more hardware in place with more capacity, perhaps that is the 15% of UK primary. 

It is one thing to talk about a simple turbine, but talking about the financing gives me a nasty Headache, I feel that certain thing coming up again what with nos like 
£130B and we can't tell how much power that will have to be as actual wind.

Anyway maybe somebody else can make sense of it.

The simple math agrees, UK electrical power is about 40GWe, 
The Scottish fraction is about 40*(5.2/62.3) or 3.34GWe.
And 45% of that is 1.5GWe or about 13,750TWh/yr.

That's comparable to a very large reactor or 2 smaller ones which could be built for maybe $3-4B.

I guess the UK has bought it self into one big mess that obscures the total costs vs the total power generated since it all in motion for some time.

The article goes on to address my pet Wind peave, when the wind don't blow, there are more costs to cover the backup of underutilized fossil plants that push the annual costs further to £13B/yr.

Bit more, the Fleet could go up to 7.8GW nameplate at 27% cf or 2.1GW avg. So after all that maybe they get 2.1GW total avg power for  £130B or $208B or maybe there will be more power included in that price. 

Sure Scotland is a leader, 1.5GW of installed avg wind but with commitments from the UK for  £130B for that and more WTF. I guess cost doesn't matter, the UK consumers will have to pay for it, but they will never have a clear idea of what they got for their money.

This is something only an accountant could love, I wonder if the Donald could figure it all out.

The second half of the article is about nuclear, chatting about Monbiot, Thorium, Prism, but nothing specific. 
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67l9ij</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/amtr</id></website><link>http://www.treehugger.com/renewable-energy/scotland-now-gets-13-its-power-renewables.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T20:03:43+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T22:31:10+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwqhb9</id><link>http://www.treehugger.com/renewable-energy/scotland-now-gets-13-its-power-renewables.html#comment-481274306</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rkupv</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>