<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi5iix/post/2012-03-22T15:40:19</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mialmk</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8vqoi</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> ...and their healthcare is terrible.  I live in England for a while.  The socialized medicine was inadequate.  A guy had an internal perforation in a lung and was drop by drop Bleeding out from his mouth.  The paramedics gave him two aspirins and said for for him to call again if he got worse.  That was in 1995, the guy's name was Daly, and I was dating his sister at the time.

Canada, where I currently live (I used to live in Lacey before I retired), emergency room wait times were on average 16 hours, according to the liberal national news publication "McCleans".  I was mailing a letter last week at Shopper's, and the Canada post attendant was complaining that she had spent the whole day waiting to get an ultrasound that a doctor referred her for at Peter Lougheed Hospital.  She sat waiting from morning until that evening.  The doctor finally came around and told her to go home, because the ultrasound section was now closed.  She lost her whole day Off waiting around for nothing.  She then had to give up another 5 hours to another doctor who then sent her for another test....she still has no idea what is wrong with her health.  

Also, I'll take the CBO's report above an Op-ed anytime of the week.  So, no, I don't buy into the editorial at all when it goes against the conclusions of the CBO. 

We have the best medical care that money can buy here in the US which can be accessed on demand.  There is a reason why Canadian come down to the US to have medical treatment all of the time.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yljcq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnms</id></website><link>http://www.theolympian.com/2012/03/22/2040129/court-has-chance-to-affirm-meaningful.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T07:55:46+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T19:40:19+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi5iix</id><link>http://www.theolympian.com/2012/03/22/2040129/court-has-chance-to-affirm-meaningful.html#comment-473878317</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hfno</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>