<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwy5dg/update/2012-03-30T10:28:02/d02bec29a6a8a86952d9e3e2915b50a1feda03866ffc99f20ae23d4e20a8a450</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmo6r</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ypif</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>very simple recipe:-
1.Don't get the canned chick peas, get fresh chick peas, soak them in Cold water with about 3 teaspoons of baking soda mixed nto the water over night. Why baking soda, it reacts with the chick peas or for that matter any beans and dissipates the gas which will escape and you will be left with a light brown skin on the surface next day. Wash the chick peas and boil them in a pressure cooker or in a pot.
In a separate pot do the following:
Add 2 Teaspoons of olive oil  let it Heat up, 1 teaspoon of cumin seeds, 3 bay leaves, 3-7 cloves, 3-4 pods of cardamon. Let it all brown.
To this add 2 onions that you grind up in your blender, 5-8 cloves of garlic that you mashed up along with a teaspoon of ginger you mashed up as well and salt to taste.
Let this mixture brown. 
When this mixture has browned add 1 teaspoon of cumin powder, 1 teaspoon of turmeric powder, 1 teaspoon of corriander powder, 1 teaspoon of red chilli 
powder.
Now add a can of San marzano tomatoes ( they have the best flavor, unless tomatoes are in season). Add a carton of frozen cut spinach ( Cascadian farms)
let this mixture simmer, you may add a cup of water as it may be thick.
When the mixture is bubbling add the cooked chick peas and mix it all in together and let it simmer. After about 10 minutes add 1 teaspoon of garam masala and freshly chopped corriander. 
Let it sit for a bit before you serve it with whatever you wish, I have taken this put it on a crisp baguette added guyere  cheese, put it under the broiler for 45 seconds and it is an amazing snack with a crisp New Zealand Mud House Sauvignon Blanc. 
Enjoy. By the way it is gluten free and no dairy, rich in fiber and protein.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67aor2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/1</id></website><link>http://www.avc.com/a_vc/2012/03/fun-friday-favorite-cuisine.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T11:16:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T14:28:02+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwy5dg</id><link>http://www.avc.com/a_vc/2012/03/fun-friday-favorite-cuisine.html#comment-480795557</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ag8wc</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>