<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m02wmu/post/2012-03-31T14:52:27</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I am a subscriber to Tea Party standards and am proud of it.   Just who is Tad Cronn and what material does he possess to be able to categorize the four Tea Party groups as he did ?   I personally support the 
Tea Party. Org group (located in CA) and I do not see that group involved in any schism as he states .....
My Oxford Dictionary defines thus:  "a division of a group into opposing sects or parties usually over 
doctrine. (split, rift, break, division, rupture, separation, disunion, faction, camp, set, sect)   Where does he see the 'DIVISION' ????   From my viewpoint I have spoken with many Tea Partiers and due to all of us 
maintaining STRICT adherence to the Declaration, Constitution, Bill of Rights  (in my case the  Bible also) how can there be sect, division, or any of the other synonyms above ???   If anything, this is a method of creating  discontent among the troops.   I would say that all the persons that I know are standing tall and
firm in their beliefs and are sick and tired of the (Karl Rove) "machine" shoving something down the public's throat they do not want.   Yes, our primary objective is to defeat Obama in November but let's not do it with a Moderate leaning Liberal.   Let's tell Rove and his cronies to take a long walk  a short pierand then "We the People" need to busy behind a true dyed-in-the-wool Conservative to take this country back and rebuild it the way it was supposed to be.
If we don't, it is going to crash and Burn ..... then we will have to rebuild it out opf the ashes created by all
the Democratic, Socialist/Marxist Progressives running Off at the mouth.
Citizen "Bill"</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67j1nm</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ogrn</id></website><link>http://godfatherpolitics.com/4473/conservatives-being-locked-out-as-romney-ascends/</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T11:10:09+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T18:52:27+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m02wmu</id><link>http://godfatherpolitics.com/4473/conservatives-being-locked-out-as-romney-ascends/#comment-482094131</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>