<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjc26/post/2012-03-26T14:11:08</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>My main concern is that Dombrowski didn't address their lack of a leadoff hitter. Austin Jackson, with his extreme propensity to strikeout, is not the long-term answer. I'm not saying I wanted Jose Reyes, but I am sure Dombrowski could have gotten more creative. 


I am not nearly as worried about the lack of a fifth starter as everyone else seems to be. The fact of the matter is that with the four right-handers they have solidified in the rotation, the  need a lefty in the fifth Spot, and 3 of their top 10 prospects happen to be LH starters in Drew Smyly, Casey Crosby, and Andy Oliver. I am sure the  are equally confident that they can find a 5th starter in at least one of these 3. Not mention, they have a top 50 RH pitching prospect in Jacob Turner if need be.

The move to 3b for Cabrera is also overdramatized. He is eager to prove the doubters wrong and through hard-work, he will be an average fielder. The offensive of  of Cabrera plus Fielder far outweighs the defensive cost.

I do think that they need to address the middle of the infield defense however. It might have been a good idea to sell high on Jhonny Peralta after a career year and focus on defense up the middle and at SS. I think the Braves would have been an excellent trade target for them. A deal of Peralta + Raburn and cash to cover salary differences for Prado to play 2b might have made sense for both squads.

The Dotel signing was a very smart baseball move, even if it was a bit overpriced.

Overall, I love the  offseason and can't complain about the moves they made. Looking forward to another great season of Tiger baseball.





</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rkv74</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gyfc</id></website><link>http://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2012/03/offseason-in-review-detroit-tigers.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T12:38:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:11:08+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjc26</id><link>http://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2012/03/offseason-in-review-detroit-tigers.html#comment-476594938</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/sbag</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>