<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3b0yl/post/2012-03-29T14:58:17</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>My dear friends of GW, I know the sadness you feel in your heart for the loss of one of ours to a horrible disease.   Having been associated with medicine for over 50 years, my first contact with the Disease was watching a young 28 year old sailor, who was a patient of mine, die of stomach cancer.  The pain he suffered while in his last day was impossible to immagine.  The sorrow of seeing family members sit by his side watching him die, knowing there was nothing they could do was agonizing for me, as a 17 year old navy hospital corpsman.  This image has been Burned into my brain to this day.  Then to have a low life like Frank come along and make a harsh remark to northernmost's memory is beyond the pale.  

Therefore in my sorrow for northernmost and his family and friends, I am asking that whenever Frankflinch, logs on to this forum, that he be shunned to the inth degree, and there is a Ban on replying to his remarks, unless he makes a heart felt appology to the friends and family of nothernmost.  I know that many things are said in anger on this forum, and I am one of those who have done it.  It is not who I am, and I humbly appologize, again to all those whom I may have hurt with my posts.  But I have not nor will I ever make a comment such as Franks, and i doubt that any of you would either.  Frank needs to appologize or leave the forum, forever.  Thanks for listening to the rants of a tired old GW regular.  Pops...</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zalc3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t33k</id></website><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/blog-95/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T03:55:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:58:17+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3b0yl</id><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/blog-95/#comment-479762688</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yjgvt</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>