<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/198524/post/102358089/comment/322404083</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>A lot of the time there\'s a historical unteommm to major events that doesn\'t  on the individuals involved as much as people expect. We can see snapshots of this in the fact that without Darwin we would still have had Wallace\'s work, without Newton we would still have Leibniz. From her Wikipedia article, Rosa Parks was not the first to take a stand the way she did, but she is remembered for it because of what occurred afterwards (the bus boycott). This is not to diminish her brave and important Act of civil disobedience, but sometimes it doesn\'t matter who does the job so long as someone does it (and this is often true of the most important jobs).Personally I suspect that the small differences made by a person are more likely to affect major changes in the long run. For example even if Einstein had not developed general relativity, the scientific zeitgeist was right for it at the time and it would, in all likelihood, have been developed soon thereafter anyway. However, a different person in Einstein\'s place might not have signed the letter urging president Roosevelt to begin developing the atomic bomb. The absence of a request from such a prominent scientist might have delayed the completion of the bomb, possibly until after the defeat of Japan, resulting in wildly different post-war relations all around and changing several key facets of the beginning of the Cold war. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:198524:102358089</id><idPostId>102358089</idPostId><idBlogId>198524</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:198524</id><idBlogId>198524</idBlogId><link>http://chivethebrigade.wordpress.com</link><displayName>theBRIGADE</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://thebrigade.thechive.com/?attachment_id=37468</link><displayName>Houston-500-45</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T03:25:42.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:198524:102358089:322404083</id><link>http://thebrigade.thechive.com/?attachment_id=37468#IDComment322404083</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T03:25:42.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Houston-500-45 by Devante</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>922166e098b3efbc2c03b53b901c8c6d</idEmailMd5><displayName>Devante</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>Devante commented on &lt;a href="http://thebrigade.thechive.com/?attachment_id=37468"&gt;Houston-500-45&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>