<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mihskt/update/2012-03-23T03:38:29/28044f7b951c804828e3cb8b5f73bfba78506f3d16a8d2129fe40e2557f1511f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The most amazing thing about this story is that the person through flour at Kim supposedly for wearing fur when in all these photo’s i do not see one Spot of fur on her. Another thing i find amazing is that the person who through the flour put a big Charity Event for dressing woman who can’t afford appropriate clothes for job interviews and work that Kim was hosting in partnership with her new perfume was put on hold, how can anyone be so selfish to the woman waiting patiently in that room, But Kim as usual being her amazing mature self quickly got cleaned up and came back on the red carpet within 10 minutes and carried on. Kim is not forcing anyone to buy her products and kim is not hurting anyone by doing the things she loves, people should really inspire Off that side of Kim her amazing and strong worth ethic to do the best you can’t and do what you love. Not her negative past with her sex tape and all the other thing which you haters like to bring up because you should never use someone’s past against them. Your just reminding them of the mistakes they made back then. If you watch their facial expression carefully, then you’ll see the hurt in their eyes as they reminisce on everything that happened. Never use emotion as a weapon, it strikes deeper than you can imagine.Nobody deserves this and if all of you are looking for peace in the world this isn’t the way forward in fact this is bringing peace in the world a few steps back. I personally love Kim, not for her past, but for her amazing worth ethic and where she is now doing what she loves! Xo</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yw7mz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/mtxn</id></website><link>http://edit.hollywoodreporter.com/node/303460</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T04:03:50+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T07:38:29+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mihskt</id><link>http://edit.hollywoodreporter.com/node/303460#comment-474300845</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>