<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwnm79/update/2012-03-30T19:23:00/56565f73d5a28c93b461589bf3d8dcffec2b1b1a1ab4d0be0d3ee870f1a15786</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Assuming anonymity is what you prefer, consider this.

Everything  on the rules of the state in which you win the lottery.  In my state, lottery agencies can ONLY release the following info without the winner's consent ... the winner's name, city of residence, the amount of the jackpot, and the name of the store where the ticket was purchased.  Info releases beyond that require consent of the winner, ie., press conferences, holding up big checks, photo sessions, etc.  When lottery agencies ask you to participate in "voluntary" publicity, your answer should  be "NO !!!"

Lottery winners tend to be their own worst enemies.  They brag to buddies, live large, and metaphorically paint "RICH GUY HERE !!!" targets on their own backsides.  If anonymity is what you desire and you happen to live in a state like mine, it's easy enough to achieve.  If I won the big one, this is what I'd do:

1)  First order of business is to place the "unsigned" ticket in a safe deposit box at your bank.  Ask them for advice on setting up a Treasury Direct account (with the U.S. Treasury) and put $100 into it.

2)  Second order of business is to file for a legal name-change.  If you're really "John Parker," change your name to "Bill Smithers."  Name changes take between 60-90 days to finalize and you have 180 days in which to redeem your ticket.

Why a name change?  Because not all states allow redemption by "trusts" or "corporations."  Mine doesn't.  And even if they did, if a state payment is authorized, most states (if asked by anyone) would be required to release the name of the trust owner or corporate head under the state's open-records laws.  To my knowledge, the only exception to this is Kansas - where lottery anonymity laws supercede state open-records laws.

3)  When your name change is finalized, take your name change order to your motor vehicle department and get a new license.  Most such requests are either done on the Spot or take a week.  Also, send a copy to the Social Security Administration so they know.  Then, go to your "old" bank, get the unsigned ticket from your safe deposit box, and sign it with you NEW LEGAL NAME.

4)  When you get your new license, open up a bank account under your new legal name in a bank with which you currently don't do business.  Get their bank routing number (and your account number) since lottery agencies prefer wiring your winnings to a bank.

5) If the lottery agency allows for it (mine does), redeem your ticket via Registered Mail.  There's no point in actually "showing up" at an office since you'd have to wait two weeks for them to "verify" the ticket anyway.  NOBODY gets a check/payment the same day they redeem a ticket.  And besides, when jackpots get big, news entities hire "stringer" reporters to hang out at lottery offices - waiting to pounce on you with cameras, microphones, and questions.

6) Every con artist and charity (and whoever) will be looking for a "Bill Smithers" who, for all intents and purposes, only exists on paper.  Once you receive your wired winnings at your "Smithers" account, wire it again to the "Parker" account at your old bank - closing your Smithers account afterward.  And once the money is in your "Parker" account, transfer it to your pre-existing Treasury Direct account.  Remember, banks only FDIC insure $250,000.  But Treasury Direct accounts insure the full face value of the account - no matter how much is in it.

7) Tell your attorney you had a "change of heart" about your name change ... and file papers to reclaim your old name.

8) Once you reclaim your old name, let Social Security know and get your driver license changed again.

9 Then, the most important advice of all.  KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT !!!

Don't hire a financial planner.  Boston University in Massachusetts, Bryant University in Rhode Island, and other prestigious colleges offer self-paced online financial planning courses.  Become your OWN financial planner.  Assuming you're trained to give good financial advice, chances are you'll get better advice from yourself than if you'd asked an "expert" (like Bernard Madoff) who might not have your best interests at heart. And once you've given yourself that "wise" advice, then and ONLY then move money out of your Treasury Direct account.

If you want to be "charitable" to friends, relatives, or charities later, have your attorney set up a blind-trust account that will keep your name .  Pick a name for the trust that's fun - like The Guardian Angel Charitable Trust.  Then, you authorize checks from the fund and  your attorney signs them - keeping you .  And if you cut a check from the trust to a friend or relative, make sure to cut a check for yourself, too (grin).  If friends suspect you as their benefactor, show them YOUR check.  They'll just assume you're another beneficiary of this mysterious trust fund, hehe.  Seriously, though, don't let ANYONE know you're rich.  You'll likely regret it later if you do.

Off pulpit (snicker).</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67zrf8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/fev8</id></website><link>http://tucsoncitizen.com/usa-today-news/2012/03/30/won-the-lottery-troubles-may-be-just-beginning/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:17:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T23:23:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwnm79</id><link>http://tucsoncitizen.com/usa-today-news/2012/03/30/won-the-lottery-troubles-may-be-just-beginning/#comment-481312934</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hzu0r</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>