<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/240793/post/72702815/comment/328437046</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>\"Let the nurse care for patients, families,christian louboutin, let workers left the ward\", this is the Ministry of health advocates \"quality care demonstration project\".Honghe Third People\'s Hospital as \"unattended\" pilot hospital, in the hospital ward nursing model ward without tumor development.But the nurse Huang has recently encountered a very embarrassing things, family members of patients asked her to give patients wash underwear.The families of patients presenting with an awkward request cancel family members accompany, by nurses assume a patient\'s life,adidas f50, basic nursing,mercurial vapor, this is no accompanying the basic meaning.In the nursing process, the nurse basically replaced families, care of the patient\'s life,michael kors sale, and family members of patients only need to care for the patient to eat, wash clothes, go out for a walk and so on can, which is to give patients relief.Honghe Third People\'s Hospital should the requirements of the health sector, in July of this year will begin without accompanying nursing demonstration work, hospital in oncology begin without nursing model ward.One night in November, on the night shift nurse Huang, her task is to give patients face,coach outlet handbag, feet,louboutin, asking what the patient needs to be.Yellow to Aunt Zhang after wiping the body after leaving.The patient\'s daughter said: \"but, you put my mother rubbed the sweat pants.\"Hear this, there was an awkward.Yellow to a patient\'s request to nurse Liang Zhengju, nurse immediately to the families are explained,franklin marshall pas cher, then families also understand, no longer offered yellow wash underwear requirements.This thing on the surface of that past, but this news has spread to every ward in hospital,michael kors handbags on sale, causes Heat to discuss.Execute without accompanying nursing, nurses caring for the patient\'s life,herve leger, basic nursing, help the patient to wash ass, rubbing bodies, wipe the shit,chaussures louboutin, but should wash the underwear?Most of the patients and the nurses felt should not, there are also quite a few people in favor of.The hospital is responsible for the publicity of Mr. Zhao said, they are prepared in the hospital to conduct a discussion,coach outlet stores, listening to patients and their families.Opposing: nurse not a nurse not all things are done in Honghe Third People\'s Hospital nursing director Hu Lin said,lunette de soleil chanel, advocating for quality nursing service departments, is to give the patient lives nursing, basic nursing,chaussure de foot, do some technical service,michael kors outlet, to give the patient rehabilitation guidance.The nurse is not a nurse, not can do anything,louboutin pas cher, she felt that the families of this approach was a bit much.This shows, family for no accompanying nursing concepts are not understood,herve leger dress, the hospital should intensify the propaganda.Support: since the end of feces and urine wash underwear and why the public end of Mr Lee said, since the connected end to end urine feces nurse job, wash underwear nothing?Families may not  allow nurses to wash,herve leger sale, probably because of busy work,lunette de soleil ray Ban, difficulties to make this request, the nurse should according to the actual situation to deal with.He thinks, wash do not wash underwear, or charging case.According to the state of the actual situation,coach outlet, ask a nurse in the 1200 yuan to 2000 yuan,lunette de soleil louis vuitton, if every patient every month to the hospital to make enough money, the nurses should do.If not,mercurial vapor pas cher, the nurse just do their job on the line.Yesterday afternoon, the nurse Huang said: that is really busy, if time is abundant, can consider to help with the washing.For the families of patients to wash underwear, she heard no feel grievance,michael kors, since the development of no accompanying nursing, it should as far as possible to meet the requirements of the patient, as long as not too much on the line.Related articles&amp;#65306; Today the court he drives home &amp;#24429;&amp;#20852;&amp;#26480;&amp;#22836;&amp;#37096;&amp;#12289;&amp;#32937;&amp;#37096;&amp;#21463;&amp;#20102;&amp;#20260; &amp;#25454;&amp;#24713;&amp;#65292;&amp;#22905;&amp;#34987;&amp;#25351;&amp;#25511;&amp;#30423;&amp;#29992;&amp;#20182;&amp;#20154;&amp;#36523;&amp;#20998;&amp;#65292;&amp;#22914;&amp;#26524;&amp;#32618;&amp;#21517;&amp;#25104;&amp;#31435;&amp;#65292;&amp;#26368;&amp;#39640;&amp;#21487;&amp;#21028;&amp;#21009;6&amp;#24180;&amp;#65292;&amp;#22806;&amp;#21152;1&amp;#19975;&amp;#32654;&amp;#20803;&amp;#32602;&amp;#27454;&amp;#12290; </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:240793:72702815</id><idPostId>72702815</idPostId><idBlogId>240793</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:240793</id><idBlogId>240793</idBlogId><link>http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com</link><displayName>Are You Healthy?  Are You Happy?</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com/2011/01/26/do-you-have-the-post-holiday-blues-happiness-how-to-get-it/</link><displayName>Do you have the Post Holiday Blues?  Happiness:  How to get it.</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T10:44:36.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:240793:72702815:328437046</id><inReplyTo><link>http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com/2011/01/26/do-you-have-the-post-holiday-blues-happiness-how-to-get-it/#IDComment125967655</link></inReplyTo><link>http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com/2011/01/26/do-you-have-the-post-holiday-blues-happiness-how-to-get-it/#IDComment328437046</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T10:44:36.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Do you have the Post Holiday Blues?  Happiness:  How to get it. by luckymanvb</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://louboutinenlignesfr.com</link><idEmailMd5>068ec9a9268c00d456b29803a080156c</idEmailMd5><displayName>luckymanvb</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://louboutinenlignesfr.com"&gt;luckymanvb&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com/2011/01/26/do-you-have-the-post-holiday-blues-happiness-how-to-get-it/"&gt;Do you have the Post Holiday Blues?  Happiness:  How to get it.&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>