<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/moyebt/update/2012-03-20T19:37:52/31c0c4bf965383e3ea6584fbb7675ab985829e0d9d1bac00ef6c3d302e1da749</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Patrician or not, elitist or not, Mississippi is a dysfunctional, troubled and profoundly ignorant place.  The southern part of the state around Biloxi and Gulfport is refreshingly less bible-thumping than the rest of the state, on account of the casinos and a larger Catholic population (the rest of the state is strictly of the bible-thumping protestant variety).  Still, Harrison county has the nation's highest rates of unwed single mothers, and they are mostly white.  

The state as a whole is an atrocious backwater and generates no meaningful revenue for the rest of the country.  And while the video is certainly condescending, the snapshot of ignorance, intolerance and depravity is certainly consistent with my own experiences in the state.  

Bill Maher's thesis that these people consistently vote and Act against their own self-interests is Spot on and actually has a lot of historical precedence.  During the Civil War, the vast majority of free Mississippians were of the cracker white-trash variety and benefited not one iota from the feudalistic and highly aristocratic nature of their plantation economy.  The irony can't be overstated, but what is interesting is that the worst of the racists and bigots were not the well educated and patrician plantation owners, but the poor white trash who themselves were being ruined by the slave trade.  This puzzled a lot of Union soldiers, who had a hard time understanding how these people could fight against their own best interests. But it really just illustrates the historical nature of Maher's thesis.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6glg4s</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/eyjq</id></website><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/national/archive/2012/03/the-liberal-sneer/254635/</link><postedTime>2012-03-16T20:22:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-20T23:37:52+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/moyebt</id><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/national/archive/2012/03/the-liberal-sneer/254635/#comment-470720969</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ytg5c</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-16</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>