<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3uic0/post/2012-03-29T15:37:16</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msi4oc</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>No one said black people should'nt wear Hoodies. But Geraldo Rivera is right. B/c of the perception of others who may in fact be bigots, dressing like that may draw bad attention. it is wise to not temp disaster by using caution. Know your surroundings, understand the subculture of the place you're at and don't add to a situation by Acting suspiciously. The funny thing about your comment is, you just made racist remarks about Hispanics. That is clear indication tat you may in fact be a racist yourself. Again, this situation has nothing to do race. It was two guys, one paranoid and hyper vigilant and one unwise and foolish who were both at the wrong place at the wrong time. 


Secondly, our right to bear arms in America is protected by our Constitution. If Zimmerman had a legal concealed carry permit,there was no crime in having a loaded weapon on his person.Another cautionary note,be careful in Florida.Think twice before you try to inflict harm on another, b/c they may be packing Heat. Trevon made a mistake. When Zimmerman lost him, he shoulda just dipped. He never should have returned to assault Zimmerman, it cost him his life. This again, should serve as a cautionary tale to young people. Better to avoid a fight than to start one.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hhm6l</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/mtxn</id></website><link>http://edit.hollywoodreporter.com/node/305340</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T13:12:14+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:37:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3uic0</id><link>http://edit.hollywoodreporter.com/node/305340#comment-479802671</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h9o8p</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>