<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34yqf/update/2012-03-29T10:46:57/101530e28ad5677acf3373a47f3ce83c4dffee26a5dda069a916645be0e04bf3</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3vcy3</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/e56bx</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Presidential elections are almost Always two choices.  More than that splits the vote...thank goodness for Nader. I agree with much of your sentiments and those shared feelings lead to the Clinton administrations' election (Perot split the GOP vote). That team sold  ICBM super computer technology to China allowing the entire USA to be targeted accurately. The Dems unrealistic geopolitical failings brought us 9-11.  Informed citizens can use wisdom rather than sentimentality.
    One can view this as the choice between two administration teams. The policies and people in toto are worlds apart. Yes there are political class types in the GOP but,  Rand Paul types were elected in 2010. We need more... through smart tough Cold blooded  patriotic electioneering. Hence, a way forward: ask yourself what percent of policy and appointments you agree with for each of the two party's Presidential candidates.  This leads to any easy choice for your majority agreement candidate. Votes the GOP do not receive only allows Dems to be elected, there is no "statement". Only one team wins, the other loses. Leave sentimentality out.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zc1u7</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yv37</id></website><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/2012/03/m-how_mitt_can_win.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T06:22:24+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:46:57+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34yqf</id><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/2012/03/m-how_mitt_can_win.html#comment-479542741</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yewv8</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>