<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/8eaed7/update/2011-01-18T21:34:19/1947087060b18a656c0095d119e9b81c802f729c1040eec31ece7c2feb03a962</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Being a little weary of Bill O. and his constant defense of Obama, I watched the ever bizarre Nancy Pelosi being interviewed by the 'lipstick' Rachel Madcow.  Pelosi rhapsodized and slobbered over the 'bill', went on and on about how wonderful the bill is, children will be on their parents coverage till their 26, etc.  A 26 year old 'child'?   Among other things, she blathered about how proud the Dem's were of their votes for ObamaCare, she related sad stories of people who will now be covered that weren't before (though nobody is denied HC now).

Besides the 'Nanny' effect of HC and dependency on 'BIG government who will take 60%+ of our income, to pay for their monstrous new social program, the real purpose of HC  is to re-engineer our nation into a Socialized society...like England, who are now revolting against that arrangement.  It will institute  the death panels that will exclude the elderly (the Obama regime will deny it) or at the very least marginalize their care because the elderly are not paying taxes and they will be good only for the small inheritance the government can plunder.  Pelosiosis didn't mention that the taxpayer is not only stuck with the money Pelosi PAID for those 'proud' democratic votes she extorted to get the unread, undebated HC bill passed, but generations will be stuck with the outrageous expense of her 'pay offs' to states like Nebraska (shame on you) and Louisiana (shame on you).  Pelosi and Reid and Obama are ruining our nation and  like its all for 'love' and 'compassion'.   This woman can produce more silage than a farm...and BS.  

Pelosi, in fact, doesn't get into any of the damaging effects of our having had our first Marxist President in office and the fact that she is an accessory to the most horrendous four year drive by on America I hope we will ever see.  Pelosiosis and Madcow were a  pair of crows gabbing and lying and cooing over their liberalism to the point of inducing mass, national Vomiting.  For me and the other four people watching MSNBC.  Pelosi's generailized answers (not answers but rather 'cheerleading) to Madcows non-intrusive questions were a sham.  They might as well have just made out for twenty minutes.  

When I see a horrible, demented person like Pelosi lying to a sympatico operative like Mr. Madcow, that is when I thank God for Rush Limbaugh.

Does anyone really trust the government and their HC scheme?  I mean really.  Having gotten the go ahead from Lyndon Johnson (another hideous Democrat theif) to plunder Social Security, do these crazed liberals really believe the government is going to 'set the money' they extort aside and keep their hands Off of it.  NO.  And what really make me angry is that is is going to be metered.  The death panel thing is the absolute reality of this nightmare.  In Britain yesterday they are scaling further back on what they will authorized for the elderly.  

AMERICA....WAKE UP!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/c45wla</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6bwl</id></website><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/media/2011/01/18/new-liberal-civility-i-wish-i-could-choke-rush-death</link><postedTime>2011-01-19T00:38:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-01-19T02:34:19+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/8eaed7</id><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/media/2011/01/18/new-liberal-civility-i-wish-i-could-choke-rush-death#comment-131064783</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8nldh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-01-19</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>