<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw8eru/post/2012-03-30T03:40:39</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3s3aw</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ruaxl</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Thank you thank you thank you. 

Going down in flames? Do you actually know something? R U the guy CJ Roberts &amp; Justice Kennedy let in thru the  rear entrance at early coffee each morning? 

I'm already on record saying this is going to be 4:1:1 or 4:2 for upholding the ACA, but the most amazing thing I've seen the coverage of the court hearing is people who don't know their 'approach the bench' from their archaic spittoon pontificating on the significance of what happened in court this week - as if the ability to do a Jon Stewart-like BOOM ... BOOM is how constitutional cases or really any Supreme Court case get decided. 

The guy taking the Heat for his supposed lack of performance, US Solicitor General Verilli, Mister Hem &amp; Haw, is somehow supposed to have lost this thing. And do you know how? Because he didn't lower the BOOM ... BOOM! That's not how things work there; sorry. How do think one gets to be selected as SolGen for the U.S.? And particularly when it's plainly the case that if you ever had the capacity to go BOOM ... BOOM! it was surgically removed decades ago. You get there because you actually understand how the actual Constitution, not the Drudge one, not the Red State one, not the Fuppet News one, not the Tea Party one, not even the Republican one, actually works - &amp; as well, you know how to bring that home to the Supreme Court, i.e. ergo that is, the job you were hired for. 

3 days, 4 battlefields, let's count the bodies:

Day 1: main issue - a strange duck that DC Circuit judge Brett Kavanagh used to get around bucking the inability that lower courts have to make new law, &amp; thereby creating a record that would come back to haunt him if he ever got nominated for the SCOTUS; subplot: CJ Roberts drops a pretty intriguing bomblet right near the end, to the effect that the so-called Mandate wouldn't be a 'true' mandate if it gave those subject to it a choice -which the ACA most definitely does do. Verdict: the Supreme Court is absolutely not about to use an 1867 law designed to keep tax payments coming in during a huge national crisis as a cheap jurisdictional out to duck the other 3 issues that were granted leave; but ... what about that 'true mandate' thingee? 'Cuz that applies to ...

Day 2: main issue - the "Mandate". And Verilli stands up &amp; doesn't even get past throat clearing before the wingosphere blog memes come reigning down like Kamikaze planes, then the REST of his time gets eaten up by the 4 D-appointees making his points for him. Now: tell me Verilli didn't see all of that coming. The big question on the left blogosphere is: How could he not have seen all that coming? I ask: What possibly makes you think he did NOT? The guy is U.S. Sol Gen &amp; he looks like he might have been around pouring drinking water during the Constitutional Conventions. So - you let the winger judges have their fun, because you lose nothing in doing that, &amp; you let the Dem judges make your case for you, because that's what's going to happen anyway. But - then - again - right near the end of the day, Justice Kennedy starts riding former SolGen Clement &amp; the other guy, Carvin, for the challengers, on an issue that ISN'T out of the wingosphere blogs, but right out of the central idea underlying the Mandate: that huge pool of yutes necessary to support the actuarial pools, playing chicken with their inevitable less yute-ful futures. And Clement &amp; Garvin have. no. answer. So, then Verilli gets 4 minutes right at the end, &amp; brings home the fish.

Ever read anything about the European theater for WWII, and how Ike, running the show, looked like a bumbling moron, was made to look to like one, by the conspiratorial Montgomery for the Brits on one side &amp; the mercurial Patton for the US Army on the other? And yet, which of those 3 was most credited for winning Europe back, &amp; later getting elected the head of his nation's government - twice (&amp; a more underwhelming public speaker one cannot imagine): pistol-packing Patton? mendacious Monty? You already know the answer. We make a big mistake underestimating underwhelming stolid types - hell, the GOP base has been practically begging Mitch Daniels to jump into the nomination process; what does all that tell you? 

Day 2 Verdict: Thomas against - d'uh; Scalia abusive, lazy, derivative, moronic &amp; against - d'uh; Alito - kitchen sink oppositional - d'uh; but Roberts? ya know, he ever did get an answer to his Day 1 question from Clement or Garvin - it just sat there, unanswered, all day long; Kennedy - that big question at the end about the yutes CHOOSING to be out of the pool, plus he kept hammering away on "a limiting principle" to the Commerce Clause, &amp; never got any answer; the most he got was Clement egging him on to trash the entire ACA.

About that "limiting principle" - it's just not all that hard to do:

http://balkin.blogspot.ca/2012/03/limiting-principle.html 

I think you might even be able to COMBINE those 3 tests. And if you did, you, Anthony Kennedy, would instantly  your legacy in the American constitutional firmament. And stuff like that matters to Kennedy; the guy travels, the guy goes to judicial conferences throughout the world, the guy reads, the guy even writes plays. And if he just does what Clement was urging, he goes down as the a-hole who authored Citizens United AND killed Obomneycare - plus killed 50,000 Americans a year from here on. 

So, you're Verilli: why not raise these options yourself? Because you're the SolGen &amp; it's above your pay grade, that's why. Better to leave it to the court, to the academics &amp; to dreams of Kennedy in Constitution Valhalla.

Also, if Kennedy writes this up really well, it's quite possible he'll get some support from not just the 4 Dem judges, but also CJ Roberts, also a legacy guy - &amp; - who knows? - maybe even a nod from Alito.

Day 3: Clean-up day - Severability &amp; the Medicaid expansion.

Please. The best thing that can be said about severability as an issue is that it's being granted leave meant 90 minutes of proving that if you kill the Mandate you kill the ACA. Worse! And hat tip to lazy Scalia for giving away the farm: either you line-item this beast, and thereby risk destroying the entire health care insurance industry &amp; forcing the U.S. towards Medicare for all, or you kill the whole law &amp; 50,000 Americans annually, plus destroy the lives of upwards of ten times as many more. 

Wanna know why they actually gave leave to &amp; spent time on the Medicaid expansion? Dignity, that's why; the idea is, throw the wingers a bone. They can't do it honestly, but that's not an insurmountable obstacle. Plus striking this down in particular WAY can both, Depending on how they do it, feeds the winger dream of protecting the states from the tyranny of federal diktat.  It's doable: 9 zip on severability; 4:1:1 or 4:2 for upholding the mandate, 5:4 or better for severability to allow for dumping the Medicaid Expansion, &amp; a bare 5:4 for actually dumping it, along with maybe a list of helpful do's &amp; don't's on how to fix this impediment, or more likely some soft lights &amp; music &amp; the subtle urgings to Congress of "Yes you can, baby - &amp; I might even respect you for it". 

It's not gonna be pretty, but it's gonna git done.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zp7r6</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tz1k</id></website><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/jon-stewart-goes-after-spike-lee-tweet-even-with-right-address-sending-lynch-mob-is-bad-mistake/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T03:42:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T07:40:39+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw8eru</id><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/jon-stewart-goes-after-spike-lee-tweet-even-with-right-address-sending-lynch-mob-is-bad-mistake/#comment-480471683</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rp1vp</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>