<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/el4isj/update/2011-12-10T22:23:16/871edbfecf0fe9e352bf0897c30e756b4985d6401db1f0b991dd7ea3b6d3f4cb</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>A few notes on what I have read:
First Off, I have been running in Newton's for roughly 3 years now. Starting out with the Sir Issac went through 4 pairs of the Distance and just did the Vegas Rock-N-Roll in the MV2's. 
Initially, my calf's Burned like crazy! Gnarly lower leg work out! But after the change over and becoming a fore foot runner, the pain goes away and the run times increase. I am active duty military in a "unique" field that tends to run a lot. Used to have timed 4mile runs, and after about a year I knocked my time down to sub 25min( in boots) and I no longer have knee pain(2 past surgeries in college and high school I stand 6'2 about 205lbs). With that being said, I can officially say that Newton Running and their shoes have increased my performance and decreased the wear and tear on my body.
As far as the lugs on the fore foot of the shoes go, well I only used the Distance shoes for road runs. To me and what I stress to anyone (which is a lot) is that if you spend the money on a set of Newton's they are to be used only for running and in the manor described. I do not go to the gym in them, I do not walk around and go grocery shopping because I like the color, and i certainly do not play basketball or any other sport that would require me to change direction fast. They are running shoes! The lugs at times though have created some "traction issues" on some unstable ground ie; gravel, loose sand etc. I did not feel I was getting the same performance or equal effort as to what I was putting out and what the ground was giving me.
The MV2's however seem to have fixed that issue. I have taken them on short, fartlek runs on sand trails, to LSD runs on pavement and to a 3:07 marathon all within 3 weeks of owning them. The wear on the shoes is on par for Newton's and they are holding up well with close to 150+miles in those 3 weeks. So far the only complaint I have, is that I normally run barefoot. I get hot Spots in the MV2's and as stated in the original post, the mesh actually rubbed on my 2nd to last toe. A little superglue or body glide solves the issue for me, but still a bit annoying more than anything.  Over all, another winner from Newton Running in my eyes.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ers2qi</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/8rzk</id></website><link>http://www.runblogger.com/2011/08/newton-mv2-zero-drop-running-shoe.html</link><postedTime>2011-08-11T02:52:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-12-11T03:23:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/el4isj</id><link>http://www.runblogger.com/2011/08/newton-mv2-zero-drop-running-shoe.html#comment-383832315</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-08-11</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>