<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4xya/post/2012-03-30T17:47:26</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>To all the people asserting that Trayvon Martin was not a child, because seventeen-year-olds are not really children: I wonder if you'd indulge me as I conduct a thought experiment. 
&lt;br/&gt;
Let's say we were looking at an entirely different case. Say there was a 21 year old male dating a 17 year old female, and the male was now up on statutory rape charges. (I'll leave unspecified the ethnicities of the people involved, as an exercise for the reader.) Should he be let Off the hook because his lover is, you know, &lt;i&gt;tall?&lt;/i&gt; Should the law look more kindly on him because she was photographed looking angry? or flashing a gang sign at the camera?
&lt;br/&gt;
There is something about the discussion of these matters that seems to prevent people from seeing things as what they are; from acknowledging even baseline reality. An Anxiety seems to set in, then a desire to paint alternate narratives that explain what is otherwise inexplicable unless you acknowledge what the rest of us seemingly knew all along. 
&lt;br/&gt;
Remember that Trayvon Martin wasn't a predator on the hunt -- he was coming back from the store. Maybe in some people's reality, seventeen-year-old black boys who are visiting their fathers to watch the game on TV go to the store for snacks and, on the way back,  decide on a whim (and completely unarmed) to pull some guy out of his SUV and mug him, or beat him to death. 
&lt;br/&gt;
But in the reality the rest of us inhabit, this does not make sense. What does make sense is that a paranoid individual with delusions of grandeur fell into the easy habit of seeing his world as a single, undifferentiated threat environment; of inferring too much from too little -- and the result was that he killed a seventeen-year-old boy. Now look: maybe he's sorry he did it. Maybe he would have made the same error in judgement if Trayvon Martin had been white. But what difference does that make? An unjustified killing is, at the end of the day, what it is, though an egregiously incompetent police department may make said killing more difficult to investigate.
&lt;br/&gt;
 A man killed a boy in Florida. People who wish to spin or softpedal or outright deny that fact should, speaking of investigations, conduct one -- into their own motives and biases.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67l8cs</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/eyjq</id></website><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/national/archive/2012/03/on-the-age-and-innocence-of-trayvon-martin/255293/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:30:29+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:47:26+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4xya</id><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/national/archive/2012/03/on-the-age-and-innocence-of-trayvon-martin/255293/#comment-481237525</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a9sdz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>