<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xl2r/post/2012-03-29T13:41:47</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3yocv</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rtsw6</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>If you're shooting in AP mode that means the camera is choosing your shutter speed. 

Slow shutter speed = more likely to blur
Fast shutter speed = less likely to blur

But you also have to factor in your ISO &amp; your Aperture.

So let's use this example:

You're inside your house at night- so it's sort of dark.

You're shooting in AP mode
You're current f/stop = 2.5
Youre current SS = whatever the camera wants
Your ISO = (Depends, are you choosing your ISO or are you letting your camera choose? YOU should be choosing- ISO is one of the first things you should choose on your own. Low ISO = use when you've got plenty of light. High ISO = use when you've got limited light. so let's say you're letting your camera choose &amp; it gives you a ISO of 600)

You snap a picture of your kid who is running around like a demon- ALAS! your kid is a big blur. LAAAME!

you take alook @ what your camera did:

ISO: 600
f/stop: 2.5
SS: 85

well crap- there's your answer. a SS of 85 is WAY too low. basically, if you're shooting anything that's moving you should never have your SS under 200. 

the problem is that the lower the SS the more light that comes in. so if you're letting your camera choose for you it's going to choose the SS it wants to let in more light to "technically" get a better exposed picture. 

the problem with that is that you may have better exposure but you're going to sacrifice a crisp shot.BUT- it can work better if you're controlling your ISO- if you bump that ISO up to 1200 (for example)- this time your camera will probably give you a SS of around 275 or so- there you go. no blur. but you might get grain (higher ISO = grain. although many higher level cameras handle higher ISO very well, like the D90)

i'd rather have grain that i can fix PP than a blurry shot. you can't save blurry- even if you sharpen the shit out of it pp- you know?

you could also lower your f/stop to 1.8 (this will also let in more light therefore reducing blur)- but then you're not going to be able to nail focus on what you want (well, you could- but i highly doubt it with a moving toddler- ykwim?)

i tend to shoot around 2.5-3.5 (up close) thats the sweet Spot for me.

also, a lower f/stop doesn't guarantee no blur- you could still be dealing with a lower SS (given to you by the camera) &amp; still get blur.what i kind of boils down to is that it's best that you're in control. even if it's only 95%.
so if you're going to be shooting in AP or S mode then you should be controlling your ISO at the very least.

when i first started i would set my camera to AP or S &amp; see what it gave me- if I liked the picture i would right down the settings &amp; practice in manual. using those settings- then i went from there. then one day it just clicked. like- whoa. you know?now that you've read my novel...sorry yo.

just try &amp; remember:

ISO: lots of light = low | little light = high
SS: high ss = less blur | low ss = more blur
f/stop: wide open = let's in more light &amp; gives you better bokeh | higher = let's in less light &amp; you get less bokeh
then you just have to make them work together nicely.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hk619</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7tmh</id></website><link>http://www.harpershappenings.com/2012/03/28/what-the-f-stop/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T21:46:58+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:41:47+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xl2r</id><link>http://www.harpershappenings.com/2012/03/28/what-the-f-stop/#comment-479685899</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>