<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwsejs/update/2012-03-31T10:29:01/049688ca900e2cad5806c7e8b3afcd3d834b8b38a07470ae80cff0760d86a8ef</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwulhd</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cjxkt</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Smart: Such thinking is essentially known as moral equivalence...You and Obama would love us all to believe that he's no worse than Republicans are. Ahh, but Obama has a record now. 

 Republicans did publicly warn Obama not to try and pass such bitterly divisive legislation--like this onerous boondoggle known as Obamacare--with such slender partisan majorities. It just wasn't ever going to pass the smell test with the American People. Much less the laugh test of the Congressional Budget Office--based on its screwy funding gimmicks. And hey, politics is  the art of compromise--in a nation as culturally and politically diverse--as America.

Obama paid no heed to them. He contemptuously told Republicans to sit in the back of the car and shutup. Then he proceeded to cram this constitutionally suspect bill straight down our throats. 

I must strongly disagree with you. Nothing in Obama's pompous and chuckleheaded demeanor suggests he's scary. He's just plain stupid. And too thick-headed to ever take anyone's counsel but his own.  But he was duly warned--by the Republicans--that a bipartisan approach is Always best...And Obama and the Democrats publicly told them--and all America--to go screw. Now, Burn baby, Burn.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zi8ry</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/71fv</id></website><link>http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2012-03-30/obama-campus-fervor-losing-to-apathy-as-students-sour-on-2012.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T04:21:35+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T14:29:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwsejs</id><link>http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2012-03-30/obama-campus-fervor-losing-to-apathy-as-students-sour-on-2012.html#comment-481871948</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/az6hu</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>