<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m946wx/update/2012-03-17T11:08:10/a6423515e8c15a8dbd888def367ec5fd50508e71d2ee4803b3cafcf69b1c1ceb</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>You are not doing a good job of explaining what is going on (mainly because it is hard to do in one article and is beyond the Scope of what your editor wanted).  Each different element has a differing ability to attract electrons, this is based upon the number of orbitals filled, or left vacant from their Spot in the atomic table.  In general elements react according to how many orbitals they have open.  Carbon has 4 open Spots in its orbital pattern.  Hydrogen has 1.  Thus when carbon and hydrogen react they can produce methane (CH4).  Benzene rings are the basic structure behind graphene, they are particularly unusual because the shape of the orbitals are modified by the 3 dimensional shape of the ring of carbon atoms. This shape in turn, causes the P orbital to become displaced above and below the plane of the carbon ring.  The voodoo or magic that happens here is what has everyone excited about graphene.  This displaced orbital completely changes the properties of carbon.  The only similar type of chemical properties that exist in our world are the properties of living organisms.  Not surprisingly, living organisms are full of molecules that have benzine rings in them.  What this article is saying is that we will be able to make new materials based upon carefully spacing the placement of atoms on a layer on top of the material that is shaped like the spacing in graphene.  This mimics the deformation of the p orbital that carbon has.  It is not exactly like it which is even more exciting because it will allow for even more specialized forms of material to be made.  The electrons in the example were actually in a magnetic field made by the atoms of the material rather than from the surrounding area.  This is an example of quantum mechanical effects effecting the broader material and is another exciting aspect of these experiments.

Nano-tech like this will not directly allow the production of elements (gold, platinum ect.)  It will make whole new combinations of materials that could not even be imagined by a scientist before this study.  Reading between the lines here, what we are seeing is that contrary to current speculation in popular press, the limitations placed upon Moore's Law by the properties of atoms is not a bad thing.  It will in all probability allow us to build materials and manipulate matter in ways that were blocked by our inability to control masses of specific atoms in specific ways.  A bike built from the placement of individual atoms in specific places will be incredibly light, durable and cheaply made by machines alone.  The boundary between living matter and dead will be much harder to see because materials used in ordinary items will have some of the same kinds of strength, regeneration, self replication, and beauty that we associate with living things.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6gm22d</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rohx</id></website><link>http://www.extremetech.com/extreme/122693-scientists-create-graphene-from-scratch-heralds-new-age-of-designer-materials</link><postedTime>2012-03-16T16:17:42+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-17T15:08:10+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m946wx</id><link>http://www.extremetech.com/extreme/122693-scientists-create-graphene-from-scratch-heralds-new-age-of-designer-materials#comment-467787261</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5g9wy</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-16</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>