<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk4y62/post/2012-03-25T22:50:44</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Dr. Jack Cashill really homes in on the beam, like the investigative reporter I've
long admired, building on the analysis of Dr. Jerome Corsi and superb gumshoe
work by Sheriff Joe Arpaio's Cold case posse. Has Dr. Jack shaken the Irish
disease, tossed the sauce and clambered aboard the wagon from which I’ve just
fallen?

What would we do without our Ph.D.s? Maybe they will eventually realize that
official investigation is needed, not only to confirm Obama's constitutional
eligibility at birth, but also to find out that the key eligibility question is
the effect, if any, of Obama's Indonesian naturalization on his U.S.
citizenship. Nobody will find Obama ineligible at birth, but full disclosure of
all relevant and material evidence of the effect of Barry’s Indonesian
naturalization on his American citizenship provides a reasonable basis for
finding that Barry relinquished his U.S. citizenship by 1981. Loss of
citizenship means loss of eligibility to the Office of President. Obama can't
be a natural born U.S. citizen if he is no longer a U.S. citizen at all, even
though he was a natural born U.S. citizen on the day of his birth.

It seems to be dimly  on Dr. Jerry that Obama was adopted in Hawai'i. He
says, "Obama refuses to waive privacy rights that would allow the
Hawaii Department of Health to release any adoption records that may exist for
him." See http://www.wnd.com/2012/03/postman-ayers-family-put-foreigner-obama-through-school/ (article linked in the Dr. Jack's piece herein).

Dr. Jack is still lagging Dr. Jerry a bit. I heard Dr. Jack mightily affirm to a
group that Barry was born of Stanley Ann Dunham, notwithstanding my frantic
silent signals waving him Off the point. Never mind she wasn't on the island
when Barry was born there and the mitochondrial DNA of her daughter Maya
Soetoro-Ng doesn't match Barry's.

Dr. Jerry rates a B-. Dr. Jack gets a gentleman's C for trying hard and improving
so much since his book on disrespecting, or whatever, Obama - didn't "dis" him enough.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ygcnw</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f7e3</id></website><link>http://www.wnd.com/2012/03/why-the-ayers-family-helped-obama/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T00:17:31+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T02:50:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk4y62</id><link>http://www.wnd.com/2012/03/why-the-ayers-family-helped-obama/#comment-476183160</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lfcs2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>spam</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>