<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m397uw/update/2012-03-29T17:36:44/43b6ec12168b07445aa05c644bcbdbf3a86e44261b5b525b5e2640e4d5792ddf</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39ari</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ha7cu</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I suppose I'll take this opportunity to point out that you boomers are selfish moochers.  Of course it's no big deal to you that the retirement age is going up, you and the rest of your boomer cohort are exempt.  Pretty typical that boomers are spared any hardship while the rest of society works longer and harder to pay for your lives of selfish opulence.

Kindly take the rest of your generation and go freeze to death in the dark.

Update:

It won't let me reply to any of you, but hahahaha, I love the outrage you useless geriatrics are displaying.  You think you're the only generation to ever work hard?  Every generation in history has worked hard, the only difference is that boomers feel society owes them for it.  

I also love that you people think "wait until you get to 65 and there's no pension" is a legitimate threat.  Having come behind the biggest and most wasteful demographic bulge of all time, I've lived my whole life knowing that because of you people, there won't be a pension fund or OAS, or, in all likelihood, there probably won't be a universal health care system either.  I've made preparations accordingly, which would have been alot easier if I didn't have to make CPP payments that won't be there for me because your generation is ridiculous.

Your generation is a useless, spoiled garbage barge.  Your parents knew it, your kids know it, and thanks to the tradition you people started of abandoning old people in crooked for-profit nursing homes, it's only so much longer before we'll get to dump you  at the home to enjoy Cold food and twice weekly showers with lights Off at 8.

You've made your bed, boomers.  This budget might not make you lie in it, but you'll get there eventually.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zxs8w</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zsj8</id></website><link>http://www.torontosun.com/2012/03/29/conservatives-refrain-from-deep-cuts</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:36:43+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T21:36:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m397uw</id><link>http://www.torontosun.com/2012/03/29/conservatives-refrain-from-deep-cuts#comment-479923918</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rt7i7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>