<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwq1ch/post/2012-03-30T18:49:21</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Here is some information for anyone who thinks their group has an exclusive on suffering. Jews in Europe were  forced to live in Ghettos in the European Papal States until 1885. They were not allowed to own real estate or a business outside the ghetto or even leave the ghetto after dark. From 1938 until 1945, HALF of the Jews on the planet earth were murdered by hitler and the nazis while most of the world stood silent.  

1400 years ago, Egypt was 95% Christian. Today, Christians make up less than 10% of Egypt's population and they are not permitted to build new churches and they need a special permit from the Egyptian Government to even repair a  hole in the roof of a church. In the last year, dozens of churches have been Burned by Muslim mobs and many of Egypt's Coptic Christians killed or seriously injured. It should be mentioned that the word COPT means Egyptain.  

In Africa, black Africans are still being sold into slavery, even in 2012. Although outlawed in nearly all countries today, slavery is practiced in Secret in many parts of the world. There are an estimated 27 million victims of slavery worldwide. In Mauritania alone, up to 600,000 men, women and children, or 20% of the population, are enslaved, many of them used as bonded labour.  Slavery in Mauritania was finally criminalized in August 2007. It is estimated that as many as 200,000 Sudanese children and women have been taken into slavery in Sudan during the Second Sudanese Civil War. In Niger, where the practice of slavery was outlawed in 2003, a study found that almost 8% of the population are still slaves.


PEOPLE OF ALL COLORS, NATIONALITIES AND RELIGIONS ARE SUFFERING. IT IS TIME TO STOP DIVIDING OURSELVES BY THESE SELF IMPOSED DIVISIONS AND  BECOME PART OF THE SAME HUMAN RACE BEFORE IT IS TOO LATE. NO ONE HAS THE MARKET CORNERED ON SUFFERING. IT IS UNIVERSAL.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zclg5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q0fi</id></website><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/29/second-trayvon-martin-twitter-feed-identified/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T06:00:18+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T22:49:21+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwq1ch</id><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/29/second-trayvon-martin-twitter-feed-identified/#comment-481287865</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hwlhl</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>