<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwcgqn/update/2012-03-30T04:29:29/2dfe102e8adefef5057f53c2c61451cedd08d62f94bf904cd13b6cecb373ba17</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The brother was composed, articulate and believable in the interview. Up until I saw it, I figured Zimmerman was guilty big time.
Still, the Zimmerman - 'he was on his way to Target' thing seems pretty weak. Listening to 911 tape, I still have the impression neighborhood watch was on his mind, and it seems that his recording 'these --holes  get away' really puts a chip on his shoulder. I don't see how that portion of the recording was manipulated. He was definitely pursuing Martin, even after being told not to, and with a gun, and obviously at some point there was confrontation.
The beat his 'head on the concrete' seems implausible when they were Spotted on the grass.
He did appear pretty normal on video at the police station, so soon after his 'near death' experience.
At first I thought the help calls were from Martin, but if from Zimmerman, it seems like he probably was being attacked and may have felt he needed to use his weapon for defense.
However, that doesn't make it right. A neighborhood watch person's duty is to observe and report and shouldn't be carrying a weapon. This a perfect example why the stand your ground law is insane.
We should also Ban guns in this country, except for law enforcement.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z3b9t</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T07:25:56+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T08:29:29+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwcgqn</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html#comment-480517328</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzibb</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>