<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw77h6/post/2012-03-30T15:14:18</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gk34hn</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ap51v</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Howdy, and sorry to be bumping a months-old story like this, but having just today railed on someone myself for not supplying sources, I wanted to kind of slip in here and mention:

a) @newser-3360cc3c25a2cb6c448ae7b8a08b257e:disqus  is Spot on in asking for sources from those who make claims

b) While I completely appreciate pointing out where news agencies (and then Newser) propagate falsehoods, half truths, inadvertent inaccuracies, or really obvious failings;  I think there's a pretty big misconception of how Newser works.  The staff at Newser who do the writing are NOT journalists.  Newser aggregates lots of news sources and ranks "hot" stories based  of a sort of % by volume of the sources covering the same stories.  The writing done by Newser is aimed at providing a shortened summary of the story, so that you get the general picture without having to go to a whole bunch of places.  I'm pretty sure that the initial intent was to list something on the order of 5 article sources, as opposed to the generally just one that you get with each Newser story.

In any case, while it might be maddening that Newser makes errors in reporting, they can technically claim the errors weren't theirs, but the sources from which they summarize.  A good example (that drove and continues to drive me bananas) is here: http://www.newser.com/story/130864/t-rex-was-more-massive-than-we-thought.html  This article gets the math wrong by a lot, and it's easy math, but the AFP either didn't catch the error or didn't bother calling the museum curator on it.  (Because finding out something weighs 9 tons when you estimated it at 6 is a 50% increase, not a 30% [the curator incorrectly based his numbers and deltas Off of the newly found mass when talking about size relative to their initial estimate])  Newser reported the figure exactly as the AFP did, and it's totally strange to me not to catch something so easy.

I agree with you - Newser should owe it to its readers to be smarter than that, if they claimed to be a news agency or journalists.  But as-is... the source is a handy scape goat (so they'd blame Time), and keeping it like that takes a little of the brain involvement out of their process.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/mb0gi5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gblz</id></website><link>http://www.newser.com/story/comments/132539/legalizing-medical-marijuana-doesnt-up-kids-pot-use.html</link><postedTime>2011-11-04T13:51:00+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:14:18+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw77h6</id><link>http://www.newser.com/story/comments/132539/legalizing-medical-marijuana-doesnt-up-kids-pot-use.html#comment-481089934</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzh0a</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-11-04</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>