<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwhrhu/update/2012-03-30T13:37:59/26591352bc2e496f6c285916ca467c4dc7f08aa1c0ebd688c024f509981514eb</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwh8m6</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzq7n</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Yes it is often fair to bring a gun into a fist fight. For
example my ribs are not joined in the front seam at all due to open heart surgery. One punch to the chest could easily kill me. I have high blood pressure. I have a cow valve in my heart. I am diabetic and have two artificial knees.  I appear to be a large, strong and healthy male. But I am not. Anyone showing aggression towards me would give me great and reasonable fear for my survival. Top that  with laws that prevent us from giving a warning and it sets up a real storm. I can not draw a pistol and tell someone to stop or back . That would put me in prison. If danger occurs and I draw I must shoot.
Notice in the case under discussion that the dead fellow did
not have a 14 round clip emptied into him. One shot suggests self defense and not a vigilante mentality. Also when Close ups of that grainy video are seen there are large head wounds on the accused person. So his head was being bashed on the concrete. Right now this kid is being badly used by groups trying to create an issue. The on the Spot conspiracy of all the officials is so unlikely that it does not deserve credence.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zh427</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ant8</id></website><link>http://www.alternet.org/newsandviews/article/873983/police_surveillance_video_shows_no_blood%2C_bruises_on_trayvon_martin%27s_shooter%2C_george_zimmerman/comments/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:28:28+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:37:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwhrhu</id><link>http://www.alternet.org/newsandviews/article/873983/police_surveillance_video_shows_no_blood%2C_bruises_on_trayvon_martin%27s_shooter%2C_george_zimmerman/comments/#comment-480991451</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z9e5</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>