<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/136753/post/26057847/comment/329233449</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>before departure, Wang Shuguan 5 million in cash, receipts, ID cards and business cards all fit in a purse, and put in the box of the motorcycle. 14 am after arriving home, however,louis vuitton outlet, Wang Shuguan take the package, such as was thunderstruck: After the box is not locked, with the money bag was gone. 15,louis vuitton, Wang Shuguan rushed to the South Street Station, and  the other telephone and found that looked a simple dress of young people are the biting wind. Each other again and he confirmed that the items in the identity and the bag after the bag into his arms. motorcycle lost 50,000 payment the Wang Shuguan excited to open the bag: 50,000 yuan in cash exactly right. He immediately drawn from 500 yuan to thank the good guy. I did not expect, shoes, the other quite unhappy refused: this several months of hard revenue,louis vuitton purses! Family life are counting on the money! Wang Shuguan anxious about 14:20, his cell phone rang. the owner the Wang Shuguan is the perennial run outside a freight driver, December 27 at noon,coach bags, Wang Shuguan received in Handan have the purchase price of $ 50,000, take a friend\'s car came to Xingtai city high-speed intersection, store, driving his motorcycle home. How much is your ID number? &amp;gt; the sound coming from the microphone as the savior, will the Wang Shuguan rescued from the Anxiety of chagrin. guy Jianqian monthly income of 800 yuan the &amp;lt;/ p , waiting, and making inquiries,louis vuitton luggage, and finally returning lost money good-hearted people named Li Wei, the Xingtai St. and the wine one drinks distribution work. Day of the incident 14 Xu Li Wei delivery via Xingtai City, South Yuen picked up on the roadside when he lost the bag. the St. and liquor boss Zhang Mengwu about the incident, banged the table and said one word: wage of 100 yuan. Zhang Mengwu Xin-Wei Lee did not mention to any return money thing, phone came the voice of the savior of the &amp;#30456;&amp;#20851;&amp;#30340;&amp;#20027;&amp;#39064;&amp;#25991;&amp;#31456;&amp;#65306; Victoria&amp;#8217;s Secret the History of the Biggest Lin &amp;#19994;&amp;#20027;&amp;#36973;20&amp;#20313;&amp;#21517;&amp;#20445;&amp;#23433;&amp;#27572;&amp;#25171;&amp;#21518;&amp;#36992;&amp;#26469;20&amp;#20313;&amp;#32769;&amp;#20065;&amp;#24110;&amp;#24537; U . s . Saddle carefully bred - Total View </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:136753:26057847</id><idPostId>26057847</idPostId><idBlogId>136753</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:136753</id><idBlogId>136753</idBlogId><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com</link><displayName>HOCKEYCENTRIC</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-canucks-are-more-than-one-line-and-luongo/</link><displayName>The Canucks Are More Than One Line And Luongo</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-01T13:24:03.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:136753:26057847:329233449</id><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-canucks-are-more-than-one-line-and-luongo/#IDComment329233449</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T13:24:03.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The Canucks Are More Than One Line And Luongo by jkht1w8m</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://www.pumastore.biz/</link><idEmailMd5>eeb2fc34a4dccb616c84dd33fc89808b</idEmailMd5><displayName>jkht1w8m</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://www.pumastore.biz/"&gt;jkht1w8m&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-canucks-are-more-than-one-line-and-luongo/"&gt;The Canucks Are More Than One Line And Luongo&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>