<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/epfap0/delete/2012-01-16T11:56:07</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/epurxk</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6k4pp</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Firstly, you're talking about different contexts: I have no difficulty with Santorum or anyone influencing a bunch of nutbar fundy yell coaches to endorse him - the entire process of endorsements is bogus to start with &amp; probably doesn't work except with the weakest of minds. I DO have SOME problems with ballot box stuffing in a primary (tho a lot more in the general, where it really matters) - but Iowa wasn't a true  vote ballot box context - it was a caucus, &amp; caucuses are open discussion plus some voting processes which don't involve the  ballot to any critical extent (It's optional at most, &amp; where used, mostly pointless.), but besides all that it's a PRIMARY.  

There is absolutely no problem at all with the Kochies &amp; of a few banksters getting together at a vacation Spot in the Bahamas &amp; picking their very own nominee for the Rs - which is the same things that they've BEEN doing in every presidential election cycle since the Civil War ended, with a few notable exceptions - or one anyway: 1964). Where the Secret ballot democratic process matters is in the general, &amp; ONLY in the general. If you cons want to go thru some Kabuki exercise in fake intraparty democracy every four years, go ahead - you're only fooling yourselves.</body><verb>delete</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/dw6d1k</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tz1k</id></website><link>http://www.mediaite.com/online/report-karen-santorums-ex-boyfriend-was-an-abortion-provider/</link><postedTime>2012-01-16T14:27:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-01-16T16:56:07+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/epfap0</id><link>http://www.mediaite.com/online/report-karen-santorums-ex-boyfriend-was-an-abortion-provider/#comment-412674695</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7zl7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>killed</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>killed</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-01-16</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>