<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms8l0v/update/2012-03-26T23:05:58/eee0bc8d2dbebaada4d55e9f576eefacf2c220c4111531cffba8e68bcae2957b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Well that was disappointing. Right from the start you show a complete misunderstanding - the point about freedom of the developer to make proprietary software, rather than freedom for the consumer. If you had thought for 2 seconds about it, in RMS's mindset, this is like a slave master saying he's being oppressed because he doesn't have the freedom to enslave people! And you say that that's where *his* logic falls apart! Just....wow. Really, it's not that hard to understand.

Now, you may not agree that proprietary software = enslaving people, but Richard does. This is the simple fundamental disagreement here as far as I can see, and you could have just stated that and moved on. But you decided to say, "that's where his logic completely falls apart." Well, no, the logic of that argument holds perfectly. It's just that you disagree on the core issue of just *how* terrible proprietary software is. Which is fine. There's no need whatsoever to say that his logic "completely falls apart", it's unnecessary and comes across as pathetic and desperate. 

And yet you both managed to babble on for the better part of an hour on a mad ego trip. You may disagree with him (and btw I do disagree with some of what he said, I'm certainly NOT an RMS worshiper), but you were completely unable to actually address any of it in a way which wasn't easy to pick apart, and without being insulting and incredibly dismissive. This is not how one handles oneself in a debate, or an interview. Very weak. It was Fox News worthy.

I've no idea why you allowed yourselves to get so wound up over this (especially Bryan, his good natured, likeable ribbing turned to bitter spiteful snark). First , it's just a guys opinion, expressed without any personal contempt of you as far as I could see (which is far more than I could say for Bryan), and secondly, it's RMS for Christ sake, did you not know what his views would be?!

And what does pedophilia have to do with any of what you were talking about? What? You can't argue with what someone's saying so you try and point out other things they have done which are unrelated? Drudging up old forum/mailing list comments? How about I go and interview all your friends and see if you've ever said anything I find insulting? Pathetic. 

And the child-hating comments...why can you not understand the point he's making? And if you do, why did you not acknowledge it? And then say you disagree? You said he said "no-one should have kids" - that's not what he said, you even played the clip, you must not have heard it. And no coherent intellectual response to the reason for what he said. There are arguments to be made there, (and actually you can bet that it will become the biggest problem for all humankind, over consumption, forgetting global warming, is a reality which will hit the human race hard over the next 100 years, and if you want to be effective about it, Americans consume way more per head than anyone else, followed by UK, then the rest of Europe) but you decided to go for the public humiliation route again. Chris's response was just hilarious:- "(sarcastically)yeah, you gotta think about that global Heating...." Well......don't you?! Do you not recognize that as a problem? Or do you think that there are solutions other than constraining population expansion? I do, but you never addressed it. That just kinda summed up the whole thing for me. There's a point that's being made (admittedly this one's way outside the Scope of LAS), which you could genuinely address and argue with, but no....lets insult him some more...and deny global Heating! Wha...?!

The e-book contradiction Bryan pointed out was in fact not a contradiction, it's entirely possible to find the concept of both DRM and non-anonymous payments immoral. Again, I understand Stallman's concerns, but I've bought digital goods with both, so I'm not as hardcore about it as he is. But why is it not possible to think that both are bad? There's no contradiction there!

I've been watching for the past few months,and was finding it entertaining. Sadly I won't be watching anymore. That was laughable, sad and moronic all at the same time. The way you guys conducted yourselves during the interview itself and in the aftermath here was reprehensible and embarrassing. And that's coming from someone who doesn't agree with Stallman that much.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6exitu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5m5p</id></website><link>http://www.jupiterbroadcasting.com/18071/bryan-hates-freedom-las-s21e01/</link><postedTime>2012-03-18T22:13:08+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-27T03:05:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms8l0v</id><link>http://www.jupiterbroadcasting.com/18071/bryan-hates-freedom-las-s21e01/#comment-477121084</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-18</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>