<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6bzs/post/2012-03-30T11:36:19</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Mr. Christensen,

First in response to your opinion, let's (on a Debunk page of course) rely on facts.  In spite of all caps, the protest message is essentially correct with one caveat.  If more and more people are only posting the protest notice (and correspondingly boycotting Facebook advertisers) and less social posts (not likely), Facebook would indeed be forced to listen.  As I'm sure you are aware, there are countless number of non-violent, non-compliant protests by massive numbers of people that have been successful - I'll not take the time to list them.

Second, Timeline is not all bad, but is specifically bad for gamers.  Now this in of itself, is not why Facebook exists - for gamers; however, gamers do support some of the major advertisers on Facebook.  If gamers leave Facebook and utilize direct game access portals, the click through revenue drops (and is now even stagnant on Facebook as recently reported by Business Week) and Facebook suffers.  That's the message - hit Facebook in its Pocketbook.  In issuing a diatribe against legitimate opinions, you have dropped to a level where your opinion becomes meaningless because it attempts to discourage intelligent discourse regarding a disagreement with the direction of the Facebook and its devolution into an Advertising and Referral Harvesting tool.

Third, your argument to just "grin and bear it", my paraphrase of your complacent attitude in the arena of disagreement, is disingenuous and quite frankly, useless.  Actions that you posit and encourage to just accept change, while not Always bad, can lead to some rather harmful results.  While Facebook's implementation of Timeline will harm no one physically, mentally or even socially (other than forcing a few gamers to "get a life"), it's the principle behind the change that concern the majority (rather than the "lots of people" who like timeline) of Facebook users - the continual and routine fixing something that is not broken.  There is an agenda here, like it or not.  Facebook is being slowly morphed into a harvesting tool and the users, for the most part will accept this (much as a toad in a frying pan will literally sit himself to death as the Heat is slowly increased under the frying pan).

How can this be good for Facebook?  The creators and developers will be long gone with money in the bank when most people finally get "cooked" enough to go on to the next "thing".  Sadly, it's the social connection that loses and our society becomes even more disconnected.  Too sad.

Finally, I can appreciate and respect your opinion that you like Timeline, but most of us find it extremely difficult to navigate, especially if I am looking for posts from one person or posts concern one particular issue, especially on a Timeline which thousands of posts.  Try, for instance, going to a heavy gamers page and look for all of his posts regarding one specific game that he/she plays.  You may have to wade through pages and pages of posts by friends, until you find his little box with 2 3/4 current posts and a "98 more" click link (that you can review within the same little small box.  To literally program a time consuming, less efficient way of doing something, is sad and speaks volumes to the increasingly obvious purpose of Facebook - to change and conform users to a set of strict guidelines and principles on computer social interaction.  Your opinion demonstrates to me that one more user has been "conformed".

Thank you any time you utilize in even considering a different opinion.

Wind Rider

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yy655s</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/a2qc</id></website><link>http://www.hoax-slayer.com/timeline-protest.shtml</link><postedTime>2012-02-01T04:25:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:36:19+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6bzs</id><link>http://www.hoax-slayer.com/timeline-protest.shtml#comment-480865784</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>