<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mf49me/update/2012-03-15T13:01:45/e756130cd295300bacbe46d571e2d596ee2946856eff8b0587e72adfd401b735</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>[continued VII:] Finally, regarding this particular propaganda piece written by Mr Akbar and Mr Akins. Not only is it filled with major distortions, it's riddled with cynical and out-right lies! For such learned men to be making such erroneous claims doesn't bode well with all I know. Perhaps Mr Akbar and Mr Akins would care to explain themselves in the near future... 

Nevertheless, allow me to touch on two such claims.

"165,000 Sahrawi refugees in Algeria"

Foremost, these round figures are according to who Mr Akbar/Akins? Such bias claims might only expose the type of sources upon which you rely for your (dis-)information. UNHCR claims 90,000 "refugees". Now tell us Mr Akbar/Akins, how many of them actually originate from the former "Spanish Sahara"? Or better yet, tell us if these "refugee" camps are managed by UNHCR; and if not, why not? Further tell us, what of these "refugees" freedom of movement? And above all, why hasn't there been a census of the population held hostage in these camps?

"For more than 30 years, the Polisario Front and Algeria have systematically and categorically turned down requests of the High Commission on Refugees (HCR) to carry out a census of the Sahrawi population in the refugee camps of Tindouf province, in Southwest Algeria. While the unjustifiable refusal of Algeria can be easily understood in the context of its relations with Morocco and its need for political propaganda over the issue of refugees living on its soil, the refusal of the Polisario is primarily motivated by the profit which the separatist Front  from an overestimation of the number of refugees and, as a result, larger  amounts of humanitarian assistance flowing in. This is, among others, reflected in a confidential report of the European Union we were able to browse through."
("THE TINDOUF REFUGEE CAMPS: THE RESPONSIBILITIES CONFRONTING ALGERIA AND THE POLISARIO FRONT")

"West Africa: Polisario's Involvement in Drug Trafficking in the Sahel Exposed by U.S. Experts"
allafrica com/stories/201109151369.html

"Study Warns of Rising al-Qaeda Threat in North Africa - Urges closing Polisario camps which have become recruiting ground for terrorists"
w w w redorbit com/news/entertainment/1112468007/study_warns_of_rising_alqaeda_threat_in_north_africa_/

Furthermore, regarding your wild claims about the events in 2010, at the Gdeim IZK protest camp. "In November 2010, Moroccan security forces attacked the camp without warning, killing 36 protesters". Can you please substantiate these moronic appeals to emotion with some evidence, please. In this case, I'd even settle for reports from AI and HRW! Where in the world did you find these accusations!? 

For the record, the Gdeim Izik camp was set up entirely as a socio-economic protest and it was authorized by the government. To maximise the success of their demands, the organisers set up the camp a few weeks prior to scheduled talks at the UN regarding the Sahara conflict; throughout this time, the Polisario and their mouthpieces in the western media were painting the protest as an awakening against "Moroccan occupation". Unfortunately for these scheming manipulators, who hoped to exploit the situation in the UN, the demands of the camp organisers were met prior to talks at the UN even began. What followed truly exposed the merciless nature of the Polisario Front. Having received complaints from locals that armed gangs were preventing people from leaving the camps, the local police authorities stepped in to peacefully dismantle the camp. Contrary to Mr Akbar and Mr Akins claims, not only were the protestors given warning, they were supplied transport. Having allowed the protestors time to leave in an orderly fashion, the police authorities, armed solely with batons, proceeded to enter and dismantle the camps. How does that even compare to the police brutality displayed in western countries - from Greece, to the Occupy Wall St movement and copy cat occupations across the globe, to the Dale Farm evictions in England!! Not only do the police in such countries resort to sheer violence in such circumstance, but they're armed to the hilt! Nevertheless, what transpired in the Gdeim Izik camp was a shocking exposure of a mercenary organization (accused by Libyans themselves of fighting for Gaddafi during Libyan revolution!) that is often absurdly lauded as a defender of human rights! A dozen officers were slain in Cold blood, their heads severed and their bodies stoned and urinated on (see video below). Where was the international outcry?

(you-tube) watch?v=XyTx-E6HMRo
 
Yet despite this, pro-Polisario activists both native and foreign were brazenly proclaiming all sorts of malevolent lies against Morocco! Including the now infamous claim made on Spanish national television that the Moroccan authorities were attacking women and children, citing a picture of a wounded child - FROM PALESTINE - as evidence!!! May God expose you all.
 
(you-tube) watch?v=PMi57ma2Ha4

Is miss crocodile tears in the video above the reliable sources upon whom you ?

"I want to liberate Sahrawis from separatists' servitude" - Mustapha Salma (a name and story you will never hear the likes of Mr Akbar and Mr Akins mention!)

But is it really any wonder why this absurd and mendacious "conflict" has lasted so long?

"Algerian intelligence agents routinely bribe European police, journalists and MPs" (a claim made by 'Yussuf-Joseph' a defected Secret agent of Algeria)

...and then ask yourselves: "Who really bombed Paris?" (- an article by Naima Bouteldja, published in the Guardian 2005)</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6cb3gc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/h8a5</id></website><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2012/03/2012314101516261596.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-14T13:56:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-15T17:01:45+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mf49me</id><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2012/03/2012314101516261596.html#comment-466127394</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/za06x</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-14</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>