<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mws4fa/post/2012-03-31T10:49:43</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>*Amended reply*

What do you mean by "loaded terminology"? Why is my choice of terms incorrect here? After all, things in life are originated by an intentional source, albeit the end result may be unintended. After all, with the exception of unhuman activity, nothing originates by motu propio. Therefore studying evolution will only reveal HOW things operate, not WHY.

Your philosophy falls a hair short from the unveiling of the truth and this is why.

If we look at life through your optics, when we find, let's say for example: a) a corpse that has Bled out through a bullet wound; b) a smoking handgun; and c) a shell casing on the floor...we would suspect the decedent was killed by a bullet. 

Then when we adhere to your philosophical approach, we must be ready to limit our exploration to merely studying the caliber of the round, its consistency with the caliber of the pistol, the point of impact and the amount of blood lost through the bullet entry point, etc...and then attribute the death to the handgun.

When someone like me asks you to assert who determined the firing of the gun; your answer seeks to satisfy the examiner by simply asserting something to this effect: "No one determined the firing of the gun...the nature of the gun is to fire bullets, and the nature of the bullet is to cause grievious bodily harm. Hence, when the bullet was fired and killed the person on contact, the bullet/gun relation  in conformity with their nature and the evolution of the bullet ...from sitting on its shell + its activation by the gun hammer + the explotion in the bullet casing that Propelled the bullet through the gun barrel + its traveling through the air + and the piercing of the decedent's skin = CREATED the death of the person.

In other words, la bala y la pistola se mandan solas, right? 

Why is it? Is this lame world view an "academic" excuse that has been welded to justify a rejection for personal accountability? 

Who knows, man...all I know is that "El palo por sus frutos se conoce" and only time will prove to you the futility, fallacies and inadequacies, if any, of your philosophical argument.

As it was said in a british court centuries ago, Res Ipsa Loquitur (The thing speaks for itself) .  No matter how logically my arguments/evidence are profferred here, it is readily apparent that your stubborness does not allow you to see beyond your own cognition.  It is Ok, your are entitled to hold your own views no matter who outlandish they may be...no pun intended by the way.

Anyhow, best of luck on your studies and thank you for your time, don deus.

Sapere Aude,
Dr. Benito

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/y3auml</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/43mz</id></website><link>http://philosophiadeus.blogspot.com/2012/03/telos-without-god.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-05T18:41:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T14:49:43+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mws4fa</id><link>http://philosophiadeus.blogspot.com/2012/03/telos-without-god.html#comment-481887397</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-05</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>