<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3uqm1/post/2012-03-29T15:23:23</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3b2n4</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/don4h</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I think her reluctance to acknowledge the huge religious and cultural role the Prophets has had on Bajor until she's directly put on the Spot by Winn implies that she indeed has been putting an undue focus on the science and belittling the Bajoran viewpoint. But it's admittedly just one way to read it. If you just go Off what was shown in class, no, there's nothing objectionable, and Winn seems like she's overreacting. But I have to wonder why Keiko doesn't say "well, this is the science unit, where I explain the physical underpinnings of the wormhole and the aliens' interaction with our universe. I cover the aliens' interaction with Bajor as Prophets in a different unit."

Side note: There's really nothing the Bajorans claim about the Prophets and the wormhole that isn't scientifically true, except perhaps their intentions as benevolent beings. They really do perceive time in an otherworldly fashion, they really do provide visions to people that give them a different perspective on their lives through actual functioning artifacts on the planet, they really do live in a unique spatial anomaly in the space above Bajor. The whole thing sometimes seems like an argument about names - why shouldn't these particular aliens be called the Prophets anyway? They have prophetic power, they don't seem to care about naming themselves, and the first race to have a relationship with them calls them that.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zzdur</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/in-the-hands-of-the-prophets,71184/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:00:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:23:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3uqm1</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/in-the-hands-of-the-prophets,71184/#comment-479788548</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ridqk</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>