<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwml0k/post/2012-03-30T09:01:49</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I'd love to adopt a dog -- but on my own, in a big city with a long commute, it isn't a possibility.  I figure when I'm older, and retired with a yard, I'll rescue a dog or two.  I  love reading the stories here about Dud and Zelda.  I have three cats, and all of them are rescues.  

The city I live in has so many street animals, and I hate so much to see them out there, dirty and wandering and hanging out by dumpsters.  But it has really changed my notion of how things are done in the U.S.  I can't support euthanasia any more.  I used to see it as an evil necessity, but people here, where I live now, handle things so differently.  The city gives the street dogs shots, and then businesses around here, or groups of neighbors, sometimes will semi-adopt them, and will feed them and even put collars on them.  Butchers throw scraps out on the street; restaurants put out their food garbage; people cut down medium-sized water bottles and put them on street corners or doorsteps as watering stations for the street animals.  There's a person in every building, it seems, who feeds the street cats, and neighbors sometimes get together to pay for vet bills for neighborhood animals.  People put out cardboard boxes when the weather gets Cold.  Yes, there are too many street animals, and they do indeed suffer, but their presence compels a whole lot of people to Act with compassion, when they otherwise might not think about it.  The animals compel interaction, and thought and care and concern -- for them, and between neighbors who otherwise might not talk.  I think that is way better for them (and for us) rather than just **killing** them.  The cycle never ends, but here, there's more respect, in a way, for animals, even though there's not as much "pet culture" as in the U.S.  I've never seen anything quite like it.

As a postscript, I can't help but wish breeding were abolished.  So many good mutts out there....</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zqvzu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ync</id></website><link>http://shakespearessister.blogspot.com/2012/03/daily-dose-of-cute_29.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:50:49+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:01:49+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwml0k</id><link>http://shakespearessister.blogspot.com/2012/03/daily-dose-of-cute_29.html#comment-480713611</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5720i</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>