<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjgep/post/2012-03-26T14:14:52</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>No, it's not &lt;i&gt;saying&lt;/i&gt; more to fight back, it's &lt;i&gt;doing&lt;/i&gt; more.

You can talk against GOP propaganda all the live long day about how the stimulus prevented a Great Depression, but what I believe is the error in your thesis is if an  by a political party doesn't make things measurably better for people - things that THEY measure in their own lives - your party's political prospects are in peril.  How's that for alliteration?  LOL.

The problem for the stimulus is not that the GOP is propagandizing spending the money into an evil  - it is that it was done and so many continue to be laid  and to otherwise live in and around poverty more extreme than anything in living memory.  To fight back in words saying the stimulus prevented another Great Depression is Cold  next to their actual lives.

And now, among some, it's &lt;i&gt;arrogant&lt;/i&gt; for Obama and the Democrats to fight back in the manner you suggest.

If the ACA works to get people real health care, people will know it.  If things really do get better, &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; better on the streets of America, people will know it, and no GOP propaganda would be able to make that go away.

I know people on this blog were arguing for better than a Heritage Foundation health care bill and a bigger stimulus, but you can't wave away what actually happened by pretending things are wonderful for Americans.

People defend Social Security because they see their parents getting it!  People defend Medicare because they see their parents/grandparents getting it!  And you'll notice that there, GOP propaganda is about "saving" those programs, not about how "evil" those programs are.  Because those programs were decades old Democratic success stories for as far as they went.  You don't need to sell Social Security to people, you need to save/strengthen it.  You don't need to sell Medicare to people, you need to save/strengthen it.  Because the programs sell themselves.

If the ACA doesn't sell itself, selling it won't really save it.  It'll be results that dictate whether it lives or dies, and in the end, only results.

To wave away failure with the wand of the confidence fairy is NOT to fight back against the GOP propaganda machine, to treat people who don't observe success by peeing on their feet and tell them it's raining, isn't a recipe for success.  It's because of Democratic failure, not because of not fighting back, that GOP propaganda vilifying those Obama Era policies works even though they're wrong on the specifics.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rwgje</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5xa</id></website><link>http://www.americablog.com/2012/03/supreme-court-has-begun-hearing.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T14:51:42+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:14:52+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjgep</id><link>http://www.americablog.com/2012/03/supreme-court-has-begun-hearing.html#comment-476597765</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>