<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3j3ww/post/2012-03-29T18:56:46</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>10 As Samuel was offering up the Burnt offering, the Philistines drew near to attack Israel. But the LORD thundered with a mighty sound that day against the Philistines and threw them into confusion, and they were routed before Israel.

God is so faithful to answer prayer! He is so able, and it's clear just from looking at this one passage in the Old Testament that we truly can  on him alone!

If we pray according to his will and with expectancy that God will answer we can KNOW that he will deliver. Just like Samuel here, no matter how tough the situation may seem we need to remember we can Always count on God. And even though an army was advancing on Samuel and the Israelites -- who were completely unprepared -- they didn't freak out, they didn't try and scramble into fighting position, they left it up to God and he delivered them! Sure, it isn't going to play out exactly the same in our own lives; but our "advancing army" so to speak could be anything -- college decisions, family problems, etc... In everything we simply need to remember to trust in God rely on him through prayer!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zgg56</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/vkhn</id></website><link>http://www.compasschurch.org/sotd-samuel</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T07:38:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:56:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3j3ww</id><link>http://www.compasschurch.org/sotd-samuel#comment-479994298</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hy4ve</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>