<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/e285xf/update/2011-11-14T12:07:41/830e0d0b03dfed1f42e4f91632008d0a7adbb2221b59bb0c1436153db726cddc</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>There's one other aspect that makes others believe that our support is "cult-like": we don't jump around candidates, switching candidates at the drop of a hat. The mainstream media has been playing the GOP like a violin in this regard: make one particular candidate look popular and the unthinking masses will jump to that candidate and throw their cash and support behind them.

Look at the history of GOP support over the last 6 or so months. More than half of the candidates have spent time at the top with regard to popular support: Bachmann, Gingrich, Perry, currently Cain. Santorum I think had a Spot at the top for a short while. The GOP can't make up their own minds, and the media is playing on this to see to it they don't.

Whereas when someone becomes a Ron Paul supporter, they tend to stay Ron Paul supporters... Am I right? And that is simply because we do look beyond the man to the ideas they support. I don't care if Cain is black, though I think that's the only reason he's in the lead at the moment. I do care that he was once chair of the Federal Reserve in Kansas City (I live about 10 minutes from that building) -- albeit for only a year. I don't care that Gingrich has a PhD, but I do care about his stance on various policies and what occurred while he was Speaker of the House. I don't care if Bachmann is a woman, but I do care that she has stated that the Founders intended the United States to be a Christian theocracy and has ties to organizations that believe the same. And I don't care that Santorum used to be a Senator for Pennsylvania, but I do care that he is vehemently pro-life to the point that he feels a hospital in Phoenix should not have terminated a pregnancy to save that woman's life, and that he is strongly pushing for a amendment to the United States Constitution forbidding gay marriage and wants to reinstate DA/DT.

I don't share Ron Paul's views on a few things (and his introduction of the "We the People" Act has me a little worried), but I do support him on one key thing: some questions are not meant to be answered by the Federal government -- note that I exclude from that questions to be addressed by the Federal Courts where State laws conflict with the United States Constitution. The Constitution lays out a limited government, and that is to where Ron Paul wants to return us, and why so many people seem so vehemently against that I've still yet to entirely understand.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/mo9u5k</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/h63b</id></website><link>http://www.tomwoods.com/blog/ron-paul-does-not-have-a-cult-following/</link><postedTime>2011-11-14T16:10:33+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-11-14T17:07:41+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/e285xf</id><link>http://www.tomwoods.com/blog/ron-paul-does-not-have-a-cult-following/#comment-362896333</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/acikw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-11-14</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>