<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwy9cd/post/2012-03-30T10:55:37</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Since Burke has shown up we have not made the playoffs, we have not got better, we looked just dreadful last night, and the power play was just a joke…what a pathetic effort. You players should be ashamed of yourselves for playing like that at home.

 
I will tell you what Burkes has done. He has flushed 10”s of millions down the toilet on useless contracts for over paid, over the hill stiffs like Beachemin, Guegere, Liles, Connlley…not to mention millions wasted on a dreadful goalie coach, an assistant GM that was never needed to begin with…again millions flushed down the toilet.

 
That’s all this guy has done is spend, spend, spend…on what??? Where are the results for all this money spent? We have not gotten better, we have not improved…

 
I like the fact that we seem to have some good young players, that we gotten younger…but wow what a mess over the last month.

 
No direction, no guidance, no improvement…I was willing to wait, rebuild, but over 3 years of this, and nothing to prove, no improvement, no . Its obvious now that this guy just  doesn’t have it. I have been a fan for life, I have never seen a cup, I will Always be a fan but we do not seem to be heading in the right direction at all. I Cold not believe how bad we looked last night, just dreadful. Who is responsible for this? Someone has to lead, to guide…</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zjfp5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zsj8</id></website><link>http://www.torontosun.com/2012/03/29/leafs-worse-than-bad-against-flyers</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:00:23+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T14:55:37+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwy9cd</id><link>http://www.torontosun.com/2012/03/29/leafs-worse-than-bad-against-flyers#comment-480823892</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a5yho</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>