<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/musmen/update/2012-03-12T11:25:51/57dfbf3700a4c1ab430bd9473d666f8061c48b72b0c0f56fd38446ffa6f66732</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I am the friend who wrote what you quoted. I do not mind if you use my name. I stand behind what I wrote then and what I write, now.

Perhaps in the interest of brevity, you have failed to offer up the greater points I was making in my post. Unfortunately, I think this mischaracterization of what I had intended with my post might cause your readers to assume things about me that are not true.

In regard to your point about Dr. Bell's version of Critical Race Theory, I am no expert. And perhaps I have missed some of his nuances - but I have read about HIS interpretation of CRT and I've heard parts of his movie and I find the implications of assumed heartless, deep-seated racism by whites against blacks to be perverse and sickening and not based in reality. Fiction like this does not serve to educate us about racial issues in America, it serves to increase divisiveness, suspicion and even hatred.

In regard to the arrest of the professor outside of Boston, I don't think it matters how famous the doctor is - Dr. Gates had a chip on his shoulder and was looking for trouble. Instead of cooperating with a police officer, Dr. Gates used the opportunity to CREATE a racial issue and do further damage to the races. President Obama, instead of showing more cool, reasoned leadership, chose to buy into handling this occasion as an example of race-based prejudice - and our President really blew it in this regard. His reaction served to do nothing to heal racial tensions, it stoked the fires of division and distrust.

In regard to the Gates situation, you got a very important part of the Gates story wrong, Errington. This famous professor initially REFUSED to provide his ID to the police officer. That's when the officer asked him to step outside, which Gates initially refused as well. And don't forget that the only reason the officer was called out to the home was because a neighbor called police when the Professor was showing difficulty in being able to get into his own home. The officer was doing his job, attempting to protect Dr. Gates' home. If Dr. Gates had shown his ID as requested, the incident would have been over.

But Dr. Gates was looking for trouble. He didn't see the white police officer as a racially unbiased man who was attempting to determine whether Dr. Gates was an improper intruder, he prejudicially assumed a racist white police officer was abusing his authority by harassing a black man.  Instead of respecting the officer's authority, rather than assume the officer should be respected, Dr. Gates unfairly escalated the matter due to his own presumptions of racism.

I don't know about you, but if I had just come back from being away on a trip, and then have a hard time  entry into my own home, and then find a black police officer at my door (I am white) who asks me for my ID as proof that I live in my own home, I am going to choose to show the officer my ID immediately. And then if asked to go outside, I am going to comply. I am not going to immediately assume this black officer is harassing me for my race - or even if I do suspect racism to be at play, I will still provide my ID. Wouldn't you do the same?

My greater point in bringing up this example and the travesty of justice against whites by AG Eric Holder that you chose not to mention is racial prejudice is a two way street. As a white man who has tried to raise three color blind sons, I find race baiting choices like the ones made by Dr. Gates, Eric Holder, and our President to be examples of racism by blacks against whites and I find this to be working against racial healing in our culture. And unfortunately, I sense a surge in this activity and attitude ever since our President took office. What a wonderful opportunity our President had to help heal racial divisions - but instead he has chosen a strategy that has helped increase racial tensions in America.

I have come to the conclusion that politics loves racism. Politics has no true interest in making racism go away. It's too easy to point to one race and say "That race has unspoken, deep seated desires to treat you wrong - so vote for us. It's too easy to say "That man is only where he is today because affirmative action prevented another more qualified man to take the same Spot at school or work."

If you will recall, my last two paragraphs concluded my thoughts on this issue with the following:

"We
 as a people should not buy into the race-baiting that the KKK, David 
Dukes, Jesse Jacksons, and Reverend Wrights are trying to sell us. We 
should not allow our politicians to fuel the hopefully dying embers of 
our racial paranoia. Each of us needs to actively work hard to resist 
being taken advantage of by the fear mongers and instead strive daily to
 approach each fellow human being as an equal child of God regardless of
 color, class, religious preference, or whatever may be the current 
political divisive card du-jour." "Yes, we have come a long way, 
but the inherent political power of perpetuating, and never solving 
racial divisiveness will Always work hard to keep us - the little people
 - from achieving true color blindness."

Thank you for giving me the opportunity to respond.

Jeff Stager
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6abjx8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/eq37</id></website><link>http://www.whereistheoutrage.net/wordpress/2012/03/11/race-in-america/</link><postedTime>2012-03-11T23:05:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-12T15:25:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/musmen</id><link>http://www.whereistheoutrage.net/wordpress/2012/03/11/race-in-america/#comment-463396700</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-11</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>