<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/234352/post/86320894/comment/328119819</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The 49ers and their fans don\'t want to hear this, but they know it\'s true, even as they shut their eyes and clasp their ears shut:The New York Giants played a thoroughly 49ers kind of game against New England on Sunday, and won what could have been a very 49ers kind of Super Bowl.Dominate field possession. Commit no turnovers. Play physical, smart,My Sisters Keeper Movie Details - San Jose Mercury, tough, last-man standing football. Win 21-17, by imposing your will on the opponent.Sound like any Jim Harbaugh-coached team you know?All credit to the Giants,Warriors Mercury News Media Center, MVP Eli Manning, and coach Tom Coughlin, who repeated their Super Bowl glory from four years ago and are now 2-0 vs. the Patriots in the big game.But anybody who watched the 49ers closely this season knows that Sunday\'s game had the feel and crunch of a 49ers game.Super Bowl XLVI was a practical game -- not a showy one, that\'s for sure -- decided by many of the practical things the 49ers did best.Easy example: If Tom Brady struggled to put drives together against the Giants defense, he probably would\'ve had an even tougher time against the 49ers\' elite unit.Yes, if you swapped the 49ers for the Giants,hermes site officiel, the 49ers could have won the franchise\'s sixth Super Bowl, right there in Indianapolis.I know,borse louis vuitton, I\'d better stop right here and clarify some things.The two most ridiculous, reckless,borse burberry, impossible words in sports are: Could have. Anything could happen if you just twist the logic enough. We deal in what actually occurred, not in alternate sporting realities.(Too bad, because I think I can devise a plan that would send Mike Iupati back in time to save JFK.)The 49ers, of course, could have earned a Spot in the Super Bowl if they had defeated the Giants two weeks earlier at Candlestick Park.The 49ers could have and maybe should have beaten the Giants, if not for two botched punt returns, which still is a sensitive issue for fans and franchise.Still, one more play -- from a wide receiver, a running back, anybody -- and the 49ers would have won the NFC Championship game.But the 49ers didn\'t get that play, lost in overtime, and that was Manning raising the Lombardi Trophy at midfield, not Alex Smith.The 49ers were not meant to win. They didn\'t win. The Giants won.Still, the way the Giants outplayed New England was fascinating to watch -- like a boa constrictor, tightening up, tightening up, shoving New England to ever more dangerous Spots as the game wore on.Again, sounds fairly familiar.The Patriots\' best drive-start was their own 29-yard line, and that was in their second possession. That meant Brady had to go almost the full field every time he got the ball.Even better for the Giants, three of New England\'s nine possessions started inside its own 10-yard line.And when the Giants had the ball,A+E Interactive Archive for Gameboard, Manning was solid and they also ran it 28 times (for 114 yards) -- just effective enough to keep the Patriots pinned back.The Giants took advantage of the better field position,burberry borse outlet, and they didn\'t give New England any breaks.Manning threw 40 times, but I can\'t remember one pass that was anywhere close to an interception.That is Alex Smith\'s game, right there (except the 40 passes part).Meanwhile, the Giants put the ball on the ground a few times -- but they recovered their own fumbles in each instance.New England had to keep generating its own momentum and Brady was good enough to have the Patriots ahead through most of the second half.But when New England was driving into Giants territory, leading 17-15, Brady and Wes Welker couldn\'t connect on a deep pass.The Patriots had to punt, and that\'s when the script diverts a bit from the 49ers story.On the first play of that drive, with just under four minutes left,sac hermes pas cher, Manning arched a pass high and deep to Mario Manningham.Manningham, open by a half-step, made the play of the game to catch the ball as he was pushed out of bounds, for a 38-yard  to midfield.From there, the Giants were set up to win the Super Bowl.That was the kind of play that wins huge games -- and the play the 49ers could not make in the NFC Championship game.The Giants proved, again, that you can win a championship with blue-collar philosophies and the proper survival skills.The 49ers are  nicely to make the same kind of run in the next two or three seasons. They were Aligned nicely to do it this season, actually.But the Giants also proved that even if you play things perfectly, it usually takes one magic moment at the end.And while the Giants dance under confetti, the 49ers are still working on that last part.Read Tim Kawakami\'s Talking Points blog at . Contact him at or 408-920-5442. 
 
[WORDPRESS HASHCASH] The poster sent us \'0 which is not a hashcash value. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:234352:86320894</id><idPostId>86320894</idPostId><idBlogId>234352</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:234352</id><idBlogId>234352</idBlogId><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog</link><displayName>Wanton Wordsmith</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/</link><displayName>The day he went away</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T23:17:19.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:234352:86320894:328119819</id><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/#IDComment328119819</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T23:17:19.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The day he went away by wetgjjk2786n</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://nikefrchaussures.com/</link><idEmailMd5>d38ce04bd4984f60e6c8bc2a78799c14</idEmailMd5><displayName>wetgjjk2786n</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://nikefrchaussures.com/"&gt;wetgjjk2786n&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/"&gt;The day he went away&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>