<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m09to7/update/2012-04-02T00:39:03/1835e7ae0ad22870b48e72df52c8815580ba65deb321130281ffe6dddc1eede6</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Here’s what happens as predicted by ‘greenhouse gas theory’ when something much stronger than trace atmospheric gases is used:

     Initial surface temperature:  98.6°F

Most of the infrared emitted by this surface is then returned to the surface by our device much stronger than trace gases.   A little infrared leaks out.   The theory has it that the surface MUST absorb the ‘back radiated’ infrared, driving the surface temperature up because of the need to reject this extra Heat:

     Temperature after first  back:  222°F   (above boiling)

Theoretically, the extra infrared rejected is itself returned to the surface (most of it), driving temperature even higher:

     Temperature after second :  248°F

This “trapped light” goes back and forth, leaking a little out each time until it’s all gone, and the temperature settles:

     Settled temperature after 15th Bounce:  302°F   (roasting!)

The surface:   Your face
The device:    A bathroom mirror

If you ‘believe’ the ‘greenhouse gas effect’ exists at all, you must ‘believe’ you can Burn your face with your own reflection in the mirror.   If so, I’d like to sell you some fireproof shaving cream.

The flaw?   Light is not Heat.   Heating by ‘back radiation’ from a source cooler or even the same temperature as the surface would violate the Second Law of Thermodynamics.   The effect is not small - it is zero.

Real greenhouses?   They work not because the walls and roof are clear and absorb infrared, but because they are clear and solid.   NO gas can do that.   The belief in 'greenhouse gases' makes as much sense as 'fart darts,' yet greenies are terrified of both.

Fortunately, actual science does not require belief.   Science is experiment, which you can repeat for yourself.   Give it a try.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67lb8m</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rrah</id></website><link>http://cnsnews.com/node/529826</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:57:25+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T04:39:03+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m09to7</id><link>http://cnsnews.com/node/529826#comment-483285903</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ygemr</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>