<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3vpr5/post/2012-03-29T09:08:08</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Good debate!

Gareth - thanks for the clarification. 

The change from plan to policy as noted by Kerron is very relevant.

I am completely flabbergasted by Badil's response. Yes - South Africa (through the DTI and DOC and financial support from Canada) started looking at the issue in 2000/2001. However since then the research has not been published and no progress has been made. In fact the Minister of Communications has yet to promulgate the ICT policy called for in the ECT Act, almost 10 years late.

To suggest that this is "making progress" is ludicrous. As I operate on an international level, I can confirm that South Africa is losing or possibly has already lost its prominence in the Internet Governance space, which is now dominated by Kenya - successful hosts of the 2011 IGF and thought leaders for our continent.

South Africa has become a Faint echo of the ITU, with no original thought or leadership emanating from the South. If this continues, it seems likely our Honourable Communication Minister will return from the BRICS gathering echoing the policy pronouncements of the BRIC states, as if SA has no opinion of its own.

Guess whose research paper I am NOT planning on buying?</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hynco</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/xt55</id></website><link>http://www.itweb.co.za/index.php?option=com_content&amp;view=article&amp;id=53022</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T10:01:35+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:08:08+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3vpr5</id><link>http://www.itweb.co.za/index.php?option=com_content&amp;view=article&amp;id=53022#comment-479475040</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>