<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkmdot/delete/2012-03-25T01:08:37</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkauih</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zyyhj</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Debt-ridden socialist state! Laughable. Nice rhetoric sir! Speaking of High School, any history classes in that period of your life? It's one thing to have the classes, but it is another to grasp it's content, isn't it?
Historically, the Conservative Governments of Canada have been the ones making stupid decisions when it came to spending. Remember the Mulroney years? People who where in the Forces remember that time pretty well I hope. Annual budget deficits ballooned to record levels, Reaching $42 billion in his last year of office. This, back then, was damn close to being 100% of the GDP. I have proof to back my claims as it is historically accurate. That is a hell lot more than all the retarded diatribes Vomited by a bunch of buffoons who could not even tell you who where the last five Prime ministers in the right order without having to look it up first. Shame on you for your lack of memory and national pride. Shame on you for your lack of judgment. Shame on you for not being able to educate yourself. Shame on you for believing the Neo-Fascist propaganda machine that is SUN news. Shame on you for falling into the disinformation pit. Next step is believing that Mankind herded Dinosaurs or that Satan planted the fossils to tempt the sinners we scientifically minded people are.</body><verb>delete</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66phc0</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zsj8</id></website><link>http://www.torontosun.com/2012/03/24/no-winner-on-first-ndp-ballot</link><postedTime>2012-03-24T14:47:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-25T05:08:37+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkmdot</id><link>http://www.torontosun.com/2012/03/24/no-winner-on-first-ndp-ballot#comment-475669313</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z843y</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>killed</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>