<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwkn9k/update/2012-03-31T09:49:21/b93271eddafcc70029b8701e20e44ba5e8475da409ea14f2b85a9587a938c08b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>    It amazes me, it stupefies me that some people feel the Trayvon Martin case is the product of the “black racial services machine” or is a tool of “race hustlers”. So-called “free range thinkers” laud the discovery that most black victims of crime are the victims of black criminals.  It has been pointed out to relieve white people of charges that they are in this day and age inflicting criminal havoc upon blacks in black neighborhoods. It is not a sociological or criminological revelation. Elevated levels of crime have been associated with poverty in every ethnic demographic throughout history. And statistically, most white victims of crime are similarly victimized by other whites. Wow, see how smart I am.
    What the above phenomena demonstrates is the strange dichotomy in the conservative black mind. When the subject of Israel comes up on this site, the overwhelming majority position is support for the Jewish state, and the usual reason, apart from religious mythology, is Jewish history, particularly the Holocaust. Israeli stridency is usually supported because people understand and agree they should “never forget”. But when it comes to blacks in America, for some reason the strange psychology is that they “shouldn’t remember”. When the Holocaust was over, Jim Crow was operating at full speed – remember?
    The shock and amazement that millions of still living people were jolted from their pleasant reveries in our post-racial utopia by an incident too reminiscent of the bad old days when the grim reaper was assigned to harvest people guilty of being black in the wrong place, is mystifying. Just forget. Just forget.
    What about the conservative hissy fit when Rev. Jeremiah Wright mentioned from his pulpit the Tuskegee Experiment. Was he, are we allowed to remember that? What about the Cincinnati Experiments? Or the Oakridge Experiment? What about Carver Village GA, an exclusively black community, where in 1960 the Army Chemical Corps deliberately dispersed mosquitoes with yellow Fever and dengue Fever to test the results on a population? Fevers, bronchitis, typhoid, encephalitis, still births and other mysterious deaths, all must be forgotten. What about the 200 black women who were given the drug Dilantin without their knowledge or consent in an experiment to see its effect in women having cesarean section deliveries? Did that occur back in the olden days? That all Depends, was 1988 the olden days? So why was Rev. Wright castigated for mentioning the speculation of some that AIDS was purposely introduced into traditionally despised communities? Is it that far-fetched or inconceivable in light of past history? Awkward memories be gone!
    I am not saying our society hasn’t changed, or that there aren’t more opportunities and freedom.  I’m just exploring the question of why black conservatives have such a pathological need to “forget”.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67q31z</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gyz4</id></website><link>http://www.bookerrising.net/2012/03/open-thread-friday_30.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T02:50:51+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T13:49:21+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwkn9k</id><link>http://www.bookerrising.net/2012/03/open-thread-friday_30.html#comment-481843399</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>