<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3khou/post/2012-03-29T22:23:36</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I was recently in a hospital for a severely broken leg.  After surgery, hospital staff was concerned that I might have a clot because of pain I was having and also because of my leg feeling Cold.  I believe I was checked with 3 things....an X-ray, CT-Scan, and an ultrasound, none of which, fortunately, found anything.

I am no doctor and do not know which one of these 3 tests, if any, is the best or most important, but perhaps this lady wasn't given all tests she could get to detect a clot.....maybe that CT-Scan might have shown something.  If I had to guess, I'd say a CT-scan is probably the  most expensive of the tests.

Just seems odd that she died so quickly after just being checked in this hospital and they did not find anything.  Maybe the fact that I have insurance meant that I was given a CT-Scan while she was not because she did not have insurance?  Really don't know, but it's quite sad she died, especially in this manner.  If lack of insurance prevented her from a full Battery of tests, then this is a further indictment of the lack of universal healthcare in this country.

I live in the St. Louis area, and I do believe St. Mary's actually does have a good reputation, so I don't know what went wrong. (I was treated at a different hospital). </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zfizf</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cusm</id></website><link>http://www.rawstory.com/rs/2012/03/29/woman-arrested-for-trespassing-in-hospital-dies-in-jail/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:05:42+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:23:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3khou</id><link>http://www.rawstory.com/rs/2012/03/29/woman-arrested-for-trespassing-in-hospital-dies-in-jail/#comment-480154775</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hd7z</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>