<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3immx/update/2012-03-29T21:08:42/da2075a0923e72bfbf06296796545fdf2f7234f78e2cc2356bc333aab0867fd1</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msjnw5</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ly5q2</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>The  sum of all of the considerable scientific research from the investigation of the incidence and distribution of life on Earth has conclusively determined unanimously that life occurs in virtually any and every environment with the very least conditions to support its existence, including at fiery hydrothermal vents in the oceans, in no-light marine and subterranean locations, in the harshest and most desolate hot and Cold deserts and low-oxygen mountain elevations, in prehistoric lakes or water beneath the poles, in chemically adverse environments (including severely radioactive and toxic environments), ad infinitum.  That is, the overall finding is that life is tremendously (indeed, incredibly) hardy and adaptive and fills and occupies, in some form, any environment, however generally inhospitable to life, in which it can survive or to which it can adapt and survive.  Logically, the compelling extrapolation from this scientific knowledge -- the facts -- is that where the conditions conducive to or supportive of the vast diversity of life as we know it on Earth also exist on other celestial bodies beyond our planet, life as we know it will most probably be present under those conditions or the minimally adequate least of them, favorable to the existence of life, regardless of our current insufficient knowledge of the biogenic minutia accounting for the origin of life.  The latter will come.  

We will have science with a moral compass or science without a moral compass and the resulting social, political and environmental impacts of whichever we chose between these two options.  Science and scientists are not above moral consciousness and conscience, as there have been psychopathy and grievous irresponsibility in science and among scientists and perpetrated by these in the past to date.  Rather moral consciousness and conscience must be an ever present integral part of science work and the work of scientists and engineers.  They contribute significantly to all-around, universal good human relations and diplomacy as well as such harmony.  Physics greats Niels Bohr, Albert Einstein and Robert Oppenheimer spoke out on the necessity of moral consciousness and conscience in science and the great harm of their absence from science.  The psychologist Kenneth B. Clark wrote an essay counseling scientists to introspect fully their otherwise unexamined personal, or shadowy, motives and objectives for their research and science so as to avoid unwittingly, where applicable, biasing or misapplying their science work.  Of course, there are cognitively gifted and highly educated individuals who couldn't give a damn about moral (but even scorn) moral consciousness and  conscience in science and bellow that they have no place in science thinking and work, and hold them irrelevant as regards other people or social outsiders, like the A-bomb and H-bomb physicist and enthusiast Edward Teller, Nazi rocket designer and engineer Wernher von Braun and Nazi medical researcher Josef Mengele, M.D. 

Now that I have declared the scientific basis of my wagering (confident) hypothesis, it remains to be tested.  I assure you that this is not exclusively my hypothesis but that NASA and many in the science community share it and are most eager, or in a frenzy, to explore, data collect on and test it.  Given the stingy budget imposed on NASA for timely and aggressive space exploration -- in this case, follow-up exploration -- NASA should consider R&amp;D for low-expense, mini spacecraft (maybe all-frills laptop-computer size, if feasible) that can double as in-situ satellite submarines and hover craft, in the case of Enceladus, to scientific data collect and video take and transmit findings data and video stream continuously back to NASA, ESA &amp; JAXA, etc., long term.

With regard to the possibility of present-time life on Mars, such is a realistic possibility in its underground based on the uncertain-pointing evidence that methane gas clearly emanates from Martian ground seasonally.  NASA scientists have explained that methane gas is often the product of active biochemical processes but is also produced on occasion by geological processes, accounting in part for the uncertainty of the source of the methane.  However, the seasonality of the methane emanations suggests cyclicity that is non-geologic but organic, to my judgment.  The body of knowledge on the distribution of life on Earth has also found microbes that live and thrive in the absence of oxygen and complex life forms that reside in caves, caverns, other hollows, and lakes and streams deep in isolating rock formations and underground, including bacteria and fungi of all kinds, millipedes, centipedes, spiders, a variety of insects, scorpions, crayfish, fish, newts and more.  As our exploratory spacecraft have confirmed the presence of water ice at the poles of Mars and in the soil, or dirt of the surface of Mars, and their examination of the gouged terrain and craters of the surface of Mars indicate the effects of major bodies of past water and salt on the surface of Mars, there is a good chance that there may be water or seasonally sublimating ice water supportive of life as we know it in the underground of Mars, possibly consisting of a substantial portion of the indicated  liquid water long gone from the surface of Mars.  Possibly some of the past life forms, or related species, that once may have lived on the surface of Mars survive underground presently.      

It's time to get back to my picnic. 

I have taken the time to respond to your comment in appreciation and recognition of the intellectual honesty and sincere scientific dialog expressed in your comment.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h5u42</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tckh</id></website><link>http://www.universetoday.com/94344/snowing-microbes-on-saturns-moon/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T05:45:23+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:08:42+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3immx</id><link>http://www.universetoday.com/94344/snowing-microbes-on-saturns-moon/#comment-480099585</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8jfd0</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>