<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwlvl7/post/2012-03-30T12:58:55</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwgber</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rq1ou</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Really, I could care less about the airline industry and their problems.  Let the free market decide on the proper price of flights and fees.

And excuse my misspellings - I'm an engineer, not an english teacher.  Why don't you go attack drunk sailor for his horrible grammar.  Oh, that's right, he's one of your union buddies.

My beef is with the unions - at any company.  The don't get paid based  their worth, their skills, or their quality.  They get based purely Off their demands.  How is this even remotely fair to the rest of the country?  It's not.  They do not deserve anything they get - they didn't earn it.

In my 12 years in the defense industry, I've worked around many groups of people who do approximately the same work - aircraft manufacturing and maintenance.  This ranges from techs in the military, techs in the ANG, unions at the factory, and salaried techs.

Want to know who does the best work?  The salaried techs, followed by the active duty, then the ANG, and then lastly the union ones.  The salary techs and most in the military love their jobs and want to learn and do well for themselves and their country.  The ANG is interested in learning and getting the work done, if it's only to hurry up and be done.  But the union guys - they could care less about anything.  All they want to do is sit around and BS.  They only want to work or learn if they have to - and then they're going to pout, complain, and stall as much as they can.  They are vampires on society.

Want to know who gets paid the most?  The salaried ones, followed by the unions, then the ANG, and lastly the active duty guys.  Do this seem fair?  The salaried guys work hard, love their jobs, and deserve every cent they make.  But the unions, who are the crappies guys I work around, get mapid more than the other people who do the same - no, better - work as they do.

Those are Cold hard facts.  Care to explain why we as a society should live with this situation?  It's dispicible, and I can't sit around and just let them get away with it.  I tell everybody I know about this scenario when it comes up.  The unions get 3% raises every year no matter what.  The salaried guys get performance reviews and are paid based on their work skills and performance.  Why not the unions?  Because they're losers who will do anything to hide behind the threat of strike.  Prove to America otherwise - you can't ebcause I'm right.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h0hv2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnmw</id></website><link>http://www.star-telegram.com/2012/03/28/3843318/amr-details-reasons-to-break-union.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T01:50:50+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:58:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwlvl7</id><link>http://www.star-telegram.com/2012/03/28/3843318/amr-details-reasons-to-break-union.html#comment-480951231</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5h1fz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>