<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwl3fo/post/2012-03-30T13:20:46</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I am a 45 yr old female who thinks I may have 1 or both of these diseases. I have been seeing a psychologist for almost 3 yrs now and he thinks I have both of these but can't diagnose me, as he is not trained to give me such a diagnosis. He recommended I see a psychiatrist but I have no insurance. I am able to see the psychologist through my fiance's insurance for couples counseling. Through our sessions, it made me think back to my childhood and "SNAP"....wow, this has been going on since then....it all makes sense!!!! The more I think about it, different new quirks come up. I've been fighting Anxiety and depression (treated) since my early 20's. In school, I aced home economics, music &amp; majorettes but failed miserably in history, geography, english  etc. I was easily distracted and couldn't listen for any length of time. It took, and still takes me, forever to comprehend a sentence. As I write this, my leg is jumping a mile a minute. I am extremely visual.....DON"T GIVE ME INSTRUCTIONS TO READ..PLEASE JUST SHOW ME!!! I have the attention span of a golf ball. When I do try to read, I find myself going to the end of the sentence first and not the beginning. I would rather watch a true story on TV rather than trying to read the book....I get Anxiety when I read as it is VERY frustrating. When driving in the car, I find myself looking at the telephone poles and tapping as the middle of each one comes up. When looking at words, I  try to find a common letter in them. My hands  need to be doing something. I can be at the computer, playing games or whatever, and my legs just go and go. I then find that I need to go have a cigarette...as if the constant use of the mouse isn't enough for my hands to be doing. I have a hand to mouth fixation. I am an alcoholic but haven't drank for many years. Throughout those years, I drank at least a case of beer a day. Heaven forbid I had my glass empty. Now, I find that I will over abuse drinking water or any other liquids I may consume. I don't like change in my life. I have become a hermit. I feel alone in this and am Reaching out for help. Most of the time I am emotionless but then come the days where I am extremely angry or sad. I just want to be normal...whatever that is. If there is anyone out there that may have some advice for me.....I AM ALL EARS!!!!!!!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/8djwrd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/deo8</id></website><link>http://www.additudemag.com/adhd/article/6113.html</link><postedTime>2010-08-31T09:05:15+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:20:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwl3fo</id><link>http://www.additudemag.com/adhd/article/6113.html#comment-480973744</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2010-08-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>