<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m17x0l/update/2012-03-13T12:08:39/6f77af8a226b2a73dc408dc5d17a69dd076530bd9a05e7df22afe0e8f66e1201</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m1zn5c</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8817j</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Uh ... apparently this will come as news to you. The American Enterprise Institute? Right wing think tank - tax exempt. The Heritage Institute? Right wing think tank - tax exempt. The Catholic church? Right wing institute for navel gazing, not necessarily their own. The plethora of non-Catholic religious institutes ranging from Mormonism to those folks who  military funerals? All tax exempt. 

The problem with going after MMFA, CAP &amp; other such lefty orgs for their tax exempt status is that it threatens to kill the golden goose. So - note that the Daily Caller attack on MMFA. Yes, it's framed in terms of going after the tax exempt status, but it's really meant to tie in with the funding of MMFA from George Soros. If you look at, say, the Cato Institute, that's heavily funded *Cough* pretty much owned *Cough* by the Kochies, but it's run on a business model. The needle hole that widdew Tuckster Calrson is trying to thread is an equivalence: going after SELECTED tax exempt orgs based on the idea that a. they are fronts for wealthy business types, &amp; b. fronts for wealthy business types should not be granted exempt status. 

It's a dangerous line, so dangerous it might never have been launched by widdew Tuckster in the first place - had it not been for another factor that renders the attack even more narrowly calculated. As we know, the Daily Caller really a widdew Tuckster enterprise at all: it's an attempt at an Bizarro World replication of the Daily Beast, with some Huffington Post &amp; Talking Points Memo thrown in - in the tradition of how the Pajamas Media project tried, &amp; failed dismally, to ape the mostly organic lefty blogosphere. One of the major differences from the Pajamas Media failed experiment is that the Daily Caller model pulls from specific winger governmental &amp; money resources: in this specific case, from the neocon base that surrounds Dick Cheney as to the former, and from long-time winger cause moneybags Foster Freiss as to the latter.

Yes, the same FF who's funding the Santorum campaign, but one thing about FF that should be understood better is that he's ALWAYS been a front for the military-industrial complex that Cheney is connected to. FF made his money from the Armour Group - the folks that made out like bandits on US government military contracts while ironically stiffing the troops on body armour. This same group is tied tight as a drum to the confluence of Middle Eastern oil sheik interests of oil &amp; security - who are in turn major backers of FNC. Thus, it's easy to see why many regard widdew Tuckster's Daily Caller as really nothing more than a cut-out for FNC &amp; the neocons - because that's exactly what it was designed as. 

In the particular case of the Daily Caller attack on MMFA, then, the focus on tax exempt status is cover (I should maybe use "was cover", because the attack seems to have died, partly I'm sure for lack of interest, but mostly for it being replaced by what's thought to be far safer ground: choosing up sides in the Fluke-Limbaugh "debate") for something else entirely: the Murdoch family's Anxiety about what's happening now in the U.K., &amp; soon will be coming to America, with the NewsCorps wholly-owned sub in the U.K., NewsInternational. Just now, the breaking news is a raft of fresh arrests, &amp; for the first time actual charges: in the case of the highest ranking NI officer outside the Murdoch family, Rebekah Brooks, arrested this morning, along with her husband - a BFF of Brit PM David Cameron - &amp; charged with obstruction of justice (I'm guessing in relation to ordering the destruction of internal NI memos in the context of official investigation, among other crimes.). 

The 'good' news for the Murdoch is that the big buzz right now is all about other things: Fluke-Limbaugh, gas prices, Afghanistan, the GOP clown car race; &amp; that means MMFA is focusing on those things, not the Murdoch Downfall saga. The 'bad' news is that MMFA's status as a public utility is only being enhanced by its concentration on those same subjects, in particular on Fluke-Limbaugh, &amp; that by that, MMFA has effectively immunized itself from that goofy Tuckster-as-FNC-cut-out attack. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/68lfs2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tz1k</id></website><link>http://www.mediaite.com/online/memo-shows-96-national-companies-want-their-ads-pulled-from-limbaughs-show/</link><postedTime>2012-03-12T20:42:58+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-13T16:08:39+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m17x0l</id><link>http://www.mediaite.com/online/memo-shows-96-national-companies-want-their-ads-pulled-from-limbaughs-show/#comment-464302344</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7zl7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-12</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>