<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3cjgq/update/2012-03-28T18:54:06/20064995606130cf1f29454dc9749912b22539f30cd2344e5e810b5f742ddb66</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3a5wf</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ept1k</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>"We can have different opinions, but we can't have different facts".

There are (4) original race groups: (Black; south), (White; north), (Red; west), and (Yellow; east).


*(Black people's contributions to the world):

(We Never Needed Anybody for Anything, they Needed us, and Still do).

1). Agriculture: Began in the (Fertile Crescent), aka the (Cradle of Civilization) between the (9th-7th millennium B.C.E) in (Mesopotamia).

2). Alphabet: The (1st) pure alphabet emerged in the (2nd millennium B.C.E) in (ancient Egypt).

3). Ancient Egyptian Philosophy: (Ptahhotep), was an (ancient Egyptian) official during the late (25th century B.C.E). He is considered the very (1st) philosopher in virtue of having the earliest and surviving fragments of moral philosophy; ("The Maxims of Ptahhotep").

4). Art: The oldest art objects in the world are a series of tiny, drilled snail shells, around the year (73,000 B.C.E), that were discovered in a (South African) cave.

5). Calendar: Created in (ancient Egypt) based on the (Lunar Cycle) of (12 months), consisting of (30 days) each, comprising of a year, with the year beginning on the (Nile River's Inundation). 
The (5) days added at a later date, were to synchronize somewhat with the (Tropical Year).
In (238 B.C.E), the Greek ruler of Egypt, (Ptolemy III Euergetes), ordered an additional day to be added to every (4th year). 
It wasn’t until (25 B.C.E), when the (1st) Roman Emperor (Augustus) introduced it, that it was effectively implemented into the calender.

6). Chess: (Senet), was created in the (3rd millennium B.C.E) in (ancient Egypt), which is the oldest board game known to have existed. Senet is an old ancestor of chess.

7). Civilization: Historically, (Mesopotamia) between the (7th-4th millennium B.C.E) is given credit as the (Cradle of Civilization). 
Between the (24th-22nd millennium B.C.E), gave rise to the (Akkadian Empire), which is widely regarded as the (1st Empire) in history.

8). Democracy: Democratic practices started in (Mesopotamia) around the (5th millennium B.C.E).

9). Domestication of Animals: Around (30,000 B.C.E), the (Dog) was the (1st) to be domesticated, which took place in (Africa and East Asia).

10). Economy: Around the (2nd millennium B.C.E), the (Babylonians) and their neighboring city states, developed the earliest system of economics as we think of, in terms of rules/laws on debt, legal contracts, and law codes relating to business practices, and private property. 
They developed the (1st) known codified legal and administrative systems, complete with courts, jails, and government records.

11). Engineering: The earliest civil engineer known by name is (Imhotep). 
He designed and supervised the construction of the Pyramid of Djoser at Saqqara in (ancient Egypt) around (2,630-2,611 B.C.E). He is responsible for the (1st) known use of columns in architecture.

12). Law: The history of law is closely connected to the development of civilization. (Ancient Egyptian) law, dating as far back as the (3rd millennium B.C.E), contained a civil code that was probably broken into (12 books). It was based on the concept of Ma'at, characterized by tradition, rhetorical speech, social equality and impartiality.

13). Literature: The history of literature begins with the invention of writing, in the (4th millennium B.C.E) in (Mesopotamia and ancient Egypt).
The (ancient Egyptians) were the (1st) culture to develop literature as we know it today, that is, the (Book), in the (4th millennium B.C.E).

14). Mathematics: Egyptian mathematics is the mathematics that were developed and used in (ancient Egypt) from the (3rd millennium B.C.E) to (300 B.C.E) for arithmetic, algebra and geometry for taxation and other financial calculations, for building and construction, and for astronomy.

15). Mining: Mining of (Gold, Tin, Copper, and other metals) began in (ancient Egyptians).

16). Paper: Paper is derived from (Papyrus), which is a thick paper-like material produced from the pith of the papyrus plant. (Ancient Egypt) used this plant as a writing material as well as for other things in the (3rd millennium B.C.E).
*(China), around the (2nd century B.C.E).

17). Petroleum: In the (2nd millennium B.C.E), according to (Herodotus and Diodorus Siculus), (Asphalt) was used in the construction of the walls and towers of (Babylon); there were oil pits near Ardericca (near Babylon), and a pitch spring on Zacynthus. Great quantities of it were found on the banks of the river Issus, one of the tributaries of the Euphrates. 
Ancient Persian tablets indicate the medicinal and lighting uses of petroleum in the upper levels of their society.

18). Spiritual Systems: The (Pyramid Texts) from (ancient Egypt) are possibly the oldest known religious texts in the world, dating back to the (3rd millennium B.C.E).

19). Stethoscope: Created in (ancient Egypt) around the (5th century B.C.E). 
In (1816), (René Laennec), a French physician, received a patent for the stethoscope.

20). Wheel: Evidence of wheeled vehicles appear in the mid (4th millennium B.C.E) in (Mesopotamia, the Northern Caucasus, and Central Europe).

21). Writing: Developed in (Mesopotamia and ancient Egypt) in the (4th millennium B.C.E). 


In Comparison:

*(White people's contributions to the world):

1). (Crime):
Kidnapping
Murder
Robbery

2). (Drug):
LSD aka Acid 
Methamphetamine

3). (Disease):
Aids
Black Death
Bubonic Plague
Gonorrhea
Scarlet Fever
Syphilis
Tuberculosis

4). (Hate):
Alligator Bait
Apartheid
Atlantic Slave Trade
Black Codes
Casual Slave Killing 
Confederacy
Fugitive Slave 
Genocide
Indian Removal Act 
Indian Reservations
Jim Crow Laws
Ku Klux Klan
Nazism
Racism

5). (Sexual Behavior):
Beastealilty
Child Sexual Abuse
Homosexuality
Incest
Rape

*Now ask yourself, who's the real problem here? </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hqaeg</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ewhe</id></website><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/the-dish/hunger-games-fans-outraged-over-black-characters.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T16:38:37+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T22:54:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3cjgq</id><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/the-dish/hunger-games-fans-outraged-over-black-characters.php#comment-478865719</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zrvev</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>