<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ewsug6/update/2012-01-26T10:13:06/fdc5fb84f9f9cc4efd4ad1f92525cc9fd9fc5ce0a2140b90e45967567e34bf09</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I have a very old home built in 1910 and updated in the mid sixties by my Father, very limited closet space.  I purchased a canvas shoe holder with mesh pockets, has twelve pockets, hung the holder on the back of my door to the basement in my kitchen.
A wonderful way to organize your most used items in the kitchen, cost was twelve dollars, you can find this item in any Walmart, K-mart, less expensive version in dollar stores.  Also added this idea on the inside of the bathroom to hold my hair styling items, cleaning items for the bathroom, essential bathroom items.  In my tiney  way I do have a closet with shelves for linens, towels, etc.  I hung the canvas shoe holder with mesh pockets and created a emergencey center, organized each row with the most helpful items.  Bandages to fit the injury, items to cleanse the injury, excellent items to add , ie, Cold packs, bee stings, remove splinters, sun exposure, cuts, scrapes, and Burns, etc.  All purpose first aid station, very easy to use, open the closet door and Reach all needed items, have the person sit on the closed toilet, next to the sink, have found a wonderful way to work with first aid.  I am a retired nurse, and organization is the key to work it all out!  In my upstairs added the shoe holders on the back of the bedroom doors, have them set up for anything a guest may need in the guest room, one room is used for crafts and have a knitting center on the back of one door. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/5r6plv</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/y30t</id></website><link>http://www.cozi.com/live-simply/best-tips-cleaning-organizing-kitchen</link><postedTime>2011-03-23T04:52:33+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-01-26T15:13:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ewsug6</id><link>http://www.cozi.com/live-simply/best-tips-cleaning-organizing-kitchen#comment-421426990</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>