<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ewngkn/update/2012-01-25T15:47:59/dc6d83a796a4cd1c86c5125065207f6cca735e52f2e3c00f073d48101953fbf7</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ewt6lf</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/r6jxu</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>absolutely Spot on, in my opinion. As a person who just stepped  of the CTA (and am using my smartphone, as a matter of fact) I can say that this info is definitely skewed. Based strictly on the clouds represented here, I suspect there's a serious lack of "tweets" emanating from less affluent parts of town.  Maybe people in the sections don't tweet, or maybe they are used to service interruptions and don't think it's something to tweet about. 
I'm going to let you all in on a -slash-broad generalization:
In Chicago ([like a lot of Metros, I imagine], in our more affluent areas, there's a higher concentration of folks who are not from Chicago. Especially younger folks (you know, the type that are early adopters of smartphones and stuff).
 Not as much of "Da Bears" accent here... these folks are from some hamlet somewhere, or perhaps grew up in the Rust Belt. They might even live in a loft. This whole "El" situation is perhaps also fairly new, as the list of Cities with such a behemoth transit system is short in the States. 
 In less affluent areas, people are not only more likely to have lived in Chicago for most of their lives (love those new Census numbers!) they are also, I propose, more likely to be used to "a huge fire" or "downed trees" inconveniencing them. You know... Acts of God/Nature/et al... Because they're keenly familiar with the triumphs and trappings of a huge transit system serving a million and a half people a day.
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/y5fzzu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/xmw5</id></website><link>http://www.theatlanticcities.com/commute/2012/01/i-hate-blue-line-and-other-things-transit-can-learn-twitter/1040/</link><postedTime>2012-01-25T13:31:01+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-01-25T20:47:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ewngkn</id><link>http://www.theatlanticcities.com/commute/2012/01/i-hate-blue-line-and-other-things-transit-can-learn-twitter/1040/#comment-420844736</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l1qxu</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-01-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>