<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwdvi1/update/2012-03-30T09:57:13/06678b1aae6e1315ad602da62ee7686f9b9336befe35262f16c2c9ab900902b6</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmadq</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/heu9e</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Sam: Okay...fair points---Let' take them on: 

1.) The police summarized the witnesses report--they interviewed him in person and took his statement at length. You only saw him stuttering on camera for the first time in his life. The police have the full story and they corroborated it with their own observations.

2.) No. The young black kid that saw it said Zimmerman was on the bottom calling for help and Trayvon was atop him...This came out in his stuttering interview--but again, the police have the fuller story and it appears to confirm Zimmerman's account.

3.) Not quite. The video was enlarged and clearly shows a vertical scar running down the back of Zimmerman's head.  But it's awfully decent and fairminded of you to admit that a video is a poor example and hardly conclusive--yet the Justice for Trayvon crowd insists it's sufficient evidence to post a reward for Zimmerman's capture--dead or alive.

However, the testimony of the medics on scene and the police--both on scene--and at the station also appear to confirm--injuries to face and scalp. Let's all dismiss the video if you want--the eyewitness examination of police and medics cannot be easily dismissed--they were there to see the wounds and these race hustlers and so-called experts were not.

4.) One of the investigators wanted to charge him with manslaughter--that is quite different from 1st or even 2nd degree murder. Yet, Zimmerman has been called a Cold blooded murderer and a racist, to boot. 

But investigators don't get to decide the validity of a case--prosecutors do that. He's a cop--not a lawyer...And the prosecutor made the call--as is his job. It matters not a whit if all the cops on the force wanted to charge George--they didn't by the way--most felt his story was consistent with the facts. Still, name me a single instance where a lone cop gets to prosecute a criminal case? 

5.) You're wrong about the Grand jury--the DA's office had never used a Grand Jury to indict a murder case before--they admitted publicly they'd Always did the heavylifting themselves in the past. If a Grand Jury in now convened--it was due to political pressure that's been put on them to do so. What's fair about that? You shouldn't be tried by politicians with their finger in the wind and an unelected press---but by professional prosecutors and judges. This reeks of political interference in our criminal justice system. That's not good.

6.) You're repeating yourself. The investigator didn't chrge Zimmerman with anything--because he couldn't make his case to the DA. End of story. Zimmerman didn't escape on a technicality--the investigator had no case that could pass prosecutorial review. Thus, no arrest was justified.

7.) We had no witnesses to the OJ killings.That's entirely irrelevant. But of course, people are condemniing a man that hasn't even been charged with a crime--much less found guilty of anything. 

And the witness that did step forward has confirmed that Trayvon was atop Zimmerman and beating him. He even called it in to police and they have his additional statement.

Sam., you sound like a very reasonable guy. But I think you're the lone voice on the Left currently defending Trayvon so reasonably.  Everyone else is screaming for Zimmerman's blood...Are you sure you want to associate yourself with some of these jackoffs and race hustlers?  

He deserves a fair trial and the presumption of innocence until proven guilty in a court of law--and not to be lynched in the court of public opinion by the media and the usual suspects on the Left.... Do you dispute that?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z7h1s</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q0fi</id></website><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/29/latino-organizations-dismiss-george-zimmerman-question-his-ethnicity/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:50:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:57:13+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwdvi1</id><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/29/latino-organizations-dismiss-george-zimmerman-question-his-ethnicity/#comment-480765264</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/az6hu</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>