<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/323728/post/127798188/comment/327570418</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This post has gone on for far too long. It needs a Halftime Report. Here goes nothing.&#13; 
&#13; 
&amp;quot;A Defense of Red Eye&amp;quot;&#13; 
&#13; 
I think you are giving yourself far too much credit. What do I mean by that? First of all you are treating this like some magnificent scandal you&amp;#039;ve uncovered, which, of course, it is far from. Second you appear to be ungrateful that the show exists. One of the main things that bugs me about Red Eye fans (of whose number I am a part) is the complaining. Constant complaining. &amp;quot;This guest is stupid&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;That joke wasn&amp;#039;t funny&amp;quot; or even, as you quote the guys from the podcast (which by the way, was the best Red Eye podcast in a while), &amp;nbsp;&amp;quot;I would be a better guest than XYZ&amp;quot;. That really bugs me. It won&amp;#039;t keep me from watching the show, I love it too much. However I can&amp;#039;t help but cringe every time I read one of those complainy tweets. And I&amp;#039;ll tell you why. The guys have  said they are incredibly lucky to even have this time-slot. In a podcast which discussed fame, Greg made the point that he doesn&amp;#039;t want to be famous, or to be a big voice, or even to have a show in primetime. That spoke, I thought, directly to your petition which, although well-intentioned, was really not going anywhere. If anything Greg would say no to the opportunity to do Red Eye at 5 PM, 10 PM, 11 PM, or whatever time people suggested in the many conversations about Red Eye and its timeslot provoked by your article. So, from the standpoint of &amp;quot;Well, Greg doesn&amp;#039;t really want to do Red Eye at any time other than 3 AM, given the facts that the ratings have been higher than ever *at that timeslot* and that Greg has said he doesn&amp;#039;t want to be too well-known, or as well-known as, say, a Beck or an O&amp;#039;reilly&amp;quot;, I have to say that your complaint that the guys never overtly recognized your Open Letter To Fox is not worth making, for the reasons I have laid out.&#13; 
&#13; 
NOW: Your &amp;nbsp;un-necessarily brutal analysis of the show, of Greg, of Andy, and even of Bill is completely wrong. So much that you said is wrong I don&amp;#039;t know where to begin. (and please keep in mind I say none of this mean-spiritedly) You say Bill doesn&amp;#039;t even read the Red Eye feed anymore, as if he&amp;#039;s alienating his fans by his ignoring the feed. Rubbish. The fans have alienated themselves. One thing you should learn about the Red Eye guys is that they have people on whom they respect and like. So whoever is bothering you on the show, just understand one thing: the guys respect and like them AS A PERSON. Now I also see the negative tweets stemming from an idea that all conservatives must be smart and all liberals must be dumb. An example: John DeVore and/or Anna Gilligan. Two, i think, very liberal people. Yet here they are. They disagree with Greg and Andy all the time but we expect it because they are liberal, and we don&amp;#039;t say bad things about them. But with Kayleigh Mcenany, it is different. We see three conservative people (Baker, Schappert, Amd Mcenany) on Red Eye and we expect them to agree. Why? Because we are conditioned to expect people who have the same basic ideology, who are coming from the same political standpoint, to see eye to eye on everything. Why? I don&amp;#039;t know. &amp;quot;But Tom! But Tom! Baker and Schappert are military experts! She is just a strategist!&amp;quot; So she can&amp;#039;t have an opinion? That&amp;#039;s what Red Eye is about. Showing you multiple sides of an issue. Heck, maybe this segment would have been boring if someone hadn&amp;#039;t challenged Baker or Schappert. Not because what they said was wrong, that&amp;#039;s for you to judge, but the conversation, the discussion is worth it. &amp;quot;But Tom! But Tom! I don&amp;#039;t want to hear someone I disagree with!&amp;quot; What can I say? Fox is fair and balanced. It isn&amp;#039;t MSNBC where everyone agrees and disagrees on the little things. Sometimes like minded people disagree about big things. Does that make them any less smart? Come on, really? One topic you disagree with her on and she&amp;#039;s an idiot for life? So now think about this in light of the guys, how they might respond to this. They won&amp;#039;t mind if you don&amp;#039;t like one performance on one show, but don&amp;#039;t be surprised when you find yourself not getting retweeted or replied by the guys because you, the Twitter fans, basically blacklisted these people, who, as I said, are obviously liked by the guys. (not saying you, Chris, were the only one, but the combined negative effort makes it seem deliberate...)&amp;nbsp;I don&amp;#039;t know exactly what they think of you and your article, but I&amp;#039;m pretty sure they have come to the conclusion that if the fans choose to dislike someone who has been on the show several times, they will ignore the fans, which is what has happened.&#13; 
&#13; 
Something else you said was that &amp;quot;I was told it was only a small minority of fans being addressed, but I just gave that podcast another serious listen and, I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, that just isn&amp;rsquo;t true.&amp;quot; Now I&amp;#039;m sorry, but what the hell does this even mean? It is a small minority of fans. Red Eye&amp;#039;s entire audience is not exclusively on Twitter. You  like you&amp;#039;re the vox populi, speaking for the audience that has been unwittingly maligned by these mean mean hosts. You&amp;#039;re speaking for nobody but yourself. If anything I regret the people that will read this and think this show is awful. This show is one of the few resources for smart, funny,  the wall conservative commentary on the day&amp;#039;s hottest topics. At least accept the fact that you are alone in your belief and that no one else agrees with you; let other people judge for themselves. I don&amp;#039;t see how you can get past the fact that you are tainting the water with your misguided anger.&#13; 
&#13; 
You talk about Bill (Bill! of all people, Bill Schulz who hasn&amp;#039;t done nothin to nobody) Before y&amp;#039;all ruined Twitter for Bill, he walked out of the studio every day wondering what loyal fans of the show will think of the show they just taped. And now YOU have the balls to rag on Bill as if he doesn&amp;#039;t care and never cared? &amp;quot;Ohh he&amp;#039;s not reading the feed and HE DOESN&amp;#039;T CARE AND NEVER DID CARE&amp;quot; Yeah, like you have the insider knowledge to what he&amp;#039;s thinking? Like you&amp;#039;re so damn important that he&amp;#039;ll move a mountain JUST for you and whoever else didn&amp;#039;t like one person on one show? Wrong. You&amp;#039;re not all that to the guys. Just because you&amp;#039;ve made a name for yourself writing conservative content in a blog which is certainly (in my view) worthy of praise, does not make you somehow important among the thousands of fans out there. You complain as if you&amp;#039;re the only fan out there, the most important one who deserves all the attention. What I&amp;#039;m trying to say here is, you&amp;#039;re treating Red Eye as if it is a show owned by the fans. Wrong. It is made FOR the fans. I sometimes wonder why Greg never reads mail or answers his phone messages anymore (I think he&amp;#039;s done Mail Time once in a few months and Messages For Greg has been away even longer)&amp;mdash;maybe it&amp;#039;s because the messages he gets are not unlike the negative tweets in the Red Eye feed.&#13; 
&#13; 
Red Eye has changed, sometimes majorly set-wise (basement type setup to today&amp;#039;s set) and minorly content-wise (given the variety of guests who appear on the show these days), but never drastically because of one bad experience (Kayleigh is not  from the show, she&amp;#039;s on again tonight) and especially never because the fans decide they don&amp;#039;t like someone. From what I understand the bad part that caused the tweets was only on Halftime? Y&amp;#039;all will crucify this guest cos they had a bad Halftime Report? What a waste of breath! Why not say &amp;quot;This Halftime wasn&amp;#039;t the best, but still a good show! Better luck next Halftime.&amp;quot; or something that SOMEWHAT smacks of encouragement? Instead this outrageous attack-mode craziness...&#13; 
&#13; 
And you cite the Halftime Report with Mecurio as if it somehow endorses your mad theory that the guys don&amp;#039;t care about the fans... It makes no sense! Mecurio originally said something ridiculous, Andy called him out on it, then Mecurio proceeded to say other ridiculous things (being that he&amp;#039;s a comedian) which Andy, hilariously, I thought, used as a build-up which had myself and the panel in stitches. (that means laughing a lot) But I guess you were too peeved by the podcast, and you told yourself everything that happens on the next show that&amp;#039;s mildly antagonistic (even when it&amp;#039;s over the top like Andy&amp;#039;s outrage was; I can&amp;#039;t believe you took him seriously) is directed at you. That Halftime Report was hilarious, and I&amp;#039;m sure as heck sorry you were too busy feeling sorry for yourself and building up resentment towards the guys who have done this over a thousand times, through good or bad, smart guests, funny guests, the rare unfunny guest, serious topics or outrageous topics, to enjoy that Halftime Report.  Lets think about that briefly, shall we? Over 1000 shows. Better ratings at 3 AM than CNN primetime. Some of the smartest and funniest guests who have ever been on TV. All that, done by these three guys day in and day out for over four years, and to not be just a little grateful to them, and more importantly to Fox News for airing it AT ALL (which is something Greg has  said he feels very grateful for), shows that you don&amp;#039;t care about the show or even about being entertained: you want what you want and if Red Eye is not what you want you don&amp;#039;t have to watch it. I get that. But don&amp;#039;t come out here and  all depressed when you really don&amp;#039;t care,  all angry at the guys when you caused the problem, and all smart and in-the-know when you clearly are being far too sweeping in your judgment of the show and its regulars, and biting in your un-called for characterization of the guys as indifferent jerks, which they are not, SIR.&#13; 
&#13; 
Your comment about Andy and his&amp;nbsp;blog from ages ago? Funny stuff. There is a YouTube video of Andy calling Mike Huckabee a snakeoil salesman. Andy&amp;#039;s Always been his own man, same with Bill and Greg. That&amp;#039;s only affirmation of his comment in the conversation you cite about Greg Bill and Andy all having differing views. I doubt Andy holds that view now, given how often Ms. Coulter has been on the show, and I doubt Ms. Coulter holds it against him. But I wouldn&amp;#039;t know or quote frankly care. Be your own reporter.&#13; 
&#13; 
Catspolitics, you said it is not respectful because thencommentary was directed at an entire fanbase? You know what else is not respectful? When an entire fanbase intentionally insults a frequent guest on a program.&#13; 
&#13; 
And finally, one thing that just was so wrong and really shows your lack of understanding of the show in general was where you call it hypocritical to diss some jackass fans for insulting a friend of the show repeatedly and offensively when Red Eye regularly mocks celebrities? Justin Bieber? The Dalai Lama? Lindsay Lo...&#13; 
&#13; 
THE DALAI LAMA? When did Red Eye EVER insult the Dalai Lama? Red Eye makes jokes and has fun with people who are out there either by virtue of their position or who put themselves out there intentionally. Besides the only reason the Dalai was mentioned was because of a doofus reporter or whatever the story was who tried to tell him a joke.&#13; 
&#13; 
Justin Bieber is what is wrong with Canada. He thinks everyone in Canada has healthcare (probably thinks the same of England), his audience is teenage girls, and his hair belongs on a wig-stand. He puts himself out there. He sings, he comments on culture and so forth, etc. Lindsay Lohan? She&amp;#039;s a train wreck (in my humble opinion). &#13; 
&#13; 
Red Eye is, as I said, an under the radar show, and Greg is happy that it is this way. In fact something Polly said really bugs me. She says the guys are &amp;quot;celebrities&amp;quot;? Whiskey tango foxtrot? They&amp;#039;re no more celebrities than Justin Bieber is a hobo. Greg is happy NOT to be a celebrity. He can say all these silly things and people enjoy it! It is funny because he doesn&amp;#039;t TRY to be a celebrity! He doesn&amp;#039;t try to be a 5&amp;#039;4&amp;quot; O&amp;#039;Reilly or Hannity At Nite or whatever! That said at the same time the show can have incisive commentary. Cutting humor and smart commentary in the same show. At 3 AM. That&amp;#039;s the beauty of the show, that Greg will keep doing his show with people he, Bill, and Andy like no matter what people like you and the Twitter folks say. That&amp;#039;s what you missed and it&amp;#039;s exactly why you won&amp;#039;t be missed.&#13; 
&#13; 
This has been a defense of Red Eye. Opinions given are mine and mine alone. I apologize for nothing (except for maybe how long this reply is). </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:323728:127798188</id><idPostId>127798188</idPostId><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:323728</id><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><link>http://www.chrisisright.net</link><displayName>Chris Is RIGHT</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/06/29/red-eye-in-which-i-get-off-the-short-bus/</link><displayName>Red Eye: In Which I Get Off The Short Bus</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-07-08T09:52:40.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:323728:127798188:327570418</id><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/06/29/red-eye-in-which-i-get-off-the-short-bus/#IDComment327570418</link><postedTime>2011-07-08T09:52:40.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Red Eye: In Which I Get Off The Short Bus by TomGMS</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://twitter.com/TomGMS</link><idEmailMd5>aaa0b4463622ae706036118057dd6eaf</idEmailMd5><displayName>TomGMS</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/TomGMS"&gt;TomGMS&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/06/29/red-eye-in-which-i-get-off-the-short-bus/"&gt;Red Eye: In Which I Get Off The Short Bus&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2011-07-08</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>