<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7uyj/update/2012-03-30T15:24:28/ac9eed9e4a3122c1f77ce5400f0061a49b6ae1ef8787a853232843225a6e7258</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>All of this is a result of the Industrial Revolution of the 1800s, which 'suddenly' had the capability to produce immense amounts of hardware, but had little market to make it profitable. Clearly war was the most logical place to make the most money and  the greatest influence in the shortest period of time. What became an international cabal of government, military, industry, and private investor families conspired to foment war on the flimsiest of circumstances in WWI (1917) and WWII (1941). These two projects were so profitable that war would become an engine of economic tyranny that persists to this day. After the atomic bomb it became clear that wars would have to be fought with conventional weapons, but with an ever looming ‘threat’ of nuclear measures. Fear became the driver of conflict and along came the Cold War, perfect in that only a few thousand people died, but there was so much panic whipped on both sides by, for instance, the Cuban Missile crisis (completely fake) that Americans and Soviet citizens would gladly Cough up trillions of dollars, over 45 years, to support the defense industry and its ever-growing ego-soaked hunger to Gain power, money, and influence. The continued fear of the 'Red Menace' was enough to brainwash the United States into troop involvement in Korea (1953, really about a strategic presence) and Vietnam (1964, really about oil). Shortly after the collapse of the USSR in 1990, it was no surprise that we got involved in what would become the New Cold War--the 'War on Terror'. Decades of American international economic and/ or military imperialism was conveniently overlooked or reinterpreted so that the now thoroughly entrenched cabal of US profiteers could inaccurately smear The Taliban, Al Qaeda, and other such groups as monolithic terror organizations that had no justifiable purpose or goal. Feminism entered the arena in the early 60s and was funded to do two major things: break up families to increase the tax base; and attack the educational system over time to dumb the US population down to the point that professional competence, critical reasoning, and common sense were all things of the past. The reason for the latter was that the average citizen of the 1950s would never have accepted the shallow arguments put forth for spending and taxation that would be used in coming decades. We are someplace between 20th and 35th in the world in math, science, and English because the ‘silent majority’ of the American public lacks the political will to change, and more seriously lacks the cognitive skills necessary to clearly understand what is going on. The most insidious part of this catastrophic epidemic is the continued seduction of our young people into following a life style bereft of self determination and common sense in exchange for the shallowest and unhealthiest of short term rewards (fast food, casual sex, alcohol, and constant &amp; baseless praise). In the decades to come, who will have the awareness to see and challenge the forces that continue to psychologically imprison so many average American citizens?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ekdc9c</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rrah</id></website><link>http://cnsnews.com/node/117373</link><postedTime>2011-09-15T10:57:21+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:24:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7uyj</id><link>http://cnsnews.com/node/117373#comment-481100175</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzd4z</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-09-15</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>