<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m4djx6/update/2012-03-01T18:55:02/cb353ce6899b79e1cb22b81d15987824b5756aa1eac49ddaa8baf1c1b00dd9a5</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Reminds me of MY complaints concerning  asbestos and paper dust exposure as well as fire hazards in the Morgan Station BMF in Manhattan (29th St &amp; 9th Ave). 

I'd been on 'career conditional' employment status as a new hire (PS-9) Electronic Tech when I witnessed smokers dropping cigarette butts down the metal chutes used to move mail pieces (out of mail sacks) to under the floor conveyor belts. 

We had fire evacuations on average of 1 per week while I was there in 1987. Trouble was - my supervisor claimed the USPS wasn't subject to OSHA regulations (being a federal agency) and when I questioned the violations of civil service safety regs he'd claim the USPS was a private employer - not subject to civil service regs (damned if you don't - damned if you do!). During my first fire evacuation I and my fellow trainees ran down 'firestairs' to the street level only to find the outside doors locked with chains and padlocks.

When looking across the sorting floor we could see a barely visible 'snow' falling from the ceiling. Another supervisor explained they'd 'fireproofed' the ceilings following a massive fire in the 1970s. "Relax (he said) it's only 'rockwool'" (another name for fiberous 'mineral-wool' such as 'asbestos')

We were constantly fixing electronic and mechanical sorting machines due to paper dust which clogged the circuitry - causing Overheating.

Finally: When I offered a suggestion to improve operations I was told by the Training Supervisor "Nobody likes a 'boat-rocker' (and) People HAVE been known to fall down and get hurt around here". All I had offered is a way to retrofit the automated sorting machines so they could 'read' typed addresses on colored envelopes. 

The first day we were allowed on the sorting floors a mechanic was carried out on a stretcher. The supervisor had ordered him to 'kick-loose' some mail sacks jammed in the conveyor belts inside a 'riser' tube (transporting mail sacks to upper floors). The mechanic fell down the tube 30ft to the floor below. We heard the supervisor tell one of the other workers "Make sure you punch-out his timecard BEFORE you call for an ambulance!" (to Ensure the injury didn't happen 'on the clock')

Following this exchange the Training Supervisor withheld (from me) the same 'training materials' given to all other trainees attending classes at the USPS Training Center in Norman OK. He also denied me the mandatory 2 week in-station hands-on training required for ALL equipment maintenance employees. As a result of this I flunked the training course and my employment was terminated.

The only time I ever called OSHA (on aThursday) to report health and safety violations in the workplace I was working as a 'temp' on a DOD project in Danbury CT after a co-worker Fainted at her workstation and fell to the floor (due to lack of oxygen). Workers were complaining of symptoms common to CO2 poisoning so, as no one else would do it, I placed the call.

I didn't name the employer yet the NEXT morning I found my supervisor in early to work (Friday). He took me aside and told me they'd hired 1 too many people for the project and as I was one of the last hired AND I had no family to support (unlike the other person hired with me) I was the one being 'let go'. Since my security badge didn't expire until the following Friday - they were letting me complete the temp assignment until then.

The following Monday I found a NEW person working in MY station. Now, if I had been deemed 'excess' WHY was THIS person hired?

That very day they started posting OSHA safety posters and chemical safety warnings throughout the facility. Binders of MSDS were now left in the work rooms, hazardous chemicals (xylene) were taken from the baby-food jars and put in OSHA approved plastic jars, drums of TCE were covered and sealed, exhaust fans in chemical workstations were switched 'ON' (now in the correct direction) and the room ventilation system was retrofitted to bring-in FRESH air rather than merely recirculating the room air (containing fumes of TCE, xylene and Burned solder paste).








</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yp1qg0</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/fywf</id></website><link>http://www.govexec.com/oversight/2012/02/labor-sues-postal-service-over-whistleblower-mistreatment/41342/</link><postedTime>2012-02-29T21:38:43+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-01T23:55:02+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m4djx6</id><link>http://www.govexec.com/oversight/2012/02/labor-sues-postal-service-over-whistleblower-mistreatment/41342/#comment-453905326</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h9gdq</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>