<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwwikh/post/2012-03-31T12:58:19</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>From the very beginning of this story, I believe the vast majority of people felt that Susan Powell had come to harm and that her husband was the guilty party. Susan's character and past behavior ruled out her taking  and leaving the children.  The late night camping trip was the elephant in the room and if nothing more should have at that point been enough reason for the police to remove the children from his care.  It is the parents who in the majority of cases of children being killed/abused end up being guilty.  Unfortunately, the laws in this country don't Always allow the police, social services people to remove children even when they know the child is in harm's way because maybe what they have won't convict in court.  The child often times ends up paying the price for this.  I think we need an exceptional circumstances clause to the laws designed to remove children from the care of a parent who is under suspicion of killing their spouse, especially when the person has demonstrated less than stellar parenting.  You wake you small children on the Coldest night of the year and take them camping?  That should have been enough in my mind to disqualify him as a responible parent and certainly point to the fact that the children would be in danger living with someone with judgment this poor.  Josh became the number one person of interest very early on and as far as I am conerned the kids should have been removed then and any supervised visits under this kind of cricumstance should have only happened with Josh having to see his kids at a Social Services Bldg  where there could be some level of security.  I know one theory is that Suan was leaving him and he killed her because he was afraid of losing his kids, and I have heard people say well he won't hurt his kids, that is why he killed her.  That arguement doesn't hold up for me.  If you will kill somone in order to stop something from happening then you will kill again and Josh did just that.  He couldn't kill all the people who were keeping him from his children so he took the option he had left.  Kill them and then no one can ever take them from me again.  Josh's solution is one that law enforcement has seen over and over again.  Time that we figure out how to keep children from being caught up in these horrific circumstances.  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67e9nq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6rx1</id></website><link>http://www.sltrib.com/sltrib/news/53824340-78/powell-search-susan-warrant.html.csp</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:19:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T16:58:19+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwwikh</id><link>http://www.sltrib.com/sltrib/news/53824340-78/powell-search-susan-warrant.html.csp#comment-481996489</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rmach</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>