<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/133950/post/69820706/comment/328543186</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>shortage Temple Cold smoke 1911 years of the Wuchang Uprising, overthrew the Qing Dynasty emperor. When people see the symbol of the republic of five nationalities of the Republic of colored flags fluttering in the bright sun under clear sky,christian louboutin Chinese students depart their, the ground was really happy for a while. However, until the provisional president Sun Yat-sen\'s seat give the Yuan, the provincial military governor military governor changed after the troubled world has become increasingly worse, more and more difficult of life. The harsh social reality, with the original people of the In Qu view,sac louis vuitton, replacing the old towards the new national even better. Qu under the extreme disappointment, felt great pain and anger. Once, he spoke with the sheep husbandry of the transfer hero of Zhu Gui style from bartender. October 10, 1912, when the organs of Changzhou residents and schools are decorated to celebrate two characters Sister Yiqun see a red light or lights are hung next door, hanging on the door from a unique one that read, Qu know, it still hangs, expressed his when Qu ideas, a few years later he was 1911 Chinese revolution proved the bankruptcy of the old society. Unfortunately, due to China five years of the Chinese bourgeoisie suppressed colony of his forces, homeless proletariat Daxian its function, the achievements of Chinese society after the revolution that abnormal metamorphosis. Bourgeois life: care, or have fled, seeking far in the political science of the mind where to settle, or actually forget the anti-downstream, into the Words and Flowery Expressions obscene words bad fiction career. So when I, when by the Europeanization of secondary education,louis vuitton sac, a time when southern literary thought the chance of bankruptcy. The so-called I am the fifth high school students, Jiangsu, Yangzhou Ringer brothers and Yixing Wubing Wen and I are at the same environment, we happen unexpectedly at the same time to At that time, however, and social isolation. Qu in the spirit of the depression, is intertwined with the hardships of life. great aunt Yin Zhuang, and soon died. Qu family life, leading a poor aunt can no longer rely on financial aid, increasingly embarrassing situation. Before and after the age of twelve to Qu, the family had to gather together to sing seven yuan a month rent back rent housing, under the tribe looked down upon as a phase, moved west along the Qu temple shrine. This is the last one in Changzhou Qu residence. Qu Ancestral  is a white autumn uncle funded the construction of Qu Gung Fu, located in the north west of the city seek Bridge, together with the star polymer are separated by only a river. Ancestral  in front of the squat with two stone lions, stone lintels on the top of a white marble engraved Seal six characters: Ancestral houses into things, into the four. From the door into the east side first into the kitchens and maid\'s accommodation. For the second into the dining room. Third into only two, outside the reception room - every sacrifice for the ancestral temple is here. Interval between the East within the first curtain is a small fall of white mother\'s bedroom. Between the two into a small courtyard, surrounded by a small gallery round the middle planting some chrysanthemums. Summer night,christian louboutin, a person on dinner in the courtyard and enjoy the cool air. Have a well near the west side of corridors, Qu and siblings draw water from the well water the flowers; water is carried to Zaojian they go from here. Again after a , lit from morning to night, which stood painted tables and shelves,Louboutin, Qu\'s father often paint brush here. The following is a hallway Qu siblings three bedrooms and landscapes where debris. Every day, Qu\'s mother is here to teach children to read and write. Qu\'s bedroom and study at the cottage next to the last three years after the turn Xuan. Place by the east wall of the room in a small bed of old, the middle of the window set to a square desk, an old armchair. Bed on the right wall hangs a map, a Phoenix Yuping flute, a Yueqin. Qu in leisure, in addition to playing chess outside, often a flute, the sound Yu depressing euphemism, it seems to tell a smoldering heart of human darkness of depression and hatred. Students to fall in to the White House, the more talk here, the game. Zhang Tailei to the students is often one. Animal husbandry of sheep often come here to ask for advice Qu English, mathematics. old customs, living shrine is the most shameful thing, not only live in a shrine in front of it could not lift their heads, is also loses face with the family of people. Qu Jiashi behalf Zanying, In such a prominent family in Africa to the last resort, no matter which room is which one, who wants to move to the ancestral  in the residence. Moreover, the ancestral  was still parked in the coffin of many ethnic, dark, desolate, where is the home of the premises? Qu a move into temples, many friends from it and cut  from them. Many cousins &amp;#8203;&amp;#8203;and relatives of an officer,chaussures christian louboutin, not a single person willing helping hand. In this extremely snobbish society, Qu one tasted human well-being,sac vuitton, the world state of Yan Liang, Qu mind it aroused strong resentment, but also tempered his tough character and spirit of resistance. Such a pent-up discontent in his blog a poem pregnant, had to show it: mother\'s death Qu situation at home, year after year. Father Qu Shiwei in the fall of 1913, the grandmother to Hu Shi Qu Hangzhou home, and then he went to Hubei Huangpi two aunts Zhou management accounts, monthly salary of about thirty dollars. But soon, the World Hu dismissed from office, no longer send money came. By 1914,christian louboutin He does no must quit their villages and towns, the family eight people to maintain minimum living standards thanks to borrowing. Sometimes lunch at home, only to eat the rest of the morning\'s porridge. Qu said with deep feeling, we had every hope that Sun Yat-sen, but the victory of the revolution, the people\'s life,chaussures christian louboutin, or better Off. We also point to eat porridge, the countryside still do not know how many even have to eat porridge miles. Time, Qu met a farmer in the streets, standing beside a girl to be the subject of the first plug to sell grass, surrounded by a lot of people watching. Qu bear down, he said bitterly: Wrote: azelaic nephew back,christian louboutin Jacky Cheung 2010 mini- concert . HAVC480P @ mini three can, the time has not. Doctor says: lack of blood, so the tire over the previous two seriously ill. I persuade them to medication, he refused, the Executive want to be under the tires. Doctors and women are refused admission, the cloud than the private non-living, and they all hurt Yin stallion. I repeatedly made yesterday by the voluntary,louis vuitton site officiel, before allowing; be foreign five dollars,Louboutin, to come here tomorrow. Yu Qian told his nephew after notification, the best I have in this and so on. ... ... He is one of five yuan to be required to respect the place out, I not pity this tip, you can avoid future strokes strange meaning. ... ... If willing, the nephew of Wang cap will look only with Zhu Hua and bedding are brought from, cotton has brought, For A nephew double Wenying Wen Qian for the ear. this Song Shi Zhi twenty Er Yi word Qu Shiwei postscript at the end of the letter goes: Moreover, Wang Yang Tousheng socks to be from the end of this nephew,sac louis vuitton, because of physical unhappy, and could not end; if asked people to end, would cost one dollar. Nephew Qian If you want no? Monthly third year and this year has brought me a read through. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:133950:69820706</id><idPostId>69820706</idPostId><idBlogId>133950</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:133950</id><idBlogId>133950</idBlogId><link>http://webdevcodex.com/blog</link><displayName>Web Development Codex</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://webdevcodex.com/mod-your-404-pages-of-your-wordpress-blog/attachment/4042/</link><displayName>4042</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T14:21:50.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:133950:69820706:328543186</id><link>http://webdevcodex.com/mod-your-404-pages-of-your-wordpress-blog/attachment/4042/#IDComment328543186</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T14:21:50.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on 4042 by 651ykx8966</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://1ouboutinpascherfr.com</link><idEmailMd5>083f81db0dda5599bc5ac12418fb8eca</idEmailMd5><displayName>651ykx8966</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://1ouboutinpascherfr.com"&gt;651ykx8966&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://webdevcodex.com/mod-your-404-pages-of-your-wordpress-blog/attachment/4042/"&gt;4042&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>