<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m37ffn/update/2012-03-29T07:30:32/724759bc1b045fc0afc446c68d644df3adccdf86fde4c0f77eb9314a3d8966c0</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m378r0</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c10i1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>We disagree, and I know a few developers; they thrive on rising markets and idiots who don't understand how many noughts there are in the purchases they make.

Private ownership has decreased from 70-71% to 66 - 67% in less than ten years due to BtL. BtL is less sensitive to cost - it is essentially speculation, and has been driven by the deregulation of Housing benefit and a tidal wave of immigrants looking to rent, alongside changes in the mortgage market. 

Nice to see you pointing out the recent decrease in equity release - if you go back pre-2007, yes, was very much a characteristic of the ludicrous bubble generated by that incompetent Brown, and the remortgagers may have blown their easy money in a rather reckless fashion - that isn't really stimulus, now, is it - it's a one Off squander and increase in leverage, not an economic improvement.

Conclusion - Flash in the pan bollocks from people who thought the economy was solely maximising the Spot gross tax revenue value with no consideration for the consequences of their unwise and unproductive policies - it was beyond moronic.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z515f</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/finance/economics/houseprices/9172925/House-prices-fall-as-stamp-duty-holiday-ends.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T07:18:30+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T11:30:32+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m37ffn</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/finance/economics/houseprices/9172925/House-prices-fall-as-stamp-duty-holiday-ends.html#comment-479423720</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5com3</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>