<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/323744/post/127830688/comment/327812195</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Okay, I am interrupting my reading of this blog which I have decided is brilliantly written (as ) to ask, am I remiss in exposing you to the great loves of my life?! Besides Dana, who you have met... sadly, badly.  
 
Move past that into the music that drives my soul.. first and foremost Rob Thomas, then Cold Play, then 3 Doors Down, lastly but not leastly (sp?) Plain White Tees and Red Hot Chili Peppers... Have you been exposed to their earlier (less mainstream, entirely over played) music? None of these artists appeal to you?!?!  
 
Rob Thomas, he is brilliance. Every song is personally written about a direct life experience. For instance, 3 am is about his Mother&amp;#039;s struggle with cancer, he was 12, I think, when she was diagnosed. His brilliance is that this song applies to many people, due to his ability to write about a deeply personal moment and apply it to many facets of life experiences (main stream idiots looking for love/lost songs) Yet, they are so deeply personal only a true fan of the musician appreciates the artistic creation of the music and the piece.... listen to it again.  
 
By the way, I would shoot myself rather than listen to Beiber or Spears, or anyone else pop. Norah Jones, that is a side thought... and another personal favorite is Tracy Chapman and CD&amp;#039;s of mainstream artists hold significant treasures you can not experience of streamed (PAID) radio. If you semi like a current artists song, it is worth delving into the CD, there is almost Always better music there than what is chosen for us on paid music stations.  
 
For those of us who are music driven... </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:323744:127830688</id><idPostId>127830688</idPostId><idBlogId>323744</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:323744</id><idBlogId>323744</idBlogId><link>http://jesterqueen.com</link><displayName>Jester Queen</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://jesterqueen.com/2011/09/28/satellite-radio-part-ii/</link><displayName>Satellite Radio Part II</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-09-28T09:56:51.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:323744:127830688:327812195</id><link>http://jesterqueen.com/2011/09/28/satellite-radio-part-ii/#IDComment327812195</link><postedTime>2011-09-28T09:56:51.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Satellite Radio Part II by Kathy Gaughan</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=1006518696</link><idEmailMd5>ef3764081c758fc5e6ff13cb9e980c35</idEmailMd5><displayName>Kathy Gaughan</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=1006518696"&gt;Kathy Gaughan&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://jesterqueen.com/2011/09/28/satellite-radio-part-ii/"&gt;Satellite Radio Part II&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2011-09-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>