<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mskkt8/delete/2012-03-28T12:11:50</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Contract law: whenever misrepresentation/deception is used in contracts of any kind it is null &amp; void; it is FRAUD; they are kicked out! SINCE these have used "elections" as PART of their deception, claiming to be that which they were NOT; they were legally &amp; lawfully kicked out EVERYWHERE!  they have used "elections" claiming "the will of the PEOPLE"; SINCE will of the PEOPLE IS UNIVERAL; doesn't matter the color of your skin, texture of your hair; shape of your eyes; NO ONE LIKES BEING OPPRESSED! NO ONE LIKES "ficticious" "governments" with FICTICIOUS LAW MAKERS with FICTICIOUS LAWS WITH FICTICIOUS AGENCIES WITH FICTICIOUS COURTS that DENY JUSTICE TO EXIST! 
   "democracy' WORKED by EXPLOITATION; which is TARGETING AND HARMING ALL OTHERS FOR THEIR OWN PERSONAL PROFIT &amp; !  THUS no working JUDICIAL branch HERE as existed since the BRITS reconnected with Yale university, skull &amp; bones, aka 322; (gods) of this world; saying that THEIR WAY OF RUNNING THE WORLD was so much BETTER than ANY OTHER;  with BANKERS &amp; "intellectual" elites; THIS is what THEY "call" intellectual elites people: Elizabeth WARREN, PROFESSOR of LAW; at HARVARD NOW, previously they said was YALE; perhaps OXFORD now; this is how QUICKLY they try to CHANGE things; including LAWS! 
   as chairman of the "supposed" economic recovery CHARADE when ASKED: WHAT OF THE USURY LAWS? response was WHY, THEY JUST DISAPPEARED DURING THE 70's; when ASKED HOW DO LAWS JUST DISAPPEAR? her RESPONSE was THEIR TYPICAL OOPS! caught us THERE huh! ha ha ha! 
    WE THE PEOPLE WALK LAWFULLY; THESE DO NOT! WE REFUSED to ACCEPT ANY of their SO CALLED "laws" that kept DISAPPEARING every time you SNEEZED! or ANY RULINGS WHATSOEVER from ANY courts they have set up; including the MILITARY! 
     ELECTIONS will do NOTHING to CORRECT the PROBLEM which CAME FROM ENGLAND; WEST POINT should bE KNOWN TRUTHFULLY as BENEDICT ARNOLD ACADEMY with their "MOTTO" as DUTY : being to do as much HARM as they possibly COULD to the PEOPLE here in the USA ; those DAMN GOOD MEN as they REFER to us, who DARED to be FREED from the TYRANICAL RULE BY THE BRITS! 
    city, county, state was the PATTERN OF OPPRESSION set up HERE in the USA; it is NOT recognized NOR authorized as "government" and the "officers" of the "law" which of course is ABSOLUTELY FICITICIOUS &amp; USED ONLY FOR THEIR OWN PERSONAL PROFIT &amp;  have been told that WE HAVE NO NEED WHATSOEVER for THEIR kind of "protection"; we are WELL ABLE to protect ALL within our communities without such corrupt beings as THEY are! 
    LAWS are to EXIST! FIRM, STABLE; like the WORD OF GOD IS! they are for the PROTECTION of the PEOPLE; the ANIMALS &amp; the PLANET ITSELF! 
     JUDGES are to EXIST to ENFORCE that JUSTICE EXISTS! 
OFFICERS then EASILY keep peace &amp; harmony within communities as the CORRECT AND TRUE PATTERN IS THERE OF TRUE GOVERNMENT; not ones set up to  &amp; ever OPPRESS THE PEOPLE! 
    BANKSTERS can be referred to as GANGSTERS; who seek to  &amp; ever thru forcing the PEOPLE to PAY; then to pay more more more; with FICTICIOUS 'legal" SYSTEM &amp;^ corrupt JUDGES try to PRETEND to be "governments' to  &amp; ever OPPRESS THE PEOPLE with FASCISM; while they themselves follow no rules, regulations, protocols, Constitutions, laws, etc; they sought to tie up ALL of the nations under these "ficticious" and corrupt "governments" that were NEVER FOR THE PEOPLE but to HARM them; 
    thru FASCISM and TOTALTARIANISM;  
SYSTEM of STEALERS here in the usa pocket almost $1 TRILLION WEEKLY doing NOTHING FOR THE PEOPLE; claiming  &amp; ever "broke"; SYSTEM of LIARS; everything you ever THOUGHT you knew to be true SHRED SHRED SHRED it ALL; because NONE of it has EVER been; NOTHING said or shown to the PEOPLE on this planet, has EVER had any truth whatsoever to it! 
   Copeland, executive branch; 
   Meyers, legislative branch; 
   Hagin, judicial branch; 
DC  &amp; ever to be KNOWN as the PLACE OF DECEPTION! 
    Located in Wyoming, with multitude of WISE counselors, 3/5/7;  WORLD GOVERNMENT ESTABLISHING TRUE LEGISLATIVE WHERE LAWS FIXED; STABLE; like the WORD OF GOD IS! with COURTS OF JUSTICE to differenitate from THEIRS which they have "called" courts of law but were used ONLY for their OWN personal profit &amp; ; same as "state" etc; was CORRUPT SYSTEM FROM ENGLAND; they STOLE our forefather's plan to have NATION FOR THE PEOPLE! 
    WE took it BACK AGAIN legally &amp; lawfully ending the corruption HERE, &amp; GLOBALLY! 
    HATS OFF TO ALL THE PATRIOTS! EVERYWHERE! IN ALL NATIONS! ENDING THE OPPRESSION OF POLITICIANS! </body><verb>delete</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hzp69</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tsjl</id></website><link>http://truth-out.org/opinion/item/8154-let-the-million-flowers-bloom</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T14:23:41+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T16:11:50+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mskkt8</id><link>http://truth-out.org/opinion/item/8154-let-the-million-flowers-bloom#comment-478498070</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>killed</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>