<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7jjc/update/2012-03-30T15:30:06/1af219e8f9b624e1241e7a986e58bed4d7d8c36774ccd8fe6f45ba3fa2ca82cf</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Recently became aware of work in Newport Beach CA where MD out of UCI has unique method for neuronic recovery. Patients with a variety of Spectrum Disorders, including Autism, become able to  control of their emotions and actions out of choice versus conditioned response (typical of current palliative behavior therapies.) These patients' EEGs demonstrate "near normal" (some undistinguishable from those of "normal" cohorts). Other patients with addiction, Anxiety, and other psychological disorders, where neuronic repair is possible, experience similar results. The MD is published but not in major periodicals. However, he does have 3 years of longitudinal data from patients that is impressive. It matters to those with Spectrum disorder patients how they got there, what matters most is how to return to "normalcy"!Recently became aware of work in Newport Beach CA where MD out of UCI has unique method for neuronic recovery. Patients with a variety of Spectrum Disorders, including Autism, become able to Gain control of their emotions and actions out of choice versus conditioned response (typical of current palliative behavior therapies.) These patients' EEGs demonstrate "near normal" (some undistinguishable from those of "normal" cohorts). Other patients with addiction, Anxiety, and other psychological disorders, where neuronic repair is possible, experience similar results. The MD is published but not in major periodicals. However, he does have 3 years of longitudinal data from patients that is impressive. It does matters to those dealing with Spectrum Disorders how they got there, however, what matters most is how to return to "normalcy" !</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67asej</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/oelx</id></website><link>http://bighealthreport.com/3372/cdc-sees-autism-rate-rise-25/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T11:22:28+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:30:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7jjc</id><link>http://bighealthreport.com/3372/cdc-sees-autism-rate-rise-25/#comment-481105983</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gj2mc</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>