<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mstle0/update/2012-03-27T17:55:01/4d2a2a14a1c5da5d37a00ef284c4799caba6e132fbb065e30bfa09beac55ec52</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Alcatraz finale.  Wow.  That was it?  I mean, the locked room we’ve been waiting to see behind all half-season holds a 1960s Era computer?  I think I was laughing as maniacally as the newly introduced mad scientist.



Where do I start?  The show had promise - the worst criminals of Alcatraz somehow reappearing in modern time, not aging, and with some unknown purpose.  Cool idea.  That was how it was billed.  But why were they coming back?  Well, other than stealing a few keys in early episodes, it seems these guys were just back to commit the same crime over again.  And get caught again.  We still don’t know why they were coming back and doing what they did.  A hint of an evil conspiracy was supposed to answer this question.



We know as much about the main characters as we did after the pilot.  What happened to Madsen’s parents?  What happened to Soto as a boy?  Who is Hauser and what motivates him?  Ah, that dang plot keeps getting in the way of character development.



The computer that is tracking the 63s.  Ok, the concept of silver in the blood stream being able to be tracked, GPS style, is intriguing.  But you realize that those lights that are plugged into the giant map aren’t moving, right?  They are plugged into a cardboard cut out hole!  So if somebody hops on a plane, train, or bus from Minneapolis to Seattle, it won’t actually move with them?  And you won’t know where they are (or your magic computer will print out their location).  The second thought I had when seeing the map was, great, so now the second season will be “Alcatraz-New York” and the third season “Alcatraz-Miami”...



The car chase.  I couldn’t tell when the Ford commercials began and ended.  Cool sound effects and visual effects.  But basically Tommy Madsen is superhuman and he stabbed his granddaughter who was about to be pronounced dead as the camera faded, but we all know that she will probably be resuscitated by this magical elixir, colloidal silver, whose miraculous properties have somehow escaped modern science.



Call me Alias-Burned.  But another corporation that is behind some power struggle?  Broadway Mutual? Really?  Let me guess, it’s an anagram.  For deus ex machina plot device.



What was with the meeting with the military guy?  Random information dump.  Aquifer.  Paraguay.  Hauser repeating mistakes.  This low-life criminal released by the Warden is more powerful than the president?   Riiiight.



And perhaps the biggest disappointment of the night...  how are the inmates skipping 50 years into the future?  A geothermal event.  Wait... or time dilation...  or quantum tunneling...  or cryogenics.  I guess the writers haven’t decided and just took whatever was on the whiteboard in the room they script their story.  Multiple theories isn’t mysterious, it’s just irritating.  If it was a geothermal event, you can’t predict when it will occur.  Cryogenics means someone is unthawing these bodies and putting them in random places across the country?  Time dilation sounds made up.  My guess is quantum tunneling, which is pseudoscience enough to never have to be fully explained.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lrg4y</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/vh3p</id></website><link>http://popwatch.ew.com/2012/03/26/alcatraz-season-finale/</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T02:01:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-27T21:55:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mstle0</id><link>http://popwatch.ew.com/2012/03/26/alcatraz-season-finale/#comment-477819899</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>