<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwft0g/post/2012-03-31T01:20:06</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwuu3b</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/81713</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>JohnDoe2b - I recommend you actually LISTEN to the Zimemrman phone call with the police dispatcher, and the other 911 calls.  also, search the internet for the interview a Tampa affiliate of FOX News did with an eyewitness named "John" who saw Trayvon Martin beating George Zimmerman and crying for help.  On one 911 phone call, you can hear Zimmerman crying out for a full 45 seconds, which means Martin was pummeling him at least that long.  Simmerman was Acting he role of a responsible neighborhood watch volunteer. If you listen to his phone call to the police dispatcher, you will be able to see that when the dispatcher suggested that Zimmerman stop following Martin, Zimmerman said, "OK".  from that point on, there is NO evidence that Zimmerman continued following Martin.  In fact, he says on the audio of the phone call that he lost sight of Martin.  early exceprts of his phone call make it appear he profiled Martin because of his clothing or because he was black.  But if you listen to the phone call, you will see that he only mentioned the hoodie when the dispatcher specifically asked him what the suspicious person was wearing, and when asked if the suspicious person was white, black, etc., Zimmerman said he "thought" the guy was black. There has been some argument as to whether Zimmerman suffered any injuries.  The first officer on the scene wrote in his report that after handcuffing Zimmerman, he observed Bleeding from Zimmerman's nose and on the back of his head.  He also indicated he placed Zimmerman in the back of his police car, where Sanford Fire Department EMTs treated Zimmerman's injuries.  If Zimmerman suffered a broken nose, swelling and bruising would not be evident early on, but would be very pronounced in the following days.  The f#%$*ng c%$ns has thus far been determined by analysts as inconclusive.  And Zimmerman did not "hunt down an innocent kid.  He broke contact, and Martin re-appeared and attacked him.  Martin had no injuries on his body (according to the funeral home director that handled the body), except for the gunshot wound.  On the other hand, Zimmerman was treated at the scene before being taken to the police station.  This was not a race crime.  The  only race crime involved in all of this is the behavior by the likes of Al Sharpton and Jesse Jackson to inflame the public into believing there was one.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/678mca</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/opinion/mills-trayvon-martin/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T11:40:03+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T05:20:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwft0g</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/opinion/mills-trayvon-martin/index.html#comment-481559873</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ecsyd</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>