<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qxn4/update/2012-03-29T12:01:28/2937357b34670644b3fd443d4352683168de197d69729505f40de13e6ea7853e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This situation could have been avoided on so many levels, but defining them will be tricky.  I do not believe the shooter made a decision that day he was going to kill a black man.  I also believe once he Spotted the victim he did not make the decision that this was his opportunity to kill a black man.  What I see is an overzealous individual who thought he should follow and/or confront the victim for looking suspicious.  I believe the victim was probably scared about being followed by a stranger at night and reacted to the situation, for which I do not blame him.  The shooter, who is now receiving a beating for approaching an unknown individual at night overreacted and shot the victim.
 
Thus, I do not believe this was a racist incident, just an unprepared individual who had no training to approach the victim or respond to the victim.
 
I firmly believe that Sharpton and Jackson, collectively, have done more damage to the black population than any white man could do.  They make their living  of black suppression and must teach it in order to be significant.  Never have I seen them speak of black affluence or the path to Reach it.  If the black population was thriving and instilled a culture of prosperity, these two individuals would be out of business.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hafjy</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnmw</id></website><link>http://www.star-telegram.com/2012/03/27/3840316/wheels-of-justice-moving-in-trayvon.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T02:47:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:01:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qxn4</id><link>http://www.star-telegram.com/2012/03/27/3840316/wheels-of-justice-moving-in-trayvon.html#comment-479604978</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cmcgm</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>