<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mid3nz/update/2012-03-22T19:49:16/6e81a52530169e54855e43a54da22ff1d0e17cda185ba68c570f610288b3702a</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miaxds</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zdlq8</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Precisely, murrayfal.  It's nice to know one more individual is aware of the proprietary subterfuge on behalf of corrupt corporate interests, and the legislators they have in their pockets, collectively referred to by at least one honest and savvy author (David Cay Johnston) as "the corporatists."

For quite some time now, the commons have been pillaged by interests who undermine the 99% of the populace, under color of seeking to repair the system and make it more efficient.

As Johnston so abundantly documents in his book, FREE LUNCH, the process of sucking not only assets and income and opportunity from 90% or more of us but, also, of buying away from our voting power the only potential advocate that could defend us (if we can stop their corruption of it) is the the government, the very government they blaspheme and blame for the harm they have wreaked -- the very government they want to weaken, because it is the only vehicle the people have with which to resist against criminal corporate tyranny.

The corporatists have controlled the rhetoric and the political narrative skillfully over these past three decades -- so skillfully that they have many of the very citizens from whom the most has been stolen, blaming the government, and blaming it for what criminals have done THROUGH buying control of it.  They have hired legal geniuses to word bills in such a way as to have them appear to do some good thing, when it actually does the opposite.  So cleverly have they disguised their subterfuge that they have citizens believing their last and only friend, their government, is the enemy.  Of course, as bought, as corrupted, as lobbied to the tune of millions and millions in campaign donations and favors of all kinds to legislators and to their family members and their law partners and their business partners and their cronies... the people have been harmed.  But the government BOUGHT is not the government of laws it was thirty years ago, and could be again today, if only the majority of the voters knew who the corporatists are, and how they twist words to accomplish their deceptions, and vote laws to conceal what the fraud they perpetrate behind the scenes.  They create agencies that nominally are meant to punish bribery and fraud and the funneling of money from the taxpayer funded treasury, into the pockets of the richest of crooks.  

Too many citizens have been brainwashed into thinking that the dividing line between the corporatist inheritors of the legacy of the robber barons, on the one side, and those who would preserve democracy, on the other, is the line between one of the two major parties and the other.  But there are corporatists in Republican Party and in the Democratic Party, as well.  

We see brainwashed voters crying out for further weakening the government, for further concealment of the  of corporate criminals who, through their bought political cronies, subvert the checks and balances that ONLY the government can exert any resistance against, and only THEN if the corrupt are exposed and ejected from their current self-serving nests within it.  

I perceive you to be -- judging by your comment above -- one of the minority of citizens of sufficient intelligence and awareness and courage to recognize, and to speak out against, the bribery, the lies, the corruption and the blaming of the government for what only the government (purged of those criminals) could disabuse us of.  

Being intelligent and aware of the subterfuge and deceit, you know that NOT  ALL  corporations are criminally managed and that not all wealthy corporations and individuals came by their wealth and power dishonestly and deleteriously for the people.  You know, therefore, that to criticize the unjust and the corrupt is not -- as the publicists for the corrupt would have the world believe -- base on a hatred of the honest and reputable and beneficial corporations and persons of wealth.

If the criminals among the wealthy and powerful were to succeed in persuading the people to so deregulate and weaken the government, the result would be that EVEN  IF  THE  CRIMINALS  WERE  THEN  PURGED  FROM  IT, it would not have the power for good and honest citizens to restore this nation to the status of a nation of equal justice and opportunity for all.  The criminal rich would then have won.  Yet there are those among us who sincerely believe and cry out for the government to be robbed of power to control even in the hands of good and honest leaders (leaders who have not been so blinded and compromised by "gifts" from the criminal rich that they have lost any semblance of any moral or democratic compass.

Thank you so much for adding your voice to those of others of us who realize, as you do, the nature of the disguise worn by the very perpetrators of destruction of opportunity for anyone OTHER  THAN  the  rich, who pretend they are making the United States MORE fair and more economically healthy, when they are doing everything in their power to cripple and subject the middle and the working poor to their -- the elite's -- greedy will.  

There is, indeed, a war of sorts going on in the U. S. and the world today, but not a war of ideology against ideology.  It is a war of the clever and devious among the rich and powerful, to Gain control by crippling or eliminating every check and balance remaining to the people, wherewith they might resist.

It is not a war between the poor and the rich, but against the power of the entirety against the power lust and the greed of the CRIMINAL element among the richest and most powerful.

We the people seem to have lost the game of establishing the narrative and the rhetoric so far, and hence we have difficulty articulating what the REAL war is about, without using words crafted to muddle our thinking and our words in pointing out who the CRIMINALS are, in defending against their inserting into the laws and into court rulings tricky fine print that takes away what the bold, large print of democracy is all about, and cannot live without.  

Hopefully we can begin to FIND the words to describe what the deceptive name calling, and metaphors are that would turn citizen against citizen and cause us to blame the only organ the people have to resist being tyrannized -- their government.  

What OTHER organ is there that the people can use (provided we purge it of the corrupt that are out to take it from us, or pull out the teeth that would prosecute the criminal that have
bought their way into it.

Hopefully, we have not yet lost every toe hold, as well as every articulation of the problems actual, whereby we might begin to purge the criminals, and then use our governmental power to restore the U. S. to the status of being a land of opportunity for all, and not merely a place of concealment and destruction from inside, by its imbedded enemy -- the criminals.

So victimized are the middle and low-income working classes in the U. S., as a result of corrupt buying of our politicians that the only way many of os may continue for very much longer to be deceived by tricks and false rhetoric, might only be attributable to something akin to a mass epidemic of Stockholm Syndrome.  After all, how could so many changes that have been brought about by corporatists over the past thirty years have gone so enormously wrong, and have the people continue to support the exploiters, and blame any who would resist the exploitation. 

There are signs that the people are awakening to who their real enemy is, and who is their real friend.  

You acknowledge that the playing field is NOT level.  The deck IS stacked against the good of all the people, and in favor of the criminally greed-driven.  

May you keep the torch Burning in the quest for clear and untwisted words, and for exposing for all the people to see, who is blaming the fox for the disappearance of the chickens.

Thanks again for calling it like it is.  If even one citizen reads you and awakens to how he is being lied to, robbed and cheated, and persuaded the thieves are his friends, we need that one more voice.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dwp8e</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/4bnh</id></website><link>http://www.marketintelligencecenter.com/specialreports/1340711</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T18:47:00+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T23:49:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mid3nz</id><link>http://www.marketintelligencecenter.com/specialreports/1340711#comment-474068462</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6qfs2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>