<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/206085/post/127451060/comment/327928179</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I read the Hunger Games a couple summers ago and when I heard the movie was coming out, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t wait to see who made up the cast.  When I got to Rue and Thresh I was not at all upset, or surprised because I had Always pictured them black, because the author specifically states in describing them that they are dark skinned.  I was only surprised when I saw that Cinna was black.  I was not at all upset and I thought it was an interesting choice.  I thought the movie was perfect and portrayed almost everything the author wrote down to a tee.   After seeing the movie I thought to myself that there was nothing people have reason to complain about, it portrayed the book great to satisfy the book fans, and showed an interesting story to those who have not read it.  When I read this article all I could feel was disgust.  How can people get so upset over three character&amp;rsquo;s color of skin?  Just because they felt they had a special connection to the story for reading the books and creating their own characters in their head doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean they have the right to criticize the cast due to skin color.  The thing that baffles me most was how they back up their anger by saying that she&amp;rsquo;s not supposed to look like that.  If they&amp;rsquo;re going to get mad over appearances not exactly matching the vision in their heads, maybe they shouldn&amp;rsquo;t see the movie, or any other movie that was made from a book they read for that matter.  This is a clear example of racism in our society, and although people believe the older generation has more racism, I completely disagree.  Young people of today see differences in skin and take out their anger and racist thoughts on the internet.  They do not believe it has as much affect since they are typing and not stating their racism to people&amp;rsquo;s faces.  However, posting online is worse, because it is so underrated.  People post racist things online all the time and it reinforces acceptance of discrimination.  I honestly cannot believe the blatant racism toward the Hunger Games cast.  Especially to the little girl who played Rue, how can people live with themselves for calling a 12 year old a &amp;ldquo;black bitch&amp;rdquo; and a &amp;ldquo;nigger&amp;rdquo;?  It truly shows how Cold hearted people really are on the inside, and the internet gives these people an outlet to their feelings.  It broadcasts the hatred within these people for everyone to see and when it gets back, or has already gotten back, to the actors in this movie, I can only hope they look past these awful people.   </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:206085:127451060</id><idPostId>127451060</idPostId><idBlogId>206085</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:206085</id><idBlogId>206085</idBlogId><link>http://www.worldinconversation.org</link><displayName>World In Conversation</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.worldinconversation.org/2012/03/26/the-hunger-games-and-race-relations-in-2012/</link><displayName>The Hunger Games and race relations in 2012?</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:48:08.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:206085:127451060:327928179</id><link>http://www.worldinconversation.org/2012/03/26/the-hunger-games-and-race-relations-in-2012/#IDComment327928179</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:48:08.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The Hunger Games and race relations in 2012? by juliafederici</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://intensedebate.com/people/juliafederici</link><idEmailMd5>0e6efbe7a19dda5e704e966c40f2dd6f</idEmailMd5><displayName>juliafederici</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://intensedebate.com/people/juliafederici"&gt;juliafederici&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.worldinconversation.org/2012/03/26/the-hunger-games-and-race-relations-in-2012/"&gt;The Hunger Games and race relations in 2012?&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>