<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nmhc/post/2012-03-29T12:36:53</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body> CRIMINAL AMERICA


 DepletedUranium: Pentagon Poison


      USARMY    TRAINING       VIDEO      Depleted Uranium: Pentagon Poison, by Minnie Bruce Pratt 2004-05-30| New York 


      Deadly radioactivity is drifting in thesands and       fertile fields of Iraq, in rain falling inEurope,in       breezes that toss palm trees in Vieques,Puerto Rico,       in the water of South Korea - the toxic debrisof       exploded U.S. depleted uranium (DU)shells.  


      The International Action Center continuedits historic       exposé of this terrible danger with aforumin New       York City on May 25, "Poison Dust - AnotherU.S. War       Crime: the Use of Radioactive Weapons in theGulf." 


      DU is a byproduct of the process used tomake nuclear       bombs and reactor fuel. Because this metal is1.8       times denser than lead and Burns on impactwith steel,       bullets and shells made of DU can cut throughtank       armor like butter.  


      U.S. tanks, Bradley fighting machines, A-10attack       jets and "Apache" helicopters routinely fire DU            rounds. When a DU shell hits a target, as muchas70       percent Burns on impact, releasing invisibleand       insoluble uranium oxide, a radioactive dustthat       people inhale and ingest. 


      'Metal of Dishonor' 


      To the political hip-hop of Movement inMotion arts       collective chanting "Drop beats, not bombs,"200       people crowded the United Nations ChurchCenter for       the meeting on "Poison Dust." The meeting was            co-chaired by Naomi Santos of Move ment inMotionand       IAC co-director Sara Flounders. 


      Flounders alerted the gathering that overhalf of the       700,000 veterans of the first U.S. invasion ofIraqin       1991 have the chronic illness dubbed "Gulf War            Syndrome."  


      Millions of Iraqis died of preventablediseases from       the obliteration of water and health systems by            bombing and 12 years of sanctions starting in1990.       More recently, Iraqi doctors began to note anominous       increase in cancer and diseases of the immunesystems. 


      Sharon Eolis, a health care worker whotraveled to       Iraq in 1998 and 2000, confirmed that both U.S.            documents and independent scientists stronglylink       this pattern of sickness and death to DU.       


      IAC founder and former U.S. AttorneyGeneral Ramsey       Clark first raised the issue of DU shortlyafter the       1991 Gulf War. The IAC has continued to informthe       public through its DU Education Project withsuch       publications as "Metal of Dishonor: How thePentagon       Radiates Soldiers and Civilians with DUWeapons." 


      The project also challenged U.S. governmentdenialsof       DU's impact in a video, also called "Metal of            Dishonor," produced by the People's VideoNetwork.At       the meeting Sue Harris of PVN announceddevelopmentof       a new video, "Poison Dust," which will go ontourto       military bases and communities. The film isnecessary,       she said, "because the situation is gettingworse."  


      The U.S. dropped 375 tons of DU on Iraqduring the       first Gulf War, and 2,200 tons during thecurrent       invasion. The U.S. has also used DU weaponsduringits       assaults on Afghanistan and the formerYugoslavia,in       training exercises in Vieques, Okinawa andSouth       Korea, and doubtless in numerous U.S. militarytesting       grounds. Other countries also use DU weapons.      


      Clark: 'DU is war against the poor'      


      Ramsey Clark traced his journey towardunderstanding       the murderous impact of DU on the people ofIraq.He       noted that the first signs came two yearsafter heavy       U.S. bombing of the desert near Kuwait in 1991.            Nomadic Bedouin people, seeking help, began tobring       newly born deformed babies into urbanhospitals.  


      In March 2001, Dr. Aws Albait, an Iraqiphysician who       worked in Baghdad from 1990-1999, said thatleukemia       and lymphomas in Iraqi children had increased12-fold,       and in adults, six-fold. 


      Illness and genetic damage is alsooccurring in the       children of U.S. soldiers. Children of maleGulf War       veterans are born with twice the usual rate ofbirth       defects. In female veterans, the rate is threetimes       normal, with double the rate of miscarriages.      


      A study in the April 2003 New Scientistmagazine       suggests DU toxicity combines synergisticallywithits       radioactivity to produce much more seriouseffects       than either poison alone. 


      Clark stressed that the impact of DUunfolds over many       years, and that the movement must be committedtoan       equally long struggle: "We have to  out,be       unified, with every ounce of energy. This is awar       against the poor with the U.S. military thereonlyto       protect and increase the wealth of the few."      


      'A huge catastrophe' 


      Juan Gonzalez, president of the Nation alAssociation       of Hispanic Journ alists and a co-producer ofthe       "Democracy Now!" radio show, is currentlyrunninga       series of columns on DU in the New York DailyNews.He       acknowledged that he was standing on theshouldersof       the IAC and other activists, saying: "A huge,huge       catastrophe has been visited upon the planetby useof       these weapons and the spread of low-levelradiation."  


      Gonzalez broke the story on DU after themother ofa       U.S. soldier on leave from Iraq came to himfor help.       Her son, serving with a New York StateNational Guard       unit, was suffering from serious respiratory            problems--and being forced to return tocombat. The       mother added that many other members of hisunit in       Iraq were also so sick with high temperatures,kidney       ailments and respiratory problems that they'dbeen       sent home to Fort Dix. 


      Gonzalez saw a connection to the effects ofDU, and       arranged for independent testing of thesoldiers.Of       nine tested, four were absolutely positive forDU       contamination, and three were probable.       


      Denied testing at Walter Reed MilitaryHospital, they       were examined in a German clinic under thesupervision       of Dr. Asaf Durakovic, professor of radiologyand       nuclear medicine at Georgetown Univer sity in            Washington, D.C., and a colonel in the U.S.Army       Reserves. Dr. Durakovic, who is the Veterans            Administration's nuclear-medicine expert, has            characterized DU as a "threat to humanity."      


      DU is the latest manifestation of thedangerous       low-level radiation that is a byproduct of U.S.            military use of nuclear weapons. Gonzalezcited a       January 2000 federal report on occupationalsickness       of Department of Energy personnel thatdocumented50       years of deliberate government exposure ofmilitary       and civilian personnel to radiation.       


      A 1990 report on the effects of DU, fromthe U.S. Army       Armaments, Munitions and Chemical Command, wasclear:       "[L]ong term effects of low doses [of DU] havebeen       implicated in cancer ... There is no dose solow that       the probability of effect is zero."      


      Gonzalez was emphatic: "These weapons haveto be       eliminated or the whole planet will becontaminated." 


      Resisting war crimes 


      Navy veteran Dustin Langley of SNAFU(Support Network       for an Armed Forces Union) stated that DU wasjustone       more crime of the U.S. against its ownsoldiers, ina       line stretching back to exposing troops toatomic       testing during the Cold War and Agent Orange in            Vietnam.  


      He described how soldiers - working peopleforced to       enlist by the "poverty draft" - come home with            contaminated equipment, store it in the garageor       laundry room, and sicken their own families."DU       doesn't wash  with Tide," he said.      


      Langley urged the crowd to join the IAC andSNAFU in       turning out for the June 5 March on Washingtontoend       the U.S. occu pation of Iraq, Palestine,Haiti, the       Philippines, Korea and everywhere. He indictedthe       Bush administration as a regime that is"stockpiling       weapons of mass destruction, using themagainst its       own people, and funding a worldwide network of            terrorism" through U.S. military aggression.But by       "regime change," he said, he didn't mean theDemocrats       or Ralph Nader's campaign. 


      The solution? "A global mass movement - a            multinational, multi-gendered anti-warmovement that       will shock and awe the war-makers inWashington."  


      For inspiration, he pointed to the heroicresistance       in Falluja and to the growing number of U.S.soldiers       who refuse to com mit war crimes, like MarineCorps       resister Stephen Funk and Staff Sgt. CamiloMejia,a       Nicaraguan immigrant sentenced on May 21 to ayear's       imprisonment. Mejia would not return to hisunit in       Iraq, saying, "This is an oil-driven war."      


      More inspiration for resistance came fromFrank       Velgara of the Vieques Sup port Campaign, whotoldhow       on May 3, 2003, a decades-long struggle bydetermined       Puerto Rican activists shut down the U.S. Navybombing       range in Vieques, a "victory against the mostpowerful       military in the world."  


      Kadouri al-Kaysi, an International Action
Center 
      member from Basra, Iraq, seconded that
determination, 
      focusing the evening on action: "Iraqis want
the U.S. 
      out of Iraq. The fight is still going on, and
they 
      will never give up. Most important is to come
to 
      Washington on June 5 to say to the Iraqis: We
are
with 
      you, not with the U.S. government!"  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zaa3b</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yjmx</id></website><link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2012/03/28/police-video-trayvon-martins-killer-smoking-gun-lawyer-says/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T03:38:16+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:36:53+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nmhc</id><link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2012/03/28/police-video-trayvon-martins-killer-smoking-gun-lawyer-says/#comment-479633223</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/819ym</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>