<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwfdqj/post/2012-03-31T00:59:06</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwxl8b</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l12xn</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> You didn't answer the question. Instead, you expressed your beliefs according to what a book says is so. You were taught to believe these things. From an outside source.

It's not the same thing as having a direct experience with the divine. Were you to put that book down, would your "faith" dim and wink out from lack of fuel? Would you once again be adrift in the sea of darkness with no direction home?

True divine inspiration wells up inside a person like a spring. It requires no fuel from an outside souce. It literally comes from beyond this world. It is everpresent. Even as it's human host goes through the same trials and tribulations as you do.

These living waters give Off a light which cannot be seen by the human eye. For it's host, it illuminates this world like an xray. Revealing the most intimate of details about cause and effect.Those who cannot see in this way are counted by the billions.

It's a foregone conclusion that their end will be self inflicted. But don't fear. A good gardener knows about Burning the field in preparation of next year's crop.

The seed of which lay in wait even now.


x</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r3hsd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6qc0</id></website><link>http://communities.washingtontimes.com/neighborhood/stories-faith/2012/mar/26/will-earth-end-fire/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T14:14:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:59:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwfdqj</id><link>http://communities.washingtontimes.com/neighborhood/stories-faith/2012/mar/26/will-earth-end-fire/#comment-481547655</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/590m5</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>