<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0o7ph/post/2012-04-02T05:22:15</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>















 


Divorce laws a money making
machine for women – A womans perspective on men who suffer – Myra


People are
fighting in courts for over 10 years to end a broken marriage.. Is it ever
going to be the same again?  Irretrievable
breakdown of marriage is a law which is a must to give justice to over 10,000
people who are stuck in courts.  Its not about whose fault but the way lower courts are.  If one party wants to delay proceedings
they can just take adjournments for years and years.. No one to help.  Specially if the guy has asked for a
divorce he is assumed to be gulity! 



And no I am not
a man.  I am a woman who believes
that women should not  be put a in a category of “helpless”.  There are enough women out there who
can make a man’s life miserable.  The
woman is heard by everyone.. the man will not have any one to goto.


The divorce laws
were made for the “abla naari” who was  considered helpless in this
country.  I fail to understand how
on a sensitive issue like marriage which deals with a person’s life such a view
can be taken that Always the man is wrong.  Cant a woman be ever wrong? Cant she misuse the system? Just
because someone is a man he has to be the one at faulty?


We have now
reasearched over a 1,000 cases pending in different courts where the following
has come out:


1.  Cases where the couple stayed together
for less than 6 months
and are still fighting a case for over 5 years.  The woman is demanding huge amounts of money to let go of
the husband. The girl takes adjournments after adjournments in the court.
Infact in almost 200 cases no hearing had happened for over 2 years.. just
because the girl does not come to court! If she is fighting the case and wants
to go back then why use delay tactics?


2.  Another 100 cases that are still pending
for over 8 years.. The parties have lost out on 8 years of their life.. trying
to achieve what? If the marriage has been irretrievably broken down then why
cant they be allowed to part ways. 
This is just a sample it gives me Shivers to even think 1000’s of life
that are just stuck.


3. Infact in one
case the hudband had a decree of divorce from the lower court and the girl
demanded a huge amount of money even to let go at the first appeal level. The
guy has no job and she earns well. She thinks it is easy to hang the case in
the court for more 10 years the way she has done already for 10 years.  So she sends demand of huge money
through her lawyers.  Why cant the
court intervne and get her alimnony? Why do courts keep such matters where
lives are getting ruined every day pending for years together?  Should not there be a time line to
finish hearings in a certain time limit? 


Is our system
giving a legal right to a woman to black mail?  The woman earns more than the husband and still wants huge
amounts to let him go.  Is this
even fair? If mediation has failed over 10 years of fighting cases what are we
trying to achieve here?  Giving the
woman a legal right to extract money even if the husband does not earn as much
as her? In mediation the girl clearly says she cant live with him but she has
filled to get maximum money out of him! So she admits that the marriage has
irretrievably broken down in front of the mediation centre then files a case
against the divorce.  The point of
an appeal is that she does not agree with the decree. But she says she only
wants money.  


Our Honorable
Judges have a huge task while deciding a divorce case.  They should not let the system get
mis-used in a way that leads to torture of lives.  


Someone who has
tortured a guy and his family so much is it humanly possible for him to stay
with that person in the same house? 
Also, if it has been over 10 years since the marriage broken down. 


If someone makes
a mistake of marrying a woman who thinks of it as a money making machine what does
the guy do?  Does he not have right
to freedom? Right to live? Is he supposed to suffer endlessly for one mistake
he did?  


The constitution of India provides each one of us,
right to freedom but the divorce laws are an absolute sentence for death. One
mistake and we are dead for life.  A girl can do what she wants and the man has no way to go. 


This is just to
bring out the importance of introduction of “irretrievable breakdown of
marriag” as a law.  Our Honourable
Judges should be able to use their descrition in cases where there is cruelty
and over 5 years have passed in legal battles.


 


</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6708gz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gidt</id></website><link>http://www.hindustantimes.com/Entertainment/SexAndRelationships/The-end-game/Article1-833652.aspx</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T18:12:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T09:22:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0o7ph</id><link>http://www.hindustantimes.com/Entertainment/SexAndRelationships/The-end-game/Article1-833652.aspx#comment-483376657</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>