<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m37bbx/update/2012-03-29T07:23:42/e523fc3e6e51df1856d18d0da01517d140099d192949ce602d78680a88799493</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3mt10</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c00os</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Your rationalization of Ned Yost's behavioural flaws is disturbing to say the least.14 runs in 2 &amp; 2/3 of an inning is not testing someones meddle it is using someone as a whipping boy to make a point.He did not want Mazzaro&amp; set him up to fail so he could win an argument he had with Dayton Moore. Mazzaro was scheduled to pitch the next day but Yost threw him in early in relief when that days starter got shelled&amp; left early.Mazarro had not finished his preparation to pitch and was not mentally or physically ready to pitch&amp; Yost knew it.When he got hit he left him in for 14 runs and claimed he was trying to protect his 8 person bullpen.Funny I've seen whole teams that carried only 8 pitchers and contended.How Yost could say that with a straight face amazes me.
Most managers still use the 4 run rule on pitchers.That is to say that most Managers pull a pitcher as soon as he has allowed 4 or more runs.The maximum any pitcher could surrender that way is 7.And that only if someone hit a grand slam after the pitcher had given up 3 runs.And many use either a 2 or 3 run rule with relief pitchers.
If Yost learned from his mistakes it would be one thing but he does not.This Year he left Chen in to surrender 10 earned runs in a start.We saw him do that type of thing to numerous starters last year.It was as if he would just give up when a pitcher got banged around early.When you let a pitcher allow more than 4 runs you are essentially quitting on that game.We have a great offense but to expect comebacks from being down 8, 9, 10 or more runs is ridiculous.But we can comeback from 4-0 or 5-2.But Yost let at least 15 games get out of  by leaving guys in way too long.I'm not saying we could have won all 15 but if  he had used the 4 run rule we might have pulled out comebacks in 5 or so of those games.
That and the psychological damage it can do to pitchers is devastating. Mazzaro, SOS,&amp; others werenever the same after taking 10+ earned run whippings.Others were temporarily shaken like Francis&amp; Chen who followed their whippings with down stretches but later recovered.Davies is another guy who was broken by 2 years of misuse by Ned.Under Hillman at one point he was close to a breakthrough but Yost finished him .Ned thinks he's testing these guys meddle but they wind up traumatized &amp; unable to trust the manager.
Mendoza made the Rotation by forcing Neds hand.but look at last years spring training.Ned was debating Mazzaro or SOS for the last Spot when Mendoza had been untouchable last spring too.Mendoza outpitched both Mazzaro &amp; SOS last spring but Ned sent him down when he hadn't allowed a run until his last start.Imagine last year with Mendoza throwing for us in the majors.We could have won 5-10 more games .He had a 2.18  in the Minors and even lower in the majors.You could have doubled that number as his adlustment to the majors and he still would have had the best  on the Royals.Personally I think he'd've posted about a 3.25 ERA in last years majors if he had been here last year.
These type of bad decisions are why many of us want Yost gone.It's hard to win when you're manager gives away 10 or more games a year by quitting.And others by picking his friends instead of the best guy available.I love that Yost Emphasizes defense.It makes the games more fun.But even here he seems to have trouble doing a balanced analysis of a players strengths and weaknesses.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hk3hy</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lz6q</id></website><link>http://kansascity.royals.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120328%26content_id=27709266%26vkey=news_kc%26c_id=kc</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T22:18:49+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T11:23:42+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m37bbx</id><link>http://kansascity.royals.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120328%26content_id=27709266%26vkey=news_kc%26c_id=kc#comment-479419725</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/csznn</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>