<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw9soy/update/2012-03-31T03:37:15/568593df5517e6c6b3d83378fa5a4a5e5b0082363cf09fc184dc083445f1316f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>why won't these neo-urbanistas and their cabal quit with their green-washing?

our "regulatory reform" package -- written by the planning commission (i.e. development interests), developers, and their boot licking (and financially dependent) minions -- is really largely meant to make it easier for them to build.  period.  

if they really believe in their 'Transit Communities", and demand beau-coup extra density at light rail stops or bus stops, then let them build these projects, but with ZERO parking. 

RDG, GGLO - come on, prove that your plan works for the Roosevelt Blocks.  you wanted extra units and "density" (density = more people, remember?).  then build NO parking in your project.  

developers, you want to put in a 200 unit project without SEPA?  then ZERO parking in it.

in fact, no parking should be allowed within that 1/4 mile to 1/2 mile walkshed from a light rail stop.  isn't that like Paris, or Brooklyn that we want to create?  

see if you will get your projects financed.  see if you'll get your tenants.  prove to us that your vision of a light rail-based Seattle works.



and if it works, hooray.  cheaper units for everyone and you are affordable housing heroes.  and you've added your density without adding to Seattle's carbon footprint (much) or place additional demands on our already constrained streets.

come on, Richard, Tim, Mike, Sally - you visionary leaders on Council -- lock this shit down!  you are so confident of this vision, then make it so!  

because all you are really doing, with your "optional" parking solution is creating expensive units close to transit that will be bought up or rented by folks that will use light rail during the week to their desk job downtown, but will own a car and continue to drive for their weekend jaunts to the mountains skiing or nightly to the 90% of Seattle not well-served by transit.  you are creating a Seattle for neo-urbanist yuppies with a Prius ("market demand").

trust me, in all sincerity, I will lobby HARD for ZERO parking around your light rail stops.  why? because i really want to see us build a car-free infrastructure and transit rich and "complete" urban villages.  

because ZERO parking** will ultimately force the City to deal with our growth correctly.  it will create such a demand for functioning and COMPLETE urban villages (not just more people, Roger!) - with adequate open space, retail and services, schools, safe streets and bike routes, and other urban amenities.  it will create such a demand for a functional and COMPLETE transportation network (remember the Urban Village Transit Network?).   it will force Council to look holistically at planning and see it for more than just upzoning or requiring pretty streets with setbacks.  it will force the Planning Commission to get past their self-serving one-size fits all Transit Communities plan.  it will require REAL engagement (and PLANNING) with the community to assess and define these things uniquely for each neighborhood.  and it will Ensure the City provides CONCURRENT delivery to these communities the things that make dense urban areas actually WORK (via capital improvement planning, impact fees, and all the things we studiously avoid).  all so that our developer friends can actually sell or rent these units with ZERO parking. 

and then we will finally get to what us so-called NIMBYs wanted in the first place, starting way back in the 90's.  it's all there in the Comp Plan and the neighborhood plans if you'd just take a look...

(** ok, you can have a few Spots reserved exclusively for car share, with electric charging stations)

</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67tuow</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/e8xv</id></website><link>http://publicola.com/2012/03/30/eliminating-parking-requirements-is-not-the-same-as-prohibiting-parking/</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T00:29:37+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T07:37:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw9soy</id><link>http://publicola.com/2012/03/30/eliminating-parking-requirements-is-not-the-same-as-prohibiting-parking/#comment-481625721</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/q5w9</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>