<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/136753/post/26057847/comment/328197721</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Thursday, 10 of November of 2011 Aprons and Chef Wear Chef Hats, Uniforms and More Chef Apparel 
Choosing the best chef wear and apparel is just right here. 
You have come to the right place of choosing the best aprons and chef wear. This blog includes interesting information about chef apparel and more. Being chef means not only your good in cooking but you also looks good outside which would make you look clean and proper. Giving more ideas and information about chef apparel,lisser ghd,Discount UGG Boots, read more below the content here. 
Choosing the right chef apparel gives you comfortable and professional appearance. A crisp uniform sets the chef apart from the rest of the kitchen staff. Your workplace may or may not offer its own uniforms. Whether you work for a restaurant,sconto burberry borsa 030,burberry sconto borse,bu, caterer or resort, a chef needs a well-chosen uniform to serve the public in proper style. 
Chef Coats 
A complete uniform starts with a double-breasted chef coat. A chef is easily recognized by their distinctive coat. The coat is typically bright white but can also be black or gray. Usually cooks wear camp shirts or single-breasted coats. Tailored coat designs look flattering on both men and women. Some coats are shorter for an executive look. Others are longer for  and coverage. Features to look for in coats include: breathable cotton material to  comfortable conditions in a Heated kitchen 
secure buttons with stylish appeal 
conveniently located pockets and accessory loops to keep kitchen essentials and other necessities 
fold back cuffs to keep your hands and arms free 
mesh back panel and shoulder vents for airy ventilation over a hot stove&amp;#173; 
a fitted design with enough room to move about freely Comfortable Chef Pants 
Impressive chef coats are accompanied by easy-going chef pants. A popular pattern for pants is houndstooth. Other top choices include gray,Compro Vendo Torino - biglietti, arredamento casa Torino, abbigliamento su Bakec, onyx and striped pants. Chef pants pull on for wearable simplicity. When you shop for pants look for: darker colors that won\'t show stains as much as lighter colors 
stain resistant,Big Ang News, Pictures, and Videos TMZ, breathable fabric that is simple to wash and wear 
an elastic waist movements are unrestricted 
front and back pockets for plenty of personal storage space Chef Aprons 
Most chefs slip into an apron to protect the cleanliness of their coveted chef coats. Often they choose bib aprons for maximum coverage. An apron should ward Off stains and splats during heavy-duty cooking sessions. When buying aprons,Cindy Barshop, consider: vinyl aprons over superior coverage in a messy the kitchen environment but they are slightly heavy to wear 
nylon aprons are slightly less protective but more lightweight than vinyl for everyday kitchen conditions 
aprons should have adjustable back and neck straps for a perfect fit Chef Hats 
An eye-catching hat is the final touch for any chef uniform. A unique hat makes the chef stand out from the rest of the kitchen crew. Wearing hats while cooking also keeps hair back so it does not get into the food preparation process. There are different kinds of chef hats including: the traditional puffy hat with classic appeal 
a skull cap to keep everything contained 
a crown ball cap for a casual look 
a dramatic beret. Alice Lane writes about different topic about home improvements and this article was based on her. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:136753:26057847</id><idPostId>26057847</idPostId><idBlogId>136753</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:136753</id><idBlogId>136753</idBlogId><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com</link><displayName>HOCKEYCENTRIC</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-canucks-are-more-than-one-line-and-luongo/</link><displayName>The Canucks Are More Than One Line And Luongo</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T02:08:20.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:136753:26057847:328197721</id><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-canucks-are-more-than-one-line-and-luongo/#IDComment328197721</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T02:08:20.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The Canucks Are More Than One Line And Luongo by iesaeff5343y</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://borsebbrits.com/</link><idEmailMd5>e81a2543df768dd2ba20e3a9c54fdf44</idEmailMd5><displayName>iesaeff5343y</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://borsebbrits.com/"&gt;iesaeff5343y&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-canucks-are-more-than-one-line-and-luongo/"&gt;The Canucks Are More Than One Line And Luongo&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>