<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwr9tj/update/2012-03-30T12:25:56/09e1890ceafd9fab093a2c63384313cc9e351b27b4e3f8cd2ff002b1dccfd634</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Profile of the Sociopath - Obama

Glibness and Superficial Charm 

Manipulative and Conning They never recognize the rights of others and 
see their self-serving behaviors as permissible. They appear to be charming, yet 
are covertly hostile and domineering, seeing their victim as merely an 
instrument to be used. They may dominate and humiliate their victims. 

Grandiose Sense of Self Feels entitled to certain things as "their 
right." 
Pathological Lying Has no problem lying coolly and easily and it is 
almost impossible for them to be truthful on a consistent basis. Can create, and 
get caught up in, a complex belief about their own powers and abilities. 
Extremely convincing and even able to pass lie detector tests. 
Lack of Remorse, Shame or Guilt A deep seated rage, which is split  
and repressed, is at their core. Does not see others around them as people, but 
only as targets and opportunities. Instead of friends, they have victims and 
accomplices who end up as victims. The end  justifies the means and they 
let nothing stand in their way. 
Shallow Emotions When they show what seems to be warmth, , love and 
compassion it is more feigned than experienced and serves an ulterior motive. 
Outraged by insignificant matters, yet remaining unmoved and Cold by what would 
upset a normal person. Since they are not genuine, neither are their promises. 

Need for Stimulation Living on the edge. Verbal outbursts and physical 
punishments are normal. Promiscuity and gambling are common. 

Callousness/Lack of Empathy Unable to empathize with the pain of their 
victims, having only contempt for others' feelings of distress and readily 
taking advantage of them. 
Poor Behavioral Controls/Impulsive Nature Rage and abuse, alternating 
with small expressions of love and approval produce an addictive cycle for 
abuser and abused, as well as creating hopelessness in the victim. Believe they 
are all-powerful, all-knowing, entitled to every wish, no sense of personal 
boundaries, no concern for their impact on others. 
Early Behavior Problems/Juvenile Delinquency Usually has a history of 
behavioral and academic difficulties, yet "gets by" by conning others. Problems 
in making and keeping friends; aberrant behaviors such as cruelty to people or 
animals, stealing, etc. 

Irresponsibility/Unreliability Not concerned about wrecking others' 
lives and dreams. Oblivious or indifferent to the devastation they cause. Does 
not accept blame themselves, but blames others, even for Acts they obviously 
committed. 

Criminal or Entrepreneurial Versatility Changes their image as needed to 
avoid prosecution. Changes life story readily.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67me14</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6bwl</id></website><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/president-obama/2012/03/30/noonan-obama-not-so-smooth-operator</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:39:32+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:25:56+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwr9tj</id><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/president-obama/2012/03/30/noonan-obama-not-so-smooth-operator#comment-480917727</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hoiok</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>