<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3jgnx/update/2012-03-29T18:12:49/c2ca6844b32a06310707f5dc9cc671c7aa8dec3d8cfab193d89ea8c2327d3b2d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m321ed</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/akw5b</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Aha ! Polypeptides show no replication ability in isolation, its not in their nature, whereas the sense-antisense strucure of RNA makes it intrinsically capable of replicating its own polymeric sequences which may themselves have enzymatic capabilities as in the ribosome today. So RNA is the best candidate for protolife.  Amines alone cannot make life, but they can react with each other to make pyrimidines and these can make RNA like molecules in which circumstance RNA and amines might conceivably coevolve. This can happen anywhere the chemistry and energy balance is right, for long enough or in large enough quantities.

The question is why would one consider that more likely to have happened elsewhere. One reason is timing. "Other planets" existed long before the Earth did, so if living molecules can spontaneously arise at all, they were likely to arise there first. Judging from the estimated age of universe 13.75 bn years (assuming for now this isn't a Kelvinesque underestimate) compared to the estimated time it took for life to be established on Earth by whatever means ie 1 bn years, the other planets had about ten times as long to evolve life as Earth had so the probability is that at least one planet somewhere else did based on time alone. But the chances of life beginning on other planets first are astronomically higher than the likelihood that life arose first on Earth, due to the enormity of the number of other planets. 

The very large number of candidate planets implies a huge diversity of chemical environments. e.g. planets akin to warm Titans with massive amounts of hydrocarbons and ammonia and water on the surface with strong tidal Heating to provide volcanic energy to compliment the light of its sun may have had ideal chemistry to  as an incubator for living molecules in the first generation of chemically diversified solar systems following the earliest supernovas long before the Earth existed.

The likelihood that life from one of these seeded the early Earth  in part on how many life generating planets exist or have existed close enough to allow physical debris from them to have drifted to this solar system. Allowing for speeds with a magnitude in the range of the solar wind speed of 400km/s over 10bn years the upper range of over 13.3 million light years easily includes all of the local group of galaxies. Whether a bacterial cyst could stay viable for that long is another matter but that Depends on the preadaptive evolution of the phenotype of the cyst and its travelling environment, which are highly variable factors. All known bacteria are adapted to the Earth environment and one cannot dismiss the possibility of seeding based on their vulnerabilies as a bacterium evolving on a dying planet would develope very different qualities more suited to space travel and lose them again once it arrived somewhere safer to live.

If one contends life evolved on Earth one has to accept it is more than likely that it evolved elsewhere first. The question is whether it can travel from there to here, between star systems and for the reasons given in my previous post I would consider it possible. What is wonderful about the Earth is that it has remained hospitable to life for so very long compared to its neighbours, due to plate tectonics and the constant tidal massage received from the moon in orbit which has (just barely) maintained an atmospheric balance sufficient to allow creatures like us to evolve who will one day carry life to other planets and whatever we evolve into will do so for as long as the universe will support life I am sure. So the Earth is a champ with great staying power and we owe it everything we have as well as our deepest respect for our own sake and the sake of life in the future, but it seems likely to me that it was given life from somewhere else even if NASA haven't dug anything up on Mars...yet!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6he6o1</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/mxvm</id></website><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/comets-linked-to-beginnings-of-life-7593751.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T07:17:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:12:49+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3jgnx</id><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/comets-linked-to-beginnings-of-life-7593751.html#comment-479957493</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8f9qh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>