<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mnks6r/update/2012-03-06T21:15:52/4a2e471a4dd50e18916c5ce6fd4961485e47114a9be38bf28d4b0302e2589d3d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Israel Strikes! Iran Retaliates! 
(A Future Headline???) 
 
The nation of Israel conducted its long anticipated pre-Dawn air strikes against suspected nuclear weapons development sites within the nation of Iran. Early estimates indicate that at least one hundred Israeli combat aircraft were involved in the attacks, which included the deployment of numerous earth penetrating "bunker buster" bombs. Though non-nuclear in nature, these bombs are reported to have produced tremendous localized damage and heavy civilian casualties. Video reports coming out of Iran would also seem to support Iranian television statements reporting the downing of several Israeli fighter planes by Iranian air defense. However the Israeli Prime Minister, Benjamin Netanyahu, reported that "by the grace of God" the bulk of the attack force returned to their bases unscathed. 
 
As had been previously threatened, within minutes of the commencement of the Israeli attack, Iran retaliated with at least six flights of intermediate range ballistic missiles. Targets were far flung but seemed concentrated against oil production facilities in Saudi Arabia, Iraq, Libya and Qatar. Suspected Israeli nuclear weapons storage sites were also targeted, as was the Israeli nuclear reactor near Dimona. The US-developed anti ballistic missile system recently deployed in Turkey was active and functional, however it's capabilities were apparently overwhelmed by the large numbers of Iranian missiles launched. Preliminary reports have been hard to come by, however estimates are that 60% of middle east oil production infrastucture was destroyed within a span of thirty minutes. In Saudi Arabia, oil fields that have been feeding the global demand for crude for a generation, were swept away in what surviving eyewitnesses called "a sea of fire." In spite of a long diplomatic effort to prevent it, the long feared regional war in the middle east has clearly begun.  
 
In the US and Europe, financial markets opened to waves of panic selling, as the Dow Jones industrial average fell over 1000 points in its opening minutes. Trading on all of the major exchanges was halted for a time, as circuit breakers designed to control sudden drops in equity prices engaged in an attempt to calm and give pause to the markets. Despite these controls, the broad S&amp;P 500 had fallen by 23% by mid morning. Conversely oil contracts for West Texas Intermediate Crude were quickly bid up to over $180 a barrel as the implications of, what is now expected to be, a virtual shut down of mid east oil production panicked buyers. Gold, long the preferred safe haven in a turbulent political climate, virtually leaped accross the $2000/oz mark and continued to rise in spastic fashon throughout the session.  
 
At neighborhood fueiling stations across the United States, gasoline prices were hastily raised to between $6 and $7 a gallon as news of the Iranian conflict quickly spread. Those prices did little to deter buyers however, and by noon, lines to purchase gasoline stretched a quarter of a mile at normally busy stations. Not surprisingly, incidences of gasoline theft and other violence also increased. At one fueling station outside of Fort Worth Texas, frustrations erupted into an open gun battle as two rival groups described by witnesses  as "survivalist types" dressed in military attire opened fire against each other killing three people and striking numerous vehicles.

 Since this morning, At least 80 people have reportedly been taken to area hospitals across the nation. Many of those admitted have suffered serious injuries during their attempts to purchase fuel. One particularly gruesome confirmed fatality involved a gas station manager was apparently Burned alive during near riot conditions at a Chicago area gas station when his security cage was dowsed with gasoline and set ablaze. Local authorities have since deployed a substantial police presence at most fueling stations. However, local officials openly feared that any large demonstrations in protest of higher gas prices may quickly spiral out of control. 
 
On the major US interstates, freight hauling tractor trailer owners soberly reassessed their delivery contracts in light of the sudden steep rise in the price of diesel fuel (now averaging $8.50 a gallon nationwide). Dozens of the fuel hungry vehicles jammed truck-stops as drivers contemplated deliveries of goods that were in many cases now valued less than the fuel required to transport them to their destination. Additionally, the drivers of gasoline tanker trucks have flooded State Police switchboards with requests for armed escorts to their delivery locations. With US food distribution almost entirely dependent on long-haul trucking, economists are now forecasting a 50% to 60% rise in the cost of food and many other goods as all but certain.
 
President Obama has announced that he will address the nation at 7:00pm eastern time, however a brief statement issued by the Whitehouse press secretary earlier this morning, outlined some specifics of the Isreali attack and Iranian counter-attack, and an assessment damage thus sustained. Questions referring to any possible US military involvement or responces planed by US forces were deferred to the President's address this evening. President Obama is expected to focus on the detailed steps that will be taken by the US and other world leaders to deal with what is now expected to be a permanent spike in the price of energy in a world absent access to middle east oil. Many are speculating that the strict rationing of fuel, at least a temporary government takeover of domestic oil companies, and a mandated prioritization of deliveries of goods will be among the first steps outlined by the President. Others expect that an immediate freeze on wages and prices will be necessary as the economy adjusts to ongoing shortages and surpluses driven by unprecedented increases in transportation costs.

On the political front, GOP presidential contender Mitt Romney blasted the president's record on supporting Israel at a speech during a rally in Las Vegas this afternoon. The speech was cut short however, when members of the crowd began pelting the former Massachusetts governor with eggs. The assailants, numbering twenty or so, were apparently members of the local Occupy Wall Street movement. They managed to illicit some of Romney's most colorful speech yet as he referred to his tormentors "you poor little E'ffing bastards."</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/y3yeon</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ydw9</id></website><link>http://motherjones.com/node/166366</link><postedTime>2012-03-06T00:32:21+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-07T02:15:52+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mnks6r</id><link>http://motherjones.com/node/166366#comment-458343731</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h5kn0</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-06</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>