<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3u5va/update/2012-03-29T15:04:52/a8cd238226692d278c65d8f4ddb2dd51df589d099996f973ddef8634a4de4860</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I think this clearly shows why MS really is such a major company in the software business.  Unlike Apple and its closed garden system - which obviously has many benefits - MS has to deal with a HUGE install base that has to support a mind-boggling assortment of components and form-factors.  So to all those that point to Apple and mock MS, please understand that to do what MS does decade after decade is nothing short of a technological miracle.  True, their interface is not the slickest, some of their design choices are downright strange, but unfortunately, when you have to deal and support about 90% of the computers in the world (ok, number has been pulled out of thin air), there are inherent trade offs.  Moreover, note that MS's approach to open hardware really Propelled the computer/tech industry forward by leaps and bounds since the 80s.

Now imagine a world where Apple succeeded, instead of the IBM PC/MS-DOS duopoly...yes, you would indeed be using it wrong, holding it wrong, and if it's Too hot, put on some gloves.  As an analogy, it reminds me of a world where the dominant power is slowly becoming China and the US/UK is setting...1984 anyone?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zlokv</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/y2ru</id></website><link>http://www.engadget.com/2012/03/29/microsoft-reveals-how-your-old-slate-will-get-all-of-windows-8s/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:57:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:04:52+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3u5va</id><link>http://www.engadget.com/2012/03/29/microsoft-reveals-how-your-old-slate-will-get-all-of-windows-8s/#comment-479769409</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/66otm</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>