<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ta16/post/2012-03-29T09:25:30</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3vpu3</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/62tz3</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>For a start, that worker will not be getting his threshold rise for another year; then there is the issue of general price inflation, fuel and petrol costs etc; then there are the services that worker may use which are being closed down; on top of which he may well be losing tax credits, meaning that even when the threshold rise comes in his family's net income has been reduced.

Of course, you can argue each case on its individual merits, but they all accumulate. VAT was 17.5%, it is now 20% - so there's a few more pounds each year; it has been expanded - so there's a few more; fares are going up - so there's a few more; petrol's up too, as are energy bills - so there's a bit more. And if we get minimum pricing for alcohol, that's another additional expense.

Obviously, you do not have to buy takeaway pies, or cheap booze, or drive a car. You can turn your Heating down and walk to work instead of getting a bus; while your child does not have to have that weekly trip to the swimming pool or subsidised football training. But life also has to be worth living. Each little pleasure that you take away, each convenience that you remove, is going to piss people  a little bit more. And when you are giving tax cuts to the best Off, do not be surprised if a trivial thing like a Cornish pastie is the straw that breaks the camel's back.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z64rh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/xps8</id></website><link>http://www7.politicalbetting.com/index.php/archives/2012/03/29/marf-the-thick-of-it-continues/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T12:00:19+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:25:30+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ta16</id><link>http://www7.politicalbetting.com/index.php/archives/2012/03/29/marf-the-thick-of-it-continues/#comment-479485882</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6crm0</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>