<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ga40yi/update/2011-09-08T08:18:34/d1241a1e72fab9feee2cb440b3525e92f3f7586ff3212a3836631f5f5cde3727</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gar0cg</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cmyz3</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Tony and Amber, you just don't seem to understand! GIBSON uses WOOD, which ultimately comes from a TREE, and trees are more important to this administration than humans since otherwise, the Feds would be  something vastly more important in the end: abortion clinics! They praise people who set up camp on the top of trees and spit on those who camp out in front of abortion clinics. 

Don't they realize that those fetuses could be future Democrats, another group of living things that are also an endangered species?

If anyone cares more for trees, seals, whales, goats, and chickens, who get their beaks cut , than for a HUMAN FETUS, you have a serious problem! 

I heard Gibson is now looking into making their guitar necks with recycled plastic milk cartons to make the Greenies happy.  But a word of warning: Milk comes from cows whose FARTS are causing problems with the Ozone and the Feds will be  dairy's and ranches, especially in Texas, real soon. Trees Burning in Texas are okay though. "Burn baby Burn!"

Besides, GUITARS make music and bring harmony to the world and the President's, and Michelle's, favorite music, more like noise, is RAP CRAP, that doesn't use guitars, which screams out lyrics that no one can understand except when the lyrics are read, and then we're  we can't understand them since they are calling for the murder of cops and using the Blacks own  "N-Word" in every sentence! 

BREAKING NEWS: CEO OF GIBSON WILL BE SITTING IN SPEAKERS BOX FOR OBAMA'S SPEECH.

 The LEAST Mr. Juszkiewicz  could do to show RESPECT for the President is to bring him a gift of his latest guitar model: "THE NECK-LES  FRET-LES PAUL MODEL" so it's just the body with strings hanging down and wrapped around the tuning pegs.

ONLY SOLUTION: Move to India.  Instead of the Les Paul model, the first guitar Off the assembly line could be named the "Lohitaksha Parikshit!" 

(Lord Vishnu  and name of the ancient king Parimal.) (No I don't know Indian names. I googled them. Kinda like those names though.  I might switch.)</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/e91wgd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry2d</id></website><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=46024</link><postedTime>2011-09-07T20:25:25+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-09-08T12:18:34+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ga40yi</id><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=46024#comment-304896018</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ajkck</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-09-07</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>