<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mimzmg/update/2012-03-22T17:58:26/18f70961da690fd7029928927eef76bcd016167f81f7fdd1344261bd4b1f3d06</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/migfy1</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g1c7x</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I more or less volunteered to the bishop to talk with people having a crisis, esp over historical stuff. Since that time, I mentioned to him that I believe  on the person and their circumstances it can be healthy for them to leave the church. After I said this, I shared a personal story. On my mission in Ukraine, there weren't a lot of male members so frequently missionaries served in branch callings. I was the EQP in one branch and we had about 150 people on the roles but only ~30 came to church and only ~4 were men. So I spent most of my time in that area going through the list to remove people who had died/note when people had moved/invite people back. Well, one house (shack might be more appropriate, but issues of poverty and wealth are a different topic) a woman answered apparently her husband was the first branch president in that city. She told me about how her husband changed after joining the church at first there was some positive changes, but after getting the priesthood and being quickly made the leader of the church in that city the authority quickly went to his head. He started giving more orders at home, he didn't want the branch to see his family making mistakes so he started increasing punishments for the most minor of offenses. At church the whole family had to Act perfect, or they get physically punished at home. It was totally abusive. So she left him and took the kids. After being released, I don't think he stayed around very long. I just told this woman how sorry I was and that as much as I was capable of giving an apology I was giving it. I told her how counter everything about that experience was to the gospel and even what the church teaches. I invited her back, telling her that things were different now, but that I totally understood if she didn't think she could come back. As I thought about it that day as a missionary, I realized that there was no way that a loving God would deny her any blessings for avoiding the place that marked the beginning of an abusive relationship with her husband and was the cause of so much pain. 

After I told my bishop that story, I mentioned that we seem very willing in the church to push loose ends to the Millenium during which time all these problems we see with the church will be dealt with. 
A woman sealed to two husbands?, but whose wife will she be? -&gt; Millenium
A righteous woman can't find a husband before she dies, according to Joseph this means she's just an angel (that's why he married Brigham's aunt on the Spot, so she wouldn't be single after death.) What do we say now in the church? -&gt; Millenium
Is it really a stretch to say that people who have been harmed by the church or by a church leader and who leave the church as a result will get all the blessings anyway -&gt; in the Millenium?

He neither agreed nor disagreed. He just listened. So I think it is possible to try to do both. For my own selfish reasons (and I'll acknowledge this), I want people in faith crises to stay in the church. I want more people like that in my ward! However, at the end of the day it is their decision and I will neither love them less nor esteem them less for leaving. I think if we talk about it this way, it's hard to argue. I mean, you can also leverage the doctrine of agency and also some D&amp;C 121:45-46. If we truly believe that section 121 tells us how to use the priesthood, then we must acknowledge that we must have our "bowels also be full of charity towards all men" when trying to serve those who have chosen to leave the church, and only through charity and without compulsion should we try to encourage them to join us again. In my mind, this absolutely leaves open the possibility for them to chose to leave and still not change the relationship dynamic. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6d7ais</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zkv8</id></website><link>http://mormonmatters.org/2012/03/20/83-84-creating-spaces-for-non-traditional-latter-day-saints/</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T05:02:19+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T21:58:26+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mimzmg</id><link>http://mormonmatters.org/2012/03/20/83-84-creating-spaces-for-non-traditional-latter-day-saints/#comment-473996705</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gsqrn</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>