<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ssp9/post/2012-03-30T00:03:34</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>"Keep an open mind about natural gas and safe nuclear technologies as part of our energy mix. "

Sami, my goodness, you are finally starting to make some sense, and as a fellow Brit I urge you to read or at least browse 

Prof David MacKay's book "sustainable energy without the hot air", 

It's a free pdf, it should be required reading for every single TH writer and reader too. 

You know he is the scientific energy adviser to the UK gov and it is written in the UK context but it can be understood by any numerate person. All the physics can be skipped with no guilt, you just have to be honest about owning up to your current 120-240kWh/day/person footprint.

If you have read the book or TH already covered it several years ago, kudos, but from the way most articles are written here, I'd be surprised.

To get there he walks the reader through where all that energy comes from and where it goes to. And how calories, therms, BTUs, toe, barrels of oil, kWh, eV, J its all the same thing, just need to use conversion ratios, just like the old stupid English measurement system we all suffered. The ideal is to go to full SI and use kWh, J  with per day person.

He basically covers all forms of energy, that's where I used to get a lot of my info. He doesn't go all nuclear either, that's only 1 page, he stays neutral. He shows how the UK energy budget which is 5kW/person or 120kWh/d/p can be transformed to 70kWh/d/p. That's your'e total reduction right there, and there is no more than that to be had. After that it's a question of going without services, education, food and Heat, or life.

After achieving 70kWh/d/p you have practically no fossil fuels or CO2 in the system, or just enough for jet planes and some things. Most transport is electrified where ever possible esp EVs and that levels the grid day and night. 

He shows how it might just be possible to go mostly wind, or mostly solar via Africa, or nuclear and 2 others as mixes.

Once you understand the basics you can make your own energy mix but you must meet the 70kWh/d/p rule and pay for the consequences.

For all these plans he includes just a few kWh from biomass and hydro as the UK permits and just shares it out to all plans. He never includes solar in the UK, it's just too silly, but you can have it in Africa.

If you go with wind, you must figure out how to make up the shortfall, by importing from Norway or France etc through the interconnector pipe which right now is only 2GW wide. The UK needs 40GW right now, but after transferring fossil fuel to electric it must go up, and the EU can't send more than 2GW unless you build more pipes and pay the Europe for your storage charges.

If you go with Desert Tec Africa solar, you now need that pipe for most of your electrical, a very expensive &gt;40GW pipe all the way to Africa.

If you go mostly nuclear, that 2GW pipe now sends some power the other way to anyone in Europe that went and bought into too much wind or solar. He calls it the economy plan because it is the cheapest of the lot.

You see the picture now, the EU grid can only take up a certain amount of variability, the power guys will tell you 10% and no more or they have to throw up, or spend massively on storage or huge interconnectors which is uber expensive. At the end of the day, some energy supplier has to man up and stop being variable, and it must be 80% or more, and it won't be coal.

Once you have no more fossils, you can no longer cover the variability with gas, renewables gets so much harder with out fossils.

The US uses 240kWh/d/p so we have a lot more to fall, maybe 150kW/d/p with similar strategies.

Also on nuclear MacKay had barely heard of Thorium. He mentions it in passing as a solid fuel as in India (bad idea) and is 3x more plentiful than uranium. 

MacKay did not know about the LFTR which amongst all the many benefits I have mentioned over and over, it follows load, that is a killer right there, no storage needed at all. It can also shut down on the fly and start up in hours, but it is probably better to modulate to match load curve.

Cheers
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zti1i</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/amtr</id></website><link>http://www.treehugger.com/renewable-energy/farming-wind-teaches-us-about-future-energy.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:41:03+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T04:03:34+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ssp9</id><link>http://www.treehugger.com/renewable-energy/farming-wind-teaches-us-about-future-energy.html#comment-480226094</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rkupv</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>