<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwunxw/post/2012-03-30T23:02:25</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>There are at least two points that are  ignored by those supporting eliminating parking requirements.

1)  If you build housing without -street parking, many people who rent or buy those units will indeed have cars, which they will have to park on the street, which will indeed cause bad on-street parking problems.  There are many old apartment buildings in Seattle without any -street parking and many people who live in those buildings do have cars, and therefore have to park on the street.  This is a major problem, whether Publicola can grasp it or not.

2)  When people without cars buy or rent housing with -street parking, they should be allowed to rent their -street parking Spot to somebody else who does have a car.  This is done all the time in Seattle and other cities, and this can defray the cost of the parking Spot for those who don't own cars.

In other words, there is a good reason for parking requirements, and there is a very effective way for people who don't own cars to recoup the money they par for the parking Spot they don't need -- rent it to someone else.

This idea of building apartment buildings without Off-street parking will turn many Seattle neighborhoods into slums, like Capitol Hill.  What a shithole Capitol Hill is.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67tuow</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/e8xv</id></website><link>http://publicola.com/2012/03/30/eliminating-parking-requirements-is-not-the-same-as-prohibiting-parking/</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T00:29:37+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T03:02:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwunxw</id><link>http://publicola.com/2012/03/30/eliminating-parking-requirements-is-not-the-same-as-prohibiting-parking/#comment-481469974</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>