<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk9h4d/post/2012-03-26T13:28:24</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mku0zf</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> Miz couldn't win cleanly against Supercena? Uh just for your information, The Miz as WWE Champion couldn't win against any of his challenges (except King I think) cleanly. So don't pin point Cena out of everybody just because you're a damn hater. And just for the record The Miz sucks and no he does not deserve another main event at least not now. And while Cena and The Rock has been the main focus, they have not been focused around the WWE championship. Alberto Del Rio, and mainly CM Punk have taken that spotlight. And if you are trying to say The Miz is bigger than the WWE Championship, then you're clearly not as smart as you are trying to say you are. If you want to blame anybody for stealing the spotlight away from The Miz blame Cm Punk, Del Rio and hell you can blame The Miz himself for screwing up and almost injuring some one as well.

And again you have it wrong, trying to put blame on The Rock and Cena and at the same time contradicting yourself. You complain that Miz isn't in the main event, but while they (Miz &amp; truth) get a Spot in the main event against the Rock and Cena, you want them to take a back seat on the lower level for the Tag Team Titles. Yes Survivor Series was all about Cena and The Rock, but at least Miz and Truth was in the main event.

WWE also had plans on giving the team of Miz and Truth a run for the Tag Titles at TLC, but R-Truth screwed it up and was suspended for one month. I guess that was Cena and The Rock's fault as well. Meanwhile The Miz was awarded with yet another main event Spot in a Triple Threat Match between Punk, Del Rio and Miz for the WWE Championship. At an event that did not feature John Cena or The Rock in a match or segment, The Miz lost in the main event. Guess that was Cena and Rock's fault as well.

You suddenly stop in your tracks at Survivor Series, but you're not talking about The Royal Rumble, that was focused around CM Punk and Dolph Ziggler with Laurinaitis for the WWE Championship and the Rumble Match itself, both matches that did not feature John Cena. However I guess somehow Miz not making it to the top again is some how Cena's fault who was stuck with a feud with Kane over embracing the Hate.

I guess Miz not winning the Elimination Chamber to get himself into a title match is somehow supercena and Rock fault as well.

There is a reason why WWE is not banking on the Miz, because even they knows he sucks. And if Miz is as good as you are trying to claim he is, Miz would not have been part of one of the worst Wrestlemania main events in history, And before you squarely put blame on supercena, that same supercena had decent martches with Triple H, HBK and at WM24. Takes two to tango!

there is currently a whole lot of people better than the Miz and more deserving of ppv main event Spots than the Miz. And you can't tell me that Miz would have done a better job than Cena if it was announced after WM27 that The Rock will face The Miz. I assure you people would still be laughing their assess Off today, from that announcement.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rsish</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zf9l</id></website><link>http://www.sescoops.com/wrestling-news/wwe/foley-teases-hell-be-on-team-teddy-the-miz-responds/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T13:49:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:28:24+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk9h4d</id><link>http://www.sescoops.com/wrestling-news/wwe/foley-teases-hell-be-on-team-teddy-the-miz-responds/#comment-476561888</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>