<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/323728/post/127795378/comment/327530592</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Perhaps you could cite an example. It&amp;#039;s my understanding particle production requires, usually, a photon (which isn&amp;#039;t nothing). That photon must have enough energy for the creation to take place. Energy and momentum are conserved. 
 
If two things push  each other in a vacuum, what new mass is there? We can&amp;#039;t view each object as a system, because then the conservation of momentum doesn&amp;#039;t apply. Therefore, we have to view both objects in your example as part of the same system. No energy or mass are created within that system. There is simply a change in vectors, yes? 
 
You&amp;#039;re right. My use of E=mc^2 wasn&amp;#039;t directly applicable to the banana example. I should have started a new paragraph. Mass, however, is eventually converted to energy, which is demonstrably true since your body gives Off Heat. In my example, it was my intention to simplify for people not familiar with science. You&amp;#039;re right. This doesn&amp;#039;t take place in the digestive process directly. However, it &lt;em&gt;does&lt;/em&gt; take place. You would have been on much firmer ground if you&amp;#039;d pointed out the body isn&amp;#039;t a closed system. However, this was only an example of how mass and energy can be converted. Obviously, not all of it is. 
 
Please keep in mind the context of my statements. It is Hawking&amp;#039;s assertion the Universe &amp;quot;created itself&amp;quot; out of nothing. This means the total amount of mass and/or energy in the Universe changed, thus violating the laws of thermodynamics as I stated. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:323728:127795378</id><idPostId>127795378</idPostId><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:323728</id><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><link>http://www.chrisisright.net</link><displayName>Chris Is RIGHT</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2010/09/02/why-stephen-hawking-is-wrong/</link><displayName>Why Stephen Hawking is Wrong</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2010-09-02T14:55:47.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:323728:127795378:327530592</id><inReplyTo><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2010/09/02/why-stephen-hawking-is-wrong/#IDComment327530584</link></inReplyTo><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2010/09/02/why-stephen-hawking-is-wrong/#IDComment327530592</link><postedTime>2010-09-02T14:55:47.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Why Stephen Hawking is Wrong by ChrisIsRIGHT</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://chrisisright.wordpress.com</link><idEmailMd5>91cee804c778e52acf84568c44dfdeea</idEmailMd5><displayName>ChrisIsRIGHT</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://chrisisright.wordpress.com"&gt;ChrisIsRIGHT&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.chrisisright.net/2010/09/02/why-stephen-hawking-is-wrong/"&gt;Why Stephen Hawking is Wrong&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2010-09-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>