<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwz7jm/update/2012-03-30T14:28:26/2ae58db839b601ecee7e856ad16c0a3cabd49ed4d5503d486c492257f921c464</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzzwh</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cjp2b</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>One explanation of the Joshua blurb..oh so now Genesis is a "myth" thanks for that trashy, next time you profess to be a church-going Christian I'll have this to remind you of the phony hypocrite we all know you to be ; )

These four verses seem to be a fragment or extract taken from some other and independent source and inserted into the thread of the narrative after it had been completed, and inserted most probably by another hand than that of the author of the Book of Joshua.

It is probable that Joshua 10:12 and the first half of Joshua 10:13 alone belong to the Book of Jasher and are poetical, and that the rest of this passage is prose.

The writer of this fragment seems to have understood the words of the ancient song literally, and believed that an astronomical miracle really took place, by which the motion of the heavenly bodies was for some hours suspended. (Compare also Ecclesiasticus 46:4.) So likewise believed the older Jewish authorities generally, the Christian fathers, and many commentators ancient and modern.

It must be allowed, indeed, that some of the objections which have been urged against this view on scientific grounds are easily answered. The interference, if such there were, with the earth's motion was not an Act of blind power ab extra and nothing more. The Agent here concerned is omnipotent and omniscient, and could, of course, as well arrest the regular consequences of such a suspension of nature's ordinary working as He could suspend that working itself. It is, however, obvious, that any such stupendous phenomenon would affect the chronological calculations of all races of men over the whole earth and do so in a similarly striking and very intelligible manner. Yet no record of any such perturbation is anywhere to be found, and no marked and unquestionable reference is made to such a miracle by any of the subsequent writers in the Old or New Testament. For reasons like these, many commentators have explained the miracle as merely optical.

The various explanations show how strongly the difficulties which arise out of the passage have been felt. Accordingly, stress has been laid by recent commentators on the admitted fact that the words out of which the difficulty springs are an extract from a poetical book. They must consequently, it is argued, be taken in a popular and poetical, and not in a literal sense. Joshua feared lest the sun should set before the people had fully "avenged themselves of their enemies." In his Anxiety he prayed to God, and God hearkened to him. This is boldly and strikingly expressed in the words of the ancient book, which describes Joshua as praying that the day might be prolonged, or, in poetical diction, that the sun might be stayed until the work was done. Similarly, Judges 5:20 and Psalm 18:9-15 are passages which no one construes as describing actual occurrences: they set forth only internal, although most sincere and, in a spiritual sense, real and true convictions. This explanation is now adopted by theologians whose orthodoxy upon the plenary inspiration and authority of holy Scripture is well known and undoubted.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/678u06</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6bwl</id></website><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/jesse-watters/2012/03/30/watters-penetrates-atheist-rally-are-you-afraid-youre-going-hell</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T12:05:49+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:28:26+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwz7jm</id><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/jesse-watters/2012/03/30/watters-penetrates-atheist-rally-are-you-afraid-youre-going-hell#comment-481043779</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rcm2j</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>