<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjotw/update/2012-03-26T14:50:15/7e1adbaf6a590436a4d611b544bec59d77aafacfbfb35766d359a326fef8eb34</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk9018</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rc3ed</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Check. No magic bullet. No [violence-saturated metaphor for] a quick and easy solution. And yes, we really have to stop Burning fossil fuels soon. But according to physicist Allan Yeoman, if we increased the organic content (aka carbon) of all the arable soils in the world 1.8% we would recapture all the carbon released during the industrial age. Of course we can't do it on all the world's arable land, and it won't happen all at once, but 20% on a little of it, 10% on some, 5% on a fair amount, and 1-2% on a lot would accomplish the same thing. This is completely possible economically and technologically. Every acre of new forest and reinvigorated soil is some carbon sequestered (how much Depends on forest density and degree of soil improvement). As long as that forest and soil are left the carbon remains sequestered. As long as it continues to grow it sequesters more by itself, for free. And as long as we continue to expand the area of forest and good soil we continure to immediately sequester more carbon. Let me point out, or remind you, that the Green Belt movement started by the late Wangari Maathai has in just a few decades planted something on the order of 10 billion trees, in the hardest place in the world to do it.  After a long slow start because of misogynist and establishment resistance, that planting has accelerated tremendously in the past decade and continues to grow. 

The carbon is removed from the atmosphere as soon as it's in the ground, or in the tree. Of course there's a lag time for temperature, because of the pipeline effect of oceans and Heating lag, Of course we're going to suffer because we've waited too long. Yes, it will take thousands of years at least to completely recover, tens of millions to recover the diversity because of mass extinction. Is that a reason to work harder or to give up? We can save civilization in the next few decades. Many species are becoming extinct now; more will. We can still save most. The ocean is Heating, ice and methane clathrates are melting. Planting trees, especially food forests to replace our current carbon-intensive, soil-destroying way of growing food, can accomplish a number of crucial goals at the same time, and buy us time starting immediately, to clear away obstructionists and replace coal, oil, gas and nukes with efficiency, solar, wind, and changed lives. 

It's a race, between the current downward direction of destruction and the current upward spiral of revivification. We don't know the future. We don't know what humans are going to do, or can do, or will or won't do. One thing we do know is that both hope and despair will keep us from doing what we need to do. Another thing we know is that belief in systems can collapse and change incredibly quickly. The collapse of millennia-old Native American (S, C, and N) societies in a month, a year or a few decades, the collapse of the Berlin Wall or the USSR, the change Occupy has created, the volatility of belief in global warming according to ongoing and changeable inputs... all point to how fast things can change. So please, take your despair to a therapist and then come help us do what we need to do.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yev2v</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ant8</id></website><link>http://www.alternet.org/visions/154652/new_technology_may_make_it_possible_to_capture_carbon_right_out_of_the_air/comments/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T01:45:06+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:50:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjotw</id><link>http://www.alternet.org/visions/154652/new_technology_may_make_it_possible_to_capture_carbon_right_out_of_the_air/comments/#comment-476627974</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rcx7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>