<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw5jua/post/2012-03-30T06:22:02</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3jhc8</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z6xjn</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>In response to avln, this story is about economy, I do not know where you took the argument that all Estonians are whining Nazis? :D Just ridiculous. Yes, we have a small group of skin-heads in Tartu who think they are badass Neo-Nazis, but that hardy mirrors the entire country. And every country has a small segments of political radicalism.
Secondly, whining? Seriously? A country that picked itself up from an economical hell by implementing austerity measures with NO protesting or demonstrations whatsoever. Plus I think it is the Estonians prerogative to be worried where their taxmoney goes. And everything that they say is true: unempolyement: EST 13.8 % Greece 6.8%; minimum wage: EST 278 Greece 863; medium wage: EST 792 Greece: 2323 (may vary a little bit by now) but overall the fact is easy to Spot: the Greeks are WAY better Off. To add to that Estonia has fierce winters and surviving this third of the income goes to extra clothing/Heating etc which the Greece hardly have to do. So I do not think they are whining with no reason. 
Having said all that I definitely support the decision to support another eurozone country in need. We should know what economic need is. Plus we have collected euro support money for years, our turn to give back.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zthop</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/business/estonia-pm-marketplace-europe/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:19:40+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T10:22:02+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw5jua</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/business/estonia-pm-marketplace-europe/index.html#comment-480592621</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzkfe</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>