<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mx04jp/update/2012-03-08T19:24:40/81806fcdf1d06e8f1af88882f0e8ea1ad4bd90be16a27ab147a0781a9ae66a15</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mxv281</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g9w1y</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Venom is amongst my absolute favorite Marvel characters, and obviosly Carnage is the penultimate potential villain for Venom, but I honestly don't think that he would make for a good first villian. Venom is too involved in the creation of Carnage, and all of that would have to be covered before Carnage himself was introduced, and considering that we would also have to establish Venom's character and story, which would take up a lot of time because Venom is a very complex character, I don't think that it would do Carnage justice.

Play it like they did Batman, I say. Joker was the ultimate Batman villian, but Nolan held  on using him until the second movie because he wouldn't have fit the story and trying to shoehorn him in would have detracted both from the Batman charcter development and origin story and from the Joker story. Similarly, I think that it would be better if you set Carnage up in the first movie, utilize a much less psychologically complex villian who can be interesting and be involved in Venom's character development, but won't try and share the Spot-light.

Perhaps someone like Kraven the Hunter would work well (or any similar sort of renegade  Hunter who would hunt Venom and play himself up as the hero, but actually be evil). Or even someone like Kingpin. Maybe Kingpin can even hire Kraven (or whoever, to kill Venom) Here is how I would do it.

Venom's origin should also be very well defined. I agree that he should be a dark character, but at the same time he should be a heroic character. Eddie Brock should fit this as well. I would like to see a story where he wanted to be a hero but his violent personality got in the way (even before becoming Venom), like maybe he tried out at the police acadamy but was thrown out because he beat another trainee up in anger.

Low on money, he got a job working for a newspaper, where his job was to investigate as much information as he could about a "certain famous vigilante", (obviously Spider-man, but not mentioned by name) and he believed the paper's lies about him being a criminal. However there was an incident where the vigilante was trying to save a group of people and because of Brock's interference, a little girl died (and he realized he was wrong about the vigilante). So now he is on a sort of journey to try and do some soul searching, being low on money he was offered a job as a night security guard by his father who works at a laboratory where they are doing some very Secret research on a potential cure for cancer. What he discovers is that they are actually researching this living ooze that was descovered on an asteroid and as such is the only extra-terrestrial live ever discovered by man, but that can replicate it's cells at an extremely fast rate (thus a potential cancer cure if they figure out how).

One knight a group of professional criminals break into the building to steal the ooze (Kingpin figures that will be worth a lot of money to someone, or perhaps he even wants to study it himself), and Eddie tries to stop them, following them into the lab, but they shoot him, the bullet also fragmenting the glass on the oozes container. As he lays Bleeding, the ooze seeps through the glass and bonds to him, turning him into Venom and giving him the strength to kill all the criminals. Horrified at what he has done (lets say instead of just amplifying agression, it amplifies all characteristics of the host, including Eddie's rage and violence, but also his heroic desires), he flees, but is seen by several people and the local cops.

Kingpin first tries to hire Venom, but when he is shot down, he hires Kraven to hunt Venom down and take the symbiote from him. And the story progresses from there :D

All in all, I would play Venom as a sort of mix between Hulk and Punisher, a lethal protector, but also a hated and misunderstood monster who at times is afraid to use his power (but isn't as reluctant as the Hulk because he strongly desires to be a hero, and knows that this is the only way that he can do so). He should hve no qualms whatsoever about killing evildoers, but his major character delimma should be whether it is more important to kill the evil doers or protect the innocent, and in the end the Eddie side wins out and he lets Kraven go in order to save the innocents that Kraven put in danger (of course, he manages to get Kraven in the end anways).

That would be my perfect Venom movie. Carnage would come next, when his character is more solidified as a hero in the potential sequal.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ywj5ce</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7d9s</id></website><link>http://movies.ign.com/articles/122/1220223p1.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-07T22:24:42+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-09T00:24:40+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mx04jp</id><link>http://movies.ign.com/articles/122/1220223p1.html#comment-460192457</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l5deg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-07</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>