<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3usi4/post/2012-03-29T15:40:43</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The 'Wendolene' puppet of the union movement will do whatever his masters tell him to do - after all they 'arranged' for him to get the job.

It is time for responsible media outlets to give us the full details of Labour politicians and their promoters/backers and explain their rise through the Left's network of nepotism.

We have lived for decades with the remnants of the Cold War communists in British politics and in many ways we have forgotten just what motivates them, their agenda (explains much about George Galloway) and their modus operandi.

Now would be a good time for the media - particularly those old enough to have long personal memories) to explain the thinking and organising behind the Left.  

For example their Secret plan which they brutally executed to occupy Britain with unlimited immigration and deliberately attacking anyone who questioned this with threats of job loss, calls of racism, isolation and negative labels.

It was obvious that the union movement would gang together and use mob tactics to mislead and bully the British people with little regard to their needs or the fragile British economy - what care they for business when they want state control of everything - and as the USSR demonstrated some are more equal than others.

Ed Miliband is just a pawn and we all know it so let us not waste time on what he says or does - please tell us what his masters and saying and doing for they are the real power in the Labour party.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hodoq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/comment/telegraph-view/9171485/Is-Ed-Miliband-for-or-against-a-fuel-crisis.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T19:37:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:40:43+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3usi4</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/comment/telegraph-view/9171485/Is-Ed-Miliband-for-or-against-a-fuel-crisis.html#comment-479806218</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a3ven</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>