<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m313ng/post/2012-03-29T16:26:03</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>How would you feel if you learned that you were the baby conceived five months after it had been revealed to your mother by your father that he'd been having an affair? All while trying desperately to reconcile and work on the marriage. Then you learn that your mother was devastated at the pregnancy; she only wanted one child (your sister) and immediately blamed your father for the pregnancy in anger. 

Your mother has Narcissist Personality Disorder. You're the Scapegoat Child; your sister the Golden Child. Although you're the over-achiever, perfectionist, the one praised for your successes -- you're also the one stuck in a being loved/being rejected cycle (some separations lasting upwards of 2 years at a time; some as short as 6 months) for ten years, and all for making a statement here or there that rubbed your mother the wrong way. She taught you to stand up, speak your mind (with grace), but to be honest. But when you use that lesson on her, she cuts you out of her life. She sends you cards at Christmas or when she hears of a life change (email for your birthday, though) and  signs it "A Mother's Love Is Forever" or "You'll Never Know How Much I Love You" but rejects being a part of your life. 

She was the near perfect SAHM; she seemed to adore you growing up and, especially when you were making her shine. For example: she was a dancer/you became a professionally trained dancer; she was captain of her cheerleading squad/you  in high school; you also married a wonderful man who adores you, whom you love with all your heart; you have a beautiful home and a quiet life a few hours away from the family due to jobs. In the past, your mother has told you she can't believe you moved away from the family because no one in your family has ever done such a thing. Family is important, after all. You learn that she harbors jealousy over your life -- your own mother. That when you're rising and she's falling, she's at her most miserable.

Your big sister (who used to lock you in closets when no one was around) who you've tried over the years to establish a relationship with is the needy one and has all her needs met by your mother. She's the protected one. The under-achiever who can't stand on her own two feet. The one who is so intertwined with your mother that she, herself, can't bear your presence. In fact, she'd prefer you weren't even part of the family. Her best friend told you a couple years after your wedding: "Do you want to know why your sister hates you so much?" You said, "I would. Do you know?" She answers: "Your huge wedding. Your perfect husband. Your fancy home. Your relationship with your dad that she doesn't have..." And the list went on and on to your horror.

So you go to church. Fall apart one Sunday in the pews. Decide something's terribly unhealthy about the way your mother relates to you. And that her periods of abrupt and long-term rejection of you is slowly eating away at your soul and making you second guess who you even are. You second guess wanting to pursue fertility treatments for fear that maybe you wouldn't make a good mother. Because if your own mother can't love you, how can you then go on to love a child in a healthy way? You're trying to stop whatever cycle this is and are determined to not pass on some genes that might be responsible for all this. Your doing society a favor. Or so you think. So you talk with Molly, the psychologist. And learn you're not the problem after all. That you're likely a Daughter of a Narcissistic Mother. And all those memories you have of your mother as a child; all the wonderful memories you have of your mother helping to plan your wedding; all the mother/daughter shopping trips...they happened. But as the years went on, her NPD took a choke hold on your mother, severe depression and Anxiety set in and she's not that mother any longer. The one you remember. And you're going on one and a half years of not seeing your mother. 

And you learn this. That you were the "After the Affair Baby." The "Fix It Baby" (unplanned version and not really all that successful because your parents' marriage ended 13 years later).

When your dad praises you for working through your hurt (that he so wishes he could take away) caused by your mother's rejection, he tells you something you  knew (that he'd had an affair), but somehow, having your mother cram it down your throat for so many years gave you time to process it and forgive. You hear it for the first time in your life coming out of his mouth, addressing you: 

"Sweetheart, I have something I want to share with you. Something I've never had the courage to share. I had an affair. It was a woman I worked with. It was all revealed about five months before you were conceived..."

And all you can think to say is, "Thank you for sharing that with me, dad. It took a lot of courage to do that. And I love you."

And all you can think to feel is...now it all makes sense. You represent all that was lost. You represent pain. No wonder she can't stand you. No wonder she and your sister are so close and you're the one left out in the Cold.

And then he tells you, "I want to prepare you...your sister scheduled family photos. Honey, please don't cry."

And in that instant, you felt erased.

*This was very personal and difficult for me to share. But I need someone to hear it. Someone who has no connection to hear it. I may delete it, so please don't be put Off if I do. For now, I feel safe enough to share it. My heart is hurting deeply today and I'm just trying to process everything.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hk6of</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7fwk</id></website><link>http://mwopblog.com/2012/03/open-floor-43/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T21:47:06+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:26:03+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m313ng</id><link>http://mwopblog.com/2012/03/open-floor-43/#comment-479853797</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zlb7b</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>