<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0mcih/post/2012-03-31T20:57:41</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Hon. Stephen Harper,
Prime Minister of Canada.

Dear Mr. Harper,

It has been repeatedly reported that you have said the debate on abortion will not be re-opened.

You personally have said, under your administration, there will be no debate on abortion.

That is an autocratic decision demeaning democracy.

In effect, it means that you, personally, condone abortion and its consequences. You are protecting abortion.

May I ask you to reflect a little on what you are protecting.

First of all you are protecting brutal medical procedures that kill children in the womb by either dismembering them or poisoning them. By any civilised standard, that should cause shame.

Secondly, in protecting this brutal procedure, you are depriving Canada of:

- children who can love and be loved
- children to play in the parks
- children who can fill our schools
- children who one day will become responsible adults
- decent hard working people who are the backbone of any nation
              - who produce the goods we Depend on
              - the caring people, those who adopt
              - the nurses and teachers, those who keep our neighbourhoods clean and fit to live in
              - the doctors and researchers
              - the geniuses who push out the boundaries of knowledge
              - the truck drivers who bring us goods
              - those who design and maintain our roads
              - those who build and maintain our homes, who provide the Heating and lighting
              - those who produce and supply our food, our clothing and our needs

... the list is endless.

And you, by your intransigence, do not want this subject discussed. You will not allow the alternatives to be examined:

- how we can support those who have difficult pregnancies
- how we can develop proper and generous support systems and facilities
- how we can just be decent people looking after one another in times of trouble.

You are denying us the opportunity of enhancing our culture with this nobility.

Perhaps, when you are watching your own children ... give this matter some thought and try to answer the question:

- what constitutes a noble culture that seeks the common good of all - including the unborn.

Then, perhaps, you will be in a position to measure your own position on abortion against some ideals and aspirations for a caring culture.

Respectfully,
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67mly8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/1to1</id></website><link>http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/canadian-teen-launches-campaign-to-send-100000-pro-life-letters-to-prime-mi</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:46:31+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-01T00:57:41+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0mcih</id><link>http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/canadian-teen-launches-campaign-to-send-100000-pro-life-letters-to-prime-mi#comment-482381365</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/r0q5o</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>