<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzmjt/post/2012-03-30T14:18:24</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Bruce, your comments about being controlling reminds me of an incident in a church I once attended, where the pastor, though Always soft-spoken and seemingly "nice", was nevertheless a control freak. At one point he decided (actually, "God" told him) that our little church needed to donate $50,000 to another church (a famous mega-church) for their building project. "God" told him that if we did that, it would constitute "seed" for our own church, which God would repay a hundred-fold. Our little church was made up of ordinary people with ordinary jobs. There were really no rich people in the church, so raising 50 grand for another church was no easy thing. In order to get the giving in high gear, the pastor challenged each of us to donate $1,000 for the project. If each adult in the church were to donate $1,000, that would get us close to the goal of 50 grand. Well, a thousand bucks is a lot of money for the parishioners, who were already giving at least 10% of their income, and this donation is over-and-above that. People naturally were slow to respond, so then the pastor started turn up the Heat and turn on the pressure-tactics. He would say things like "I can't MAKE you give the money, but IF I AM YOUR PASTOR, then you WILL give it. If you don't do it, you are being disobedient to the man that God has given to you as your pastor - the one who watches over you're spiritual life. If you don't do it, then I'm not your pastor. You can still attend this church if you want, but even if you do I will not be your pastor." That got some people to dig deep and shell out the thousand bucks, but only some people - not nearly enough. So then every Sunday he would ask those who had given the thousand bucks to stand up, and then he would praise them for their obedience and generosity. Of course, the REAL reason he had them stand up was to shame all of those were remained seated! He just kept up the pressure relentlessly week after week, until most, but not all, had shelled out the bucks. Eventually it became clear that they still were not going to meet the goal, so then he came up with a NEW challenge. The new challenge was toward those who had already given the thousand bucks. Now he challenged them to give ANOTHER thousand bucks! And again, he would have those who gave a second thousand bucks stand up in church in order to shame those who hadn't. I don't think there was a single person in that church who believed "God" was behind all this. It was pretty obvious that this was nothing more than our ambitious pastor trying to get the attention of a famous mega-church pastor, in order to, hopefully, with the help of that mega-church pastor, ride his coattail to his own entrance into the "big time". It was all just so ugly!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zwxak</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/feum</id></website><link>http://fallenfromgrace.net/2012/03/30/what-about-you-bruce/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T08:14:14+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:18:24+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzmjt</id><link>http://fallenfromgrace.net/2012/03/30/what-about-you-bruce/#comment-481033421</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>