<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/e0yqvb/update/2012-01-27T01:24:15/193ecf34430b0e583c6c0539ac0f7724ec6825df4c039017c126a137c7f3498a</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gh9ub9</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>First Off let me say, I am a medical doctor with a degree in nutrition in conjunction to me being a practicing ob. So after 10 years of University and another 21 years as a practicing doctor I am qualified to say, " Nutritionally it is impossible to create the perfect bar/shake/whatever the form, becuase everyone’s diet (what you eat) is different. I hate to break it to you but even 1-a-day vitamins are a bad option. You should not take supplements unless you have seen a doctor, vitamin C and other water soluble vitamins may have an extremely high tolerance level before you hit the UL but that does not mean that there are any advantages to taking more than the recommended amount. Free advice, it is a myth that vitamin C cures Colds, yes it does help your immune systems but you get enough of that in your daily eating. Excess vitamin C actually has been shown in the most recent study’s (8 in the last 15 years! All independent, highly respected) it has been shown that increased dosages of vitamin C (dosages were within the amount sold in pill form) cause a 27-40% increase in the amount of Colds and an increase in duration patients got compaired to those taking the placebo and those who took neither. So we as humans eat, and when we eat, we take in nutrients from foods, most people get sufficient nutrients from just eating!  But I am digressing, my point is that, as a meal replacement not a supplement this is the most nutritionally balanced product I have seen to date. My sister and a friend are on it and have gotten results; and not unrealistic unhealthly results but good results. So Foxx either keep your uneducated comments to yourself because A) any first year university student who has taken 1 nutrition class would be able to identify its nutritional value, and B) Who goes into business just wanting to break even…no one! Plus you should know that on top of that $2.00 there are more costs (shipping, packaging, overhead, advertisement, salaries and more). Also ‘diets’ are one of the most lucrative markets, worth billions because most are either very expensive to maintain,  or very unhealthy (any diet wanting you to cut over 500 kcal=calories from your diet, please run away, do not walk, RUN! You should be cutting a max of 500 kcal from what a person with your height, weight, size, activity level medically should consume, and that can be all diet, all exercise or a combination of both.) I did mean for this just to be a short comment, not a short story but my take home is 'if you are NOT an expert on the subject do NOT give your opinion, which resembles no fact. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/eynqls</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/72ay</id></website><link>http://darrenlittle.com/visalus-review/</link><postedTime>2011-08-06T18:25:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-01-27T06:24:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/e0yqvb</id><link>http://darrenlittle.com/visalus-review/#comment-422028742</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-08-06</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>