<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9r6e7/update/2012-03-16T22:13:46/451ed15b5957b67381c877a8250b8599ce209802f62fa3233d7a0cb3256e7410</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>i am not using cannabis these days, i dont really need it right now.  during my chemo last year i smoked 3 times a day and was amazed at the powerful Nausea relief.  my background is in law enforcement and i am a grandmother too, and i was pretty far beyond my  zone when it came to finding someplace to get my DOCTOR RECOMMENDED cannabis.
walked into two places, including N cross and both times the verification process was pretty intensive.  took me 2 days to get into the first place because i arrived on a saturday, and they could not Reach my oncologist. even though i had my papers and ID, they were completely thorough.  the employees were not of my generation and had tattoos and whatnot, but i saw nothing except for professional service, and focus on which strains and products would help the most. no smoking weed, getting high talk.  no speakeasy attitude.

there were 3 dozen delivery services in town when i got my recommendation, i assume they were undisturbed by the city.
I never felt comfortable using them.  dont like the idea of someone coming to my home.  and my son is a cop, and his car would probably freak the driver out pretty good.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/65pajc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dne9</id></website><link>http://www.bellinghamherald.com/2012/03/15/2439079/bellingham-police-raid-medical.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-16T02:11:24+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-17T02:13:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9r6e7</id><link>http://www.bellinghamherald.com/2012/03/15/2439079/bellingham-police-raid-medical.html#comment-467459655</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8v9br</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-16</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>