<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/323728/post/127795602/comment/327533112</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I&amp;#039;m sorry for your situation. But McCarthy has worked tirelessly supporting this claim that has been known false for several years. I feel no less sorry for her that she is short on answers. We NEED to find a cure for autism, and if there is a genetic marker ... or something ... that makes some kids susceptible, then yeah. We definitely need to study that. 
 
But I can&amp;#039;t condone anything less than 100% condemnation of Wakefield. Not only has their been a resurgence of measles and mumps, but some kids have died as a result. 
 
Greg mocks everything. I&amp;#039;ve heard McCarthy speak, and I find her reprehensible. I understand she cares about her son and about the cause of autism. But I personally find her vile. 
 
The fact is, if there is some sort of link between MMR vaccines, or even with measles itself, and an increase in autism, Wakefield&amp;#039;s study has hurt the chances of finding it, because now people are convinced he is wrong. Which he is, but he&amp;#039;s hurt the real science that might follow as a result of his scam. 
 
For example, the thing about mercury: how much mercury is in an average Flu shot? Now how much is in a can of tuna? 
 
I think caution and optimism are good things, but when I hear McCarthy speak, I&amp;#039;ve just as often heard panic and doom saying. That&amp;#039;s just me. I feel differently about AIDS, as I lost a partner to AIDS, as well as about 20 friends. It&amp;#039;s more personal, more subjective. 
 
I understand how you feel on this  issue, and on the fundamentals, I think we agree: more research, better research, more patient/parent awareness of the risks of vaccinations. For example, I never get Flu shots. Nor did I get a meningitis vaccine when I went back to University. 
 
I just don&amp;#039;t think we should be too hard on Gutfeld, either. McCarthy has made some bizarre statements and some ludicrous demands, along with her concern.  
 
It&amp;#039;s a sticky wicket. And I&amp;#039;m Glad so many people, especially you and Melissa - who are more closely affected by this issue than the rest of us - chimed in so eloquently. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:323728:127795602</id><idPostId>127795602</idPostId><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:323728</id><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><link>http://www.chrisisright.net</link><displayName>Chris Is RIGHT</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/01/07/red-eye-that-damnable-doctor-wakefiel/</link><displayName>Red Eye: That Damnable Doctor Wakefield</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-01-08T20:26:43.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:323728:127795602:327533112</id><inReplyTo><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/01/07/red-eye-that-damnable-doctor-wakefiel/#IDComment327533110</link></inReplyTo><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/01/07/red-eye-that-damnable-doctor-wakefiel/#IDComment327533112</link><postedTime>2011-01-08T20:26:43.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Red Eye: That Damnable Doctor Wakefield by Chris Barnhart</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/members/admin/</link><idEmailMd5>44c21cc82d082fef73b7270f48c95267</idEmailMd5><displayName>Chris Barnhart</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://www.chrisisright.net/members/admin/"&gt;Chris Barnhart&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/01/07/red-eye-that-damnable-doctor-wakefiel/"&gt;Red Eye: That Damnable Doctor Wakefield&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2011-01-08</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>