<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwn9cp/post/2012-03-30T19:55:11</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>If Only They Wrote it Larger..

    "For terrestrial radiation, water vapor is the most important single constituent of the lower atmosphere, although carbon dioxide is Always significant.."
Atmospheric Radiation: Theoretical Basis, Goody &amp; Yung, Oxford University Press (1989, 2nd edition)

    "Water vapor is the most important atmospheric greenhouse gas.. Carbon dioxide is the second most important greenhouse gas.."
Radiation and Climate, Vardavas &amp; Taylor, Oxford University Press (2007)

    "Generally speaking, water vapor is the single most important atmospheric absorber in the IR band.

    No other atmospheric constituent is better known to the general public as a “greenhouse gas” than CO2. In actuality, water vapor has a larger overall impact on the radiative energy budget of the atmosphere."
A First Course in Atmospheric Radiation, Grant Petty, Sundog Publishing (2006)

    "Water vapor is the most important gas for the transfer of radiation in the atmosphere."
Global Physical Climatology, Hartmann, Academic Press (1994)

    "Table 6 shows the relative contributions of H2O, CO2 and O3 to reducing the outgoing longwave flux, from which it is seen that the longwave effect of H2O is significantly larger than the effects of CO2 and O3."
Climate Modeling through Radiative-Convective Models, Ramanathan &amp; Coakley, Reviews of Geophysics and Space Physics (1978)

    "The importance of water vapor in regulating climate is undisputed. It is the dominant greenhouse gas, trapping more of Earth’s Heat than any other gaseous constituent."
The Radiative Signature of Upper Tropospheric Moistening, Soden, Jackson, Ramaswamy, Schwarzkopf &amp; Huang, Science (2005)

    "The dominant role of water vapor as a greenhouse gas has long been noted."
The Importance and Nature of the Water Vapor Budget in Nature and Models, Lindzen, Climate Sensitivity to Radiative Perturbations: Physical Mechanisms and Their Validation (1996)

    "The authors find that for the clear sky case the contribution due to water vapor to the total longwave radiative forcing is 75 W/m², while for carbon dioxide it is 32 W/m²."
Earth’s Annual Global MeanEnergy Budget, Kiehl &amp; Trenberth, Bulletin of the American Meteorological Society (1997)

    "Water vapor is the dominant greenhouse gas, the most important gaseous source of infrared opacity in the atmosphere."
Water Vapor Feedback and Global Warming, Held &amp; Soden, Annual Review Energy Environment (2000)

In fact, it’s so well-known that most times in papers it isn’t repeated. No one involved in atmospheric physics is confused about the subject.

http://scienceofdoom.com/2011/02/24/water-vapor-vs-co2-as-a-greenhouse-gas/ </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hthio</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ms5i</id></website><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/jamesdelingpole/100147742/queensland-turns-the-tide-of-environmental-lunacy/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T16:15:26+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T23:55:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwn9cp</id><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/jamesdelingpole/100147742/queensland-turns-the-tide-of-environmental-lunacy/#comment-481337129</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zh852</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>