<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39z44/post/2012-03-29T17:35:17</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms99aq</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5k8id</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Thanks for the explanation. Yes, I can see the limitation with the altimeter. It's just disappointing because, I would like to calibrate it before a hike (or a mountain climb) but if I  have an accurate calibration and start climbing up to a certain altitude while tracking the changes using the log... how will I ever know if the tracking is accurate? Also to calibrate the altimeter, I need to put in the correct sea level pressure in the reference setting? Where as to calibrate the barometer, I need to put in the correct altitude? I thought just putting in either value would be ok. Hmm.. I use google earth to find the elevation at home and at work. I set the correct altitude for home and when I get to work the altitude for work doesn't match up... and vice versa. It's  by anywhere from 60-100ft. Also, at work when I set a correct reference altitude outside the door, walk upstairs to my office... and come back down to the outside again during my break... the altitude is different from the one that I had previously set at the same Spot. Hmm... maybe that was the varing air pressure you refer to even in normal stable weather conditions.  As for the GPS + barometer in watch thing... that would probably be more accurate... but probably also more expensive and Battery draining. At that point, I might consider just getting a Garmin eTrex GPS or something. I wonder how accurate those are?</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/5d5lz2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7d5r</id></website><link>http://www.backpackingnorth.com/2010/10/suunto-core-extreme.html</link><postedTime>2011-03-16T14:37:34+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T21:35:17+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39z44</id><link>http://www.backpackingnorth.com/2010/10/suunto-core-extreme.html#comment-479922426</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-03-16</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>