<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ga8j59/update/2011-09-07T08:22:36/f505f77df3e86098bd786c9418f02ffec0b7a1fd449bdea542d2f6ef9e5c2af8</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>HEATED DEBATE:


THIS MORNING, FOX ANCHOR  GRETCHEN CARLSON, LOWERS THE BAR AND GIVES WASSERMAN-SCHULTZ AIR TIME

Gretchen Carlson:  "Mrs. Wasserman-Schultz, I would like to ask you once more before the hard break, do you, or do you not condone the language and the...the vitriolic tone of Hoffa, Jr.....I mean do you insist that, that.....no, enough of that....I only have a few minutes left and I would like to ask you what all of America wonders:  Do you live in an abandoned car?"
Wasserman-Schultz:  "Do I.....again, are you kidding?  What do you me....."
Gretchen Carlson:  "I mean, how dare you come in here without shampooing that mess on your head or from even having the decency of showeri..."
Wasserman-Schultz (sniffing under her own arms): "I, I......you....wha...."
Gretchen Carlson:  "I am a former Miss America, and for you to show up in an interview with me looking like a slattern, did you think you were going to get a pass?"
Wasserman-Schultz: "What has this got to do wi....."
Gretchen Carlson:  "I'll tell you what!  As DNC Chair, you earn nearly $140.000.00 a year.  Are you telling me you can't fall into some God forsaken Walgreen's somewhere and purchase a loofa, bar of soap, toothpaste and a cheap comb?"
Wasserman-Schultz: "Listen you sonovabyotch, you can go straight to h e 1 1 and take your....."
Gretchen Carlson:  "Oh!  REALLY?  (Turns to camera)  There's your 'Democratic Civility' America.  Out of the potty mouth of a soon to be out of work Floridian that looks like a bag lady.  (To Waserman-Schultz) So you'd like to say you threw down with an ex-Miss America?  O.K. byotch.  BRING IT!"
(Both up and circling one another like two Sumo's, Carlson throwing  her classy Prada pumps, Wasserman-Schultz, tossing aside her Birkenstocks)
Carlson: "Hey, props!  Bring me a clothes pin for my nose....this s k an k smells!" (Turns to the camera)  America...this is what happens to a mess that rolls out of bed, wraps up with a dirty bed sheet, stumbles into a FOX courtesy limo  and shows up to insult a former Miss America with leg stubble, dirty feet and 5:00 shadow.   SICK OF IT!"

(They rumble)  Carlson:  "I'm gonna rip that shower curtain right Off a' you...Let's MOVE!"</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/efpew9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6bwl</id></website><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/james-hoffa/2011/09/06/heated-debate-dnc-refuses-condemn-hoffa-hate-fox-friends</link><postedTime>2011-09-06T12:34:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-09-07T12:22:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ga8j59</id><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/james-hoffa/2011/09/06/heated-debate-dnc-refuses-condemn-hoffa-hate-fox-friends#comment-304138970</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8nldh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-09-06</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>