<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwt2ky/post/2012-03-30T16:29:35</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Are you kidding, Jeep247? This is the problem when liberals try to retaliate -- they bring their ignorance front and center for the world to see.

Bill did NOT say he served the Nixon administration for 60 years. If you bothered to read his comment and don't analyze it through your Huffington Post-tinged filter, you'd understand it's another way of saying, "I'm 60 years old, served under 2 Presidents and voted Democrat mostly my entire life..."

He did NOT mean he served the administration for 60 years. See, this is exactly why it is damn near impossible to even converse with the Bleeding hearts of America -- you all just flip on the ignorant switch in your head and only read what you want to read. And your retorts to genuine comments and concerns can be best described as rotten fertilizer.

Please join the ranks of all other liberals, hippies, occupiers, Obama worshippers, Jesse Jacksons, Al Sharptons and head-in-the-clouds celebrities who are as worthwhile as car alarms: they go Off so loud and so often for no reason at all that after a while, people just start ignoring them.

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yag0s</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f7e3</id></website><link>http://wp.wnd.com/2012/03/sheriff-joe-tons-more-shocking-obama-info/</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T20:39:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T20:29:35+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwt2ky</id><link>http://wp.wnd.com/2012/03/sheriff-joe-tons-more-shocking-obama-info/#comment-481164453</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7r9a</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>