<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ip71/post/2012-03-29T21:46:57</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3pvwf</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5s5hz</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>It is not a slight correction, it is you making up a false narrative. Zimmerman was not saying he would meet the police either at the mailbox or his truck, he was giving directions to where he was at. The 911 tapes did not show that Zimmerman stopped chasing after Martin as you claimed. It was the dispatcher that suggested meeting at the mailbox, not ZImmerman. And after saying "yeah". Zimmerman changed his mind, because he was still going after Martin. And you are usually pretty thorough, why did you leave Off the last two lines of the conversation that showed the exact opposite of what you were claiming?

I at least give you credit for accepting that if there was a significant injury to the back of Zimmerman's head that was Bleeding, that the EMT's would have bandaged it. You would also think that with a broken nose, that would have been treated as well.

I have no idea what happened that night, but it is sad to see so many people pile on the child that got shot and blame him. He is the only person that so far has been found guilty of anything in this case, and the racist comments that are coming from a lot of posters are really sad. I am not saying you are one of the people that has made racist comments, but you have worked pretty hard to discount the possibility that Trayvon was innocent. You have even made up facts to defend your position.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hc8n0</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnmo</id></website><link>http://www.newsobserver.com/2012/03/28/1963205/michael-doran-facts-arent-in.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T04:10:51+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:46:57+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ip71</id><link>http://www.newsobserver.com/2012/03/28/1963205/michael-doran-facts-arent-in.html#comment-480128388</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c7y9q</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>