<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw3u41/update/2012-03-31T11:53:49/9bae17b76a40084dbcf07fe0b4cc7731f4a8062cbcd2407e136c13156875b3bd</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwoh8q</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/al3w3</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Black people have earned their right to whine!! Let me start  wit that..now forget about everybody else it's Zimmerman vs Trayvons family now all the family want is answers n a proper investigatiom which should have first of all begun with an arrest u have a grown man with a gun m a 17yr.old boy with no weapon jus a damn bag of skittles, a ice tea and a cell phone wit a hoodie on!  Now seeinv someome lurking around ya neighborhood wit a hoodie on would seem supicouis....BUT the problem wit ZimmermN case is 5 major thimgs for one, Trayvom had a hoodie om cuz it was raining!!!!!!! NoTSUSPICOUIS NEED ANOTHER EXCUSE , Two:Zimmerman got out of his truck and followed Trayvon into an area that he had to  literally follow him up  a long walkway then male 	turn  fpllow him some more till they rea,jed tje Spot where everything pccured. Zimmerman was the one supicouis!!! Three: I hVe a som ive seen hom trip on the sidewalk and come up not only bloody bit bruised with swellon so how the hell did thia Man get his head bashed in the.concrete to the point of almost death but end up wot NO BLood SWELLON no LUMPS??!!wtf!! FOUR:Zimmaerman clIamed he didnt have his gun drawn but HOW did TRyvon Reach out and try to grab it if it wasnt drawn  ONTHIS17yr old unarmed boy??!! Huh? Answer that one!! And 5 most importNtly!!!! Trayvon phone records show him on the phone  wit his girlfriend and she heard the converstation between Zimmerman n Trayvon initoTe n Zimmerman asked him "What are u doing around here" MIND U HIS WAS JUS Wlkim home frpm the store in the rain &amp; YES he jus so happen to be my color! And although Zimmerman ia half hispaNic his appearance as well as the other half of his race is WHITE. N I SAY THOS TO Su im blk &amp; cuban but I appear to people as a blacl female...Its not RACE that is important its JUATICE! P.S. N va have I ever heard of the Piolice pattin u down after u get inside of the police station soinds supicouis Nd even more so beimg as though ZIMMERmans FATHER is a FORMER JUDGE!!!!! Is it sinkin eople!!???</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67uto8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q0fi</id></website><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/31/public-opinion-shifts-on-trayvon-martin-case/</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T06:29:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T15:53:49+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw3u41</id><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/31/public-opinion-shifts-on-trayvon-martin-case/#comment-481940304</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>