<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ch27je/update/2011-05-13T17:17:04/5378283b8c1beff0a793340ccfc7bdafb69c2ed9e8e92e15d6f47314d14e8184</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Wow crazy to see how many people support this! I think manning violated the UCMJ and lots of laws and I'm sure he will be punished, but it's laughable to see how many people support tossing the constitution out the window to Burn him. The mindless "He's a traitor! Castrate him, then Burn him at the stake and piss on his ashes!!" rhetoric is pretty old (I'm looking your way Mat). I might be missing something but how many deaths were attributed to the fallout from this information? From what I hear it has just been a black-eye for our embassy officials, who had to scramble to explain their bluntly honest assessments, and a hectic scramble for those people who had to help informants who were identified due to the release. Maybe someone knows more than me.
Other than that, WAKE THE F*#K UP! The DHS has effectively thrown out the fourth amendment of the constitution. So anyone who thinks their being "patriotic" by encouraging this ...is a tool. I am Glad you think our founding fathers were idiots and just wrote down the constitution as a list of suggestions. Maybe I am missing something but "The right of the people to be secure in their persons, houses, papers, and effects, against unreasonable searches and seizures [unless warrant is granted]" seems pretty clear. There's no asterisk that says..."unless you went to spring break in Mexico" or "...unless more expedient for DHS." You can speak legalese all day, but it's pretty effing clear...as a U.S. citizen that IS your fourth amendment right, period. I think the pendulum has swung a little too far to the outside. 
To all the people who fight for a better America, whether their military, embassy officials, DHS members, ACLU lawyers, or normal people that believe in the image of America as a force for Equality, honesty, and justice - people who just want life, liberty, and the pursuit of happiness - keep up the good work. 

P.S. I love trolls, so please feel free to post a poorly thought out, incoherent reply
 
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/g2zcny</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lkcy</id></website><link>http://www.wired.com/threatlevel/2011/05/house-suit/</link><postedTime>2011-05-13T18:25:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-05-13T21:17:04+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ch27je</id><link>http://www.wired.com/threatlevel/2011/05/house-suit/#comment-203253954</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5kkj3</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-05-13</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>