<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkvt76/update/2012-03-25T19:32:23/d25d3c685e50a92592466af0220a17d55e700da3b89d51059aa610ef70ff19c8</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkh7u4</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h0lk1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Claus, Much that I would have written to you yesterday I have decided not to broach, as much of it would raise more issues, probably, than could be given fair coverage here.

Let me say only this, that much research, in any field of study, per my hesitant and open-ended opinion, goes far beyond verification and replication, and adds a bit of as it were tweedle de dum counterpoint to a descant of tweedle de dee.  In academia the "publish or perish" motive and the "you gotta' do a thesis" mandate account for a substantial portion of this and that is more an observation than a slight on my part.  In academia so much time and energy can go to begging funding than focusing on changing the world for the better.  (Sometimes the student most likely to have an original idea at some time in his life is the student most inclined to bite  more than he can chew, and Burn out his/her time and talent and financial resources trying too much to be original and make a difference int he world.
Then, too, out in the "business world" of science, where oxymorons never cease to attract money, there, too, the project that most directly chases after a solution or a cure may fail the selling game of whispering pure greed into big money's ear.  (If one were to be on verge of establishing a new improved aphrodisiac that would be more of a money magnet than a solution to the disappearance of the world's amphibians, even if humans may simply be farther down the disappearance list, and that solution might inform the contemplation of that  ( : &gt; ).

But in looking in upon the quagmire of what scientists do, from out here in retirement Euphoriaville, I cannot help but marvel that somehow the fuzzy logic of science continues to grind out something of value here and there.
And, one of these days, I suspect, it will crank out something that will circumvent much questionable sociological and anthropological palaver )and funds-motivated groveling, and cut to the chase of effecting a cure and an immunization.

If we would dream, let us dream of solutions equivalent to Alexander's legendary solution to untying the Gordian Knot, in which he simply unsheaths his sword and slashes the damned thing in twain.  

Let us dream of a single, once-in-a-lifetime injection that would by-pass the need of diagnostics and cure an organism of HIV if it's there, or simply provide immunity if it is not.  You and I are aware of how angry that would make those who argue that things are never that straight forward or that simple, but sometimes in this complex world, there is no harm in at least beginning a creative brainstorm session with an idealized solution and working backward from there -- to say, in effect, "Okay, if not that then what would be the next best not-totally-absurd solution.

(There is a story, told on good authority, that in WWII a think tank was assigned to try to analyze the problem of German U-boats, and was coming up with nothing useful... UNTIL a very wise individual came up with the notion of asking the group to see who could come up with the silliest, goofyist, more ridiculous idea of a solution.  As the story goes, one lady in the group came up with sending the submarine chasers around in ever broadening circles.  The Navy's strategists seized upon this and say, in essence, "What do we have to lose.  Let's try it."

Try it, they allegedly did, and it is recorded that it "worked."  So many submarines ended up being detected and destroy by depth charges that the German Navy suspected the U. S. had some new Secret detection system that surpassed their technology.

I believe the source of my reading that was reliable, and did document the story and confirm it.

But even if it were apocryphal, this anecdote, together with that of Alexander and the knot, is stimulating, don't agree?

And what about sociological and anthropological and psychological studies in search of who is doing what to whom, in whose bedroom... maybe, somehow, that will add verifiable information to... the knot.

Who am I -- indeed, who is anyone -- to predict from whence will come a solution to HIV in the world, or in some highly infested region or regions of it, or whether any solution will come before comes a nuclear winter, or a cataclysmic eruption of a massive caldera?  But in my least mind-knotted moments, I suspect our highest and best chances of a solution -- if one is to be -- will arise from some bench in some unknown, poorly funded, unappreciated lab.

Whacha think?       </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yps018</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/4hmb</id></website><link>http://the-scientist.com/2012/03/01/the-specter-of-denialism/</link><postedTime>2012-03-01T05:44:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-25T23:32:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkvt76</id><link>http://the-scientist.com/2012/03/01/the-specter-of-denialism/#comment-476100406</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6qfs2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>