<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/323728/post/127795503/comment/327532075</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Joseph, 
 
You  seem to comment on my blog assuming I have no idea what I&amp;#039;m talking about. I&amp;#039;m sorry you feel I&amp;#039;m so ignorant. I have around 15 years computer industry experience, including around 3 in tech support and around 5 in quality assurance, specializing in multi-platform white and blackbox testing. I am a VERY good troubleshooter. When I say there&amp;#039;s a problem with a product, it&amp;#039;s because there is a problem with a product. 
 
While what you&amp;#039;re saying about Sprint may be true, I spent hours researching community forums of BlackBerry users (most typically the Curve: all models) where people had this same issue. Many of them weren&amp;#039;t even in the US, much less tied to Verizon or Sprint. I dealt with technical support - at both Sprint and BlackBerry/RIM, including escalated support. 
 
In fact, Googling BlackBerry Freezing Issues turns up over 600,000 hits. I&amp;#039;m sure not all of them match all three keywords, but I looked through some of the links. Some of the users, as you suggest, had bad phones. Many of them experienced the same problems I did, and one of the top suggestions is that too many apps were running. When a third party app causes an entire operating system to freeze to the point where the hardware doesn&amp;#039;t even respond to the power button, there is a problem. This happened constantly with my Curve 8330. 
 
In fact, the BlackBerry freeze issue is SO prominent, it has been given the nickname &amp;quot;the hourglass of death.&amp;quot; 
 
BlackBerry and CrackBerry forums have multiple threads on this issue, from subscribers of all networks. Often times, yanking the Battery fixes the problem. Other times, a complete wipe and re-install of the OS is desired. The reasons for the hourglass of death are typically: a bad application, a bad device, or an out of memory situation. 
 
Obviously, there is nothing to be done for a bad device but to replace it. However, the fact an OS can&amp;#039;t recover from a low memory situation, or a badly behaving app, is the hallmark of an extremely poorly designed operating system, including haphazard error trapping and shoddy multi-threading. 
 
The similarity in the standard computer world would be to point to FireFox. As you are probably aware, it is the browser of choice and has ports to almost all known operating systems. However, it has piss poor memory management. On earlier version of Windows (up to XP) and Linux, when I used FireFox maximized, and it froze, I was completely fubared. There was no way to recover other than to give the machine the old three finger salute. 
 
On the other hand, when I had the same problem on a Mac running OS X, I could simply force quit the application. 
 
I&amp;#039;ve already had low Memory problems on my Pixi. the difference is, the Pixi tells me. Rather than running into a situation where the entire device locks up, the OS warns me I&amp;#039;m out of memory, and allows me to navigate the OS, close apps and regain the memory. When an app freezes the BlackBerry: tough! When it freezes on the Pixi, I just go into Card View, close the app, and reopen it. 
 
Part of the problem with the BlackBerry is closing apps. Lots of people use the &amp;quot;end call&amp;quot; button to hide the app, thinking it&amp;#039;s close, when it&amp;#039;s still running in the background. Other times, you can&amp;#039;t even close an app from memory using the menus. 
 
You said you had to replace a very few BlackBerry phones, which says nothing about the stability of the OS or software to me, but much about the durability of the hardware. There do seem to be more peculiarities with other hardware devices than with BlackBerries, although I note the newer models are made of much cheaper plastic (at least the latest versions of the Curve I&amp;#039;ve seen) than even my 1 year old 8330 Curve. 
 
The fact that so many people on so many networks using so many different providers all had the same &amp;quot;hourglass of death&amp;quot; issue with their BlackBerries as I counter-indicates your claims as to the BlackBerry&amp;#039;s superior stability. Perhaps you had to replace so few phones as people often look elsewhere than service provider technical support these days. 
 
I&amp;#039;m not saying it&amp;#039;s a piece of crap, but I&amp;#039;ll put my Palm up against a BlackBerry in terms of memory management or stability any day of the week. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:323728:127795503</id><idPostId>127795503</idPostId><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:323728</id><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><link>http://www.chrisisright.net</link><displayName>Chris Is RIGHT</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2010/11/16/tech-review-palm-pixi-webos/</link><displayName>Tech Review: Palm Pixi / WebOS</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2010-11-17T03:02:55.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:323728:127795503:327532075</id><inReplyTo><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2010/11/16/tech-review-palm-pixi-webos/#IDComment327532073</link></inReplyTo><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2010/11/16/tech-review-palm-pixi-webos/#IDComment327532075</link><postedTime>2010-11-17T03:02:55.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Tech Review: Palm Pixi / WebOS by Chris Barnhart</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://chrisisright.wordpress.com</link><idEmailMd5>91cee804c778e52acf84568c44dfdeea</idEmailMd5><displayName>Chris Barnhart</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://chrisisright.wordpress.com"&gt;Chris Barnhart&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.chrisisright.net/2010/11/16/tech-review-palm-pixi-webos/"&gt;Tech Review: Palm Pixi / WebOS&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2010-11-17</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>