<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/323744/post/127846030/comment/328540153</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Yikes - cut and paste fail. All fixed now. But so you don&amp;#039;t have to re-visit...  
  
Are you awesome?   
No. I&amp;rsquo;m Jessie.  
This is like when my kids come running up to me whining, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m hungry,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m thirsty.&amp;rdquo;   I say &amp;ldquo;Hi, hungry, I&amp;rsquo;m Jessie. What can I do for you.&amp;rdquo;  And because they are on the spectrum, they then have to scramble to find the words to describe hunger and Thirst without saying &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m hungry&amp;rdquo;. It&amp;rsquo;s not really cruel. They need to be able to do this. But someday? Someday they will turn it on me and I will rue the tactic.  
Do you like nachos?   
Yes. But the question brings an inappropriate joke to mind. It&amp;rsquo;s not Jester-style inappropriate either, but full-out racist of the &amp;ldquo;I wish I hadn&amp;rsquo;t heard it, now it&amp;rsquo;s lodged forever in my brain with the word Nacho&amp;rdquo;. I won&amp;rsquo;t repeat the joke, but the word after nacho is cheese.  I hate jokes like that. They aren&amp;rsquo;t funny, and they are compelling for all the wrong reasons  
Do you know a person named Ashley?   
I know someone with the last name Ashley. Does that count?  
Do you have blog?   
This should be answered with some kind of a gang sign, shouldn&amp;rsquo;t it? Yeah. I got blog. You want some? Gonna cost you.  
What&amp;#039;s your favorite food?   
Steak, appropriately seasoned, and cooked rare or, at most, medium rare. Please no A-1 or Worcestershire sauce unless the piece of meat is already tough, tasteless, and dry. In which case, why the FUCK did you serve it to me?? You may feel free to get me a Texas Road House gift certificate to atone for your sins.  
Puppies, kittens, or pot-bellied pigs?   
Puppies, and kittens, and pigs. OH MY.   
Kittens.  
Puppies chew.  
Pigs get bigger than most owners expect, and they often become mean.   
Kittehs are sweet little sociopaths, and I wish Scott weren&amp;rsquo;t allergic.  
Do you forward those irritating chain e-mails?   
No. About the only &amp;lsquo;chain&amp;rsquo; I do is those blog awards that require you to answer seven questions about your gerbil, confess to being a monk in your last life, and compose a discourse on the Diet of Worms.  
Do you have any stickers?   
Is this a euphemism, or are you asking if my kid has decorated me yet today? If it&amp;rsquo;s a euphemism&amp;hellip;eeewwww. If it&amp;rsquo;s the kid thing, no, but he&amp;rsquo;ll get around to me. He&amp;rsquo;s just still working on the dog.  
  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:323744:127846030</id><idPostId>127846030</idPostId><idBlogId>323744</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:323744</id><idBlogId>323744</idBlogId><link>http://jesterqueen.com</link><displayName>Jester Queen</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://jesterqueen.com/2012/03/30/friday-fluff-march-30-2012/</link><displayName>Friday Fluff March 30, 2012</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T14:15:47.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:323744:127846030:328540153</id><inReplyTo><link>http://jesterqueen.com/2012/03/30/friday-fluff-march-30-2012/#IDComment328506039</link></inReplyTo><link>http://jesterqueen.com/2012/03/30/friday-fluff-march-30-2012/#IDComment328540153</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T14:15:47.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Friday Fluff March 30, 2012 by jesterqueenie</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://intensedebate.com/people/jesterqueenie</link><idEmailMd5>65edc5630c4a6fe18863445b9f6be138</idEmailMd5><displayName>jesterqueenie</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://intensedebate.com/people/jesterqueenie"&gt;jesterqueenie&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://jesterqueen.com/2012/03/30/friday-fluff-march-30-2012/"&gt;Friday Fluff March 30, 2012&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>