<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwb5jf/update/2012-03-30T21:22:48/7ce29a600cf019a20976aaa52a41e1757524409952b5bc51043d6cd42dd69e74</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwnosa</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8kdpp</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Spence,  should be of no surprise to anyone that wave and tidal will not amount to a hill of beans by 2020.  If tidal made sense than one could simply float turbines on barges in the Mississippi, Nile or Amazon and have access to limitless and continuous energy.  Just like married men, water needs head to work! 


Here's another bit..  did you know that that Solar PV in the USA is set to grow to.... hold your breath now.. 0.2 Q-BTU by 2035.  That would equal but 10% of the energy that the US will get from hydro, and less than half the energy the US will get from "residential wood".   By 2035, the EIA has forecast that solar PV in the US will amount to only 0.2% of the total US energy mix!  World wide.. about the same percentage.  

Here, note that the term "renewable" so often thrown around by aphidlips and his gang, refers to all the following forms of energy.. hydro, land fil gas, sewer gas, wood Burning, ethanol, wind and solar.  The bulk of renewable energy is hydro.. as in Niagara Falls... and most of the other sources excepting wind and solar, produce a lot of CO2.  The amount non carbon energy coming on line in the future as a percent of the total amount of energy used on earth will equal less than 3% of the total energy consumed in the world by 2035!  So what in hell does Europe think it can accomplish?  This data is not Secret.  Anyone can access this information in a few minutes time...


https://docs.google.com/viewer?url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.eia.gov%2Fforecasts%2Faeo%2Fer%2Fexcel%2Faeotab_1.xlsx



https://docs.google.com/viewer...</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hthio</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ms5i</id></website><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/jamesdelingpole/100147742/queensland-turns-the-tide-of-environmental-lunacy/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T16:15:26+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T01:22:48+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwb5jf</id><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/jamesdelingpole/100147742/queensland-turns-the-tide-of-environmental-lunacy/#comment-481402789</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c4unq</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>