<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw2ouj/update/2012-03-30T03:15:35/e006a4232e5ce2bd8ccdcc25aac0696cbfe9921c431079bc5330142f86582075</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The  multinational Afghan forces have almost Reached the
initial target of a combined 300,000 Afghan security force. This includes both the police and military forces.

The question now is: How combat-effective and combat-ready
are they? The Afghan forces have successfully led some of the counter-terrorism combat missions on their own, and, in
some situations, just NATO  rear-guard support in case  something goes wrong.

NATO  has fairly andd successfully organized peace talks for
the Taliban and Afghan Government: One in Qatar and the
other in Saudi Arabia. I believe one is for a kind of unity
government and the other for military and national-security
matters in post-2014 Afghan government. This is entirely
for the Sunni Muslim governments and militant opposition.

The Koran Burning and the civilian killings have dealt some
setbacks to the talks. But, what's emerging through robust
investigations is that there's no pre-medidated plan or
direct involvement of American Government or coalition
forces in Afghanistan. A video showing only the combat-stressed American troop coming back to the base all alone 
in the wee hours of the morning, after the shooting, supports 
the American version of the story that this is a lone-wolf mayhem.

In the  first commentary I wrote on this civilian massacre by the American soldier, I cited Combat-Stress Disorder as a
potential cause resulting from multiple deployments. This had not surfaced in news reports that I had known or read. But,
it's just gut instincts and pattern of what is, also, known as 
Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder. Now, it turns out this American soldier was treated for such causative, mental,
psychologial illness resulting from previous combat blast.

One of the harsh realities is that a post-2014 possible unity
Afghan Government would not include Harmid Karzai or a
Kazai. The Karzai administration is a rancd symbol of endemic
tribalism and corruption. Some Taliban groups are not ready for that under any circumstances. Then, some die-hard,
extremist, Islamic fundamentalist Taliban militants are
not ready for any accommodation of western values or
pro-western, democratic government in post-2014 Afghan
government.

So, what the Qatar and Saudi Arabia talks aim at, is an
amalgamation of moderate Taliban leadership ready to join  forces with a post-2014 pro-western, democratic government
of Afghanistan founded on Islamic traditions and freedom.
This will drastically undercut militant, terroristic Talibanism.
The West is closely watching Afghanistan, Yemen, Somalia,
Pakistan and now Northern Nigeria as hotbeds of Islamic
terrorism. Nigeria is just a new front. But, in these other
theaters, it's a full-time counter-insurgency operation. Iran
has been a long case being pursued through the nuclear
threat. But, Shiite Islamic terrorism is another problem.

Meanwhile, the United States is holding talks with Pakistan
on nomarlization of relations after US drones mistakenly
killed 24 Pakistami troops, with the Prime Minister Yousef
Gillani visiting Washington. This is in the best interest of
both countries. Pakistan needs the $1.5 billion annual foreign aid from the US (lots of them in military support). US wants to resume drone atacks that have decimated Taliban leadership,
according to a recent BBC report.

Con Coughlin's report and concerns are very legitimate. But,
this is the view of the Afghan War and transnational and 
counter- terrorism operations from another, (trans-Atlantic)
perspective.
Igonikon Jack, USA</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6znopp</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/worldnews/asia/afghanistan/9173664/The-West-will-pay-a-terrible-price-if-we-leave-Afghanistan-in-the-lurch.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:49:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T07:15:35+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw2ouj</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/worldnews/asia/afghanistan/9173664/The-West-will-pay-a-terrible-price-if-we-leave-Afghanistan-in-the-lurch.html#comment-480407319</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a3k2b</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>