<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw9t2w/post/2012-03-31T02:59:07</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwbpoo</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7tgi</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Cry some more?

 The Rock was part of the attitude . He didn't make it, creative, the NWO, Stone Cold, and McMahon made it. That doesn't make him better, it just means he benefitted by being born before Cena. What a great accomplishment that is.Most non-wrestling fans wouldn't say they support The Rock or Cena. They would say that they don't watch wrestling. So you say that you think Cena is an idiot regardless of what he does, whether it's supporting the troops or working with make-a-wish (which he doesn't flaunt, WWE does), and then you say that you're not a hater? I have no idea what you think a hater is, but by most people's definition, that's exactly what you are. The fact is, he has made that personality into his wrestling persona, so it is relevant to his character whether you accept it or not. You haven't seen a single match better than Cena vs Punk since then? Seriously? Maybe you should watch more matches before you start criticizing, because you're giving away the fact that you're either exaggerating to the point where it becomes a lie, or you haven't watched the program since Punk/Cena, which means you have no idea what you're talking about (which seems more likely IMO). I can't say whether or not this resembles "something a girl would watch on a some soap opera," since I don't watch soap operas, but I guess that explains your bad taste.So let me get this straight. What you saw in the attitude ; you thought you outgrew it, so you stopped watching. Then, when they bring attitude Era antics back, you became interested again? Doesn't that mean you basically haven't grown at all? You're the same person as back then, and you apparently can't let go of the past. My favorite part of your post is the part where you claim that you won't watch again. Hopefully we won't be subject to your frustratingly close-minded, hypocritical, and senseless posts in here in the future. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6769x0</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cq26</id></website><link>http://www.wrestlezone.com/news/252267-cena-continues-to-rip-the-rock-why-he-called-out-wrist-notes</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:27:01+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T06:59:07+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw9t2w</id><link>http://www.wrestlezone.com/news/252267-cena-continues-to-rip-the-rock-why-he-called-out-wrist-notes#comment-481605298</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6oebt</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>