<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwicgf/update/2012-03-31T08:02:51/7af2ee0a6d76c1699af8a0e5990e193b19f098e363f56a7592ac93a1150c01ce</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Army chief is the hero. 
Just the way they did with Anna Hazare they are maligning Gen V K Singh. Why so much money and resources is being spent in both the instances. The simple reason is that they have been very effective in this dark world where corruption and sycophancy prevails and flourishes.

General V K Singh dealt head on with corruption. He helped in bringing out corruption in Adarsh and Sukhna scam. Nobody comments on Gen Deepak Kapoor who has flats in Adarsh society. The army image is not tarnished nor the relationship beetween the Army and government ever  gone sour when Gen Kapoor was going about his corrupt way? How ridiculous!

Sack the general declares a minister thriving on chara and the media does not pass comment.
Former ministers are involved in Adarsh society but no arrests yet. But see the way they are after General's blood.

People like me sleep in our cosy world safely because we have General V K Singh commanding our lion hearted soldiers.

I have a humble request to the media (politicians I have no hope) kindly do not malign people who fight the tough battle against the enemy within. We have seen a Narender being trashed under a tractor. One wishes all the crusaders against corruption be more vigilant and tactful.

Media should stop airing childish, outrageous, and illogical views of people who when caught in the net have no other option.

General Singh is doing the right thing. The leakage of the letter as well as what followed is a smear campaign. Even a kid would say the contents of the letter are more important. How can you question the General's motive on this? It is not illegal(writing of letter). But the ploy was  to draw the attention away from the contents. 

All this stuff about timing and motivation is outrageous. Don't we all know the working of the Government system? Why does the media and the people airing their expertise against General try to convey as if corruption is a rarity and all is crystal clear and pious in our system?

If I am serving in any post and detect corruption all I have to do is register a FIR and the police are so efficient that they will immediately put the culprits to bar and we can live happily ever after.??

We have seen or heard people getting murdered in broad day light with the public a mute witness. It can happen to anyone one of us. How many have guts to report the crime and be a witness?

The country should thank our lucky stars a hero like General has come along and is trying to clean the muck and facing the Heat for the same.

This country misses a patriotic  mature and strong leader at this juncture.
General V K Singh is a rare breed amongst a majority who live only for themselves.
It is people like Singh who make the world go around. Lets' encourage them and not sacrifice them at the unholy altar of corruption via smear campaign.

Salute to you General Sir! Jai Hind!



</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67muuh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/776o</id></website><link>http://www.firstpost.com/india/whos-the-rogue-general-vk-singh-is-it-the-media-261719.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:01:19+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T12:02:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwicgf</id><link>http://www.firstpost.com/india/whos-the-rogue-general-vk-singh-is-it-the-media-261719.html#comment-481773949</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>