<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3pyo7/update/2012-03-29T20:12:10/2e34fa75700575dbabf6359aa422e3ee06f1a9a0e1cf552bafe3736bd42fad1e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34b9q</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6ihp6</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>you took my explanation and threw it out the window and curbed everything once more..You say.."and you forget that the apparitions first appearance was while Mary still lived (how could it possibly be authentic and of God) "..   It could very well be what you say here but, this does not mean there haven't  been authentic apperitions either..!!


Christians have  honored those who have gone on to be with the Lord. Cities that possessed the bones of saintly people proudly proclaimed the fact. However there are no records of any city claiming possession of Mary's remains. And that is because there were none to claim. Why?? ;


The doctrine of the Assumption of Mary, just like the doctrine of the Trinity, is not formally defined in Scripture. However, in both cases we find scriptural evidence to support them. 

There are two examples in Scripture that clearly demonstrate the bodily assumption of saints. Enoch (Hebrews 11:5) and Elijah (2 Kings 2:1-13) were both taken up to heaven with their bodies. All Christians agree on this, so logically all should agree at least on the possibility that the same could have happened to Mary. (1) Scripture teaches us that it was possible. Aftert all , if Enoch and Elijah were assumed then the mother of jesus has just as much rankings if not more , therefore,Mary could very well have been assumed as well for her obedience to god for bearing  our savior..!! 

The Assumption of Mary is further consistent with Scripture as it is the logical result of her Immaculate Conception (the fact that she was conceived without sin – . Death and corruption in the grave are the consequences of sin: "You are dust and to dust you shall return" (Genesis 3:19). Mary was sinless. Thus, her being assumed body and soul into heaven was natural and to be expected. (2) Scripture indicates that it was likely. 

Even though Scripture tells us that it was possible and even likely, that wouldn't necessarily mean that it happened. On the other hand, the fact that it is not explicitly taught in Scripture would not mean that it didn't. That idea comes from the Reformation doctrine of "Sola Scriptura," or Scripture alone. The leaders of the Protestant Reformation taught that all that was to be believed in matters of faith could be found on the surface of Scripture. However, this foundational teaching of the Reformation cannot itself be found in Scripture . What we do find in Scripture, is the establishment of an authoritative Church. For instance, the Church is "The pillar and foundation of truth" (1 Timothy 3:15). And rejection of the Church is rejection of Christ: "Whoever rejects you rejects me" (Luke 10:16; see essay on The Church). (3) Scripture shows us that the Church has the authority to teach. 

In 1950 Pope Pius XII formally defined the doctrine of the Assumption. He was not adding something new but was affirming what the Church had already believed for centuries. (4) The Church in its authority proclaims that the assumption of Mary is a reality. 

Reference to the Assumption of Mary is made early on. James of Sarugh speaks of Mary's sacred body going forth to paradise (De Transitu Dei Genitricis Mariae, 490 AD). Gregory of Tours writes, "The Lord commanded the holy body [of Mary] to be borne on a cloud to Paradise where, reunited to its soul and exulting with the elect, it enjoys the everlasting bliss of eternity" (Libri miraculorum, 593 AD).

The Church does not say whether or not Mary died. When Pius XII defined the Assumption in 1950, he simply said that Mary "having completed the course of her earthly life, was assumed body and soul into heavenly glory" (Munificentissimus Deus). Whether or not she died has been a matter of speculation for centuries. Epiphanius, Bishop of Constantia, wrote the following in 377 AD: "Whether she died or was buried we know not" (Panarion 78:2). If she did die, it would present no conflict with Scripture, as she did not remain in the grave. We saw earlier in Genesis 3:19 that the penalty for sin was not merely death but death and bodily corruption (to dust you shall return). If Mary died it would probably have been because she identified so closely with everything that her Son did. 

The doctrine of the Assumption in no way equates Mary with God. It is not an ascension, something Mary did by her own power. Rather she was assumed into heaven by the power of God. Someday all of the saved will be assumed into heaven by the power of God, "For the hour is coming when all who are in the tombs will hear His voice and come forth; those who have done good, to the resurrection of life; and those who have done evil, to the resurrection of judgment" (John 5:28-29). 

The Date of the Assumption
There is no record of the exact day or year in which our Lady was assumed. This should not bother us too much. After all, we are not sure of the day and year of Christ's birth, baptism, or death and resurrection. However, we can get close. Let's look a few clues pertaining to the life and death of Mary.

We know that she was alive at the death of Christ, because she stood at the foot of the cross. At this point she was placed under the care of St. John, when Christ said, "Behold your mother." She was also present at Pentecost. After that, there is no mention of her (unless you count St. John's description of the "woman" in Rev 12 - more on this later).

Why is there little mention of Mary in  or the Epistles? I believe that the New Testament speaks of the mysteries of the faith in clouded language on account of the fierce persecution that Christians received from both the Jews and the Romans. Cases have been made that Galatians and 1 Peter are basically tracts on baptism, despite the fact that baptism is only alluded to in the most minimal way. The Gospel of John in particular is reluctant to spell out baptismal theology (John 3) or Eucharistic theology (John 6), although it does so in a way that only an insider would "get it". Think also of John's language about the "blood and the water". He's making points for "insiders". Mary would have been revered, but to speak of her openly would have placed her danger.

The martyrdom of St. James the Greater is recorded in  12:1-2 and the date of this event is safely placed at A.D. 43 or 44. This was a Jewish persecution of the Christians. It seems that this martyrdom further widened the growing separation between the incipient Jewish community of Christians within the synagogues of Palestine and the establishment of a separate "Way" that began to  Gentile adherents. The unique nature of the Church as distinct from Judaism would finally be ecclesiastically recognized at the Council Jerusalem in A.D. 49 or 50 ( 15).  12 shows the Jews in a fierce attempt to destroy those closest to Christ. They kill James and imprison Peter (apparently with the intent to kill Peter).

Here is where we turn to Tradition. St. John had seen his brother St. James martyred, and St. Peter imprisoned. Everyone knew that Christ's inner circle consisted of Peter, James, and John. They had killed James and captured Peter. Obviously John was next on the hit list. Tradition also indicates that the Jews sought to kill or disgrace the Mother of Christ. So John took Mary and relocated to Ephesus sometime shortly after the martyrdom of his brother James (A.D. 43 or 44).

Thus, the falling asleep and assumption of Mary occurred sometime after this date. The tradition is almost universal that her death and resurrection occurred in Jerusalem. An alternate version has arisen from the visions of Ven. Anne Catherine Emmerich that her death, funeral, and assumption occurred in Ephesus. Interestingly enough, Emmerich places the date of the assumption at A.D. 43 or 44. However, I tend to mistrust the visions of Emmerich.

One tradition places the falling asleep of Mary after the conversion of St. Dionysius the Areopagite which occurred in  17:34. This kicks the date back into the 50s. All the traditions place her Dormition sometime after the other Apostles have gone out into the world, but before the death of the other Apostles (ca. A.D. 63).

I think Mary fell asleep at this time. It fits the historical setting of most of the apocryphal legends retelling the Dormition of Mary (even though they contain a lot of miraculous events - such as bilocation or the translation of human bodies). Here is a list of reasons for placing the Dormition at AD 63:

The Apostles (but not James Zebedee) are all still alive.
The great miracle of the Dormition and Assumption are not mentioned in , something we might expect if it happened before the composition of  (A.D. 63).
The Book of Revelation seems to describe some sort of miraculous intervention of God meant to preserve the "the woman". I believe Revelation explains the seven year tribulation leading up to the destruction of the Temple in Jerusalem. Thus, A.D. 63 fits perfectly.
So I'm going to say that Mary was assumed about A.D. 63 when Herod's temple was finally finished. So Mary's Assumption is a sort of "pre-tribulation rapture" occurring before the seven years of Roman-Jerusalem gridlock culminating in the end of the age - the destruction of the Temple in A.D. 70.


Mary is the "woman" (Rev 12:1), the same "woman" of the Protoevangelium (Gen 3:15), of whom "is born" the son of God; sent by the Father (Gal 4:4);3 the "woman" present and wholly absorbed in the sufferings of her Son crucified on Calvary (Jn 19:25-26).

Mary is the "virgin" who is shown alone with the Son, without husband, in the proto-evangelium (Gen 3:15), then in Isaiah (7:14), and in Micah (5:2); her virginity prefigured by the "Burning bush" (Ex 3:1-11), by the "rod of Aaron" (Num 9:16-24), by the "fleece of Gideon" (Jg 6:36-40), by the "enclosed garden, sealed fountain" (Song 4:12); finally, described by St. Matthew and by St. Jude in terms of the most essential biographical and historical facts of her life.

Mary is the "mother", pregnant and giving birth to a son, though remaining a virgin, according to the prophecies of Genesis 3:15, Isaiah 7:14, Micah 5:1-2; and the woman "Mother of the Lord" or "Mother of Jesus", as she is called eleven times in the New Testament; she is the "mother" of mankind, represented by St. John on Calvary (Jn 19:25-27).

Mary is the "spouse": not only the virginal, legal spouse of St. Joseph (Mt 1:18; Lk 1:27), but the virginal, real spouse of God the Father who willed her to be the Mother, according to His human nature, of His only-begotten Son (Gal 4:4); the spouse of God the Son, the redeemer, who intimately associated her with Himself in His redemptive work, as the new Eve beside the "new Adam"; the spouse of God the Holy Spirit, who, overshadowing her enabled her to conceive Jesus (Lk 1:35).

Mary is the woman immaculate: namely, she is the only human creature unstained by sin, because, together with her Son, she is the unvanquished, victorious adversary of the infernal serpent (Gen 3:15); not only this, but she is the only creature "full of grace" (Lk 1:28), true panhaghia (all holy one), pure "" (Song 6:9) of the sun who is Christ, "fashioned by the Holy Spirit and formed as a new creature" in order to become Mother of Word Incarnate.

Mary is the co-redemptrix, associated with her Son in the work of ransoming man from sin (Gen 3:15), strong as "an army set in array" (Song 6:9), already prefigured by the "strong", courageous women of Israel, present at the foot of the cross on Calvary (Jn 19:25-27).

Mary is the Mediatrix, who brings Jesus to men and men to Jesus, who cares for things spiritual and temporal (Lk 1:39ff.; Jn 2:1-11) present and active at the birth of the Church on Calvary (Jn 19:25-27) and in the Cenacle ( 1:14).

Mary is the Queen, who wears on her head the crown of twelve stars (Rev 12:2) signifying the angels (the "stars"), the twelve tribes of Israel (the Chosen People) and the twelve apostles (the Church). She is the Queen assumed into heaven, carried on the wings of the "great eagle" (Rev 12:14), dashing to the ground the destructive furies of the "dragon" (Rev 12:3-4). She is the "exalted daughter of Zion", seated as "Queen at the right hand" of the King in the kingdom of heaven (Ps 44:10).

Mary is the woman "blessed" for the faith she placed in the words of the angel Gabriel at the Annunciation (Lk 1:45), for hearing and observing the Word of God (Lk 11:27-28), for her faithful fulfillment of the will of the Father (Mk 3:31-35), as the "poor one of Yahweh" (Ps 9) and "the handmaid of the Lord" (Lk 1:38).

From the book of Genesis to the book of Revelation, therefore, we may well underscore how this "woman" according to the design of God the Father is  one with her Son,  relative to that Son, "leaning upon her beloved" (Song 8:15), intimately associated with Him in the same mission of saving man and leading him back to the bosom of the Father.

At every crucial point in the history of salvation, from the Protoevangelium, after the fall of our first parents (Gen 3:15), to the announcement of the incarnation of the Word (Lk 1:26ff.), from the beginning of the public mission of Jesus at Cana (Jn 2:1-11), to His redemptive sacrifice consummated on the Cross (in 19:25-27), up to the accomplishment of the very last detail in the universal salvific plan (Rev 12), Mary is the "woman" Always present with her Son, never alone, to fulfill her role of "generous companion and humble handmaid of the Lord".

And together with the Son there are "children", these also brothers and "co-heirs" of Christ (Rom 8:17), who constitute the Mystical Body, the Church. Thus, in Genesis 3:15, the "woman" is presented together with her "seed" (which also has an inclusive sense); at Cana (Jn 2:1-11) the "woman" is with the first "disciples" of Jesus; on Calvary (Jn 19: 25-27), at the foot of the Cross the "woman" has beside her John the Evangelist, who represents all the "disciples" of Jesus; in Revelation 12, finally, the "woman" is found again with "the rest of her offspring" (the Church).

To conclude, then, Mary's whole reason for existing is found in the Son (and in the children), according to the salvific plan of God the Father. Without the Son, Mary would not have existed at all. This is a thesis dear to dogmatic theologians, and "soundly based on fact".</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/dbomdp</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/fu3y</id></website><link>http://hehasrisen.limewebs.com/main.htm</link><postedTime>2011-12-31T09:26:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:12:10+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3pyo7</id><link>http://hehasrisen.limewebs.com/main.htm#comment-480056271</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l7m9t</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-12-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>