<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw0a8n/update/2012-03-31T13:07:55/2b4139b3aa1eb73c6347f6ad60687266e716002b24be466ec689ec699578e336</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>A few years ago, a remote peat bog gave up the remains of an Argentinian  Air Force Lear Jet shot down by a RN ship during the war because it was Spotting for bombers trying to attack the .  Inside the wreck were the remains of the 4 crew.

The Argentinian government refused to allow the remains to be repatriated for political reasons, but worse than that, they also failed to notify the relatives that human remains had been found.  The bodies were buried in a fenced graveyard at the crash site by the UK military and a nice memorial was erected by the Gurkhas who happened to be the resident infantry company at the time.

Some months later, the local settlement manager at Pebble Island received a letter from Argentina from a berieved relative saying that they had heard rumours about the discovery of human remains and, in the absence of any official Argentinian information, could he shed any light on the matter.  To cut a long story short, the relatives eventually visited the Islands and were flown by RAF Chinook to the lonely crash site where a service was held for them by military padre.

Some of the remarks here implying British intransigence are ill informed.  The UK does everything possible to Ensure that the matter of Argentinian war dead is treated as sensitively as possible.

PS I have served there and have visited the grave.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ze960</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/worldnews/southamerica/falklandislands/9172949/Falklands-anniversary-Argentine-veterans-seek-to-mark-unnamed-graves.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T08:29:53+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T17:07:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw0a8n</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/worldnews/southamerica/falklandislands/9172949/Falklands-anniversary-Argentine-veterans-seek-to-mark-unnamed-graves.html#comment-482004524</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/r0dv4</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>