<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi5pcs/post/2012-03-22T15:37:15</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>As further proof that I don't really belong on this planet, I prefer The Office without Steve Carrel, as talented and funny as he is. The show is more random and arbitrary now. I enjoy these qualities, particularly in a show whose mission it is to lampoon the horrendous nightmare that is "corporate culture." By taking the focus  "The Boss" the show now is much more open to the real monster that terrorizes office workers - uncertainty. Uncertainty about the future. Uncertainty about the new location, the new employee, the new policy, the new logo, the new dental plan, the new lunch Spot. These are all heightened by the uncertainty instilled by the prospect of a new boss.

Robert California isn't really their boss and Spader plays him perfectly as a nebulous, vague, imposing threat which no one can quite get a handle on. He is a twisted, demented higher power under which they all coalesce, but not so much out of fear but more so out of fascination. But our vantage point, as the TV audience, allows us to see him as the flawed, fallible human that he really is. That's what good story telling is all about. I like when there's at least the possibility that the writers are acknowledging that I get the joke without restating it every week, every Act, every beat. God, some people are just so damn thick...</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yu9vp</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/today-in-potential-omens-of-the-offices-demise-pau,71320/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T17:39:14+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T19:37:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi5pcs</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/today-in-potential-omens-of-the-offices-demise-pau,71320/#comment-473876060</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/doj0h</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>