<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw79bc/update/2012-03-30T15:28:40/60702b90341cb245de39d5bb28e7a23187fb712f34b726eb14f0b267c325a98d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>To the person who said they had a broken nose that didn't Bleed, it unlikely you got your broken nose in a fist fight.  I know people who have a Nosebleed without even being hit.  A lot really Depends on how thick your nasal membranes are.

A lot of people do though have broken noses in common language, but not medically termed as such.  A nose is part bone and part cartilage.  The cartilage can be injured from such a simple thing as a parent grabbing your nose to steer where you look, or other minor incidents often not paid much attention to until a doctor looks up your nose.  The result though are usually called a deviated septum, not a broken nose.Parents can do a lot of accidental harm to children because there skeletal structure is not as solid as that of an adult.  Another condition is called nursemaid's maw which is a slight dislocation of writs bones from grabbing a child's hand and pulling with too much force, such as when a child resists going somewhere or while playing with a child holding his or her hand.  It is incumbent upon parents to remember how fragile their children are in some ways.The nose doesn't stop growing until age 16, so if you are younger than that and a doctor doesn't immediately treat your broken nose within 24 hours, you may have to wait until age 16 to have it surgically repaired.  A simple expanding plastic splint in the nose or stuffing up to the nose bone, might be enough if camping or such prevents getting to a doctor to set and pack it right.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z3b9t</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T07:25:56+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:28:40+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw79bc</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html#comment-481104507</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/otv6</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>