<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3u8kj/post/2012-03-29T15:02:51</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body> Read well and study on your
 own after you have read this.





This is not a game or joke our Sun gives  a Solar Wind all day
year round if you live in the State of Alaska you see it in the sky
above what a sight it is going through our Earth’s Magnet Polls of the
North and the South, North Poll. Its Called the Northern Lights or the
Aurora Borealis.





The day will come when you will be able to see it all over Earth as
in the year 1859 Solar Flare, It was the largest in 500 years. Two Astronomer’s Hodgson and Carrington
told the World that the Solar Flare made a Geomagnetic Storm 
Earth in hours not days. Back then it gave new meaning to  For The
Skies from Telegraph Operators. For hours sparks flew from the key
board. Even after the  were disconnected. Nov 3 and 4, 2003 had a X40+ Class Solar Flare.





Our Sun’s UV Rays will get stronger as each passing day go’s by, read and i will tell you why.





The Great big forest have be striped from most of the Earth for
Greed of Money by the Wicked. The trees our are Main Source of Oxygen
on this Plant.
The Forest Trees scrubs the Pollution out of the air and makes Oxygen from the rain and dirt that it grows in.





The Forest Trees do more then just make Oxygen they stop Soil
Erosion, just Look at the 1930 Dust Bowl. Greed by our Government taxes
led farmers to clear cut all their Forest and farm all the land they
were being Tax on. They had to farm it to pay for the Taxes. Why leave
the Trees when food crop makes Money. This Did not Help the Depression
that effected most all Worldwide. This year 2012 more then 100 million
will suffer from Malnutrition and Dehydration. Many will die!

In
the United States of America alone more than 45 Million Americans
Received  Food Stamps and that number is going up every day every year.

The Pollution and CO2 Carbon Dioxide go into the Tree Bark as a shield from most bugs so they do not eat the tree.


Less Forest less Oxygen this is why the moon. That has no Oxygen is
very Cold on the side with out Sun Light, And hot as ever on the side
with Sun Light. Way too Cold and Too hot to live there. You would need
at least 10 times the Energy we use on Earth to even live there and
life on the Moon would be very short.





With no blank of Oxygen to lessen or reduce the Sun’s UV Rays and
Solar Wind they are deadly there on our Moon. Every Mt. Climber and
Aircraft Pilot knows the higher you go the thinner the Oxygen and
Colder it gets.





Just spend a night on a Mt. top above 13,000 feet with no Sun Light
and you will see or should i say feel the Cold stinging any of your
exposed skin. If you are new to Mt. Climbing stay below 10,000Ft. The
Astronauts and the Cosmonauts and Fighter Pilots that i have been with
for years know this very well, and the Radiation Hazards to humans at
High Altitudes.





Soon the Sun’s Solar Wind and UV rays will be way to strong for most
to go out in the Sun Light for even a short time. The Geomagnetic Storm
to come and the Bad Weather Storms well you have not seen nothing yet
and the Sea Level is Rising the Oceans. Many Millions have been
affected  by Floods in China and Pakistan just last year. In 2005 Over
a Thousand dead in New Orleans flood, and the list going on.

And there shall be famines, and pestilences, and Earthquakes, in
 divers places such as was not from the beginning of the Creation.



The last 30 years On Earth we have broke all high temp records and
the temp it is still going up. All the Worlds Ice Glacier are melting
at an Accelerating Rate. The Glaciers and Polar Ice Caps store more
water than all the Fresh Water Lakes on Earth.





The Bad Weather Storms now are Babies compared to what is to come.

They will get even bigger and worse less Oxygen the more UV Rays to
the Earth and more Water molecules will evaporate and go up into the
Earth’s Atmosphere. Less Oxygen the Colder with out sun light and
hotter with it. 





The Sky full of more water vapor molecules, more snow in the winter
and more Flash Floods in the Summer. All earth will see way more fires
and the Deserts are growing larger.





If every living person on Earth were to Plant A Tree Today we might have a chance.





The Earth’s Atmosphere Blanket surrounding it protects life on Earth as Our Lord and GOD will all that seek Him.





Then it is written when the tree is full it is harvest time. All the Earth will someday Burn away.





This is all Foretold in the Bible Read it
and may our Lord Bless all that do so.





The Lord’s Little Helper
Paul Felix Schott

solardowork@yahoo.com
KI4-AEX





P.S.
2 Peter 3:10
But the day of the Lord will come like a thief, in which the heavens
will pass away with a roar and the elements will be destroyed with
intense Heat, and the Earth and its works will be Burned up.

GOD Bless You  and Your Love ones Give thanks to our Lord Jesus Christ every day.  Read

 Luke 21:20-22 
Matthew 24: 30-33

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6heo4b</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gjz2</id></website><link>http://sierraactivist.org/2012/03/28/west-antarctic-ice-shelves-tearing-apart-at-the-seams/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T07:43:28+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:02:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3u8kj</id><link>http://sierraactivist.org/2012/03/28/west-antarctic-ice-shelves-tearing-apart-at-the-seams/#comment-479767383</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gw9qp</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>