<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwtupe/update/2012-03-30T17:00:40/b359a6fdf5e7bc9a66b01302ffe058f27757f94b9111d451582a01d389901c3a</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwtg3v</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ap70</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>"1. Hillary is popular because she's serving as SOS, a position that, by law, forbids her from being involved in politics. That'll change the minute she gets back into politics." 

It will change, but she's currently up around 70%.  Even if it came down to 60%, she would remain a strong electoral asset.

 "2. Biden is not as high-profile or as well-known as Hillary but that is no independent data that suggests he's unpopular." 

Well, except for the 38% approval rating he got in the Pew Poll that came out earlier this year, among others. 

http://www.people-press.org/2012/01/19/obama-begins-year-four-with-weak-job-ratings-but-positive-personal-image/ 

"3. If Obama drops Biden it would cause a backlash because he would be viewed as (a) disloyal and (b) desperate." Not if Biden plays along, says SOS has  been his "dream job", etc."4. It also wouldn't change his vote total.  have spent 4 years hating Obama. If they didn't forgive him for giving Hillary the top Spot in the administration, they won't vote for him if she's Veep" 

 weren't even a factor in the 2008 general election, never mind 2012. There are plenty of white working class voters in battleground states who never were PUMAs, and certainly aren't now.  Hillary would be a significant legitimizing force for Obama with many of them.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67co9p</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ai6</id></website><link>http://politicalwire.com/archives/2012/03/30/biden_never_wanted_a_real_job.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:02:57+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:00:40+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwtupe</id><link>http://politicalwire.com/archives/2012/03/30/biden_never_wanted_a_real_job.html#comment-481194186</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a4n7q</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>