<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwhadg/post/2012-03-30T13:25:16</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The Maloofs are right. Why should they have too pay for pre-deveolpement plans? They are only the renters not owners. As usually the City makes big claims when they knew the Maloofs had major issues. Another interesting is the Maloofs' Attorney. They are not using the the one in Sacramento or Reno but in LA. I know the Maloofs want to leave. Also the cost for this arena is money lost. Look at the prices for game tickets half the time they can't fill the bottom level at 40.00 a ticket and the top level is almost  empty at 20 dollars or less. Imagine what the prices are going too be plus licenses to buy season tickets and bigger service charges for tickets and parking in city (sorry)private parking lots around the arena not to mention all the food beer and wine. They can't get people to go and see the Kings with these prices how in god name do they think they will draw next year by their razzle dazzle losing style. Cheap flash, Smart  reminds me of a guy trying to talk himself out of trouble. The Maloofs want out that obvious so let them go. We can still build an entertainment center no problem that will bring income to the city and be something Sacramento can truly enjoy also creating . We have proved that we can support a major league sports team. The only question is can Professional Team prove too us that they are worth our support. We have the Rivercats ,cost friendly for families and enjoyable for all too watch a continual championship team.My best to the Maloofs in their new city and the best for their team we will Always have a soft Spot for them.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zs0d3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnm3</id></website><link>http://www.sacbee.com/2012/03/30/4377566/arena-ghgfgfdgf-gfgf.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T07:01:31+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:25:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwhadg</id><link>http://www.sacbee.com/2012/03/30/4377566/arena-ghgfgfdgf-gfgf.html#comment-480978293</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cj99e</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>