<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp7ryl/update/2012-03-21T15:25:59/c470bc9c6eebadc8c5915a651e917ad806884356933243aa0081823a9637d694</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Has anyone notified Maricopa County Sheriff Joe Arpaio of this?  He and his volunteer Cold case posse spent six months and loads of research to come up with the fact that the purported birth certificate was a forgery, along with his draft card.  His Social Security Number was real.  It just wasn’t HIS.  They also discovered that other evidence, such as the passenger manifest when Mrs. Obama allegedly came to Hawaii to give birth was conveniently missing.  Other documentation involving immigration records and college transcripts were either missing or sealed.  Could Obozo have attended college as a foreign student?  This also opens the possibility that Obozo may himself be an illegal alien.  I am told that an 1874 Supreme Court decision ruled that a NATURAL BORN CITIZEN had to be born here of two parents who were also citizens.  Obozo’s father held dual citizenship in Great Britain and what became Kenya, and was NEVER an American citizen.  By this standard, Obozo is disqualified regardless of where he was born.  This new revelation from Hawaii will certainly help Sheriff Arpaio’s case for kicking Obozo Off the Arizona ballot.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/y3kxzs</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/o6hq</id></website><link>http://conservativebyte.com/2011/01/hawaii-official-now-swears-no-obama-birth-certificate/</link><postedTime>2012-03-06T19:34:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-21T19:25:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp7ryl</id><link>http://conservativebyte.com/2011/01/hawaii-official-now-swears-no-obama-birth-certificate/#comment-472686528</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-06</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>