<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0mawg/update/2012-03-31T20:54:26/fb2319b61a03f01903cea3a6c4c32105a76e2aa2c123b208ac7ccea57916f783</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0552t</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/d3xzq</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I completely agree. Unlike what happened the night of the killing and for several days (weeks?) afterward, a thorough investigation is called for by someone without an Axe to grind, who will just uncover all the facts and report them. And if the facts support Zimmerman's account, so be it, but if not, then due process should occur. If the latter, Zimmerman should be arrested again, formally charged and given his day in court to argue his case that  it was "self-defense." And Det. Serino is definitely the hero amidst all this mess, for due process would have already been being applied if only his manslaughter recommendation had been honored. I have a feeling that Zimmerman's dad (if he was the one pulling some strings to get his son released that night) will regret not allowing the manslaughter charges to go forward, because evidence keeps mounting that this was more a Cold-blooded killing than Zimmerman fighting for his life. 

(Note: see RS article about two forensics voice experts comparing Zimmerman's 9-1-1 voice to the 9-1-1 voice of the person crying for help, they don't match. Thus, that leaves only Trayvon Martin crying for help, which completely contradicts Zimmerman's account. IOW, for Zimmerman to save his skin, he reversed everything. Zimmerman said he was the one crying for help, when he wasn't, which probably means that he was the one (holding the gun) who told Trayvon Martin "you are going to die tonight" or something to that effect, right before Zimmerman pulled the trigger, BAM, leaving a dead scared kid who'd just been walking back home from a nearby convenience store while talking on a cellphone to his girlfriend. But if this all eventually leads  to a day in court for Mr. Zimmerman (either one of them) , let's let a jury decide, based on the evidence).</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67iwuk</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cusm</id></website><link>http://www.rawstory.com/rs/2012/03/31/maher-no-doubt-zimmerman-is-a-big-fat-fking-liar/</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T14:35:19+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-01T00:54:26+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0mawg</id><link>http://www.rawstory.com/rs/2012/03/31/maher-no-doubt-zimmerman-is-a-big-fat-fking-liar/#comment-482378909</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/n23j</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>