<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31xdj/post/2012-03-29T16:10:51</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Homs: Summary of Events, Wednesday,March 28, 2012
Part 1 

Resilient despite the bombing and destruction

There goes another day of bombing and destruction in Homs and its neighborhoods. Communications were intermittently back in some areas, which electricity and water are still cut Off for most of the day. The food andmedical shortages continue, and no store has opened its doors in Homs for nearly two months. There is a curfew imposed, and the only movement is of residents trying to migrate from their homes out of fear of massacres that the Assad forces are committing.

Old districts of Homs: these areas are still under continuous violent bombing, which has been going on for nearly 3 weeks. The bombing is mainly targeting the neighborhoods of Sifsafeh, Hamidiyeh, Bistan al-Diwan, and Bab Houd. Assad forces are using all types of bombs, mortars, and rockets, and theyare being launched from nearby loyalist neighborhoods, like Zahra and Nuzha. Assad forces targeted Umm al-Zinnar Church with several mortars that fell near the church and completely destroyed a nearby home. Assad forces also targeted AbiThi al-Ghaffar mosque in Bab Tadmur. A number of civilians were injured and others killed, while homes and mosques were destroyed because of the barbaric bombing.

Deir Baalba: Assad forces and thugs tried to invade the southern area ofthe neighborhood and bombed it violently, which resulted in destroying parts ofsome buildings, killing some civilians, injuring others, and Burning the propane-distribution center in the neighborhood. Meanwhile, residents started migrating because of the violent bombing.

Khaldiyeh, Bayada, and Wadi al-Arab: since the early morning hours, the artillery and mortar bombing started, which resulted in destroying some homes and injuring a number of civilians.

Old districts of Homs | A T-72 tank launches a bomb at the neighborhood –March 26, 2012
http://youtu .be/s-BR5Zbm5HU

Homs | The random bombing of residential homes continues
http://youtu .be/GSCmR-iIEG8

Homs | A woman injured in the jaw by a sniper’s bullet(GRAPHIC)
http://youtu .be/fIRiF9IQ3zs

 </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dkvsy</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cjnq</id></website><link>http://blogs.aljazeera.net/middle-east/2011/10/20/syria-live-blog</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T16:11:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:10:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31xdj</id><link>http://blogs.aljazeera.net/middle-east/2011/10/20/syria-live-blog#comment-479837835</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g2pn1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>