<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miybv8/post/2012-03-22T20:48:11</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I don't know if it would be possible to do this, but if The Thrive Movement is looking for a company to recommend to people in the natural health care industry that is also 100% committed to helping people and helping the planet, you can't get better than Shaklee. It's a 55 year old company that had led the industry in green cleaning products and scientifically proven, safe, and effective natural supplementation for over fifty years.

 In 2000 Shaklee was the first company in the world to obtain Climate Neutral certification and totally offset its carbon emissions.  Dr. Wangari Maathai, 2004 Nobel Prize recipient, partnered with Shaklee in its A Million Trees, A Million Dreams campaign which resulted in a million tress being planted in North America.  In 2007 Shaklee was honored with Global USA's Organizational Design Award for its outstanding role in effecting positive environmental change. I could go on and on about all the wonderful things that Shaklee has done through the years.

Dr. Elizabeth Blackburn, 2009 Nobel Prize recipient for her work in medicine, specifically telomeres, is partnering with Shaklee now because of its solid science behind our nutritional products, including Vivix.  Vivix is a resveratrol product which has been shown to do several things, including repairing DNA damage at the cellular level - think what that could possibly mean for diseases, especially cancers!  This sounds "too good to be true" to some people,
but you don't have a Nobel Prize recipient like Dr. Blackburn partner with company such as Shaklee unless there's some serious science behind the product.  We all know that the answer to cancer is not going to come from our current medical system or any of the pharmaceutical companies!

So what's the point?  The point is exactly what you said at the end of Thrive.  Individuals can be making a significant difference for our planet by finding companies like Shaklee who are committed to people's well being and the planet and begin to redirect their spending dollars on things like cleaning products, nutritional supplements, sports nutrition, Weight loss and weight management products, and other products people use every day.  You can even get a check in the mail from Shaklee if you switch out enough of your household products to Shaklee.  When was the last time anyone got a check in the mail from any of the stores you currently shop at for simply being a loyal customer? I know I haven't!  The wife of our current CEO, Sloan Barnett, has even gotten Shaklee's cleaning products in the Obama White House and the Vice-President's mansion!

The bottom line is that Shaklee is on the leading edge of the preventative health care industry as well as being totally committed to the planet.  Shaklee also makes it possible through their new patented compensation plan for the average person to build a business with a career income so that we can begin redirecting our spending dollars away from the huge corporations and put those dollars back into the hands of anyone who wants to work hard building a business, all the while helping people get healthy and saving the planet. The Barnett family was very wealthy before they purchased Shaklee in 2004 and they aren't looking to Gain more wealth on the backs of the common person.    Google "Roger Barnett" on you tube or just google Shaklee and you'll see what I mean.

You can get on my website at www.janetwilson.myshaklee.com to see videos about the company, Roger Barnett,  our products, and our compensation plan.  This is exactly the kind of company that Thrive is encouraging people to partner with to create positive planetary change. I just wanted to make sure you knew about Shaklee and see if there was a way for your website to let people know about companies like Shaklee that have the same vision you do.  I no longer want my spending dollars going to companies that don't support the planet but it's hard to find out which companies do or don't!

Thanks for all the incredible work you are doing!  Wow - it's amazing.

In Love and Light,

Janet Wilson
Lubbock, Texas
806.778.3010
www.janetwilson.myshaklee.com
janetwilson8@aol.com</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/douw7i</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/17xq</id></website><link>http://www.thrivemovement.com/views/the_12_sectors-media</link><postedTime>2012-01-08T22:39:59+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T00:48:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miybv8</id><link>http://www.thrivemovement.com/views/the_12_sectors-media#comment-474100706</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zd9vj</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-01-08</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>