<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4x94/post/2012-03-30T17:48:08</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4lz3</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7mr6</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Let me let you in on a little . No case law is ever dispositive in front of the Supreme Court. None. I know, shocking! 

First, no two *events* will ever be exactly the same. They will Always be different- distinguishable. Keep that in mind. Let's go through some factors-

1. Completely on-point. Let's say that SCOTUS takes another flag Burning law. It's another state statute, worded exactly like the Texas statute. So Texas v. Johnson is completely on point. *But* the Supreme Court is welcome to ignore it. It happens.

2. Distinguish cases. This is what we see all the time. You can distinguish based on *any principle you can find*. And what you then say is, well, this time it's different. Happens a lot. Look at the standing cases involving taxpayers and religion. Then look at, inter alia, Valley Forge. All you need is to find your hook and explain to the Court why, this time, it's different. Red car, green car. And get them to distinguish the prior case.

3. That said, you misunderstand the onus. The burden is not on the government to find some case, somewhere, that said an action is approved. It doesn't work like that. The cases prior all indicated that this was *perfectly constitutional*. Every time the government does something, it doesn't need to find a prior Supreme Court case that explicitly says, "Yes, you may do this exact thing we're talking about." Instead, the Supreme Court cases that allowed the government to enact comprehensive regulatory schemes, combined with the N&amp;P case law, and (yes) originalism all indicated this. Which you would know if you read the arguments in good faith. This doesn't mean the PPACA would or should win. SCOTUS can do what they want. But your posts are kind of ridiculous.  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67mvqn</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/okle</id></website><link>http://volokh.com/2012/03/30/why-did-legal-elites-underestimate-the-case-against-the-mandate/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:52:09+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:48:08+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4x94</id><link>http://volokh.com/2012/03/30/why-did-legal-elites-underestimate-the-case-against-the-mandate/#comment-481238154</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zdj8t</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>