<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fyzk/post/2012-03-29T16:41:30</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Shock boot again?  Oh no!  That can only mean a good singer will be leaving and Heejun will stay on.  

I have given Phillip credit for his unique sound and artistry, but honestly it's not happening for me. It could just be his singing style.  I think he sounds the same in every performance.  I guess MJ has it right since he seems to be very popular and has that appeal, WGWG and all.  It's just depressing to see this happen every season lately.  

I think I had Elise higher than MJ last week.  I think she may be connecting with her good song choices.  This performance last night was absolutely freakin' amazing!  I would keep Jessica at the#2 Spot.  I guess Colton is another one that I just do not get.  I think he sucks the life out of his songs. He had some real vocal problems at the beginning and end of his performance.  I wonder if the whole Christian thing will help or hurt. I guess he deserves to be up near the top.

I feel like Skylar may be losing steam. It's true that she is the only country singer, but her song choices haven't done her any favors. She is  a strong performer with confidence and great stage presence, but I think she is slipping a little.  I guess it's okay to keep her in the #5 Spot.  

Deandre is mid-pack. He has been struggling to find the right song and make it work.  I thought his performance last night was his best since "Master Blaster", but if we are being real here, it's Philipp and Colton who are the guys to beat.

I hate seeing Hollie slip, but for whatever reason this song didn't seem to give her the momentum she needed.  The nitpicking from the judges didn't help either.  For Randy - there were no pitch problems in that performance. I have only heard a few Off key notes in last week's performance. Otherwise this girl's technical brilliance is unquestioned. Not that this means anything in the grand scheme of Idol.  I just think she needed to change it up somehow this week.  It's hard to take on a Carrie Underwood song and it may not have been well received by the viewers.  
I thought Joshua gave an amazing performance, but maybe he is kind of over the top with his gospel tinged r&amp;b.  I would like to think he shouldn't be quite this low, certainly not one step above Heejun.  

I am going to be extremely upset if someone really good goes instead of Heejun. It's not a comedy show, it's a singing competition and he has struggled every single week.  The judges giving him a standing ovation for not being crap last night, was beyond embarrassing. So now we are celebrating mediocrity? I hope not.

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z4ues</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q17i</id></website><link>http://www.mjsbigblog.com/american-idol-11-top-9-power-list.htm</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:15:59+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:41:30+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fyzk</id><link>http://www.mjsbigblog.com/american-idol-11-top-9-power-list.htm#comment-479869159</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/0v17</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>