<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m090s3/update/2012-04-02T02:08:00/9d8e060d980ffc7d8bd1b72b632bdeafccfeaf2fbecc76cdca892cb74c9670e3</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m06jj2</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/67453</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>A comparison between Shinto and Christianity does not go very far because the former is much simpler than the latter. For instance, Shinto ethics does not go far beyond "Pure is good, impure is bad". The rest of Japanese morality came from Confucianism and Buddhism. 

An American scholar, presumably back in the late 19th century, went to Japan to study Shintoism. He asked a Shinto priest what was their theology. The Shinto priest responded "We don't have theology! We dance!". 

That largely sums up Shinto. It is a form of paganism, which means that it is not a religion at all, at least not in the Euro-Middle Eastern sense, but just every-day life in an enchanted world. You Burned some incense to the mountain spirit before you ascended the mountain so that, hopefully, there would be less chance of you falling Off the mountain. "Faith" as understood by the Middle Eastern religions is not much of a factor. It is not so different from the way people today hire lawyers, doctors, and other professionals to reduce the possibility that something bad would happen to them. The only difference is that traditional paganism existed in a world where human beings saw themselves as organic extensions as nature, whereas in the contemporary world humans tend to see nature as extensions of human needs.  

I do not think that the older traditionalist Japanese lament the decline of Shinto (which arguably is not declining at all...the Japanese, by and large, still believe that they are a race apart), but rather of the warrior virtues of pre-1945 Japan. Shintoism long predates the samurai, whose values were formed via a particular mix of Shinto aesthetics, Confucian ethics, and Zen Buddhist ontology. Faced with the social disintegration engendered by rapid modernization, certain Japanese elites in the 1920s-30s tried to generalize the samurai spirit to the whole population. It was an understandable, albiet messy and not-so-well thought out  effort that came to a halt with Japan's defeat. Now, samurai virtues are not completely gone, it is just that they exist in a very attenuated "bourgeosified" form. The spirit of self-sacrifice, for instance, is noticeable, even if it tends to assert itself through the working-to-death of corporate salarymen.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zsnns</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/e57v</id></website><link>http://www.alternativeright.com/main/blogs/euro-centric/dogwhistle-islam-triumphs-in-bradford-west/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T06:45:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T06:08:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m090s3</id><link>http://www.alternativeright.com/main/blogs/euro-centric/dogwhistle-islam-triumphs-in-bradford-west/#comment-483309393</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/y05u4</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>