<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjeke/update/2012-03-26T14:17:37/e65213def156fb871d7a0a6d6508df59f24cd6eb33d3076a2f9acb2241e03b86</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Not to pick nits but I disagree with the premise of this article.  The four big issues are with the current health care , not with health care.

Let's zoom back out and look at Health Care which is not inexorably tied to this one piece of legislation.  Here is what I want. 

1.  I want everyone in the United States to have affordable access to basic health care.  Those that can't afford it or choose not to have it are clogging our ERs with issues that should have been handled by a Primary Care physician and those expenses are passed on to me.

2.  I want everyone in the United States to be in a single risk pool.  My company of 35 employees is fighting to stay alive and one of their biggest Headaches is providing health care.  One person got cancer a couple of years ago and the premiums tripled for everyone.  That's because of a small risk pool.  If there was one single risk pool, that simply wouldn't happen.

3.  I want basic health care policies to be fungible.  That means that they are identical and can be compared.  I don't care how many of them there are but there should be a finite number and they should be identifiable from provider to provider.  Right now, all of the policies are just different enough that they can't be compared.  Companies (including mine) hire consultants to sift through the variations and find the right policy.  Market forces can only do their thing if products can be compared.

4.  I want health care decoupled from employment.  Employer provided health care has only been around since WWII when Henry Kaiser started it.  People should not be prisoners of their employers.

5.  Everyone consumes health care.  Everyone should help pay for it to the extent that they can.  I'm fine if people want some sort of opt-out but I honestly don't know how that would work.  What is a first-responder or an ER doc to do to determine if a patient has decided that they don't want treatment.  Maybe, in lieu of insurance, requiring people to have a $10,000 line of credit to pay for transport and ER stabilization?  Then the person can arrange to either pay cash or leave.  The goal here is that no one should knowingly throw themselves on the mercy of the ER docs and expect anything if they opt out of the health insurance system I am paying for.

6.  I want the incentives changed to health outcomes.  I want docs to be rewarded for making me healthy, not performing procedures.  That's why they got into medicine anyway.

7.  I want the pharmaceutical industry rewarded for cures, not treatments.  I have read that there are many diseases that could simply be cured but big pharma can make more money  of treating chronic illness than they can Off of a cure.  We all like to joke about how the car companies suppress the engine that runs on water.  What do you suppose a pharaceutical company would do with a single $1.00 pill that cures Type 2 Diabetes?

Like I said, I don't care if this is public or private.  I suspect it would have to be public.  If it's private, my point #3 would go a long way to keeping costs down.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rh7fh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/25/politics/scotus-health-care-four-issues/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-25T16:11:56+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:17:37+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjeke</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/25/politics/scotus-health-care-four-issues/index.html#comment-476599938</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cdmi6</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>