<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjamq/update/2012-03-26T14:08:04/cff7cbae70b07df1b31d22afe84f7bdb2c1d07513f5118e94bb3ae1f28fe2f24</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Barack Obama, during his Cairo speech, said:   "I know, too, that Islam has  been a part of  America 's story." 
 AN AMERICAN CITIZEN'S RESPONSE: 
  Dear Mr. Obama: 
Were those Mu slims that were in America when the Pilgrims first landed?  Funny, I thought they were Native American Indians. 
Were those Mu slims that celebrated the first Thanksgiving day?  Sorry again, those were Pilgrims and Native American Indians. 
Can you show me one Mu slim signature on the United States Constitution? 
  Declaration of Independence ? 
Bill of Rights? 
  Didn't think so. 
  Did Mu slims fight for this country's freedom from England ?  No. 
  Did Mu slims fight during the Civil War to free the slaves in America ?  No, they did not.  In fact, Mu slims to this day are still the largest traffickers in human slavery..  Your own half brother, a devout Mu slim, still advocates slavery himself, even though Mu slims of Arabic descent refer to bl ack Mu slims as "pug nosed slaves."  Says a lot of what the Mu slim world really thinks of your family's "rich Islamic heritage," doesn't it Mr. Obama? 
  Where were Mu slims during the Civil Rights  of this country?  Not present. 
  There are no pictures or media accounts of Mu slims walking side by side with Martin Luther King, Jr. or helping to advance the cause of Civil Rights. 
  Where were Mu slims during this country's Woman's Suffrage ?  Again, not present.  In fact, devout Mu slims demand that women are subservient to men in the Islamic culture.  So much so, that often they are beaten for not wearing the 'hajib' or for talking to a man who is not a direct family member or their husband.  Yep, the Mu slims are all for women's rights, aren't they? 
  Where were Mu slims during World War II?  They were  with Adolf Hit ler.  The Mu slim grand mufti himself met with Adolf Hit ler, reviewed the troops and accepted support from the Na zi's in kil ling Je ws. 
  Finally, Mr. Obama, where were Mu slims on Sept. 11th, 2001?  If they weren't flying planes into the World Trade Center , the Pentagon or a field in Pennsylvania kil ling nearly 3,000 people on our own soil, they were rejoicing in the Middle East .  No one can dispute the pictures shown from all parts of the Mu slim world celebrating on CNN, Fox News, MSNBC and other cable news networks that day.  Strangely, the very "moderate" Mu slims who's as ses you bent over backwards to kiss in Cairo , Egypt on June 4th were stone Cold silent post 9-11.  To many Americans, their silence has meant approval for the Acts of that day. 
  And THAT, Mr. Obama, is the "rich heritage" Mu slims have here in America .. 
  Oh, I'm sorry, I forgot to mention the Barbary Pirates.  They were Mu slim. 
  And now we can add November 5, 2009 - the slau ghter of American soldiers at Fort Hood by a Mu slim major who is a doctor and a psychiatrist who was supposed to be counseling soldiers returning from battle in Iraq and Afghanistan .. 
  That, Mr. Obama is the "Mu slim heritage" in America </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rizmu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yjmx</id></website><link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2012/03/26/obama-tells-medvedev-hell-have-more-flexibility-after-election-during-missile/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T11:39:57+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:08:04+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjamq</id><link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2012/03/26/obama-tells-medvedev-hell-have-more-flexibility-after-election-during-missile/#comment-476592607</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yy8m1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>