<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkj1ph/post/2012-03-26T14:44:49</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Obama: U.S. can afford to have fewer nukes

CBS Radio News White House correspondent Peter Maer is in Seoul, South Korea, covering President Obama's participation in the international nuclear security summit.

(CBS News) SEOUL - Setting the tone for a nuclear security summit, President Obama reiterated Monday his call for a world without nuclear weapons.

Mr. Obama told a university audience in South Korea that the U.S. possesses more nuclear arms than it needs, and can reduce that arsenal without damaging America's security.

The remark will keep the president at odds with Republicans who believe any major cuts in the number of nuclear warheads would weaken the efficacy of the U.S. nuclear deterrent.

Mr. Obama spoke in unusually personal terms about the nuclear challenge.

"I believe the United States has a unique responsibility to Act - indeed, we have a moral obligation," Mr. Obama told the university audience. "I say this as President of the only nation ever to use nuclear weapons. I say it as a Commander-in-Chief who knows that our nuclear codes are never far from my side. Most of all, I say it as a father, who wants my two young daughters to grow up in a world where everything they know and love can't be instantly wiped out."

The president argued that the Cold War nuclear stockpile is "poorly suited to today's threats, including nuclear terrorism" - the main theme of the Seoul summit.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rpi96</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t33k</id></website><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/thought-about-the-healthcare-law-arguments-before-us-supreme-court-that-start-today/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T11:08:01+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:44:49+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkj1ph</id><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/thought-about-the-healthcare-law-arguments-before-us-supreme-court-that-start-today/#comment-476623201</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>