<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3bx8f/update/2012-03-29T14:41:18/df97d04fb3e356630de4c7cb6afccc23a315154849171043c7b6b7bea4dfe3c0</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qrn6</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c49sw</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I am dealing with the real world Michael. You look to be about 40ish . . . about the same age the guy who wrote my will was when he had a stroke while driving back from a Bigfoot convention. Now if you do not have insurance for whatever reason, Michael, I am hoping that you have the financial wherewithal to scratch a check for $85,000 to $200,000 or so your care will cost -- covering the cost of the ambulance, emergency room, stroke treatment, medications, hospital care, surgery to relieve Bleeding, clip of vessels, angiogram, rehabilitation facility, occupational therapy, stroke rehabilitation, etc. Yes, we as a society value you enough that we are requiring the hospital system to front you those expenses. 


This is not a libertarian or Randian utopia where those without cash or insurance are left on the street. So, yes, you getting a woman pregnant or you having a stroke MAY impose a cost on me if you are uninsured, or don't have $200,000 in cash. Because, guess what? After your stroke? It is unlikely that you will be able to return to work anytime soon and pay Off that $200,000 you now owe the local hospital. And the rest of us will be stuck paying your bill because you lacked the responsibility and the financial wherewithal to pay your bill.

Enough with the analogies and lets deal with the real world problems presented by uninsured individuals.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zl0hb</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/okle</id></website><link>http://volokh.com/2012/03/29/justice-kennedy-actuarial-risk-and-the-individual-mandates-unconstitutionality/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:05:40+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:41:18+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3bx8f</id><link>http://volokh.com/2012/03/29/justice-kennedy-actuarial-risk-and-the-individual-mandates-unconstitutionality/#comment-479744305</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/amhsb</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>