<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/e2gygh/update/2011-11-14T15:21:16/1d65eaa58362e64b3cb1f6d070de202bee1d75f4d716831b70586c3d7ba167ba</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Wow, what interesting comments.  I just moved to Louisville from Boulder.  As stated, neither of these are mountain towns.  We are just East of the foothills and the mountains, and they are easy to get to.  My first impression about Louisville being voted #1 was, huh?  There are so many amazing towns/places in the U.S., I found it hard to believe.  What I can tell you is that I personally like Louisville better than Boulder.  It is less crowded, and there is less traffic.  It is less expensive than Boulder as far as housing goes (we rent).  It is nice because you can get to Denver more quickly from here, and yet you can zip right into Boulder too!  It feels family oriented in the neighborhood I live in, and it was built in the 80's, very cookie cutter house designs, but an upgrade for me because I was living in a rundown condo in Boulder.  My husband and I and our friend rented this place and it is way more affordable than something similar that is in Boulder.  It feels very safe here.  There is a cute old town Louisville area with shops and restaurants which has been hopping lately.  It is fun to ride your bike down there on a warm day.  There are lots of bike/walking trails through neighborhoods and open space.  For hiking however you have to go West to Boulder, Marshall, Eldorado, or other places up into the foothills/mountains.  Only like a 10-15min drive to the closest hiking trails.  This area does have bizarre weather.  One day it could be in the 80's and the next day it could be snowing.  This usually happens just before winter, or just before spring.  Usually the snow storms are short and most everything melts in a few days.  We sometimes get a week or so of REALLY Cold weather, below 20 degrees.  Compared to winters in the mountains, this place is a breeze.  Compared to winters on the N. East Coast, this place is a no biggy.  Compared to Hawaii, or S. California, this place in the winter would feel harsh.  Sometimes I am very tired of winter here ( I have lived in Denver/Boulder area for 25 years of my life) and would love to live somewhere more temperate.  It all  on the kind of person you are and what you have experienced so far in your life.  I miss the ocean, but I love the Mountains.
Louisville does have some nightlife, a few bars and restaurants are open late.  What ever Louisville lacks can be made up for in Boulder and Denver.  Granted Denver isn't New York City or San Francisco but it offers lots of entertaining things to do....Arts/Music/nightlife/Dining etc...
As far a pollution goes...the Denver Metro area and areas up against the foothills, do have pollution.  In the wintertime a temperature inversion can happen where air and everything in it is trapped and a lovely visible line of pollution forms.  This is not all the time, but some of the time.  That is what happens when you live near a BIG CITY like Denver and in this landscape.  
Is Louisville really a #1 place to live?  For me it is an improvement, it is nice, and quiet...in comparison to Boulder.  Overall though, I doubt it is really THE #1 place, out of all  the places in the country.  
You don't have to be Rich to live here, you can Always find a way to live in the place you want to live...granted it may involve sharing a house.  The annual mean income that Money stated for Louisville is WAY over our income.  We almost meet that mean with 3 adult incomes.   The housing market here is way higher than Texas, or Florida, but we are quite cheaper than LA or the San Fran area.
So, I hope this clears up any confusion or questions...
I think life is what you make of it, and where you live maybe has about 1/4-1/2 of influence on your life.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/elg3vo</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/qs0b</id></website><link>http://jcmsdev12.turner.com:86/magazines/moneymag/bplive/2011/snapshots/PL0846355.html</link><postedTime>2011-08-11T15:44:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-11-14T20:21:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/e2gygh</id><link>http://jcmsdev12.turner.com:86/magazines/moneymag/bplive/2011/snapshots/PL0846355.html#comment-363042193</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rlsma</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-08-11</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>