<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrzvq/post/2012-03-30T12:11:02</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3wn47</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzoo7</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>wait how could he be and really fight him back with a pack of skittles in one hand and wifey in the other? and im pretty sure Zimmerman didnt call in to say he shot him and you try and pull out a gun while someones beating the shit out of you on top of you tell me how easy it is remember he was still talking to wifey when he said his last words meaning he didnt Off the phone now it's pretty hard to believe that he could attack him w/ a phone in his hands and a hoodie on his movements would be pretty groggy if you tried fighting w/ a hoodie on before trust me you would know, now think about this if you take forensics blood splatter signifies how the blood was released from the victim for him to be on top of him or even be str8 up and shoot there would have to be some type of blood residue on Zimmerman, if he was laying down blood would only splatter up but barely because he was killed in Cold blood w/ a speeding bullet which has a small impact area, that being said the rest needs not to be explained, its not about being pathetic it's about being justified and searching for the truth, just a few years ago Troy Davis was killed for a crime im sure he didnt commit and now Trayvon Martin is killed in Cold blood for what? What is misinterpreted as a scuffle you cant sit there and say you dont have any sympathy for the victim nor the victims family because thats highly inconsiderate of you</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hwbrg</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/u6cr</id></website><link>http://www.worldstarhiphop.com/videos/video.php?v=wshhsw6ZY9XXei0yVx57</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T01:00:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:11:02+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrzvq</id><link>http://www.worldstarhiphop.com/videos/video.php?v=wshhsw6ZY9XXei0yVx57#comment-480902131</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rlhxv</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>