<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3zqw9/update/2012-03-29T05:36:00/1d0dbf60d89e5a93a12351c58ff1cfcb608ad39ecf1e1ea80aa60b268f0931c3</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The population of Ireland needs to get over its weird obsession with property, for many reasons.  
First, because far too many people believe the rameis put out by people like Mr Weston, and are still madly trying to "get on the property ladder".  
Second, it means far too much money is tied up in unproductive investments, which is not good for the economy as a whole.  We have seen the negative effects of a rampant housing only recently.  What is good for the housing market is NOT automatically good for the entire economy.
Third, for most sober and sensible people, the idea that "..house-lending market might just be about to loosen up" is probably not one that brings a smile of anticipation.  More of a shudder, or Tremor, associated with nightmares or terror.  Ireland does NOT need another property feeding frenzy.
Fourthly, much higher standards, especially in terms of insulation and general environmental impact need to be are enacted and enforced.  The general quality and insulation standards for houses in Ireland are abysmally low. 

The Irish housing market should adopt the idea, common in most countries, of a minimum 20% deposit.  Irish people would also be well advised to look at the model of house finance used in Denmark.  And prices need to drop further.

And Mr Weston should cease pretending to be some kind of unbiased observer.  He is just another lobbyist pleading for special treatment for one economic sector.  Such is nearly Always an assault on the taxpayers' wallets. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zadpk</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/qxal</id></website><link>http://www.independent.ie/opinion/analysis/radical-plumbing-key-to-repairing-house-market-3064934.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T03:50:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T09:36:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3zqw9</id><link>http://www.independent.ie/opinion/analysis/radical-plumbing-key-to-repairing-house-market-3064934.html#comment-479369618</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5hbrw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>