<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mieuav/post/2012-03-22T17:13:25</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi2hyp</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lxzrl</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Thanks, John P. 

I think a more fruitful perspective than faith vs works is to assess Scientology as just another ideology and evaluate it in its relationship to the common morality that underlies liberal democratic societies and its core institutions. 

The great philosopher-psychologist Silvan S. Tomkins (1909-2000) provides a useful framework from his long work on the sociology and psychology of ideology particularly in scientific research strategies. 

Tomkins writes that ideologies are tightly-woven sets of ideas about things about which we are least certain and therefore most passionate. He points out that there is the greatest uncertainty at the leading edge of science as theories proliferate before they are established a experimentally proven fact. 

The is an old adage that "There are no new theories in physics until the Old Guard dies Off on the Young Turks take over."  That is the sociology of knowledge at work in regard to scientific ideologies.

Humans have ideologies about all sort of things. Mothers-in-law and daughters-in-law have engaged in intense ideological warfare since the beginning of the human race over the proper way to raise children. Who knows for certain how best to raise a child?

All ideologies require faith and so there is the faith of the scientist, the mother-in-law, along with political faiths of conservatives and liberal and the religious ideologies with which we most commonly associate the term "faith."  

In Doherty's case, Scientology apology is the reigning ideology in academia and has assumed the status of a paradigm somewhat similar to Newtonian physics before Einstein. Paradigms fall when scholars like Steve Kent and Hugh Urban begin to question and do what their colleagues fail to do:  look at the data - all the data. 

Looking at Scientology as ideology also illuminates its kinship with totalitarian organizations. Its nearest analogs are not any Catholic, Protestant, Orthodox, or Jewish religious organizations but the Cold War communist regimes of Eastern Europe. 

It is here that Scientology is fundamentally inimical to the values, common morality, and institutions of liberal democratic society. Hubbard's sacred scriptures ordain unceasing effort to destroy liberal democratic legal systems and replace them with Scientology Ethics. This is one of the main reasons Germany put Scientology under surveillance as an extremist group. 

Hubbard also ordains unceasing war on the mental health professions and their destruction and replacement by auditing, vitamins, and the Purification Rundown. 

The common liberal democratic morality has evolved from its origins with Hebrew prophets, and Greek philosophers developed through Christianity and the Enlightenment. And moral understanding continues to evolve with periods of progress and regress. 

And this is what I think you are you referring to when you write " what is good and holy in the world at large (i.e., on an absolute basis)."

It is indeed permissible and obligatory to question the validity of the Church of Scientology.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yvjp4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rpyi</id></website><link>http://blogs.villagevoice.com/runninscared/2012/03/scientology_banned_in_russia_again.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T12:05:18+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T21:13:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mieuav</id><link>http://blogs.villagevoice.com/runninscared/2012/03/scientology_banned_in_russia_again.php#comment-473961508</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>