<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwr1a0/update/2012-03-30T12:22:50/3f9d8dc5d30b4b708ef519dceb3dbf69544d5a6afc0889786805b44ae09a132d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwe3rx</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Why do you think he murdered him because he is black.  Their is no evidence of murder and no evidence of racism.   I have tried to hear the "f-ing coons" comment but I can't make it out as that.  
As for murder:
An eyewitness says he saw Marin beating up Zimmerman and Zimmerman calling for help.  The eyewitness was close enough that he talked to Martin -telling him he was calling 911Multiple eye witnesses say they saw Zimmerman Bleeding from the nose and head.

The police report records that he was Bleeding from 
the nose and head.

The 911 call records Zimmerman screaming (police 
verified it was Zimmerman's voice.) for help and out of fear and/or pain.

When the dispatcher told Zimmerman to stop following, Zimmerman said "OK"
The fight seems to have taken place outside Zimmerman's car.  

All the evidence that I see exonerates Zimmerman and verifies his story.

Listen, if he is guilty, then the investigation ought to bear that out but why is the president getting him lynched?  The real racists, The Black Panthers, have put a million dollar Bounty on his head.  There is a problem with racism alright, but there is no evidence  hispanic v black racism as you assert.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z9o9n</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/egg0</id></website><link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2012/03/29/mark_levin_if_i_had_another_son_hed_look_like_brian_terry-comments.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:03:51+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:22:50+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwr1a0</id><link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2012/03/29/mark_levin_if_i_had_another_son_hed_look_like_brian_terry-comments.html#comment-480914567</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l7bjh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>