<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mimvw8/post/2012-03-22T18:01:52</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Americans wanting even less government from just about every aspect of their lives advocates privatizing the police. 

The “Stand Your Ground” Law seems only one step away from realizing those dreaming of today’s public police force eliminated and turning it over to a corporatize private sector. 

Since the end of the Cold War, Private Military Companies (PMCs), Private Security Companies (PSCs), defense contractors, and firms in adjacent sectors play growing roles in support of state defense and multilateral reconstruction strategies. And it is coming into every American neighborhood. 

The proportion of contracted security personnel in the firing line is 10 times greater than during the first Gulf war. In 1991, for every private contractor, there were about 100 servicemen and women; now there are 10. 
The private sector is so firmly embedded in combat, occupation and peacekeeping duties that the phenomenon may have Reached the point of no return: the US military would struggle to wage war without it. The US Military looks privatized than ever before. Your local police will soon be privatized too.

The “Stand Your Ground” Law seems only one step away from realizing those dreaming of today’s public police force eliminated and turning it over to a corporatize private sector. 

This Standford Police Chief will easily get a job at the private sector. That would not shock me one bit.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y9qas</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yjmx</id></website><link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2012/03/22/sanford-police-chief-steps-down-amid-outrage-over-shooting-death-teen/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T19:53:06+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T22:01:52+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mimvw8</id><link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2012/03/22/sanford-police-chief-steps-down-amid-outrage-over-shooting-death-teen/#comment-474000266</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/55fnv</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>