<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/236461/post/69155282/comment/329400112</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>accidentally saw this article, and thought that it was a good turn. Whether male or female, should have it! ; a, have the confidence and grace , men to the twenties, it is necessary to learn the intentions to run themselves, and it is reflected in their thoughts and conservation. Self-confidence is a man of the most important quality, confident men like a battle in the storm seagull. Seagull by to say only one sentence, A confident man,  able to infect others, whether they are friend or foe. To make others have confidence in you, we must first have confidence. A confident man can overcome all difficulties. a man of grace is like an ocean, not to resist the bit, but also inclusive of rivers. Manners make the man more favor, and not be able to compete in front world, given that others can benefit. The so-called The demeanor chosen men look chic thousands. after Second, develop the habit of reading and writing man in his twenties, began to be into the community, in the process of interaction with others, conversation and self-cultivation most able to conquer others. A man of knowledge must be reading a wise man must be  writing. No matter how much busy, have to take time out to look at reading, writing articles. Because it can change a man\'s thinking and behavior. A man to change his thoughts, the first thing to do is read a good book, read a book like to pay a good friend, he was able to help you to take their own road. Reading life is the most colorful time of writing is the most enlightening wisdom. like a man of reading and writing, will be able to cultivate a good attitude. Because the ocean of knowledge and wisdom is boundless,Hermes Birkin, but like a man of reading and writing as they do from the pursuit. Pursuit of a man\'s thinking, is a man of action, never give up the pursuit of every moment to motivate men to fight. In this battle, so that a man can experience the baptism of wind and rain, to grow into a towering tree. Reading made them cool, and writing so that men become mature. the Three, to try to find the truth, goodness, the US men to life in the twenties, we must learn how to face life. What is Be kind to others, is to treat their own lives. Sometimes your a bit of goodwill will be able to bear a good fruit to make your life become happy. philosopher said, in life, this is not the lack of beauty, is missing is found that the United States in the eye Yes, life is really the case. Do not  thinking about their own misfortune, and to do so will only make your life more unfortunate. Do you think As long as you often lift to rise, look at the sun, you can feel the warmth. In the warmth and optimism to chase a better life, you will naturally find that the United States. ; ; , and thoughtful people to make friends man in his twenties, it has the purpose to choose a friend. Social connections is very important to your circle of friends will be your life plays a great impact. Man to make friends, to pay more critical friends, not bad company. The so-called friends of those friends that you have, and these people tend to own is also very good. Pay more for the friends of a person\'s life, are very useful. But the real friends of difficult to make, because this friend needs you to pay a great deal of sincere, heartfelt sincerity. friend of thinking, he knows very well that you have not him as a friend. If you are just using him, he is not in their hearts to you as a friend to look at. To make friends sometimes and there is no purpose, you just feel that this person is thinking, it is worth to you intersect. But often these thoughtful friends, in your most difficult time to  out his hand. Friends, is one of the most important element in the life of a man. A man in order to make themselves as living like a real man, be sure to make friends, to pay more critical friends. V, we must get rid of their bad habits man in his twenties, he must get rid of their own bad habits. Bad habits is to develop good habits to develop. Cultivate good habits, is to get rid of their bad habits. If a man into the twenties, and had had such as bad habits, it is a very bad thing. These bad habits will hinder the development of your life, life will lose a lot of glory, the business will be difficult to achieve even greater success. If you now like to sleep late, then the morning of the first wipe of the sun will never shine your smile. If you now  drag on, then you will never can not stand on the position of champion. If you will not now take the initiative to learn and work, your future can only be a bleak gray. I do not believe what a man want a gray life, all the men expect to have a colorful life. Therefore, in order to make their own colorful life, and men to the twenties, you have to get rid of their bad habits. the six, learn patience and tolerance men to the twenties,1000 Union businesses, it is necessary to learn patience and tolerance. In society, often many things you can not accept, but you have to accept these things, which requires your patience. The patience of others is actually tolerant of others, a man able to forgive others will look great degree. A successful man is also often one can bite the bullet man. Loneliness, a man from the lonely, the man\'s patience is in order to better the outbreak. those who say we fool people and say For those who no reason to accuse us of people, do not argue with them, because this will only change their own anger. Rather than to hurt others, it is better to forgive others, tolerance is the treatment of others wound the best panacea. after seven, to maintain a good attitude, attention to their bodies men twenties, we must learn to adjust their attitude, attention to their body. The body is the capital of revolution, the mentality of the Detector. Men in order to obtain more wealth is necessary to have a strong physique, a man in order to do the richest man in a long time we should have a positive and optimistic attitude. Diet, regular exercise, plenty of sleepy eyes, is the guarantee of a healthy body. Do not hesitate, hard-working attitude is everything. you can not have every day, morning run, in fact, that also will not take you long time, the need is persistence and perseverance. But you should  exercise your body, walking is a good choice as it will fill you with strength. You can not in the winter in Cold water, in fact, it is no big deal, because I have to insist on a winter. In the winter, you must  wash in Cold water wash, do so not only can prevent Colds, but also to keep a clear mind. You can fail, but you never have to maintain a triumph of mind to overcome their own, and you have no enemies. and keep your smile and courtesy to your card men twenties,  keep your smile. Smiling, you are a good people, all people are willing to deal with good people. Do not anguish written on your face, this will only allow others to stay away from you. What kind of person, others by smiling greeting with his judgment. This judgment is your impression in the hearts of people play a very important role. is often said that Polite people,Hermes Birkin bags, concern for others. Others will be because of your courtesy and concern, and give you to the chances of success. The man\'s business card is a smile and politeness, it is a man of a successful career passes. nine, the pursuit of a woman, his real love life you will not regret it men twenties and slowly will be very eager to love. This is a very normal thing, do not suppress their own emotional heart. When a man is the most stupid, most lovely when he fell in love with a woman. When you love a woman did not know she would not fall in love with you, you must choose an appropriate time to declare. As is the option to accept also choose to reject it  on your fate and your efforts. Men must understand that women most desire a love with her man. love such a thing can not force a man must understand. Do not not you love to let your friendship easily lost, and become friends with a woman he ever loved is a rare good thing. Love is sacred and inviolable, because it is the most willing to choice, respect and trust between people it is reflected in. So a man must respect the choice of the woman you love, and I believe her choice is a decision made for her own happiness. As long as you have the pursuit of a woman that you really love, then your life will not regret it. 10, to their careers to give everything a man twenties, must be for their own career to hard work. The most important man is the cause, the cause of man can not be counted as a real man. The cause of man\'s uncertain to be vigorous, but it must be to accomplish something, to make himself proud. A strong devotion to man, but also an equally strong man to win the heart and sense of responsibility. To win the heart of men, from immoderation. Strong sense of responsibility of men, from fear or difficulty. Men become tall because of his successful career, to Gain others\' respect and trust. as a man, it is necessary to pay for their own career. To be successful you have to pay to pay means that you have to lose something. If you do not want to pay any price for the cause, then you can only lose something more, and finally nothing. 11, love with the cause is the bumper can jointly owned of men twenties, you should strive to love with the cause of. People often say that if a man choose love will lose the cause, if you choose a career not love. I chose not to think so, I would love more sweet man, the more successful career. In fact,Hermes Bags, love and career, this is two different things, love vigorous man, not at all interfere with their successful career. A man must love moisture than the one I do not know that love is what the taste of a man is more mature, more attractive, more great work\'s determination. twenties men, do not believe that those who are extreme words. Just as is often said that The difference between marriage and love is just a number of Only men and women through marriage to a thorough understanding of what love is. Love is mutual understanding, mutual encouragement and mutual support. In life, help each other, help each other in their careers, make love with the cause of a double harvest. 12, we must strive to do better than women man twenties, we must strive in all things than women do better. Even better things than women do have to work hard to do as good a woman. Here This is not to say that men are inherently stronger than women, but say that men are born than women do better. Because women efforts, it is easy to surpass men, so men should strive to do better than women is right and proper. In today\'s society, the status of women, women first have to select the power of men. So if you can not compare a woman do better as a man, then woman Why choose you? women often say, Men not only in their own areas very well, but also be able to do as well this is a woman\'s field. 13 efforts to help his wife achieve her dream man in his twenties, if you are already married, then you must strive to achieve her dream to help his wife . The doctrine of people, The woman\'s dream and a man living together never disappear, it will only become more intense. Woman such a strong desire and dreams may not show in front of you, but your mind must understand. wife is the core of the life of a man, his wife, life is happiness, man must care. Do not think his wife to take home, that is to serve you. Every man\'s wife will be concerned about her husband,Hermes Handbags, every man must learn to care for his wife. Most concerned about the wife thing is concerned about what her dream is, how do to help his wife achieve her dreams. 14, learn some of the brave, to assume their own responsibility on the shoulders man in his twenties, to learn to be brave, from their own shoulders to take on their own share of the bounden duty of. Filial piety is the responsibility of a man, loved his wife and children is the responsibility of a man\'s successful career is a man\'s responsibility. The responsibility of men is nothing more than a family and career. These responsibilities are indeed heavy, but as a man you must play their own shoulders to bear. There is no reason, just because you are a man. the as men have the power to cry, but no the power Kuchu voice. As men have the power to cry, but not the power to cry in front of parents, wives and children. As men have the power to give up, but has no authority to give up the family and career responsibilities. As a man,Hermes Kelly, you have no choice, you can only choose to take, use your shoulders to bear. ; fifteen, never give up their own, believe they can do it men to the twenties, it must be to never give up their own. The reason why people give up on you, it is because you have to give up their own. I believe that as long as you do not give up on themselves, which people will abandon you, or that no person can give up your. I believe he is a man overcome all the power of the source, do not believe that man is not the reasons, because his foot cross to the grave failure of. have a slogan, say There is an advertisement, said, Yes, I think, I also believe that every man can believe in yourself, you can do it. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:236461:69155282</id><idPostId>69155282</idPostId><idBlogId>236461</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:236461</id><idBlogId>236461</idBlogId><link>http://www.strengththroughcommunity.org</link><displayName>Strength Through Community</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.strengththroughcommunity.org/2010/11/idit-klein-of-keshet-for-strength-through-community-it-gets-better/</link><displayName>Idit Klein of Keshet for Strength Through Community, It Gets Better</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-01T18:25:00.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:236461:69155282:329400112</id><link>http://www.strengththroughcommunity.org/2010/11/idit-klein-of-keshet-for-strength-through-community-it-gets-better/#IDComment329400112</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T18:25:00.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Idit Klein of Keshet for Strength Through Community, It Gets Better by uii9ie1p</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://hermeshandbags-sale.com/</link><idEmailMd5>96a64324f22b2c912bc43c9442b84105</idEmailMd5><displayName>uii9ie1p</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://hermeshandbags-sale.com/"&gt;uii9ie1p&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.strengththroughcommunity.org/2010/11/idit-klein-of-keshet-for-strength-through-community-it-gets-better/"&gt;Idit Klein of Keshet for Strength Through Community, It Gets Better&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>