<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwezy8/post/2012-03-30T08:07:37</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Yesterday I argued that the most significant event over the last 100 years in terms of impacting the fate of the most people was the unexpected invasion of Russia by Nazi Germany on June 22, 1941.

Today I am going to argue that two events over the past 100 years that have had the most impact on the life of the most Americans is what happened in America during the Coolidge administration (1923-1929) and the end of the Cold War and the break-up of the Soviet Union in the early 1990's.

From Ron Siwak of Golf Digest: 

Written just after 's Woods debut in 1996:

"An overwhelming significant event rarely announces its presence."

And here from Preston Slosson in The Great Crusade and After 1914-1928 is the prevailing attitude in the USA right after WWI:

"...The moral slump which followed when the tumult and the Shouting died--the blunted conscience, the overwrought nerves, standards unsettled by the recent prodigality, just as in the days of reconstruction after the Civil War..."

In addition there was the problem of an economic slump in the USA between 1919 and 1923 due to converting from a wartime economy to a peacetime economy.

Out of that reality, Calvin Coolidge fashioned one of the greatest presidencies of all time and in his watch he saw the greatest economic prosperity and technological development during his time in office compared to what had gone on just before. If you are so inclined, do your own research on what life was like in America in the 1910's and the compare it to the 1920's under Coolidge. It really is the difference between night and day. What the right-wing politicians of today only talk about, Coolidge accomplished in spades by 10 fold.

And yet the prominent politicians on our side hardly ever refer to this period in history and what an administration deeply committed to free enterprise and a low tax regime could accomplish.

But in the spirit of conservatives being poor promoters the other most significant event was the end of the Cold War.

From Napoleon:

"The most dangerous moment comes with victory."

Think about it: What were the odds that a Marxist could be elected President of the USA before the break-up of the Soviet Union? Not even slim. Nil.

Now ask yourself what conditions gave rise to Obama becoming President. I would argue the #1 event that led to the rise of Obama was that Americans simply have let their guard down vis-a-vis Communism, Marxism or socialism or whatever label you want to give it. By putting the Cold War in their rearview mirror, Americans since the early 1990's have NOT placed the same political stigma on being a socialist or boasting a socialist background. Read Napoleon's thought again. Out of sight, out of mind. Utter complacency, and indeed very dangerous.

And then you couple that with young folks under 30 having no experience living through the Cold War and being brainwashed by Leftist teachers, the scene was set for the election of Obama. 

And what was fashionable before 1991 to bash the Soviet Union and Communism is no longer fashionable as least in the minds of the intellectual elites. Even Mitt Romney was criticized the other day for being critical of the current leader of Russia. The Left and the media is dedicated in the 21st century to making Americans forget about the history of Russia and the tens of millions that were purged in the name of the revolution.

The major problem of the Right: They allow the Left to rewrite history and to transform the Zeitgeist without opposition. And part of that is being indifferent to the economic accomplishments of the Coolidge administration and the part Ronald Reagan played in ending the Cold War.

Personal humility is considered an admirable quality; political humility eventually becomes self-destructive.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ziajs</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7e99</id></website><link>http://conservatives4palin.com/2012/03/open-thread-260.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T04:20:32+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T12:07:37+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwezy8</id><link>http://conservatives4palin.com/2012/03/open-thread-260.html#comment-480668582</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5i3we</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>