<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kbxd/post/2012-03-29T22:39:51</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>February 8th, 
2002 

The following is 
a transcript of Samuel Untermyer's speech made on WABC, declaring a 'holy war' 
by the Jews against Germany, and appealing to the masses of non-Jewish humanity 
to boycott German-made imports and all merchants who have German-made items in 
their establishments. The entire speech was published in the New York times on 
the morning following the broadcast (August 7th, 1933) which was mentioned by Benjamin Freedman in his talk before a group of 
patriots. 

A short excerpt 
from The World's 
Trouble Makers gives further insight to this speech: 

When 
Hitler had been soundly established, Samuel Untermeyer, a New York Jewish 
Lawyer, called for war on Germany. The call was made through radio station WABC 
on 8-7-33. He had just returned from a world conference of Jews at The Hague. In 
the broadcast, he said he was calling for a "holy war", and described the Jews 
as "the aristocrats of the world". 

This same gentleman was connected with the Foreign 
Policy Association of New York and the worldwide organisation to move Jews out 
of Germany, not only into the United States, but to Palestine and other 
countries.  These activities were tied in with the organisation known as the 
"International Boycott on German Goods", of which Untermeyer was the head! 
  
From that time the "Hate Germany" campaign was 
intensified and made worldwide, with a special Jewish-organised "National 
Conference of Jews and Christians" assisting!  These are the hate-spreaders, but 
they never grow tired of praising themselves.  That marked the beginning of the 
Jewish exodus from Germany.  

We have all, on a world-wide scale, been sold the myth 
(lie) of the so-called Holocaust... "Six million Jews killed..."  Note 
Untermyer's mention of the "600,000 souls we must save".  That is from 
the horse's mouth, in 1933, during the time the Jews were leaving Germany by the 
thousands.    

The "holocaust" lie 
has created a great guilt complex in people all over the world who had nothing 
to do with the murder of even one Jew, never mind the fallacious figure of six 
million allegedly killed in foreign countries. 

The fact that more 
than 20 million people were killed by Joseph Stalin in the Bolshevist-controlled 
USSR -- mostly Christians -- is never mentioned; nor are the tens of millions 
slaughtered by Mao-Tse-Tung in Communist China.  I was told several years ago by 
an educated and intelligent person that, "That was different.  It was their own 
people that they killed."     

It's called 
brain-washing, folks.  Thought control and mind control to the max.  It's okay 
if a despot puppet-ruler kills "his own people".  But... the holocaust myth of 6 
million Jews is a crime/sin with which we must all live forever more. And pay, 
and pay and pay. It is time for the lying to stop. 

Why was Adolf 
Hitler so vilified?  Because he had created a state money system, 
non-gold-backed, and had negotiated trade with other nations that didn't use the 
International Banker's monetary system.  They were bartering!  By-passing the 
usurers. 

Hitler continued, 
despite the boycott, to further his barter-trading and if enough nations had had 
the opportunity to participate, it would have been the end of the strangle-hold, 
the unbridled power in the hands of a few creatures lusting after World 
Dominion. Money is the name of their deceitful and dangerous game.  Hitler 
called it "bogus money". 

There is much about 
Hitler we don't know, so this is not intended to be a Hitler- apologist 
commentary. I am sharing information gleaned from many and varied sources which 
I believe to be credible, including historian Nesta Webster. 


Mrs. Webster, along 
with other writers, had also written that Hitler had kicked the International 
Bankers out of Germany. In his speech, Untermyer claims that 'wealthy Jews are 
financing Hitler'.  Untermyer was intimately connected with the wealthy Jews. 
 Since they are the masters of lies, perhaps the statement was made to confuse 
the issue. It remains for the time being an unanswered question for 
me.  

A thought which has 
been recurring for weeks now as a result of a recent reading frenzy... a thought 
and a question: 

Given the Political 
Zionists have controlled the media for a couple of hundred years, why would we 
believe that everything we've heard/read about Adolf Hitler in the 
Zionist-controlled media was true?  - Jackie  -- 

More on Samuel 
Untermyer in Who 
Was Cyrus Scofield? 

=================================   

The New York 
Times, Monday, August 7, 1933 

Text of Untermyer's Address 

   Following 
is the text of Samuel Untermyer's address last night over Station WABC after his 
return from Europe: 

My Friends: 


    What a  and 
relief and sense of security to be once more on American soil!  The nightmares 
of horrors through which I have passed in those two weeks in Europe, listening 
to the heartbreaking tales of refugee victims, beggar description. 


     I deeply 
appreciate your enthusiastic greeting on my arrival today, which I quite 
understand is addressed not to me personally but to the holy war in the cause of 
humanity in which we are embarked.  Jews and non-Jews alike, for we are equally 
concerned that the work of centuries shall not be undone, and that 
civilization shall not be allowed to die. 

     It is a war 
that must be waged unremittingly until the black clouds of bigotry, race hatred 
and fanaticism that have descended upon what was once Germany, but is now 
medieval Hitlerland, have been dispersed.   If we will but enlist to a man and 
persist in our purpose, the bright sun of civilization will again shine upon 
Germany, and the world will be a safer place in which to dwell. 


     As our ship 
sailed up the bay today past our proud Statue of Liberty, [a gift to the U.S. from the Grand Orient - Illuminati - Lodge 
of France] I breathed a prayer of 
gratitude and thanksgiving that this fair land of freedom has escaped the curse 
that has descended upon benighted Germany, which has thereby been converted from 
a nation of culture into a veritable hell of cruel and savage 
beasts. 

The 
World's Concern 

     We owe it not 
only to our persecuted brethren but to the entire world to now strike in 
self-defense a blow that will free humanity from a repetition of this incredible 
outrage.  This time the Jews are the victims, next time it may be the Catholics 
or the Protestants.  If we once admit, as is brazenly insisted by the German 
Government, that such fiendish persecution of the people of one race or creed is 
an internal domestic affair and not a world concern, how are we to know whose 
turn will be next? 

     Now or never 
must all the nations of the earth make common cause against the monstrous 
claim that the slaughter, starvation and annihilation, by a country that has 
reverted to barbarism, of its own innocent and defenseless citizens without 
rhyme, reason or excuse is an internal affair against which the rest of the 
world must stand idly by and not lift a hand in defense. 

    I have seen and 
talked with many of these terror-stricken refugees who have had the good fortune 
to escape over the border, though forced to leave their property behind them, 
and I want to say to you that nothing that has seeped through to you over the 
rigid censorship and lying propaganda that are at work to conceal and 
misrepresent the situation of the Jews in Germany begins to tell a fraction of 
the frightful story of fiendish torture, cruelty and persecution that are being 
inflicted day by day upon these men, women and children, of the terrors of worse 
than death in which they are living. 

     When the tale 
is told, as it will be some day if the impotent League of Nations ever 
sufficiently awakens from its Rip Van Winkle slumbers to the realization of its 
power and duty to prosecute an investigation into the facts, the world will 
confront a picture so fearful in its barbarous cruelty that the hell of war and 
the alleged Belgian atrocities will pale into insignificance as compared to this 
devilishly, deliberately, Cold-bloodedly planned and already partially executed 
campaign for the extermination of a proud, gentle, loyal, law-abiding people -- 
a people who love and have shed their blood for their Fatherland, and to whom 
Germany owes in large part its prosperity and its great scientists, educators, 
lawyers, physicians, poets, musicians, diplomats and philosophers, who are the 
backbone of its past cultural life. 

Back to Dark Ages 

     But why dwell 
longer upon this revolting picture of the ravages wrought by these ingrates and 
beasts of prey, animated by the loathsome motives of race hatred, bigotry and 
envy.  For the Jews are the aristocrats of the world. From time 
immemorial they have been persecuted and have seen 
their persecutors come and go. They alone have survived. And so will history 
repeat itself, but that furnishes no reason why we should permit this 
reversion of a once great nation to the Dark Ages or fail to rescue these 
600,000 human souls from the tortures of hell as we can with the aid of 
our Christian friends, if we have the will to . 

    Protests and 
pleas from all corners of the earth, from the leaders of all creeds, having 
proven as vain and unavailing as was the idealistic dream of our martyred 
President of making the world safe for democracy and of protecting 
minorities, what then are to be the lines of our defensive campaign against 
these atrocities, on which we are already actively embarked?  Are we right in 
our plan?  If so, what steps shall now be prosecuted to attain success? 


    Our campaign is 
twofold -- defensive and constructive.  On the defensive side will be the 
economic boycott against all German goods, shipping and services.  On the 
constructive side will be an appeal to the League of Nations to construe and 
enforce the labor union provisions of the Versailles Treaty and the written 
promises made by Germany, while the treaty was under negotiation, to protect its 
minorities, which have been flagrantly violated by its disfranchisement and 
persecution of the German Jews. 

What Boycott Means 

   As in the boycott, strange to say a mere handful in number, 
but powerful in influence, of our thoughtless but doubtless well-intentioned 
Jews seem obsessed and frightened at the bare mention of the word "boycott".  It 
signifies and conjures up to them images of force and illegality, such as have 
on occasions in the past characterized struggles between labor unions and their 
employers.  As these timid souls are capitalists and employers, the word and all 
that it implies are hateful to their ears. 

     In point of 
fact, it signifies nothing of the kind. These gentlemen do not know what they 
are talking or thinking about.  Instead of surrendering to their vague fears and 
half-baked ideas, our first duty is to educate them as to what is meant by a 
purely defensive economic boycott, and what we are doing and proposing. 
  

    Admittedly, the 
boycott is our only really effective weapon. These gentlemen who are taking 
counsel of their groundless fears to the exclusion of their reason have done 
nothing and have no program except to attempt to arouse world opinion, which is 
and has been from the outset on our side, as it was bound to be because of this 
brutal, senseless, unprovoked assault upon civilization. 

     It is not 
necessary to belittle or underrate that accomplishment, if their aimless, 
fruitless endeavors in that direction may be so dignified in recognition of 
their good intentions, barren of results as they have been. 
  

    It is 
sufficient that their efforts have proven unavailing and that the campaign of 
Schreckligheit not only goes on unabated in the face of unanimous world opinion; 
but that it is increasing in intensity and that the masses of the German people, 
misled by government propaganda and suppression of free speech and of the press, 
are either voluntarily, or through fear of punishment at the hands of their 
despotic rulers, supporting their government in this hellish campaign. 


     What then have 
these amiable gentlemen accomplished and what do they hope or expect to 
accomplish in the way of stemming this conflagration of civilization by their 
"feather-duster" methods? You cannot put out a fire, and especially that kind of 
a fire, by just looking on until the mad flames, fanned by the wind of hate, 
have destroyed everything. 

    What we are 
proposing and have already gone far toward doing, is to prosecute a purely 
defensive economic boycott that will undermine the Hitler regime and bring the 
German people to their senses by destroying their export trade on which 
their very existence . 

"Force Them to Learn" 

    They have 
flaunted and persisted in flaunting and defying world opinion. 
  

   We propose to 
and are organizing world opinion to express itself in the only way Germany 
can be made to understand.  Hitler and his mob will not permit their people to 
know how they are regarded by the outside world.  We shall force them to learn 
in the only way open to us. 

     Revolting as 
it is, it would be an interesting study in psychology to analyze the motives, 
other than fear and cowardice, that have prompted Jewish bankers to lend money 
to Germany as they are now doing.  It is in part their money that is being used 
by the Hitler regime in its reckless, wicked campaign of propaganda to make the 
world anti-Semitic; with that money they have invaded Great Britain, the United 
States and other countries where they have established newspapers, subsidized 
agents and otherwise are spending untold millions in spreading their infamous 
creed. 

    The suggestion 
that they use that money toward paying the honest debts they have repudiated is 
answered only by contemptuous sneers and silence.   Meantime the infamous 
campaign goes on unabated with ever increasing intensity to the everlasting 
disgrace of the Jewish bankers who are helping to finance it and of the 
weaklings who are doing nothing effective to check it. 

     The Hitler 
regime originated are fiendishly prosecuting their boycott to exterminate the 
Jews by placarding Jewish shops, warning Germans against dealing with them, by 
imprisoning Jewish shopkeepers and parading them through the streets by the 
hundreds under guard of Nazi troops for the sole crime of being Jews, by 
ejecting them from the learned professions in which many of them had attained 
eminence, by excluding their children from the schools, their men from the labor 
unions, closing against them every avenue of livelihood, locking them in vile 
concentration camps, starving and torturing them, murdering and beating them 
without cause and resorting to every other conceivable form of torture, inhuman 
beyond conception, until suicide has become their only means of escape, and all 
solely because they are or their remote ancestors were Jews, and all with the 
avowed object of exterminating them. 

Appeal to Mankind 

     As against 
this, the foulest boycott in the annals of time, we are appealing to all mankind 
to enforce a counter-boycott.  That appeal is meeting with the conviction that 
idealism and justice are still alive. 

     There is 
nothing new in the use of the economic boycott as an instrument of justice.  The 
covenant of the League of Nations expressly provides in these identical words 
for its use to bring recalcitrant nations to terms.  President Roosevelt, 
whose wise statesmanship and vision are the wonder of the civilized world, is 
invoking it in furtherance of his noble conception for the readjustment of the 
relations  between capital and labor under the terms of the sweeping Industrial 
Recovery , to the end that labor shall receive a more just share of the 
wealth it creates.  He is about to enlist the consumers of the country in a 
national campaign in which they  themselves to boycott all manufacturers, 
jobbers and retailers who fail to subscribe to the codes and to buy only from 
those who have assented and who are thereby privileged to fly the blue eagle of 
NRA [National Recovery ].  What more exalted precedent do our timid friends 
want? 

     With this 
explanation of our aims, I appeal to the American Jewish Committee, whose public 
spirit and good intentions I do not for a moment question, but the wisdom of 
whose judgment I challenge, no longer to hold aloof but to rid themselves of 
their timid and ill-considered prejudices and join in actively pressing this 
boycott as our only weapon except the appeal to the League, which I shall 
discuss at a later time. 

     I purposely 
refrain from including the American Jewish Congress in this appeal because I am 
satisfied that 95 per cent of their members are already with us and that they 
are being misrepresented by two or three men now abroad.  Of them I ask that, 
prior to the meeting to be held this month in Prague by their executive 
committee, they instruct these false leaders in no uncertain terms as to the 
stand they must take on this all-important subject and demand that they shall 
either openly represent their views or resign their offices.  One of them, 
generally recognized as the kingpin of mischief makers, is junketing around the 
Continent engaged in his favorite pastime of spreading discord, asserting at one 
time and place that he favors and supports the boycott and at another that he is 
opposed or indifferent to it, all dependent on the audience he is addressing; 
but Always directly or indirectly delivering a stab in the dark. 


Progress So Far Made 

      There is not 
time now, but I hope and expect in the near future to be able to report to you 
the steps that have been taken and that are already under way, and the 
surprising and gratifying progress already made in many countries toward the 
success of the economic boycott in which we are engaged.  Although considerable 
progress in that direction has already been made in Great Britain and in the 
United States, you will be surprised to learn that they are the least advanced 
and as yet the most inadequately organized of all the countries that were 
represented at the Amsterdam World Economic Conference, where the boycott 
was unanimously and enthusiastically approved by formal resolution by a rising 
vote. 

     With us in 
America the delay has been due in part to lack of funds and the vast territory 
to be covered, but it is hoped, and expected, that this condition will soon be 
corrected.  The object-lesson we are determined to teach is so priceless to all 
humanity that we dare not fall. 

    Each of you, 
Jew and Gentile alike, who has not already enlisted in this sacred 
war should do so now and here.  It is not sufficient that you buy no goods 
made in Germany.  You must refuse to deal with any merchant or shopkeeper who 
sells any German-made goods or who patronizes German ships or shipping. 
  

    To our shame be 
it said that there are a few Jews among us, but fortunately only a few, so 
wanting in dignity and self-respect that they are willing to travel on German 
ships where they are despised and meet with the just contempt of the servants 
who wait upon them and of their fellow passengers.  Their names should be 
heralded far and wide. They are traitors to their race. 

     In conclusion, 
permit me again to thank you for this heartening reception and to assure you 
that, with your support and that of our millions of non-Jewish friends, we 
will drive the last nail in the coffin of bigotry and fanaticism that has dared 
raise its ugly head to slander, belie and disgrace twentieth century 
civilization. 

[end of New York 
Times article] </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l52ms</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry2d</id></website><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50458</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T19:24:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:39:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kbxd</id><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50458#comment-480166172</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zd1dw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>