<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/g3agof/update/2011-11-07T15:44:11/2cc6bda420946fbf9e7d9c11b32aca0bafe674147404f1239fbafb347aa305b3</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>What amazes me is how full of anger and hatred so many people are on both sides of the camp. Instead of understanding that everybody isn't a 17 year old with a pee brain or a business manager with specific needs and each person has their own reasons to own whatever they own, we have a bunch of little bitches that would never say the things they say on forums to someone in public. I enjoy reading articles because they enlighten me on specs and issues but it Burns my ass to have to read the little comments from the little pee brains that  ensue. On the iPhone bit, I'd own one if it had a bigger screen and offered a few key apps that the android camp has for free. However, if the phones that use the android OS don't man up and start building better quality, there'll be an iPhone in my stable sitting next to my IPad, iMac and Macbook pros. Why? Because in 1 year of owning Apple computers and a tablet, I've had to restart due to a problem exactly 0 times. As a 20 plus year user of Windows and a full on Android fan, I've had both mechanical and software issues with those two systems and hardware so many times that I can't even register a solid guess. In the end though, it's personal preference and why is one person stupid or another person a sheep because they choose what they choose. I admit, the "why" makes me cringe sometimes, but still, my money, my choice.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/5qnm82</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/vaoe</id></website><link>http://www.geek.com/articles/mobile/5-reasons-why-im-ditching-android-for-an-iphone-2011034/</link><postedTime>2011-04-08T17:12:30+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-11-07T20:44:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/g3agof</id><link>http://www.geek.com/articles/mobile/5-reasons-why-im-ditching-android-for-an-iphone-2011034/#comment-357812377</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rqtei</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-04-08</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>