<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwg6qy/post/2012-03-30T06:58:04</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Whoever is behind this doc seems oblivious to the fact that at the time Bush announced mission accomplished, the left at home and abroad was calling for a complete pullout of Iraq to give them back their sovereignty, with Saddam still on the loose and Al Qaeda having fled from Afghanistan and scattered about the region. 
At the same time one Joe Wilson was allowed to go public with a complete lie that he personally debunked the Niger Yellowcake story and knew Cheney had been told, which not only was complete bull but the White House barely tried to deny it at all. 
So it's clear to me we weren't about to leave Iraq with Saddam on the loose and have France, Russia and China just walk in and consummate their oil deals with the remnants of the Ba'athist gov't. 
We let the insurgency happen, it must have been that way, I remember this line: 
"We're only here for the good of the Iraqi people, and only as long as they want us here". It was an open invitation for Al Qaeda to come and defeat America and have their own homeland, pure genius on that front because a terrorist is just an angry muslim until he makes a bomb and sets it Off. You can't stop that, why not lead him to a blast chamber and control the damage? 
Anyway further evidence can be found in the fact that the Baghdad highway, merely 5 miles long, could not be kept free of IED's and was the most dangerous stretch of highway in the world, right where the press could see it and report it to the world. Yet we have drones with FLIR that could have the whole 5 miles covered and could Spot a squirrel with a firecracker from a mile up? Gimme a break. We wanted to project an image of chaos, so Al Qaeda would believe they had a chance of winning, and those who demanded our early exit would not bristle at our "occupation". 
So in the end we walk into a country, remove its dictator, deny two rivals and a fair weather friend (France, Russia, China) their nearly complete drilling deals to the largest high pressure light sweet crude fields in the world, derail the near loss of US Dollar hegemony over world petroleum sales, kill between 5-10,000 foreign fighters many of whom were Al Qaeda.....  and America gets to tell the rest of the world don't blame us we were all duped by George W. Bush, a man with 2 years tenure in federal government and a double digit IQ. 
We're victims too. (just like Bin Laden at Tora Bora, if you think it was an accident he got away, think again)
LOL. Any of you think you were lied to, well you needed to be lied to. 
This whole thing ultimately demands that you accept that behind figureheads like Bush and Obama, those running the gov't may actually not be so stupid at all and may know what they are doing. Sorry if self loathing has become so fashionable that is difficult, but hey- me=realpolitik. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zytth</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/znv4</id></website><link>http://topdocumentaryfilms.com/mission-accomplished/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T11:01:27+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T10:58:04+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwg6qy</id><link>http://topdocumentaryfilms.com/mission-accomplished/#comment-480617109</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/euuh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>