<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpmpbq/update/2012-03-21T09:40:11/b250d14800dccfddc43e3bff51ce98cdbf7d1ad0331965e3cfe49e2e8b2ed7d6</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpm5am</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6775y</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I know exactly what I mean, fanboi, as evidenced by the fact I've worn out and disposed of more Mac and Apple toys over the years than you can ever dream of even playing with at the Apple store in your lifetime. And guess what? Not a damned one came out of my personal pocket. 

The Apple OS, yes APPLE OS, it's made by Apple so it is the APPLE OS, sucks for real work. Guess what? Occupests on Wall Street are not movers and shakers. The finance guys looking down on them from above, while expanding retirement portfolios via Microsoft Windows powered machines, creating business content in Office, are actually producing something, as opposed to hipster Appletards creating intestinal flow while performing as pepper spray sponges and "youtube producers".

One of my Apple geek co-workers got all flustered up a while back when she was finally able to successfully install the Apple OS on a Acer netbook and it sort of worked. I really had to snicker.... Not where she could see me, mind you. I do have some tact...

If you want to pretend to be a movie producer or listen to Lady Gaga, or play Angry Birds on the subway in route to your night shift, 's your answer. If you aren't smart enough to install a driver or add a printer, then Mac's your your answer. If you want access to hundreds of thousands of free or inexpensive and useful applications, instead of a few underwhelming and overpriced Headache inducing compromises, then Windows is for you.

Windows on a Mac. Perfect.

You lost your credibility when you used the term, "wage slaves". Get those pork chop sideburns trimmed, pop out those ugly titanium nails in your face, take a shower, scrub Off those clove stains on your buckteeth, dress up in something without manufactured wrinkles, and go look for a real job.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6m0535</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/71fv</id></website><link>http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2012-03-20/apple-ipad-being-tested-by-consumer-reports-amid-heating-reports.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-20T16:00:16+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-21T13:40:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpmpbq</id><link>http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2012-03-20/apple-ipad-being-tested-by-consumer-reports-amid-heating-reports.html#comment-472337083</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zc4y3</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>