<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gbg2sk/update/2011-10-19T19:32:00/417f381f5c958e3eb7dcd79bc00851b6a60cf07e7cb2bd10cd694f0930227aa4</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>No, people won't admit that it's a racial thing and I think on the surface they may not even realize it (it may very well be subconscious), but to me it's beyond obvious.  

Just take a look at the top black female celebrities.  Do you think it's a coincidence that the likes of Rihanna, Beyonce, Halle Berry (half-black) and Zoe Saldana (also multi-racial) have become huge mainstream successes? This is just a case of "if you're light, you're alright!" About the only darker-skinned celebrity I have seen that seems to be accepted is Gabrielle Union, and MAYBE Taraji P. Henson.  But most black women will only find steady work in contrived Tyler Perry movies, which are all pretty much the same thing. 

I have been saying this for a while now, especially when it comes to True Blood and The Vampire Diaries.  I decided to drop the latter, but the fandom hate for Bonnie made absolutely no sense at all.  Characters like Bonnie and Tara have been through a lot of stuff, so to me their animosity is understandable.  Bonnie hates a vampire that has killed innocent people and yet SHE is the bad guy?!  Same for Tara and she was even worse Off since one even went as far as raping her.  

Bonnie was really the only reason I would watch TVD because she was the only interesting character.  Now that she's been thrown together with Elena's brother to get her out of the way, I just found it Nausea-inducing.   In the books she and Damon actually have a lot going on and I was wondering if the writers would go there, but I don't think they will because of the fandom outrage.  No way could a guy as sexy as Damon be with that one, right?!  Elena's boring and I don't even understand the vampire brothers fawning over her like they do.  Caroline's stupid and shallow.  So with all of the characters having flaws, I myself can only think it goes back to race.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/mh0ly3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/hp7z</id></website><link>http://www.racialicious.com/2011/10/18/fandom-and-its-hatred-of-black-women-characters/</link><postedTime>2011-10-18T12:05:09+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-10-19T23:32:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gbg2sk</id><link>http://www.racialicious.com/2011/10/18/fandom-and-its-hatred-of-black-women-characters/#comment-339516895</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dfasw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-10-18</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>