<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gq9gq9/update/2011-10-15T13:03:09/4f2ee80dd950c05c21257d43d3718d5f89161c7ee888561f5753cc30919c1c18</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gq987h</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/d406g</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Excellent point! I didn't catch that at all. 

That lends additional strength to one of the messages of this episode; when they're happy, functioning members of the entire group, their individual quirks are largely overtaken or forgotten. 

Abed actually enjoys himself while surrounded by the emotions of others, Troy sets aside his worry over his maturity, Shirley lets her pies Burn, and Annie joins in instead of rolling her eyes at Britta and being "mature" like in the other timelines (where she no doubt wanted to impress upon Jeff the fact that she's a mature adult). 

Meanwhile, the two group members with the greatest flaws and problems, Pierce and Jeff, are relegated to the outside and left still struggling with them. 

However, Pierce largely confronted his demons at the end of last season, while Jeff has yet to. 

I'm more and more convinced that we'll see Pierce helping Jeff this season; even in just the course of this episode he comes to the aid of someone else cut Off from the group several times. 

In fact, there's been a whole bunch of subtle hints that Pierce is much more of a concerned individual this season, which I really love. 

Also, something else that just came to my attention; this is a bottle episode, yet Abed seems entirely fine with it. More character development! I love this episode, I really, really do.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/mrq6r4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/remedial-chaos-theory,63144/</link><postedTime>2011-10-14T00:30:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-10-15T17:03:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gq9gq9</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/remedial-chaos-theory,63144/#comment-335463830</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zrhe7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-10-14</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>