<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mku3wr/post/2012-03-26T10:56:26</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>ย 
      ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย ย                              MUTINOUS -- BARKING AT THE MOON
Thank goodness for the poster called Edward. This person 
recognized the twin sides of hundreds of canine owners, in trying to 
conceal individualย  Anxiety,ย  while suffering from paranoid 
inclinations, that harbor split personalities, bordering upon 
self-induced
 masochism of repressive Oedipus encircling infantile thought.Dr. 
Sigmund Freud surmised these types of personalities as 
suffering with theย  ( Personality Suppressionย ย  Complex Syndrome ). This 
clever master of unraveling disassociated minds, and their subconscious 
willingness to conceal pent up erotic inhibitions, that exceptional racket was the driving force
 behind a more arising psychiatric classification, as the ( Personality 
Suppression Gravitational Complex Syndrome).
Mr.Edwards was on to something in discerning that possibly a 
variation of specific personality traits. Masochism has become a religion
 with hundreds of canine loversย  across America. The late Emily 
Zola, one of France's eighteen hundreds authoritative writers on canines, used 
Freudian concepts in declaring that too much mutt consoling would 
possibility lead into a mental disorder termed ( Ineluctable Determinism
 ). This is an individual pre-neurological mental disorder, that requires
 self-torture through elevated masochism, or a perpetual monologueย  [ย  deified ego ], in 
enjoying
 the Comfort of barking dogs. Here we have psychotic manifestationsof an
 inhibited class, in attempting to impose, transpose , disturbed 
personality traits into mutts. that cannotcomprehend that their 
so-called [ master [ might be a raving lunatic in need of mental hygiene</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/c68sv2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gblz</id></website><link>http://www.newser.com/story/comments/108333/pal-kinky-spy-was-taking-on-new-persona.html</link><postedTime>2010-12-27T08:22:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T14:56:26+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mku3wr</id><link>http://www.newser.com/story/comments/108333/pal-kinky-spy-was-taking-on-new-persona.html#comment-476448419</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gk4nw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2010-12-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>