<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzeza/update/2012-03-30T14:16:42/c46616baf239151c99296a41a356edfb98d00325a7b85b84fad1a08483327822</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Hi Nathan,

I voted for 'Soundtrack' in the logline contest, and stuck with it throughout Carson's various zany experiments in democracy. Those first ten pages had effortlessly managed something other Amateur Friday comedies had really struggled with historically: they made me laugh.

I was a little worried for you when Carson reviewed 'Norm, the Movie', giving it that rare impressive, but based on the pages I had read of both by that point, 'Soundtrack' still had a higher LPP average (Laughs Per Page), so the omens were good.

If Norm was Louis CK - edgy, experimental with a dark edge - then Soundtrack is Bill Cosby: warm hearted, goofy and fun, and there's nothing wrong with that. There's room for both in this world, but in your defense, I suspect Cosby can afford to pay way, way less tax than CK.

With that said, man can't live on jokes alone, and this script still needs a fair amount of work, but you're on the right track.

So what needs fixing? The characters mostly. And the story :-)

Let me start at the beginning. You open with Kaitlyn delivery a box of water to Ian. It's a funny gag, but it suggests that their failed attempt at a wedding was very recent… ice sculpture recent. You reference other wedding items, such as the flowers, throughout the script.

But, Ian and Kaitlyn also both have new partners, which then suggests the wedding was a while ago. You can't have it both ways. Both work: a short time frame straight after the wedding, when the emotional wounds are still fresh - no new boyfriend for Kaitlyn - or a longer time frame, where Ian and Kaitlyn have both tried to move on, which makes Ian's pursuit of Kaitlyn tricky. You just can't combine the two though.

The other problem with the beginning is that we don't get to know Kaitlyn, so don't really care about them splitting up. I think we need some backstory here, perhaps revealing that 'fatal flaw' they will need to conquer in order to be happy again. Up! is justifiably lauded for its opening montage - I'm wondering if you could maybe do a comedy take on that, relying on music to help tell their story up until the collapse of the wedding? Maybe that music is a magnificent concerto Ian's written, but he can't finish the last movement, which is when, visually, we see the wedding collapse?

You then introduce Tracy, who we immediately figure for an evil, money grabbing bitch that needs to be dumped pronto. My problem with that is that's it's so obvious. There's no question about it - she needs to go. I think you would have more drama to mine if she was at heart, a decent person, but the music in his head is pushing him back to his ex. That's conflict, drama, tension, whereas now, we're just waiting for Ian to hurry up and dump Tracy. On the other hand, Sean seems like a nice guy, but he conveniently disappears when Kaitlyn started falling for Ian again, so I guess we don't need to worry about how he feels.

After meeting Tracy, we then get to our ticking timebomb - the pitch with Gordon Chambers. I can see that device working, but the problem here is that you bait and switch us at the climax. It suddenly turns into a defense of sappy, romantic music - cheesy music - with Ian launching into a verbal attack on poor Gordon, who frankly hadn't done anything to deserve it. That's not what this story was about. Gordon isn't the villain here. No one's been complaining about romantic music up until this point.

I actually think Ian playing Kaitlyn the song he wrote for her is quite touching, and a beautiful moment, but your 'thesis' so far has been that music is a powerful, moving force in our life. The scene with Gordon degrades that. It would be far better for Kaitlyn, at her lowest moment, to hear Ian's composition and realize he's the one for her (or that he isn't, but they're going to be okay).

Incidentally, if you're looking for some other ways to fill your second , I was wondering if he could somehow use these magical musical cues to pick a winning horse, or play a trick on Mrs. Pokorny, or beat people at chess. There seems to be a lot of potential for having fun with musical cues in your head.

As I mentioned already, there were plenty of laughs - the wrong demo tape, the porn music in the library, the racist jingle in his head, some great one liners ("you're &lt;i&gt;touching&lt;/i&gt; someone?") - all good trailer moments, but I did notice you sometimes hung around too long after delivering your best punchline:

&lt;blockquote&gt;
IAN
Weird? That’s your medical diagnosis, weird?

ASIAN DOCTOR
No. In medical terms, I would say, extremely weird.
(beat)
Are you hearing it now?

IAN
Yes.

ASIAN DOCTOR
What are you hearing?

Beat.

We hear the MUSIC he hears. It’s a stereotypical, in fact, offensively stereotypical CHINESE sounding tune.
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

That's a really funny scene, but you then carry on for another page and half, kind of explaining the joke:

&lt;blockquote&gt;
IAN
I’d rather not say.

Asian Doctor crinkles his nose.

ASIAN DOCTOR
Why not?

Beat.

IAN
Because...

ASIAN DOCTOR
Hmmm?

IAN
(whispering)
It’s racist.

ASIAN DOCTOR
Excuse me?

&lt;/blockquote&gt;

Etc… Etc...

I'd say the music is the comedic high point, so cut your scene there - we know it's racist, and a good comedy actor will give you a great reaction shot. Another example is Ian dumping Tracy:

&lt;blockquote&gt;
IAN
I don’t want you in my car, I don’t want you in my life.

TRACY
SCREW YOU, YOU LOSER!

Ian jumps back inside his car. The MUSIC in his head blares and TRIUMPHAL TUNE. He soaks it up as he speeds . Ian smiles broadly as he drives triumphantly away from Tracy. Then suddenly, DANGER MUSIC plays, and the car suddenly loses its forward momentum.

Ian stares, horrified, down at the gas gauge.

IAN
(sotto)
Oh crap.

HONK! HONK!

IAN
Oh crap!

FRANTIC MUSIC plays as Ian puts the car in neutral and jumps out, pushing with all of his might to get the car Off to the side of the road. MOTORISTS ZOOM past him, the FRANTIC MUSIC intensifies. More HONKS!

MOTORIST
MOVE IT ASSHOLE!

An angered LA driver swerves past him and chucks a fast food drink at him.

IAN
How does that help the situation!?

Eventually, Ian is able to pull the car over. He gives a sigh of relief. A taxi cab zooms by with Tracy hanging out of the backseat window.

TRACY
LOSER!
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

So the high point here is the car not starting, so again, don't hang around. Something like this:

&lt;blockquote&gt;
Ian jumps back inside his car. Winds the window down.

IAN
I don’t want you in my car, I don’t want you in my life.

TRACY
SCREW YOU, YOU LOSER!

The MUSIC in his head blares a TRIUMPHAL TUNE. He grins, proud and free at last. Turns the ignition. The car chokes. Dies.

IAN
Crap.

INT. AAA TRUCK - LATER

Ian and Tracy squeezed onto the bench seat, trying to avoid each other.
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

On the other hand, on page 6, I thought you started the scene too late. We join the scene with Stuart listening to Ian's new melody, the gag being that it's very short. I think it would be funnier if we saw the whole thing, right from Stuart pressing play.

Finally, I'm wondering if you could maybe steal a trick from Pi, and try to visualize the musical cues? Ian sees ducks on a pond say, and Spots a pattern that he then translates into a music. My fear is that the musical cues might get a little, excuse the pun, one note, so adding some sort of mystery and/or visual element might give you some other angles to to exploit.

Having finished it, I will now make the bold claim that 'Soundtrack' is the funniest comedy I've read on Amateur Friday. Some might argue that's like claiming that last burrito was the tastiest you'd ever had from a 7-11, but I think you show some definite comedy chops. If you bring the characterizations and story up to the level of the jokes, then I think you could really be on to something.

A good start though.

Karl</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/676vh6</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cj6q</id></website><link>http://scriptshadow.blogspot.com/2012/03/screenplay-review-soundtrack-amateur.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:12:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:16:42+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzeza</id><link>http://scriptshadow.blogspot.com/2012/03/screenplay-review-soundtrack-amateur.html#comment-481031641</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5f16h</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>