<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwp3ha/update/2012-03-31T07:50:49/1bfc76090c70d4a33c51509760275db648b6da8abef57e737e86baf1a4251040</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>"Fairer"? That makes me furious! Today, In Florida, We are bracing for another onslaught of Al Shaprton and Jesse Jackson, Rabble rousing and destroying entire business districts. What is fair about his two avid supporters doing that? Sanford is under a sort of boycott from the Race Baiters. People are also afraid to go there after the WalGreens in Miami was looted by "Protesters" WOULD you want to go shopping, knowing the New Black Party Panthers were in  town, and apparently free to do anything they like..because the DOJ...sure is letting them put out ...manhunts..threats.
INFURIATING. THE MEDIA..has never produced ONE SHRED of evidence that Zimmerman pursued Martin after the Police told him to stand down. Zimmerman says he headed back to his car...eye witnesses say he did that..ONE 16 year old "witness" un named...un seen...says she was on the phone with him..And Ed Schultz..that man of total integrity..says it is true.  WHO knows what was said if she is telling the truth? Nothing is on tape. It would out there if it was true.
TREYVON MARTIN WAS SIX FEET TWO. HE WEIGHED 160 POUNDS..NOT 140 POUNDS. THAT IS BIG KID. BUT THE MEDIA AND HIS PARENTS INSIST ON PRESENTED HIM AS A 12 YEAR OLD CHILD.
AS ANN COULTER..who was also the head of her Law School Review..who does not carry the stigma of being an Affirmative Action Baby.....points out today..Zimmerman says he was treated for a broken nose the next day. AS ANN SAYS..EITHER THE MEDICAL RECORDS ARE THERE..OR THEY AREN'T. BUT IT WILL BE PROOF..ONE WAY OR ANOTHER.  And if they are..The Media..against as Ann says..desperately seeking a "Mississippi Burning scenario" ( that was fiction you know. Never happened except in some Hollywood mind)  will stll  find UNFAIRNESS.

OTHER THAN AL SHARPTON'S VICIOUS WHITE HATING MOUTH ( though he lays his head down in a white community every night)....show us the evidence...and i mean evidence..not some un named teenagers and her "account".  that Zimmerman pursued Martin one step. That is the crucial part of the case as Ann points out.

AND DEAR BIASED MEDIA..AND I.Q. CHALLENGED MEMBERS OF THE CONGRESSIONAL CAUCUS....THE GATED COMMUNITY WHERE ZIMMERMAN LIVES..OR LIVED.........IS ONLY 47% WHITE. THE MAJORITY OF RESIDENTS ARE BLACK..HISPANIC..ASIAN.
ZIMMERMAN LIVED IN A MINORITY COMMUNITY. THE MEDIA..NOT REPORTING THAT....AND NEVER WILL.
ANN COULTER..IF MITT ROMNEY WINS..AND DOES NOT PUT YOU IN HIS ADMINISTRATION.........MORE FOOL HIM. YOU....HAVE ACTUALLY GIVEN US THE "OTHER SIDE OF THE CASE" AND NOT JUST HATE SPEECH.
AND OBAMA  SHOULD STAY AWAY FROM WORDS LIKE "FAIR" AND "JUSTICE" AND "RACISM"</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67jxcq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f047</id></website><link>http://thehill.com/video/administration/219335-obama-buffett-rule-will-make-this-country-a-little-fairer</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T11:03:37+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T11:50:49+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwp3ha</id><link>http://thehill.com/video/administration/219335-obama-buffett-rule-will-make-this-country-a-little-fairer#comment-481766437</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>