<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw02es/update/2012-03-31T13:06:31/e199057f54eac286265f060e31eb97ac201bb09f6bf99418aca841aaab47b0d0</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwjhog</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rq21m</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>@Sexy_Sabe:disqus First of all, don't ever question my hip hop pedigree when chances are I'm older than 
you, have been to mad more shows, b-boy summits all that, and was pause-mixing/rhyming out of the right side of the headphones
 before you were born! Just because someone in your dorm room let you 
listen to an old Redman tape, you think you know hip hop!

I've bought 
and lost more hip hop than you will EVER know! I used to b-boy to "Scorpio" back in the day. I had Cassingles, homies. That's how far back I go! I remember when LL Cool J was the newest and hottest rapper on the planet, so don't pop .

Yes, I did say that Superbass will be played ten years from now. I didn't say whether it was "hip-hop" enough or not. I just said it will be around.  

I know "Barbie" Nicki is a fake KIM!!! How disrespectful of her to go at
 KIM when she bite her whole style from her?! The pity is that Nicki M 
can actually rhyme! Have you heard her before YMCMB? She sounded 
completely different.  But, that doesn;t mean SuperBass is not winning 
just because you and I don't necessarily agree with its placement in the
 annals of hip-hop history.

Now, what I was trying to say is that timeless music doesn't  have
 to be poignant and thought-provoking. Sometimes shit just sticks! "How 
To Love" will be around for a long time! 

"Supersonic" by JJ Fad was wack as hell too when it came out, but they still play it on the radio occasionally, now don't they? 

This morning, I was just listening to Special Ed's "The Mission." 
YouTube it if you don't know it.. Classic shit. its still good! Then 
"Burn Hollywood Burn" came on; classic shit. Again, YT it if you don't 
know it. Classic PE stuff. 

Love it or hate it, Drake is mean in the rap game. Yes, I dig him. Have you heard "Fear?" You're going to sit there and tell me that "Over" is not the shit? "Forever?!?" That's new hip hop, kid...

Ross, like him or hate him, is getting monumentally better at rapping; just like Biggie did between REal Love Remix and Warning. Ross' verse on Wale's "Ambition" is fire, period.  

Wayne's No Ceilings was dope too. I agree that syrup-sippin Wayne doesn't compare to Squad Up Wayne, but like it or not, if you ask one of these kids which songs they know, it'll be "A-Milli."

Plus, if you don't think that Cash Money has not made classic shit, then you must live under a rock. Ask anybody from New Orleans 'bout "Drag Em In the River!" "Bling Bling!?!?" Are you stupid! That's classic shit! Just because you prefer boom-bap style hip hop doesn't mean it's not revelant.  I live in South Florida now from California and you throw that old Cash Money shit on and people lose their minds! 

I love the WU, but I also loved Big Mike's Havin Thangs or Sir Mix-A-Lot's Gortex. Xzibit's Paparazzi. 2Pac's 5 Deadly Venoms.

Cmon man, let these kids have their own thang. It's not really ours anymore. 

That Golden Age stuff is great: Das, Gangstarr, EPMD, LOTUG, but it's gone. It's timeless to us because of nostalgia, but irrelevant to these kids.

Peace.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67lfqq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/vqpd</id></website><link>http://allhiphop.com/2012/03/30/hip-hop-rumors-is-birdman-going-to-sign-rick-ross-and-game-not-impressed-with-g-o-o-d-music/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T20:02:02+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T17:06:31+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw02es</id><link>http://allhiphop.com/2012/03/30/hip-hop-rumors-is-birdman-going-to-sign-rick-ross-and-game-not-impressed-with-g-o-o-d-music/#comment-482003384</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rj7pt</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>