<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m1l4vb/update/2012-03-13T08:49:32/38546d44243452109b60c58f8dad786c5d2d9c4e9ec12d10074f47f8fff7f0e6</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m124h1</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l243k</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> 

Society does not control
crime, EVER, by forcing the law-abiding to accommodate themselves to the
expected behavior of criminals. Society controls crime by forcing the criminals
to accommodate themselves to the expected behavior of the law-abiding.  To  guns from citizens because criminals
use them is to tell the innocent and law-abiding citizens that their rights and
liberties  not on their OWN conduct, but on the conduct of the criminals
and the lawless, and that the ‘state’ will permit it's law-abiding citizens to
have only such rights and liberties as the lawless will allow...



The laws that forbid the
carrying of arms disarm only those who are neither inclined nor determined to
commit crimes.  Such laws make things worse for the assaulted and better for the
assailants.  People who will do you harm DO NOT CARE how
many laws they violate.  Laws only
restrain those who are willing to abide by them and give you a legal mechanism
to prosecute people who do a certain type of prohibited action. 
That puts the ‘Law-Abiding’ at the disadvantage.  Criminals, by definition, are
law-breakers. They have no regard for the law in the first place, so another
law would mean very little to them.  What
it would instead do, is turn law-abiding citizens into much easier targets for
criminals. 



The anti-liberty argument
boils down to the premise, that if peaceable armed citizens cross certain
property lines, their behavior drastically changes. They degenerate into
hot-tempered, remorseless, out-of-control, binge-drinking frat boys, drunken
cowboys, and avenging vigilantes ready to blast anything for any reason--or for
no reason at all.  



Anti-liberty
proponents believe that I, and gun owners like me, are sociopaths. They seems
to think that I am a seething cauldron of homicidal rage and hate, so morally
bankrupt that my Burning desire to ‘slap leather’ and gun someone down is only
held in check by possible legal consequences. That if I had my way I would
joyfully murder people left and right. Or bump into me at the mall? BLAM!
You’re toast. Or walk on my lawn and I’ll fertilize it with your blood. Or throw
a plate of spaghetti at me and I’ll blow you away.  That’s pathetic and maliciously dishonest.





The gun is the only
personal weapon that puts a 105-pound woman on equal footing with a 220-pound
mugger, a 75-year old grandmother on equal footing with a 19-year old gang
banger, and a single guy on equal footing with a carload of drunk guys with
baseball bats.  The gun removes the disparity in physical strength, size,
or numbers between a potential attacker and a defender.  A gun is about choices. If someone enters my
home to steal a television, I can choose to hold him for police. If he enters
to harm me, I can choose to defend myself. If I have no gun, the choice belongs
to the killer.



When
I carry a gun, I don’t do so because I am looking for a fight, but because I’m
looking to be left alone. I don’t carry it because I’m afraid, but because it
enables me to be unafraid.  My firearm doesn’t limit the actions of those
who would interact with me through reason, only the actions of those who would
do so by force. My firearm removes unequal force from the equation… and that’s
why carrying a gun is a civilized . I don’t carry a gun because I want to
shoot someone, I carry a gun because if I’m attacked, I don’t want to have to
beat them Off (to death) with just any ole rock that I found on the side of the
road.  I’m just a humanitarian that way…





Violence
does not erupt on schedule, and criminals do not make appointments in
advance.  Victim disarmament schemes give people only two choices if
the worst happens: to run like rabbits or die like sheep.  Or in some cases BOTH. And when seconds count, the police are only minutes away.  


 


</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/68ctwn</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6tdd</id></website><link>http://www.csmonitor.com/Commentary/editors-blog/2012/0312/Guns-and-freedom-the-American-paradox</link><postedTime>2012-03-12T13:50:03+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-13T12:49:32+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m1l4vb</id><link>http://www.csmonitor.com/Commentary/editors-blog/2012/0312/Guns-and-freedom-the-American-paradox#comment-464157814</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l12i8</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-12</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>