<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwkzo7/post/2012-03-31T09:38:13</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>More Malthusian scaremongering by the eco-Fascists who delight in using the climate-con to promote their left-wing misanthropic agenda. Climate changes, it  has and it  will. During the Medieval Warming Period (1000-1400 AD) it was 2 to 3 degrees warmer than at present. The polar bears didn't die , oats and barely were grown in places in Greenland that are currently under a wall of ice. Life expectancy increased, and general health and well being was improved as the world enjoyed longer growing seasons. What caused such warmth? Certainly not man, but nature itself. The wheels didn't come Off the bus. Let me ask you, when is the last time you heard anything positive about CO2 from the left-wing doom-and-gloomers? To hear them talk you would think CO2 is like anthrax. But without it plant life would soon die out and so would we--think greenhouses!!!! All indications from climate history (something scaremongers avoid like the plague), to include the Medieval Warming Period and the Little Ice Age which followed it, are that a warmer climate has more benefits than a Colder climate. Atmospheric temps have cooled .25C in the last 2 years, Arctic ice extent and volume has been recovering over the last 6 years; the Antarctic has 30% more ice mass than it did in late 1970s, and the polar population is 5 times what it was in 1969--from 5,500 bears to over 25,000 today.  In other words, tonight's misguided symbolism is an absolute farce by those who worship mother earth. As for me, look for the house that will be lit up like Christmas tree--that will be mine!!!!!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67m9r5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/jn2h</id></website><link>http://www.iol.co.za/scitech/science/environment/the-irony-of-earth-hour-1.1267644</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:04:46+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T13:38:13+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwkzo7</id><link>http://www.iol.co.za/scitech/science/environment/the-irony-of-earth-hour-1.1267644#comment-481835679</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hqfpm</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>