<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/312236/post/127908505/comment/328343685</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>1 pkg Pepperidge Farm Herb Seasoned Stuffing (cubed)
4 cloves garlic, minced
3/4 cup onions, chopped
1 cup butter (2 sticks)
1 tablespoon olive oil
2 cups chicken broth
3 eggs
1/2 cup fresh parsley, chopped
1 teaspoon paprika
1 lb turkey giblets, finely chopped
1/2 cup celery, chopped
1 cup chopped mushrooms
1/2-1 teaspoon Bell Seasoning (or rubbed sage)
1/4 teaspoon each: salt, pepper, onion and garlic powder
a light sprinkling of cayenne pepper, if desired
1 teaspoon 's powdered chicken bouillon or Minor's Chicken Soup Base

In a large saucepan, sauté chopped giblets and (de-stringed) celery in 1 tablespoon butter and 1 tablespoon olive oil; adding onions and after 2-3 minutes and minced garlic and parsley and mushrooms after 5 minutes. sauté 1 minute more and add chicken broth. Dissolve chicken bouillon in broth. Add paprika, Bell Seasoning, salt, pepper, onion and garlic powder and cayenne pepper. Add remaining butter and stir over low Heat for 10 minutes.
Stir package of stuffing cubes into broth quickly. Liquid will be absorbed. Turn Off Heat but leave pan on stove.

Allow to sit for 2-3 minutes, then stir in 1 egg at a time using a large wooden spoon, mixing quickly. Stir completely after adding each egg.

Stuffing should be somewhat sticky. If it's not holding together, add 1/4-1/2 cup more broth and mix in.

Line the bottom of a bread loaf pan with aluminum foil, leaving enough along the sides to cover the top of the pan when folded over. Spray foil inside the pan with oil or non-stick spray. Pat mixture into pan evenly, spreading with spatula or the back of a spoon. Do not press heavily. Shape into a bread loaf shape.

Bake in 350 degrees 45 minutes; uncover by removing foil from top and allow to bake another 10-15 minutes or until top is golden brown.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:312236:127908505</id><idPostId>127908505</idPostId><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:312236</id><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><link>http://www.denpdf.com</link><displayName>denpdf.com</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.denpdf.com/stuffing-recipe-stuffing-recipe/</link><displayName>stuffing recipe- Stuffing recipe?</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T07:40:40.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:312236:127908505:328343685</id><link>http://www.denpdf.com/stuffing-recipe-stuffing-recipe/#IDComment328343685</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T07:40:40.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on stuffing recipe- Stuffing recipe? by depp_lover</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>01222687ca8e5038ece38004decfc52e</idEmailMd5><displayName>depp_lover</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>depp_lover commented on &lt;a href="http://www.denpdf.com/stuffing-recipe-stuffing-recipe/"&gt;stuffing recipe- Stuffing recipe?&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>