<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3uxqy/update/2012-03-29T15:26:21/a8acfe818ad34ca5893891089b00778d96dc52e46cae71cf7f44139eabadb4a3</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I am disgusted on how individuals are reacting to these videos and posting. This has to be one of the most heart breaking stories that any mother, sister, brother or friend could hear. As a member of the African American community I believe 100% that Trayvon was profiled and followed because the color of his skin and his attire, but I am not fighting to prove whether or not Zimmer liked black people. That is all irrelevant to me. I am fighting so that every man, woman and child can wake up knowing that we live in a just society that will hold each of us equally accountable for our crimes..... and this has not happend with Trayvon. 

As a sister of 3 beautiful and powerful BLACK brothers, this issue of racial profiling is not new. I am sick and tired of having to conform to what America wants me to be. I am sick and tired of mothers having to say goodbye to their children before it was there time. No man has the right to Act as God. And your right Justice 2, white children as well as black children are dying everyday in Cold blood and no one is caring. But instead of playing the pitty party and cry " why us", we ALL need to learn about the laws that will keep all of the Zimmermas on the street. We as Americans love to be passive until it affects us.  

Living 20 minutes from where this innocent young boy was shot and killed I can't help but become infuriated. Looking at the video of Zimmerman handcuffed with no blood on his shirt, yet still claiming self defense is an insult to everyone. The more information that is given to the public, the more my heart hurts. Despite my prayers for justice... and let's be frank.... despite the obvious... the killer of this young man will walk.  I have no faith in the justice system, but we must push past our hurt and change this. My heart can't take hearing another young child, whether black or white, screaming for their lives. My prayers go out to the Martin family and anyone who has undergone the pain of being let down by our government. It's sad that I will have to explain to my now, two year old brother how he must survive while being Black in America. ...... Funny, and this is where I call home
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zrph8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/opinion/whitaker-in-depth-martin/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:09:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:26:21+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3uxqy</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/opinion/whitaker-in-depth-martin/index.html#comment-479791557</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzhng</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>