<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m395vz/post/2012-03-29T17:21:53</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3admd</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5lqlv</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I am appalled by this comment. By all means, disagree with this particular measure, mention the detriment to aesthetics and question it's effectiveness. But such heartlessness and name calling is uncalled for. I am not just calling out badger74, but all other (currently 22 people) who made this the most liked comment on this thread. It would seem hostility is the rule, not the exception.

I wonder, do you think those who fall victim to the Flu a bit more often
 than the average are "weak" too? Those with cancer, heart disease? Like physical illness, mental illness is an illness. And it too has biological roots. Read 11890636 statistics below, and  some humanity and empathy.

It is precisely this attitude that makes so many people who are suffering feel that they have to keep it a , what makes it worse, what makes jumping Off a bridge seem like a better thing to do than tell someone about it. Because of the fear that it will change the way people view you forever, that you will not be allowed to grow beyond it. This destructive point of view is culpable for so much.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66mdpz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/l7r5</id></website><link>http://chronicle.com/article/Preventing-Suicide-on-Campus/131291/</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T13:54:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T21:21:53+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m395vz</id><link>http://chronicle.com/article/Preventing-Suicide-on-Campus/131291/#comment-479909390</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zztxy</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>