<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ol1p/post/2012-03-29T19:19:14</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I love one sided arguments, here's perhaps my favorite:

Dihydrogen monoxide is colorless, odorless, tasteless, and kills uncounted thousands of people every year. Most of these deaths are caused by accidental inhalation of DHMO, but the dangers of dihydrogen monoxide do not end there. Prolonged exposure to its solid form causes severe tissue damage. Symptoms of DHMO ingestion can include excessive sweating and urination, and possibly a bloated feeling, Nausea, Vomiting and body electrolyte imbalance. For those who have become dependent, DHMO withdrawal means certain death.

Among some of the startling uses are:
-as an additive to food products, including jarred baby food and baby formula, and even in many soups, carbonated beverages and supposedly "all-natural" fruit juices

-in Cough medicines and other liquid pharmaceuticals

-in shampoos, shaving creams, deodorants and numerous other bathroom products, in bathtub bubble products marketed to children.

Yet surprisingly, despite overwhelming evidence, there is opposition to the overal Ban of the use of Dihydrogen Monoxide in the United States.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6znuio</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dngw</id></website><link>http://bangordailynews.com/2012/03/29/health/math-and-myth-of-guns-and-safety/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:43:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T23:19:14+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ol1p</id><link>http://bangordailynews.com/2012/03/29/health/math-and-myth-of-guns-and-safety/#comment-480013373</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rgemg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>