<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw40gk/post/2012-03-30T18:07:30</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw45wf</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>i have to say after reading your Diarrhea you've obviously never heard someone express an OPINION. there can be inconsistencies to movies, yet they still can turn out to be great. all mp is saying is that it just doesn't really feel like it's that natural when dialogue between loki and rdj takes place. i can agree, just didn't feel menacing enough. however, of course the previews won't give us all we want and on top of that we have to remember this movie is gonna be like 2:30:00-2:45:00. and also the fact that the majority of all avengers trailers out right now are mostly from the opening "introductory" film before the opening credits, and not the movie. everyone on this msg board will most likely SEE the movie. but for people actually paying attention to technicality of dialogue, character progression, or just screenplay writing maybe we should welcome that because you never know who might end up with the marvel pencil in their hand. welcome to the world where if someone doesn't agree with you it's maybe not Always called trolling.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67yi3n</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/jybj</id></website><link>http://www.superherohype.com/news/articles/170049-new-footage-in-domestic-the-avengers-tv-spot</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:44:16+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T22:07:30+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw40gk</id><link>http://www.superherohype.com/news/articles/170049-new-footage-in-domestic-the-avengers-tv-spot#comment-481255555</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>