<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/133950/post/69820706/comment/327485826</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>They came great distances acrossdangerous seas in overcrowded ships to land at various points onthe coast. More than 800 boats made it during an 80-year period,each carrying fragile human cargoes. Lack of sanitation, poor food and disease were commonplace,Chavez Sets Price Caps on P&amp;amp;G Deodorant, Coca-Cola Water - B,sexual and other forms of violence were frequent. Many of thetransportees were deemed major or persistent criminals; others -- especially the women and children -- often were firstoffenders. Some died on the passage; some were shipwrecked anddrowned. Not infrequently, the captains had learned their tradeas slavers. On arrival, relatively few of these voyagers wereincarcerated: Most received &amp;#8220;tickets of leave&amp;#8221; to provideforced labor for free settlers or government institutions. Someresumed lives of crime in their new homeland; others prosperedand became pillars of the community. By the time the boatsstopped,Burberry Uomini, there had been about 162,000 arrivals. These were inlarge part modern-day Australia&amp;#8217;s founding fathers and mothers. Beginning in the mid-1970s, a different kind of &amp;#8220;boatpeople&amp;#8221; began arriving on our shores,burberry sito ufficiale, claiming asylum as non-assessed refugees under the . Their numbers havefluctuated since, but as , the leader of theopposition , often reminds us, &amp;#8220;the boats keepcoming.&amp;#8221; &amp;#8216;Pacific Solution&amp;#8217; Abbott, who campaigned last year on a  to restrictthe flow of asylum seekers, argues that the &amp;#8220;Pacific Solution&amp;#8221;introduced by the Liberal government of Prime Minister managed to stop the boats by incarcerating &amp;#8220;illegals&amp;#8221;in detention centers in Nauru and and thenprocessing them offshore. True, the numbers have been small. In 2010, for example,134 boats arrived, carrying a total of about 6,789 people, amanageable figure compared with the hundreds of thousands ofpeople who illegally cross into the U.S. each year, or the currently flooding into refugeecamps in Pakistan and . Many come to Australia from countries such asAfghanistan and , where Australian troops have recently beenfighting. Most arrive by air with valid passports and they applyfor &amp;#8220;protection from persecution.&amp;#8221; Our largest influxes ofactual illegal residents are tourists from the U.K. andelsewhere who have overstayed their visas. Yet the falseportrayal of boat people as queue jumpers, moneyed criminals,terrorists, imposters and welfare cheats continues to havecurrency. &amp;#8216;Children Overboard&amp;#8217; At the same time,Burberry Uomini, there is little to differentiate thegovernment and opposition asylum policies. Both parties clearlybelieve that appearing soft on refugees will cost votes. Etchedinto the collective political mind is the saga of Prime MinisterHoward and &amp;#8220;the children overboard affair&amp;#8221; of 2001. When theMV Tampa, a Norwegian freighter carrying 438 Afghans who wererescued from a sinking fishing boat,Sac Hermes 2011 New,FBrsaItaliana Key Statistics - Fiat SpA - Bloomberg, tried to enter Australianwaters, Howard ordered soldiers to board the ship. In a later incident, his claims that asylum seekers aboarda vessel threw their children into the water to Ensure theirrescue and entry to were proved to be unsubstantiatedand led to a Senate inquiry. Howard&amp;#8217;s attempted introduction ofan emergency Border Protection Bill was defeated, but the toughstance -- plus the contingent ripples of the Sept. 11 attacks --are widely believed to have secured his re-election in 2001. Malaysia Swap Both major parties continue to support .Under Prime Minister &amp;#8217;s Labor Party government, arapid escalation in the number of detainees held on Australia&amp;#8217;s in the has led to strict newpolicies aimed at deterring &amp;#8220;people smugglers&amp;#8221; and theirvictims. The government recently signed an agreement to send 800asylum seekers to Malaysia in return for accepting a largernumber of people there who qualify as assessed refugees underthe UN convention. This proposal was rejected as unlawful by the High Court onAug. 31. Lawyers on behalf of two asylum seekers argued thatsince hasn&amp;#8217;t signed the UN refugee convention,Australia has a duty of care not to expose their clients to therisk of arbitrary punishment. The irony of all this jockeying for the draconian highground is that both major parties may now be out of step withthe citizenry. last month found that, though amajority still favored mandatory detention for asylum seekers,53 percent supported the idea of processing them on Australiansoil, a policy advocated only by the left-leaning Greens party. Private Contractor It&amp;#8217;s difficult to know what has caused this apparentsoftening of public opinion. Some may have been shocked by arecent parliamentary inquiry into incidents at the ChristmasIsland center, administered by the international securitycompany Among other troubling statistics, disclosed that 1,507 detainees had been hospitalized inthe first six months of this year, 72 as psychiatric admissionsand 213 for self-inflicted physical injuries. Other commentators cite the emotional impact of anacclaimed TV reality show called &amp;#8220;Go Back to Where You CameFrom,&amp;#8221; featured on the multicultural television channel SBS.Six contestants, all but one with negative views of boat people,were sent to a variety of hot Spots to interrogate would-berefugees and their relatives. Ratings and tweets soared when theprogram&amp;#8217;s chief villain, Raquel Moore,Strike paralyzes Hungary\'s rail traffic mi phpFox, a self-avowed African-hater from a working-class suburb, showed a touching change ofheart when confronted with the anguish of a Congolese womanwhose family had been subjected to rape and murder. Shifting Opinion Conservative critics are cynical about what they believe tobe a biased and manipulative piece of television staging; andeven sympathetic analysts doubt that such sudden eruptions ofpublic empathy will translate into voting behavior. A fewpollsters deny that asylum seekers are a substantive issue forany but a small hard core of Australian voters: those who wantto send the boats back out to sea. Even after the &amp;#8217;s ruling on the Malaysian plan,it is unlikely that the issue of asylum seekers will go away.Figures collected by the UN at the end of 2009 showed that about across the world had been displaced byconflict and persecution. Amid this global avalanche of pain, some compassionateAustralians may perhaps remember their own ancestral goodfortune in having once been transported to these shores inovercrowded boats. (Iain McCalman,louis vuitton borse, a professor of history at the and the author of &amp;#8220;Darwin&amp;#8217;s Armada,&amp;#8221; is a BloombergView columnist. The opinions expressed are his own.) To contact the writer of this column:Iain McCalman in Sydney at iain.mccalman@arts.usyd.edu.au To contact the editor responsible for this column:Max Berley at </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:133950:69820706</id><idPostId>69820706</idPostId><idBlogId>133950</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:133950</id><idBlogId>133950</idBlogId><link>http://webdevcodex.com/blog</link><displayName>Web Development Codex</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://webdevcodex.com/mod-your-404-pages-of-your-wordpress-blog/attachment/4042/</link><displayName>4042</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:12:22.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:133950:69820706:327485826</id><link>http://webdevcodex.com/mod-your-404-pages-of-your-wordpress-blog/attachment/4042/#IDComment327485826</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:12:22.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on 4042 by mengsi6931</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://www.borselouisvuittonvendita1.com/</link><idEmailMd5>00972b63927e44c60563e6089f15cb2d</idEmailMd5><displayName>mengsi6931</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://www.borselouisvuittonvendita1.com/"&gt;mengsi6931&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://webdevcodex.com/mod-your-404-pages-of-your-wordpress-blog/attachment/4042/"&gt;4042&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>