<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4h7v/post/2012-03-30T17:36:05</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>We are a nation that deserves to Burn in hell because of the way we treat our sick, infirm, children, etc.  Everyone, except healthy white males!  But Obamacare is barely the answer for the sick and infirm, and we know it.  Yes, it forces insurance companies to do away with pre-existing clauses, but that is about all the good it does.  It will force people to buy crappy policies for a lot of money and for the rest of us, premiums will go up.  And if you think, Mr. Pitt, that if your wife loses her job because her disease prevents her from doing it, that with Obamacare,  insurance companies won't be able to deny you care because of your pre-existing conditions, guess again.  They will figure out how to make that care so unaffordable or so insufficient, you will wonder why you bother to buy it.  You will say, "I would be better Off paying down my assets and going on Medicaid."  But wait, you won't have a choice.  If you don't buy it, you will be fined.  They will get you one way or the other.  We need universal, single payer health care without insurance companies sucking up the money that should to toward care.  Maybe if those nine justices determine Obamacare is unconstitutional, they will be doing us a fabor.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/675v4n</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tsjl</id></website><link>http://truth-out.org/opinion/item/8202-the-savage-arithmetic-of-the-pre-existing-condition</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:35:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:36:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4h7v</id><link>http://truth-out.org/opinion/item/8202-the-savage-arithmetic-of-the-pre-existing-condition#comment-481227388</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>