<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6dk5/post/2012-03-30T11:19:19</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3jcjw</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/691td</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Nature Advocate

As an ex-farmer and hunter I know what it's like to run a farm.

As for TNR (trap neuter release) the R means release the animal where 
the animal was trapped and no where else if this is done properly TNR 
works and you don't get the build up of cats in one area that you claim 
in fact the numbers of course decrease, common sense. Our farm as well 
as all the other farms in the area had cats dogs cows pigs chickens and 
never any of the problems you speak of in your posts, these animals tend
 to stay to them selves. If a TNR group is releasing animals in one Spot
 you need to deal with that directly. If you make it hurt their money 
they will stop. This would not be happening if it were anywhere near me 
because I would work to make sure they lost money and sleep it's very 
important that they lose sleep. But if some someone insisted on the 
killing way then they would be the ones losing sleep. Believe it or not 
once they stop and they Always stop, they feel good about it. So using 
this approach is actually a friendly gesture and in the best interest of
 all involved.

Funny thing being around a farm and all that goes on can callus a person
 and lower they'r reguard for living beings including themselves, it's a
 pretty shitty life (no pun intended) but being around a hospital only 
effects a persons view of other people.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z7m5b</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/u683</id></website><link>http://www.catster.com/the-scoop/busted-loews-hotels-caught-trapping-and-relocating-feral-cats-to-kill-shelter</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:41:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:19:19+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6dk5</id><link>http://www.catster.com/the-scoop/busted-loews-hotels-caught-trapping-and-relocating-feral-cats-to-kill-shelter#comment-480848224</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>