<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk1imb/post/2012-03-26T11:56:03</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkbogv</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rixbx</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I would really love to see McGuinty live the way I have lived for the past 28 years after an accident at work left me disabled and no employer would give me a job because of that. I was given a $400.00 a month pension from Worker Comp. that pension today after 28 years is only $511.00. because the government bases a cost of living increase on a formula that basically gives me an increase to my pension if cost of living is only above 2.5%. they save a lot of money by not giving us the actual cost of living, something that is not applied to their own pensions which are fully indexed. I have had to make my own way in life with no help from anyone, working twice as hard as any politician ever in order to survive. Today I own my own home in a remote area. with no hydro except for that which I make with solar panels and a couple of Batteries. I have no running water and have to use an outhouse. My 85 year old log cabin is Heated with wood and I drive a vehicle that is 25 years old. So yes I would like to see all politicians live the way I do, and i`ll bet they don`t even last a week.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r40jq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zsj8</id></website><link>http://www.torontosun.com/2012/03/25/duncan-fires-back-at-flaherty</link><postedTime>2012-03-25T22:03:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T15:56:03+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk1imb</id><link>http://www.torontosun.com/2012/03/25/duncan-fires-back-at-flaherty#comment-476490226</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z8qij</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>