<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/e6ok2l/update/2011-12-07T02:12:07/43d593248b01d421197828a7a748a1aa592739a47ebf7a31b5c335b6a5def0fd</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>One of the places I was stationed at during my 6 year service in the U.S. 
Navy was the last and outer most Aleutian Island called Attu. I was stationed 
there for 13 months.We actually used the wooden cabins where we fished on the 
north side of Attu that were built by the Japanese in World War II.The Naval 
Security Detachment and Weather Station was located on the south side of the 
Island of Attu. Much of the year we experienced 65 degrees below zero weather. 
In the spring, around April, the snow began to melt which made it possible to 
climb over the mountain which stretched out from the east to the west at a place 
called "jackass pass." We often stayed in the Japanese cabins for 3 or 4 days 
and caught a load of trout and salmon in the very clear streams and river. I 
used salmon eggs to catch trout that were swimming right through our legs as we 
stood in the crystal clear streams. We went back over the pass with the fish 
packed in ice in our back packs and took them to the station cook's galley to 
cook fresh and ate it while drinking a few beers and watching the same movie 
over and over for at least 30 days until a Navy PBY plane could get through the 
bitter Cold snow packed weather to bring us a new movie to watch another 30 days 
or so and brought us our personal mail that was sent to us from our parents. 
Once a month the Coast Guard was able to dock their ship on the south side of 
the island where they (and we) unloaded 200 cases of beer.We found an old 
bowling lane and used it for the top of our beer bar. Beer cost 5 cents a bottle 
and cigarettes were one dollar a carton. (10 packs).There were about 20 sailors 
stationed on the island, with rotation around every 12 months.Because of the 
extreme harsh winters, it was very difficult to fly in a replacement for us. 
Everyone had their own calendar to mark  the days spent on this 
assignment. After serving on the island for 11 months you were labeled as a 
"short timer." When you returned to the states at Whidbey Island in Puget Sound 
near Seattle,Washington, guys got Off the plane and kissed the ground!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ex2vx8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/h7jj</id></website><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/infocus/2011/08/world-war-ii-battle-of-midway-and-the-aleutian-campaign/100137/</link><postedTime>2011-08-28T11:06:24+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-12-07T07:12:07+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/e6ok2l</id><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/infocus/2011/08/world-war-ii-battle-of-midway-and-the-aleutian-campaign/100137/#comment-380939772</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-08-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>