<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwwefw/post/2012-03-31T12:22:49</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Iran had a government set up FOR the PEOPLE; DC/ran by BRITS way of doing thing; NEVER the plan of our forefathers; over threw that behind Saddam Hussain; &amp; put in THEIR TYPICAL HORRID DICTATOR THE SHAH; been after THAT and every other nation for THEIR SYSTEM of ABSOLLUTE CORRUPTION WITH FICTICIOUS MEDIA; FICTICIOUS LAWS THEY CALL "LEGAL" SYSTEM and their COURTS OF CORRUPT JUDGES THAT LET THEM GET AWAY WITH EVERYTHING! 
     DEMOCRACY WORKED BY EXPLOIATATION! isn't it incredibly amazing that being so "broke" they have NO $ for SCHOOLS yet POCKET 1 TRILLION WEEKLY: and are FORCING HUMANS FROM AFRICA to FIGHT in YEMEN, SOMALIA &amp; other places they are so DETERMINED to get their SYSTEM in EVERYWHERE? KARL ROVE; known war criminal; on the CHARLIE ROSE SHOW
      CONTRACT LAW GOT RID OF THE CRIMINALLY RUN SYSTEM LEGALLY &amp; LAWFULLY! QUITE UNLIKE ANYTHING EVER DONE IN THIS NATION SINCE 1832! 
      city 
      county 
      state NOT RECOGNIZED NOR AUTHORIZED AS GOVERNMENT THEY KNOW THIS! 
         when SAID YOU MUST RECOGNIZE US AS GOVERNMENT WE REPLIED NO WE DO NOT! 
   exploitation
   victimization 
    write "laws" change "laws" delete 'laws" 
     when ASKED what of USURY laws? your RESPONSE was they just disappeared! 
    WHEN ASKED HOW DO LAWS JUST DISAPPEAR your RESPONSE was OOPS! caught us there huh! ha ha ha! 
       you thought you were superior 
    TO ALL OF THE ABOVE THE RESPONSE WAS YES! 
             SOLE PURPOSE OF GOVERNMENT IS DOING THAT WHICH IS MOST BENEFICIAL FOR THE PEOPLE; LAWS are to EXIST; STABLE; FIRM, FIXED like the WORD OF GOD! 
    FOR THE PROTECTION of the PEOPLE, the animals &amp; planet itself! 
COURTS OF JUSTICE quite unlike the corrupt ones they have been running with the ficticious legal system they set up for their own personal use; 
       DC Always &amp; ever to be KNOWN as the place of deception! 
 Copeland, executive branch 
 Meyers, legislative branch 
  Hagin, judicial branch 
THUS TRUE GOVENRMENT IS EXISTING WITH TRUE LAWS THAT DO NOT BE DISAPPEARING EVERY TIME YOU BE SNEEZING! 
   LOCATED in completely different location than DC; WYOMING; multitude of WISE counselors; unlike THESE witless wonders of the universe! 
       Will be as if heaven were on this planet for the people, animals &amp; planet itself! 
ABSOLUTE LPOWER is NOT NOT NOT corrupt people! HE IS THE OPPOSITE! 
   He never meant for mankind to have to live under the oppression of darkness! </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67s2uc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tsjl</id></website><link>http://truth-out.org/opinion/item/8225-scrutinizing-the-threat-from-iran</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T15:32:03+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T16:22:49+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwwefw</id><link>http://truth-out.org/opinion/item/8225-scrutinizing-the-threat-from-iran#comment-481965190</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>