<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwl5yu/post/2012-03-30T12:43:31</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>We watched your show last night regarding the little girl who went to the ER and ended up with a $4,000 bill and a diagnosis of a stomachache.  Ha!  They got Off cheap!  My 7 year old son went to bed one Friday evening with a Stomach ache.  The next morning he woke up with pain in his right side.  We took him to a walk-in clinic with what we thought was an Appendicitis.  They said to take him to the ER because they didn't have a way to get any blood work on him.  When we arrived at the ER they immediately told me it did not appear to be an Appendicitis.  They said they were going to put in an IV and I asked, why?  They said it was normal procedure.  Then, they did an Ultra Sound and I was told that they couldn't see his appendix but they did see the inflamed lymph nodes which point to Mesenteric Adenitis.  However, they needed to run more test to be sure.  After a CT Scan they indeed determined it to be Mesenteric Adenitis.  A few weeks later I received a bill in the mail for $443.00 and I thought that wasn't too bad.  Little did I know that the very next week I would receive more bills.  One was for $11,038.90 and another one for $300.00!  His hospital bill was $11,781.90!  Normally, I would have just taken him to see his Pediatrician but because it was on a Saturday our Pediatrician's office was closed.  Then, we went to the lesser expensive walk-in clinic and we HAD to go to the Emergency Room.  I am not disputing the fact that I had to take him somewhere to rule out the Appendicitis but instead I am disputing the fact that it cost us $11,781.90 to rule out the Appendicitis.  I will say for all you doctors and nurses who are posting....the doctors and nurses at this ER where the most wonderful people that I have ever met (minus the CT Scan Technician)!  They really took wonderful care of my son and I just am in awe at the work they do on a daily basis.  It is the cost of it all that is out of control.  I totally understand that all Nurses and Doctor's are underpaid and overworked.  I total agree but someone here is getting rich and if it isn't me and it isn't the doctor's or nurses....then who is it?  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zotaf</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t33k</id></website><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/have-you-had-any-medical-bill-nightmares/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:45:56+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:43:31+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwl5yu</id><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/have-you-had-any-medical-bill-nightmares/#comment-480935579</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>