<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi4bev/update/2012-03-23T11:17:16/e19e607928173757a5ebf061076c49fc824bbcedda98cf584e30b70468859ced</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/migvy4</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I hear you RaiderHater and I too was one who said if nothing else win our last game against the Raiders even "if" it meant Norv and AJ returned...then we got Spanos saying how things would change and as soon as the Heat is Off AJ is back to his old self. Where are the improvements on Defense? All I know is playing good defense and winning the turn over game wins games and championships...while I don't think Rivers will ever equal the gifts he gave our opponents last year I don't think we improved on the defense and again AJ is snubbing the top tier FA's. Okay some of it could be to get the most of the $ available but come on now it's time to give the fans something to get excited about. Like the pick up of Royal, great move answers a couple of needs like returner and slot guy similar to a wes welker but why haven't we seen the same thing on the defensive side. Or the pick up of Mechem good move but I'd rather use those $ for the defense and pickup a receiver in the draft. Why? Because we need a ton of defensive help and even though VJ was a huge loss we have another Vincent who IMHO is as good of an option as Mechem!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6mg5za</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6kww</id></website><link>http://www.bolthype.com/2012/03/meet-your-new-chargers.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-19T15:02:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T15:17:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi4bev</id><link>http://www.bolthype.com/2012/03/meet-your-new-chargers.html#comment-474520264</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-19</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>