<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/276915/post/104218228/comment/328055744</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>-194 To depart their homes - I have to read,louboutin chaussures,louis vuitton sito ufficiale from G City to the United States, is a very distant distance, but forgotten is the extra lengthy process. Yuanyuan pull  a plane on the ground, never back and look at a this piece of her students reserve her land. However, the eyes can not discern, the center tin not forget, would the situation even more complicated to let work of the anguish. Since then, Hao Rui entirely out of her life, since then, they are strangers. She wants to forget the elapse, re-start a fashionable life. she repeatedly told myself apt be lusty, apt forget to smile, yet from the moment the plane took  her tears for the rill explosion its banks, overrunning disaster. Sean frowned in nauseate, the girl from the plane nigh the beginning, like a broken tap, as has been constantly crying. in crying for two hours, she began slumbering. Sinking a small pate is often tempting to  on to his shoulders and let him cope with their, but do nothing. her cry for him to provoke the eyes of innumerable mysterious,  of who coincided to his Hengmeilengdui. If he dares to shove her to open, it is simply heinous it! quietly endure ten minutes later, while her body more and more down, and slowly the heaviness of the body to  him, he finally  not to indulge her insatiable. several days of insomnia paired with emotional ups and downs, this time Yuanyuan has long been weary, and fell down dormant, get up up where the scream? Sean could not aid mushroom the volume: feared stricken stare at him: proud to heave the snout, favor a shine xingmou Sapphire Shibao Can condescending see askance at her coldly. her another for the complete elimination of cross-border, he even got up on the trips to the lavatory, come back look, embarrassing the. that fool matron, lying head down the channel in between two seats, as whether they fell asleep. site commotion, flight attendants over services for them to take over the Yuanyuan, is handed a towel and bottled water is well over the cleaning of. Sean Dizhou soon to the bathroom to wash and organize, Huanhaoyifu, out of the body also exudes a strong acid smell, Jun Yan Tieqing his pique. he now found flight attendants, apply a replacement seat, away from the Fiends. this thrilling spewing on the plane, a cruel reminder of the fact that she - she made a deadly blunder. hurry, she completely forgot also with a small body in life. The United States for the protection of person rights is very rigid, there is no guardian signature to prove that she is no path to abortion. Yuanyuan carrying a simple bow out of the landing lobby, standing on a busy avenue, into a loss. In the unaccompanied foreign country, how could she do? dragging baggage, loss of distinct loss, hesitated and hesitated, she passed 1 country after different. the beginning, she skirmished between the child\'s destiny is not decided, to the after, but it is also impossible to remove. Slowly over the time, big belly one day up, the money card is diluted day at day. she pathetic as only stray dogs, and forever ascertain a habitat for the warmth of her home. holds the heap of thin francs, standing on the pretty fields of sunflowers in Provence, she finally thought of going to earn money to support themselves. However, more than 4 months pregnant and long-term outcast, the abnormal disability of her body, about transform skinny as a skeleton manner, attach with the language barrier, there is no go experience, she is   on the first interview was a ruthless gainsay. fall of Provence, it is lavender in full bloom, countless observers flock from all intentions, such as flood Provence. Yuanyuan finally in a Chinese restaurant, base a job cleaning dishes. her stupid, do not use detergent, the 1st daytime namely not accustomed to namely slippery slide hand touch, missed destroying the pile of exquisite dishes. speaking in a strong Cantonese emphasis employer heaved eyebrows, gesticulating,  aloud in her ear. Yuanyuan endured embarrassment, attempting to go with attention, agreed installment of compensation to him. restaurant at night to activity masquerade, she tugged the body extremely tired, went to a restaurant\'s attic tiny body curl, arrange on the bed, the tears flow discontinue Once again, uncontrollably. her incipient maneuver, the thought of foreign universities looking to perch down to continue reading after the call home low rate. But the navel of the child, is completely rent her plans. hybrid so now, she did not defiance to phone home, but did not defiance to calculate about their own hereafter, only low self-esteem to live day to day. In such circumstances, numerous periods she thought Hao Rui. immediately, he ought still nothing had occurred in a location with human fighting, gambling or racing, right? Sadly, his life completely for of her involvement and anybody changes. And her earth, but because of his exterior completely overturning it! is he playing with her sensibilities, marred her future, her dream shattered, tear Off her family ... ... immeasurable suffering to bring her and suffering. the exotic nation in this chilly, stomach that had never met the child, but strange to give her strength. She found that she could not longer do without him (her). Love has nothing to do, but a spiritual pillar, one sensitive outlet for. every night, she ambition be stroking the stomach, buzzed to her (him) spoke of the day\'s experience, approximately her emotions, speak on their ideas. day, and only the mama and child live together in this moment, will make her feel that they still live like individuals, can find cause to live. she felt strange, Qi sister goes out empty checks, why she has been reluctant to discard away, insisted his side. When not survive, they will come up on a point of view, a Back pain severely after the bite will bring an end to ... the day. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:276915:104218228</id><idPostId>104218228</idPostId><idBlogId>276915</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:276915</id><idBlogId>276915</idBlogId><link>http://www.cinefamily.org</link><displayName>The Cinefamily</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.cinefamily.org/blog/qa-archive-4-combat-shock/</link><displayName>Q&amp;A Archive #4: "Combat Shock"</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:07:16.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:276915:104218228:328055744</id><link>http://www.cinefamily.org/blog/qa-archive-4-combat-shock/#IDComment328055744</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:07:16.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Q&amp;A Archive #4: "Combat Shock" by 450lyp16tq</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://chaussuresnlouboutinpascher.com</link><idEmailMd5>ea1de456b223c7adcd72a641dd54c7e2</idEmailMd5><displayName>450lyp16tq</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://chaussuresnlouboutinpascher.com"&gt;450lyp16tq&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.cinefamily.org/blog/qa-archive-4-combat-shock/"&gt;Q&amp;A Archive #4: "Combat Shock"&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>