<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4xfd/post/2012-03-30T17:48:06</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>So far Pineda's  is 3.31. Now this is Spring Training, but 3.31 is pretty solid. And since Kuroda is going to be the number 2 starter, any  around 3.50-3.80 is just fine for the rotation. But this does make me wonder, if Pettitte does pitch well, and the Yankees haven't found anything to do with Garcia, then it could be a real problem. However, Phil Hughes looks like he's won a rotation Spot (2.03 ). 

To be honest, I feel like Nova is the one that's in trouble here. His ERA is 6.86, and I know it's Spring Training again, but he has one start remaining, and even if he throws a complete game shutout (unlikely) he might be the loser here. Not to say he can't pitch, (he hit 98 mph on the gun against the Orioles) but I think it's getting to that point where they'll have to start judging who clearly won a Spot. 

Overall, I think Pineda has done a better job than Nova has so far. Yes he's overweight (He's gotta correct that), and yes his velocity is not where it was last year, but the velocity is not such a big deal. He's been working on his changeup mostly, he did not pitch in Winter Ball this year, and he's not really focusing on lighting up the radar gun. At least for now. The velocity will come when the season starts, because it is increasing every game. That's just my two cents. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zongl</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lz6q</id></website><link>http://newyork.yankees.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120329%26content_id=27747196%26notebook_id=27746974%26vkey=notebook_nyy%26c_id=nyy</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:51:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:48:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4xfd</id><link>http://newyork.yankees.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120329%26content_id=27747196%26notebook_id=27746974%26vkey=notebook_nyy%26c_id=nyy#comment-481238108</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hinde</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>