<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/med24q/update/2012-02-09T02:12:00/1519ad685ae5bb7cb074051208ce63516346d12c004f3cda78690df9bd669d93</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Excellent article, Verashni!
 
'Instead we were subjected to the same tired line we have heard from too many DA leaders: that the party and all its members are post-race. Move on, they seem to imply. Or Act like a "born free" and stop bothering us with these issues'.
.... and this observation is Spot on. I must say, however, expecting the DA to say anything different is really hoping for too much. Their core constituency persists in denying that race is at all important despite massive evidence to the contrary.
 
The Institute for Justice and Reconciliation's SA Reconciliation Barometer 2011 finds that 59% of South Africans see their prime identity as racial (language, ethnicity and race) while only 14% see their prime identity as South African. By way of comparison, in England, where I originally come from, 49% of people see their prime identity as English followed by British at 42%. Clearly South Africa remains a deeply race conscious country that has still to build a strong sense of unified nationality.
 
But don't expect to get any recognition of such realities in the La-La-Land that the DA inhabit! This is not about Lindiwe Mazibuko, who is an essentially cosmetic promotion designed to market the DA to young black middle class folk. If she followed your advice and spoke honestly about race she would be out just as quickly as she has been promoted!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yzbold</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6buk</id></website><link>http://mg.co.za/article/2012-02-09-lindiwe-mazibuko-is-not-the-role-model-we-need</link><postedTime>2012-02-08T13:40:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-09T07:12:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/med24q</id><link>http://mg.co.za/article/2012-02-09-lindiwe-mazibuko-is-not-the-role-model-we-need#comment-433714843</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/chlrx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-08</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>