<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/296175/post/127515465/comment/328148416</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body> 
Let me first begin by saying that I am very passionate about all things Castle. I love the characters, love the actors that play them, love the drive, competition and passion everyone displays on the show, to get the bad guys episode after episode. Adore the witty banter between Castle and Beckett. It&amp;acute;s a simbiosys rarely seen on TV, at least by me. 
Beckett carries her &amp;quot;cross&amp;quot; because she feels guilty about her mom&amp;acute;s unsolved murder. She becomes a homicide detective machine, without feelings, without emotions, eventhough she&amp;acute;s  defending the rights and emotions of the victims and their families. It&amp;acute;s really the substance that heroes are made of. Then walks in Castle, someone that likes to solve puzzles, mysteries, because this Caresses his child-ego. His child-like demeanor, his need to please those around him, his charm and comedic side melt away, Beckett&amp;acute;s emotional and physical  barricades. Going after her mom&amp;acute;s murderers just reopen all of the emotional traumas she buried for ten years. I think the writers, to this point, stuck to and were loyal to the character&amp;acute;s and the original ideas of the program. 
I am afraid for the Castle series now. I feel that Beckett is a broken character now, that when faced again with trying to solve her mom&amp;acute;s murder, will get killed, or die trying. If Castle is not there to protect her, or save her, or solve the riddles (because in the Castle TV series, Rick is now the sole finder of relevant clues, and he&amp;acute;s the only one that puts the cases together---Less real, more make believe, than the Nikki Heat book series, where she&amp;acute;s the detective, the brains of the operations, and Rook is in it as the side-kick) I love the books more that the TV series, it&amp;acute;s written better and the characters are more realistic. 
But getting back to my point, I think the writers are opening up the possibility of Beckett taking a final bullet for the show. They have built up so much emotional and psychological pressure, on a non-physical, emotional partnership that most likely, it will not end well. 
Even if they are still filming the last four days of 4x21 (Adam Baldwin) episode with the Zombies, I think the writers and creators have distanced Castle and Beckett on purpose. They have instisted on revisiting Beckett&amp;acute;s mom&amp;acute;s case again before the end of the season. 
This artificially created distance, makes the central plot idea for the show irrelevant. Castle has no real reason to ride shot-gun anymore, and his character has been build up so much (he&amp;acute;s the one solving everything, even faster and better than Homeland Security, the FBI, and everybody), that he is now his own island. Too bad he&amp;acute;s not a real cop, or detective, or licensed private eye, cause his show could head that way anyway. With Castle&amp;acute;s/Fillion&amp;acute;s big following, everyone else in the show becomes irrelevant. 
what I am trying to say with this is that the creator and the writers have opened the door to close down the Beckett Castle relationship once and for all. The fact that Fillion&amp;acute;s own opinion of Caskett coming true would be a &amp;quot;show-ender&amp;quot;, the fact that neither the writers or Stana were present last year at comic-con 2011, are all signs that the essence of the show is coming to an end. 
On 4x20 the writers and Beckett will try to make Castle jealous, or &amp;quot;rethink&amp;quot; his idea of finally being free of a complicated and poisoned relationship with Beckett and or viceversa. Like most fans here have already stated, this has already been repeatedly done before, in seasons 2, 3 and 4. 
I think everyone will agree that a &amp;quot;middle ground&amp;quot; is impossible here and now. To each his own, back to when Castle and Beckett rode together to solve cases, meanwhile having relationships with other people. His motivation for it is gone, he has graduated from detective work and now he does it better than the pros. I think Beckett on the other hand, will not like how things were at the precinct before Castle arrived. 
How long can a person wait for a emotionally broken someone?? Months? Years? How many years? two, three, four? I think this &amp;quot;waiting&amp;quot; has been too much, even for someone as loyal and &amp;quot;prince charming-like&amp;quot; the Castle character. 
The two new books, one of Derreck Storm, the other of Nikki Heat, just make it a more likely scenario that Beckett and Castle are somehow parting ways. It reminds me of that song: &amp;quot;Que ser&amp;aacute;, ser&amp;aacute;, whatever will be, will be, the future&amp;acute;s not ours to see, que ser&amp;aacute;, ser&amp;aacute;!&amp;quot; </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:296175:127515465</id><idPostId>127515465</idPostId><idBlogId>296175</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:296175</id><idBlogId>296175</idBlogId><link>http://tvovermind.zap2it.com</link><displayName>TVOvermind</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.tvovermind.com/castle/castle-4-19-47-seconds-review</link><displayName>Castle: 4.19 "47 Seconds" Review</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T00:19:13.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:296175:127515465:328148416</id><link>http://www.tvovermind.com/castle/castle-4-19-47-seconds-review#IDComment328148416</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T00:19:13.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Castle: 4.19 "47 Seconds" Review by @pdag25</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://twitter.com/pdag25</link><idEmailMd5>9fcd1b0cb6fa5d423bbd9c15ccbc20ca</idEmailMd5><displayName>@pdag25</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/pdag25"&gt;@pdag25&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.tvovermind.com/castle/castle-4-19-47-seconds-review"&gt;Castle: 4.19 "47 Seconds" Review&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>