<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4bng/update/2012-03-30T17:49:19/8d8544dd98da619cd880f6ef5f8b09ca57c2b2560c80670c8910313f64113493</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>OK, let's clarify some things here. 

Card-counting, using your own grey matter and nothing else, isn't cheating or "cheating" or whatever. Card-counting using a device of any sort &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; illegal in many, if not most, jurisdictions that have casinos in them, and people have been arrested for using them in casinos. No one can prevent you from simply using your own talents and skills to keep count, however, and the most that they can do is simply ask you to leave (with whatever you've won up to that point) and not come back, possibly not to any of their casinos if they're a chain; you might remember the scene in &lt;i&gt;Rain Man&lt;/i&gt; where precisely that happens. Casinos can also share that information with other casinos, as with the Griffin Book, one of the "black books" that casinos use (the other type is a list of organized crime figures that are officially Banned from casinos in a particular jurisdiction by the local gambling board); one of the industries that is behind the development of face-recognition software is the casino industry, in order to Spot known counters even if they use pseudonyms and disguises. 

As much as they'd like to keep the real counters out, though, casinos also want to fish in the people who &lt;i&gt;think&lt;/i&gt; that they can count, or have some other home-grown system, but can't really make it work. These are people that either simply don't know what they're doing, or have practiced at home on a computer where it's nice and quiet and they can concentrate, but lose track of the count in a casino where there are flashing lights and free drinks and good-looking dealers (of whatever gender seems to catch your eye) who smile and leave an extra button or two on their shirt undone, and if it seems like you're keeping the count anyway they'll swap out dealers so that they can redo the shuffle, or suddenly you'll have someone really obnoxious come to the table and try to strike up a conversation with you.  And those are just the &lt;i&gt;obvious&lt;/i&gt; tricks. Say it with me: if you can't Spot the sucker at the table...</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67l25v</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/agg8</id></website><link>http://boingboing.net/2012/03/30/how-a-high-roller-took-million.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:27:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:49:19+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4bng</id><link>http://boingboing.net/2012/03/30/how-a-high-roller-took-million.html#comment-481239221</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/aswep</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>