<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk97ps/update/2012-03-26T13:32:04/b518b3d000c2b87058084b4368acd85fc8c22aab6daf1b785e28a44f2e4cd231</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk72aa</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/am3n3</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>&gt; any significant shopping without one,
You'd be surprised what you can carry on a bus or train. And with proper cloth shopping bags, you can carry a LOT of groceries on foot or mass transit. You should also get proper racks and storage for your bike. But there's Always car sharing and delivery for huge items. 

&gt; take my cats to vet appointments, 

Get a better carrier. I walk or bike my cat to appointments. The bus is also possible. 

&gt; visit friends in the suburbs, 

Trains or, if your friends are really, really disconnected, car sharing. 

&gt; take longer road trips a few times a year 

I don't really think doing something "a few times a year" is a reason to own a car in a city full time. Save your money and fly, or rent a car if you really want to drive. I guess I never grew up with "road trips," so a car is just a (pretty slow, expensive, and tiring) way to get somewhere on vacation, not the point of the trip itself. 

&gt; or go anywhere at all when the weather is bad.

Really? You don't walk outside when it's raining or snowing? Biking in the rain sucks, but it's doable with proper clothing. Biking in the snow or Cold is no problem at all. But I have a hard time believing you've ever used public transportation if you can't imagine using it in bad weather.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r6ujn</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/eyjq</id></website><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/business/archive/2012/03/why-dont-young-americans-buy-cars/255001/</link><postedTime>2012-03-25T13:00:19+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:32:04+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk97ps</id><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/business/archive/2012/03/why-dont-young-americans-buy-cars/255001/#comment-476564900</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zrrw4</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>