<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwvkjg/update/2012-03-30T16:22:39/0ba8b11bd3565604fd10d9c5a41d37b7b3b43118d999d42f2436c20cb3058208</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I enjoy how wonderfully cautious some commentors are about how we can't rush to judgement, and we can't jump to conclusions etc. Funny how we could jump to immediate conclusions about the Terri Schiavo case. We could have conservative "news" sources screaming their heads Off day and night. Doing show after show focusing on just this case. Camping out in front of this woman's hospital room. We could have them speculating and outright lying about the marriage of Michael and Terri. We could have Senate leaders giving speaches on the floor of the senate, talking about how they had been able to accurately diagnose this woman based solely on a few minutes of video. We could have conservative operatives circulating memos about how, "this is a good issue for us and a bad one for the Democrats." We could have the US Congress pass a special bill just for this one woman. We could have the President of the United States interupt his vacation (but stayed on yet another vacation while New Orleans was drowning) to fly back in the middle of the night to sign the bill. We could have conservatives howl and scream when a judge struck down that absurd bill, because the judge was a, (Shiver!)...Clinton apointee! We could then continue to bash that same judge over and over while a string of conservative judges upheld the decision. Lots of actual politics then. Lots of actual jumping to conclusions then. But now, we must be ever so careful. Gee, I wonder why the standard is so different?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z3dif</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnma</id></website><link>http://www.fresnobee.com/2012/03/30/2780691/is-this-a-civil-society.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T07:11:06+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T20:22:39+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwvkjg</id><link>http://www.fresnobee.com/2012/03/30/2780691/is-this-a-civil-society.html#comment-481157825</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c6x9h</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>