<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fe22/update/2012-03-29T16:36:58/2be9b8fdd5f0b02467322190c67603b92d3223b4be061d232f5a372a41ad874d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3q4vl</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzm73</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> "Unfortunately, no one wants to focus on another issue that is intertwined with Americans' feelings about race and prejudice"

You can't be serious. What do you think Al Sharpton, Jesse Jackson and other professional race-baiters are flying down to Florida for? Not to mention black hacks like Soledad O'Brien.  Jackson has already announced a campaign to repeal the "stand your ground" law.

What the police did was standard police procedure. Tape Off the scene of the incident and collect evidence. Take statements from principals and witnesses. And then make a summary decision of whether to make any arrests.

If later evidence comes up to cast suspicion on anyone, the DA can decide to petition a local judge for an arrest warrant and indict the suspect for the crime. Then the case eventually goes to trial.


The root problem of this media feeding frenzy is black crime. BLACK CRIME. 

BLACK CRIME!!!! 

Are you getting it yet?

Funny how the media is trotting out black entertainers like Lionel Ritchie, Chaka Khan and Oprah (of course) to hear their predictably outraged views on this topic.  So far I have yet to see one black entertainer on TV about this.

Bill Cosby.

Remember him? Remember him getting the Cold shoulder from the black "community" for daring to suggest that the problems with black people start with black people and the disgusting, animalistic behavior that is tolerated by the mass of them.

If blacks won't listen to Cosby, (perhaps the closest thing to royalty that American blacks have) who will they listen to?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6run7d</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ywkl</id></website><link>http://takimag.com/article/trayvonnosaurus_rex_jim_goad/print</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T04:03:19+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:36:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fe22</id><link>http://takimag.com/article/trayvonnosaurus_rex_jim_goad/print#comment-479864736</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rlkvg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>