<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6p7m/update/2012-03-30T11:45:02/38b5e610fd2698028cab9fe4357838f8d5c1dde09dafbbee05b9da8642440e25</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I have not posted here in a while but have been reading all the comments. I looked back at all the posts and i agree with some and some i dont,  i will comment on some that i have seen.

Walter and George make  posts that are a combination of facts , stretching of the truth , others are out right lies and some are very entertaining ( its good to be able to some comic relief in these stressful and hard times). Heh.. i think some are just to bait responses:)

They are big supporters of the Point and there is nothing wrong  with that. Some posts were made by them about The point laying golden eggs and that everything is running like a well oiled machine.The point is running yes but not like a well oiled machine.

That can not be expected after Severstal did everything it seemed to run it in the ground after it did not get its way with the union. They did not supply us with the ores and  that they had. Severstal had to have known we had a high cost per ton of steel because of not having a long term contract on these items but instead made us run on sub standard materials that would injure any plant.

RG comes in and does not have a contract either and has to buy on the Spot market which does not help us in the cost per ton.RG replaces upper management . Are they the best ? that i dont know. We were slow at getting things together but were starting to get things going and along the way had some unfortunate things that set us back and used up cash that was intended to be used to help us move forward .

To be honest it seemed to me that the Point was not changing and that we were stuck in the same old same old.But then i saw a change. i dont know for sure what it was that started it. Maybe the people that Ira put in charge at the Point got Ira thinking their way.

There were people brought in to replace some of the upper management in some areas of the mill. A new steel making chief and a  new BOF general foreman. from what i hear they are close to the plant general manager. some are former AK steel people, so i guess there is a" family and friends" network in management too like there is in the union.

The person  brought in to replace the BOF manager seems to have free hands when it comes to spending money and implements everything he wants to do.The former manager wanted to do alot of things that he did so far and more and they would not let him do that. He was a very good manager and he truly cared about his department and men and had a passion about his job but unfortunately he was not part of "the network" and was replaced.

We are starting to see alot of improvement in our performance.Our Heats per day are on the rise and making Strides in maintaining that rise. All the talk about us being unproductive are not true we can make Heats if given the material to do it.

The caster is improving too and if things keep going in that direction we will be just fine. along the lines of the Point not making a profit that is true to a point. We have gotten profit sharing from all the  companies that owned us.Have we lost money in years? yes just like all the other steel companies in the world.

The Dr. makes alot of posts too supporting the Mingo plant and that is good also. He seems to have alot of knowledge about steel making plants and such , but some of his comments i feel are like Walter and Georges.

He says the point is running out of money it would make sense that they are but to say that he knows and also says that RG is very tight lipped about giving out on formation does not add up. He says that Brazilian pig iron is the only good and profitable pig iron and the Point is wasting their time on it then says that it would be good for the ohio plants 

The Dr. says that Mingo is the way to go but they were in bankruptcy in 2000 came out of it in 2003. unlike the Point we did not get a 250 million dollar loan from the goverment.They used this money from the goverment to build a modern EAF.It has never run properly and is a big disappointment and now sits idle.

These are some of the things that i see. We all are more biased towards the plants we work in. So it seems that the nature of the beast comes out in all of us and we look out for our selves first. Lets be truly honest here  sure it would be great for all the plants to be fully manned and running but are we not more concerned about  our own individual jobs?

We are in the hands of RG and the international and we can only hope that between them good or bad that everyone can have a job make a good living and retire to a good end to our lives. 




 </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yk1t23</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dc9t</id></website><link>http://www.baltimorebrew.com/2012/03/03/some-good-news-sparrows-point-will-restart-an-operation-next-month/</link><postedTime>2012-03-03T17:23:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:45:02+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6p7m</id><link>http://www.baltimorebrew.com/2012/03/03/some-good-news-sparrows-point-will-restart-an-operation-next-month/#comment-480874867</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-03</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>