<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tmtz/update/2012-03-29T09:36:48/7b63dfa0abc840dda8d64cadc78e4888446669becb7298e2e2922cf3b30d9a79</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Wow Anderson Cooper really Reaching for anything to rescue his zero credibility. Showing a video in an effort to say a man had no significant injuries, and then reporting that the very same man was treated my EMT's earlier in the evening.....Anderson are you really so dumb that you dont even realize how stupid that is? Let me spell it out for you.....YOU CONTRADICTED YOURSELF. Bleeding does stop, you do know that right? An EMT's job, in part, is going to be to stop someone's Bleeding and administer first aid.....you DO know that right? 

My new hope in life is that this drags on long enough for me to go to law school, pass the bar, and then take up what will be the biggest defamation suit in US History and put all of you, CNN, FOXNews, NBC CBS ABC....all of you, into chapter 11 bankruptcy. You incompetents in the media don't even have the slightest clue how much of a slam dunk it will be as you dig the single biggest hole I have ever witnessed anyone dig for themselves. Your dishonesty, your blatant bias, your ignorance of reality, your denial of truth, is disgusting. Up until now you have all operated this way with total impunity. If any good can come out of this shooting, it will be that this impunity is brought to an end and you are held responsible for fomenting violence, hatred, and division in this country.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zcxr4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T06:16:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:36:48+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tmtz</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html#comment-479493410</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zgqj5</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>