<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/96402/post/127424377/comment/324987340</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>e_wraith is correct. Ted Kennedy is the one who first saddled SDI with the Star Wars moniker in a derisive speech against the program.  Reagan, in his initial televised speech to the nation about SDI, referenced the idea of an alien intelligence attacking Earth and how quickly we &amp;amp; the Soviet Union would work together to fend Off that threat.  He never mentioned Star Wars. 
 
Not mentioned (an unfortunate omission, I think, given the subject matter) in this essay is the reality that, while we still have yet to achieve complete defense against missile attack, the Soviets believed that we could achieve it to such a degree that they would have to seriously respond to counter it...and they realized they couldn&amp;#039;t afford to do so with their economic system as it was.  This played a role in bringing about our victory (such that it was &amp;amp; is) in the Cold War. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:96402:127424377</id><idPostId>127424377</idPostId><idBlogId>96402</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:96402</id><idBlogId>96402</idBlogId><link>http://www.thespacereview.com</link><displayName>The Space Review: essays and commentary about the final frontier</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.thespacereview.com/article/2052/1</link><displayName>The Space Review: Why we fall for the hype: contextualizing our thought on space warfare</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:34:06.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:96402:127424377:324987340</id><inReplyTo><link>http://www.thespacereview.com/article/2052/1#IDComment324975154</link></inReplyTo><link>http://www.thespacereview.com/article/2052/1#IDComment324987340</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:34:06.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The Space Review: Why we fall for the hype: contextualizing our thought on space warfare by Bob Mahoney</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>fe63cc8f00a3ed99b36805ce62da0dff</idEmailMd5><displayName>Bob Mahoney</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>Bob Mahoney commented on &lt;a href="http://www.thespacereview.com/article/2052/1"&gt;The Space Review: Why we fall for the hype: contextualizing our thought on space warfare&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>