<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw74vz/post/2012-03-30T15:18:18</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Happy Birthday Rob!


Leaving us to ourselves without a FF was a bad Idea. Bad for us , that is. Now we have to share all the sick Storys we stumbled upon. That will be hard to top in the Future, if there will be something like a Future after this FFF-Meltdown.

A new Story from the "sick puppy" that wrote cupcakes, it'S kinda exclusive :D


The Colt's Death

This is the transcription of my audio record of the moment. Please like and share! I'm sure if you don't like it, at least somepony else will! :D*Me, descending the stairs in pitch black, closing the trapdoor behind me*''Aadam? You awake?'' I said. Adam, already awake, replied very nervously, ''Y.. Yes I am.. P-Pinkie''Walking noise is heard as I approach Adam's room, The male pony then says ''I suppose you're ready to put this to an end, right?'', I replied ''I thought today about what we were going to do together tonight..'' He then replied, calming down a little bit, ''Oh... You were starting to plan? What did you have in mind?''Not replying, I turned on the lights, illuminating the torture room filled with the usual carcasses, bone chairs, leather covered tables, and the multiple dried organs hanging on the walls.''I thought about cutting you up upside down!''Adam's eyes widen as he notices my magnificient decor and says ''Nice decor. Normally, I'm not for the blood and gore, but you went all out. And interesting idea.''I then replied, surprised, since he was there for quite a long time by now, ''Haven't you seen it before?''''Not in this much detail.'' He replied,''You spent four days down there, Oh I forgot,'' (I don't remember what I've forgotten at this point lol)Adam interrups me and says ''I was more focused on you than I was the walls.''''Oh, okay, Well, do you like it? I worked hard you know!''''It's very creative.''He said.''Thank you!'' I replied, He then said ''As for what you plan... it sounds quite nice.''I smiled at him at this point, thinking how hard the straps are to hold him that long. I was satisfied of my metal table. He then said''That way, not only can I have the blood rush to my head, I can taste it as it runs down my body.''I then said ''I thought about emptying you from all your blood. Then gut you and....''He replied ''Although, I'd suggest we empty those.. other fluids first.''''Oh, yeah.''. I was kinda surprised that he didn't shat on the floor already.After a brief silence he continued talking,''Wouldn't want to get more than just blood all over the place now would we?''He then started chuckling.Poor him, he didn't know he would piss and shit everywhere anyway lolAt this point, all we do is talk. And I can't guess much of what I did based on an audio record. so I'll identify who talked by writing a P: for me, and a A: for him.P: Well, I do like when victims piss on themselves,but still.You haven't pissed on the floor, I'm surprised.A: Yeah... It comes from my ability to stay at a game for hours on end.That, and having to guard her majesty.Can't keep your eyes from the bedchamber doors for ANYTHING.I then start walking out of the room, going to the toilet, or the water room. Basically it's a room I dedicated for storing water. Since there's no water pipes going in this basement.I then come back with an empty bucket.P: Well you sure got a skill there, I need to go to the bathroom at least one time a day,A: Right. One moment. This might take a minute or two.P: Hold on!A: Okay.P: You're not an unicorn as far as I can see.A: I was one for a little bit.P: I don't think you can simply piss like that in mid air and hit in the bucket.A: True that....P: But I don't want to touch you after passing four days strapped to a metal table..I think.. I think I'll wash you first.No wait. I'll let you take a shit, turn the table a little bit backwards, then turn it forward and let you piss on the floor where it'll flow into the other room.And then I'll wash you.A: Oh! Why, that's rather sporting of you.(I then put the table in a position where Adam can take a shit. I didn't cared much if he accidentally pissed too, the wall is made so it'll all flow into a hole on the ground)Adam shits in the empty bucket on the floor and I then come to remove it. I then turn the table allowing him to piss directly on the floor. Everything worked well and the hole wasn't that filled.A: Tell me.. remember when you thought Zecora was an evil enchantress?P: Huh, that was a long time ago.Why?A: Well, I believe your fear wasn't COMPLETELY unfounded.See, where I come from, there's a culture not unlike the Zebra tribes. From what I've read, some of them indulge in...well...very black magic.Things like living sacrifice and the like.But, I've never met a Zebra Necromancer, so I don't have exact proof.(he then chuckles)In any case, I'm just rambling at this point.(I then remain silent)A:So.. How exactly did you intend to clean me up, anyway.(I then remember staring at Adam, I was silent, basically it wa a complete silence in the room at this point)P: You talk a lot..Ponies used to hate me because I talked a lot.A: It's both a gift and a curse, I'm afraid.P: Should I hate you because you talk a lot?I think I'll cut your tongue. But you might shit and piss everywhere then...A: Well, I tend to have my days when I talk and the days I don't.it  on my mood and what I did during the day.I do have to wonder, Seeing as you.P: I guess when you're standing alone in the dark for four days you must be very excited to talk to somepony...A: Pretty much.( then let out a big sigh.)A: You could've lit up one of the corpses, I could've used my imagination,then.P: You're annoying me. Your body isn't even open yet and you smell like shit.A: Well, can't argue there.P: The blood usually flows to the room on the left where I have the body disposing equipment.It falls in a hole dug into the concrete floor.A:Ah. That's cool,Blood must make a great condiment for pegasus wings...P: ... But I'll have to remove all the water I've used to clean you before starting to actually torture you.And no, blood isn't that good in that hole. If I want a sample I'll have to take it now. Hence the reason I wanted to turn you upside down and empty you out of all your blood.A:Like any doctor would.(I have no idea why he said a such random thing, maybe that's because he didn't ate for a long time)I stay quiet for a little bit, then I just say ''watever''. (lol)A: So.. Have you ever eaten pegasus wings before?I then go outside the room and come back with a bucket filled this time with water. Dragging it on the floor since it's heavy.P: Smoked pegasus wings.I used the feathers for decoration in the kitchen.Anyway.I wish I had Cold water.but we don't have any water source down there.A: shame, that.I then lift the water bucket into the air and approach Adam who is back in a horizontal position.P: time to take a shower.Adam shuts his eyes and I drop the water on his coat. Trying to cover the entire body."There we are" he exclaims.I then throw the bucket on his face, hurting him and spilling the rest of the water everywhere. The bucket  on his forehead and he started Bleeding a little bit.In a sarcastic way, I said: "Oops I'm sorry."He winced, and then expressed his disagreement by letting out a slight hum.P: It slipped out of my hooves.A: It happens to us all.I then smiled at him and walked outside. A: I think I'm starting to go a little loopy.I start talking loudly from another room which was actually the body disposal room, where the water  drains to,P: I hope your wet coat won't kill you by hypothermia!A: That would sure suck, huh.The sound of water flow is heard in the distance and I yell from the other room trying to be heard: You get pretty Cold when you lose a lot of blood!!A: I  hear that in movies!Just before the Bleeding person keels over!Water sound stops and I walk back into the torture room, approaching adam on his left, and I start turning the wheel on the metal table and it goes vertically.P: I'll put you into a vertical position, so you'll be able to see what I'm doing.A: As you wish, pinkie.The table stops at about 10 degrees backwards. Almost vertically. I then walk in front of him."The thing is thatm I can't really put you upside down.."A: Because it doesn't go that far, right?P: Well, yes it does, but you'll face on the other side.And there's not much space behind you.A: Ah. THat would be a little bit of a hassle.P: Just enough (space) to see your sexy wings flopping nervously. ahah!It would be a shame if something bad happens to it!Won't you think!Hopefully you'll never break a wing by an accident,I then walk on the left of him, still looking at his eyes,A: Oh, that never happened.P: Hopefully, somepony else won't do a mistake, that would break one!A mistake like.. tripping on one of them?A: hm...I then voluntarily push myself on the back of the chair, squeezing one of his wing into an awkward position. Giving him a lot of pain but doesn't really damage the bone structure.I then stand back on my four hooves and walk in fron of him to see his face.On the audio record we can hear a ''Ah.. ahh..!" Like if he was sexually excited. This pissed me  a little bit. But I should've expected this reaction since he was dumb enough to come and surrender at me.Anyway. I still said ''Did that hurt? I'm sorry." Even though I didn't had the desired reaction.P:That would be bad if.. Some saw suddenly fell on your wing!That stupid fuck smiled at me like if it was some kind of bondage or something. And he said ''Bring it Pinkie.'' Yeah, bring it, Did he really expected it to be like the ultimate bondage thrill ever? I think he fantasised too much about it to the point where he forgot what death meant.Anyway.I then walk behing him and take a metal tool which was probably the saw. And I put it on the base of his left wing. He then explaims''Mmm...Cold steel..''P: Oh mister! A hacksaw fell on your wing! She has a phobia of feathers!She's scared! Calm down miss hacksaw! Calm down! I then start sawing at an irregular rhythm, he started screaming at last and when I started cutting his veins, blood sprayed everywhere as I keep sawing.I keep trying to reason miss hacksaw and tell her: "Calm down! You're hurting him!"I continue sawing more and more violently.His breath intensifies and his wing then falls on the ground. Cut entirely from his body.I then reproach miss hacksaw and yell over Adam's first screams:"OOOOH LOOK A T WHAT YOU'VE DONE! BAD SAW!BAD SAW!"He then stops screaming and looks at his wing on the ground, grunting and says"Ms saw, you have some 'splainin' to do."I then slowly walk in front of Adam. I remember my coat being full of blood as well as my hair. My smile widening as I turn in front of Adam's face.I then said "I think, miss saw doesn't like the way you're talking to her."I then put the hack saw's blade into adam's mouth.He looks at me, smiling back. I guess he was an autassassinophiliac.I then quickly say to Adam, "She wants you to stop whining."He chuckles and says with difficulty: "Your humor is infectious..."I then start sawing his lower teeth, blood is filling his mouth and he Coughs violently, being drown in his own blood. I continue sawing trough his lower jaw, giving a sad expression on his face. Halfway down, I stop sawing. removing the saw from his mouth, a cute tongue comes out too, attached to the saw blade.P: you seem to like it!He continues Coughing on his own blood.P: But i hate your enthusiasm.I then stab adam with the saw into his right temple. Then start sawing trough his skull. Piercing his eyeball. White liquid leaks into Adam's face and enters into his mouth because of the earlier jaw cut.As I was sawing, he started swallowing his own blood. Having cut halfway his eyeball, I then pull it out and walk backwards. looking at him.P:You look charming!Almost.P:Now..His right eye closed, he then starts peeing on the floor seconds after I pulled out the blade from his skull.P: Oooh look at you! Didn't mummy tell you to go to the bathroom for those kind of things?!He then shudders as his bladder empties once again.I walk back avoiding the pee stream of the male pony.P: You're disgusting!You shall be punished for this!His bladder finally emptied, I go out into the water/bathroom and come back with a bucket of water. Dropping it all over the floor where Adam previously peed."That should clean the mess" I said,"Do you often salt your food?"Adam, weakly nods as his head shakes from the earlier trauma.I then tilt my head on the right, looking at his face in curiosity,"Huh, would you like to be salted?""You seem to like pain."He then lets out a moan. probably in agreement. Let's just say.. it's not the kind of reaction I wanted."Let's see if your suicidal brain will like the Burning sensation of salt on your fresh wounds."I then go out of the room and into my kitchen on the left, and comes back with a plate of salt."I'll just.. widen your sad face a little bit.""I don't think this will widen your cut, but you might feel more pain.""That may make you look more.. terrified."I then pu the plate of salt on a leather covered table next to me, and go on the left of Adam. Turning the wheel counter-clockwise, putting the table on a horizontal position.I remember at this point, the smell of shit suddenly filled the room. Took me a little while to realised he shat on the floor."DAMMIT!!""You should learn some manners!"He continues shitting on the floor as I run on another room. Then come back with a small spade and pute the shit into one of the empty buckets.I then approach his face, he had an expression of apology, and I says with a low voice,"You look like a scary monster now ahah, with your leaking eye, your sawed face.."He chuckled again.He finally stops shitting everywhere and I struggle to put all the shit into the bucket. Running to another room, I then fill the shit bucket with some liquid, then go to another room, coming back with a water bucket that I spill on the floor."I already got baking soda scattered in the room, hopefully that will be enough."I then throw the bucket a Adam but miss it. "What was I going to do.."Noticing the plate of salt, it comes back into my mind. "Oh yeah! I was about to Burn you!""I wonder..."Taking the salt on the table and approaching adam,"If you were to be rescued at this point, would you survive?"His last eye's pupil shrinks when he hears that. Did he really thought I'd let him go like that? AHAH"Probably, but you would surely be scarred forever."I suddenly drop the salt on the table and take a metal knife next to it.Walking in front of Adam, I then  the big knife at his genitals."That  annoyed me."I then rapidly cut his genitals and blood suddenly sprays everywhere."YAY A FOUNTAIN!"Adam then lets out a big roar of pain which amuses me very much. Very much.I then jump everywhere around, skipping in happiness but then trips on a chair and falls on the ground."OW!""I walked on blood.."I then try to stand up on the slippery blood puddle. My mane was now soaked with blood. Dripping intensely. "Let's put some salt on this messed up face now."Walking with my dripping mane (the sound is constantly heard in the audio record) I then take the salt plate and hovers it over adam's face. Trying to scare him. "That would be a shame if some salt would from on your face!"His eye widens as he sees what is about to come. I am very pleased. Very much.Quickly, I turn the plate upside down and all the salt drops on his face.He immediately starts screaming in intense pain, almost having spasms. The salt turns red on his face and melts and enters in all into his wounds.I then drop the plate on the ground breaking it and start jumping, giggling, skipping all over the place, screaming in extasy, letting out a screech in this extasy and then laughs uncontrollably,"AAAAAAAAAHAHAHAHAHH!" "THIS IS WHAT I WAS LOOKING FOR!!"Calming down a little bit, I look back at his face, expecting to fall in extasy again, his right eye was crying and I was still laughing,But suddenly, Adam starts laughing. (Yes, that trolling fuck started laughing,) I walked backwards, in strong disappointment, I then starts growling very violently and starts "YOU WERE NOT SUPPOSED TO LAAAUGH!"I then take a metal object (seemingly heavy by the sound) on the tool's table behind Adam and I start hitting his torso and stomach randomly. He starts grunting in pain again, slowly his chuckle fades away.Blood spills everywhere as adam finally realises the the heavy object is actually an .I violently and randomly continue to him Adam's body with the  growling in anger. Then starting to aim at the lower stomach.Adam begins to deathly silent. His look on his face showed that he finally surrendered. (Acceptance. The last step of the five stages of grief.)I continue cutting Adam's stomach until I start feeling his spine. I then stop for a second and start cutting the spine. Coming back in extasy, I "AHAHAHAHAH! I LOVE THIS!I LOVE THIS!"His body then separates in two."now, CRAWL!""CRAWL!"I then start aiming at his wrists which were the only thing holding him on the table, cutting them both.Now free, Adam fell on the ground. I then drag adam by the mane and throw him in the middle of the room where I usually were standing to talk to him."CRAWL!""AHAHAHAHAHAH!!"Skipping in Joy, jumping around adam who aimlessly crawls on the floor, I then stop jumping in front of him. He then crawled to me, taking his last desperate breaths of air to grasp pinkie in a short-lived, but tender, and kind embrace, before falling supine as his body gave way to the snapping of it's mortal coil.I then hug his carcass and put my right hoof on his heart. Only to feel it slowly stop.His heart, slows to a stop, the brightness of his eyes fading, a voice is heard, separate of the body."Farewell...for now, at least...I hope that we meet on better terms...someday..."Startled, I forgot that Adam wasn't actually a real pony but another kind of animal inside a pony. Hence his relationships with the princess and such. I'm aimlessly looking around in fear, noticing nothing around, I concluded this wasn't from a living entity.I then lay back on Adam's body to feel the death.The voice then said "Don't be scared, Pinkie...it's only me...Adam...I felt I should say goodbye...""Okay.. good bye.." I calmly replied." At least you died with a happy pony.."I hen let out a very long sigh, and my smile slowly fades away as his body becomes increasingly Cold.The ghost then says "At least I did...yeah...oh...I see it...the light...I think it's Heaven...it's...real..."I replied: "No.. Nothing's after death."His voice faded at that point, the final words echoing in the room for half a minute, if not longer, all recorded by the recorder.I said "Probably just the spell that made you turn into a spirit before dying..."Trying not to listen to the painful echoing voice, U hug the dead carcass trying to somehow Heat it up a little bit."Perhaps...the pale horse may meet me.........................................................................................." said the spirit of Adam.I then close my eyes and sadness grows in my face. "It's over now.." I said. "My twenty fourth victim.."Remaining silent, I lay over the dead body.The End.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/676dmc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/hjt8</id></website><link>http://www.toplessrobot.com/2012/03/fan_fiction_friday_takes_a_holiday.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:01:42+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:18:18+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw74vz</id><link>http://www.toplessrobot.com/2012/03/fan_fiction_friday_takes_a_holiday.php#comment-481093934</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ec7o7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>