<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrdbv/post/2012-03-30T12:04:02</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwdjl3</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> The sign of progress I wished to see this season was not us winning the league but  us being in a position of mounting a serious challenge for a CL Spot. Sadly that has not materialized and hence this season is yet another that goes down as a disappointment. 

Yes, you are correct when you say that my use of the word "indictment" is a reflection of my feelings. This season has been a disappointment not just in terms of our league position but also in other respects. 

This season was a glorious opportunity for us to step-up to the plate and grab a CL Spot with Chelsea and Arsenal stumbling. Yet we were unable to do so. What most people fail to recall is that we were up there at the start of the year. This calendar year though has been disastrous. What I hold against the management team, even more than their useless signings, is the seeming inability to turn things around. We often seem to lack any sort of Plan B, no idea of what to do when things are not working or when the opposition are just plain packing the box. 

This inability/ deficit in our plans is evident even in context of the whole season Every donkey knows that we're having trouble scoring goals, that Suarez is not clinical in front of goal. Yet we did not make any effort to either give Carroll a decently long run alongside Suarez or look to sign another striker in January Everyone has been saying all season long that we need a defensive midfielder what with Lucas being injured. Yet we did not look into the market in January but continue to play Spearing or Adam in that position. Spearing is a hard-worker, not yet on the level required to be a starter for Liverpool but a good squad player nonetheless. The less one speaks of Adam as a DM the better.

I'm happy that we won the Carling Cup but it's a mere Band-aid over a stab wound in terms of my expectations ofLiverpool F.C. I truly hope that you are right in saying that we are on the right path. It's just that I fear we've missed a trick in leaving things for the summer window. Nobody can deny that we need some quality new players - at the very least a world-class striker (We've got Suarez, Carroll -who hopefully will come good and Bellamy - whose knees prevent him from being a regular starter; Kuyt is finished- he has been a valiant servant to the club but sadly he's just not sutting it anymore). I find myself hard-pressed though to think of one who we have a realistic chance of signing with all 5 teams in the current top 5 in the league are looking to sign strikers. Similar is the case with defensive-mids or centre-backs. All I can do as a fan is sit and pray with all my heart that we manage to land most if not all of our summer targets. My bloody head though call it a very long shot.....</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rihxh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dxs5</id></website><link>http://www.thisisanfield.com/2012/03/give-kenny-just-a-little-more-time/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T11:38:58+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:04:02+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrdbv</id><link>http://www.thisisanfield.com/2012/03/give-kenny-just-a-little-more-time/#comment-480894568</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>