<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tdsh/update/2012-03-29T09:39:29/94ed84d385b89f31cbe2954cf4bb363800896ce8ecb643c27f1d034cd6079a73</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msbqcy</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> 1. "contaminated with "deadly" e.coli..."
- It is an established medical fact that some serotypes of E. coli can cause serious food poisoning in humans, and food poisoning can be fatal. Look it up, because stating that it is "deadly" does not help.

2.  "ALGAE has been there for decades already. Nature itself causes them, and if any contamination happened, it is not the cause of Algae only."
- And you, of course, know the species of algae that has been there for decades, right? Because while it is true that algae, in general, are a regular sight in healthy marine ecosystems, some species are indicators of declining water quality. Green hair algae, in particular, are the result of an excess of available nutrients in the water, particular phosphates, nitrates, iron and potassium. And guess what? These are the exact same nutrients that are found in abundance in human poop! Wanna know what else is found in human poop?? E. coli!!
- While you are correct to say that the algae are not the cause of Diarrhea, they are in fact indicators that the conditions required to sustain Diarrhea-causing organisms are present. Thus, as long as these algae are able to thrive in the waters of Boracay, you can be sure that E. coli is present and thriving as well.

3. "... but please also take notice that this is an isolated case, which, NO SCIENTIFIC, NOR APPROVED basis."
- Did you miss the part where the doctor tells the article writer that it's "probably, E Coli. We get that all the time with people coming back from Boracay"?? Are you saying that "people coming back from Boracay" signifies an isolated case, or that this doctor from St. Luke's is a quack practicing without a license? Really??

4. "As an enthusiast of Boracay and as a responsible Filipino, why don't we just work hand in hand doing things for the better, and not for the destruction of our tourism industry."
- So being a "responsible Filipino" means we sweep this issue under the rug, am I right? Let's pretend that we don't know what is contaminating Boracay's waters, instead of committing to actions to get the water cleaned up, correct?

If you truly wished for the long-term success of the tourism industry in the Philippines, you should be taking part in the effort to get the responsible authorities to  properly and Act now, instead of implying that the article writer is spreading falsehoods in a smear campaign aimed at Boracay. Because all you are doing right now amounts to shooting the messenger, and that has never helped anyone, ever.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66uaki</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/llp5</id></website><link>http://chuvaness.com/7439/kids-moms/e-coli-more-fun-in-boracay/</link><postedTime>2012-03-24T06:34:33+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:39:29+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tdsh</id><link>http://chuvaness.com/7439/kids-moms/e-coli-more-fun-in-boracay/#comment-479495245</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z66ye</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>