<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3biy5/update/2012-03-29T14:52:21/bb5b6f7c86325d9ad28f73730a03e1175d1e8afad862d5b8f23cd81a8241b091</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I am afraid that once again the GOP establishment, in the tank from the beginning for Romney has dealt this nation a bad deck of cards.  Romney, is not presidential - Romney WANTS the presidency but can he take the reins of a country now is dire circumstances from every direction due to the liberal Usurper in the WH?  Stop and think - who else has the real knowledge of getting a government back on track?  Gingrich does.  Who else can knock Obama Off the stage in a debate - please don't say Ronney or even Santorum.  Gingrich is the only one who has spelled out exactly what and when he would do it - he has a real plan.  

Our Constitution says "WE THE PEOPLE" - Congress works for us (supposedly but they have overstepped and in some cases ignored us) - the GOP and the Democrat party are trying to tell us who to vote for...If I have too, I will hold my nose and not Vomit and go to the polls and cast a vote for Romney - as I did McCain (I actually voted for Sarah).  As a note:  If Sarah Palin were president you would see a huge exit of Congress - remember members of both parties in Alaska are now wearing Orange jumpsuits - maybe that's why the Dems fear her so much....think?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hpczx</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zmzu</id></website><link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2012/mar/28/newt-no-deal-romney-end-campaign/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T20:12:59+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:52:21+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3biy5</id><link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2012/mar/28/newt-no-deal-romney-end-campaign/#comment-479756200</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/epa72</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>