<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrnue/update/2012-03-30T12:18:29/cb9a113e1cd0dce9025784cd38cb3fc180585bd06bebddb12049597df2e28ad6</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Legally, Zimmerman following Martin is irrelevant to the defense of Martin.... actually It's REALLY good people keep mentioning it even Martin's lawyers and supporters....

 it helps Zimmerman's case tremendously! . Why? Because if Martin left the area supposedly because he felt threatened by Zimmerman watching him (that's what the girlfriends says).If Zimmerman "lost" Martin as is evident on the 911 tape... then Zimmerman was no longer a threat to Martin. When Zimmerman lost Martin he began heading back to his truck. Tapes show that, witnesses account that, and the fact Martin was dead close to the truck provides evidence that Martin did indeed loop around the units in order  to head back toward Zimmerman. 

What was Martin's intentions? We know it wasn't to go home. 
 In fact the complex map provides a clearer picture. Martin did not have to loop back around to get home. In fact he was walking in the proper direction when he left the area where Zimmerman last Spotted him, and he would have made it home even before the police arrived if had contiuned to walk. 

911 Tape: 

At 2:08, Trayvon starts running. Six seconds later, we hear Zimmerman leave his truck to see where he went.While Trayvon runs south towards Brandy Green’s townhouse, Zimmerman continues east, and remains on the line with the 911 dispatcher.At a slow jogging pace, Trayvon is estimated to have arrived back at Brandy Green’s townhouse at around 2:40 on the 911 call.Trayvon may have gone inside the townhouse, but it seems more likely that he remained outside to see if Zimmerman was still following him and just continued talking to his girlfriend over the next few minutes.After a few minutes, Trayvon seems to have walked north, back up the sidewalk to confront Zimmerman about why he was followed.George Zimmerman leaves his truck at 2:14 and Reaches Retreat View Circle just over thirty seconds later at 2:45.He agrees to stop pursuit and after the 911 call is complete, Zimmerman begins to head back to his truck to meet the police. At this point, he claims he was confronted by Trayvon, and walks a few steps down the sidewalk south to respond to him.As we can see, it appears unlikely that Zimmerman ever “chased down” Martin. Zimmerman only pursued long enough to maintain visual contact to see what direction Trayvon was going.Zimmerman traveled his entire route in around 30 seconds, he only went a very short distance and did so specifically to tell the 911 dispatcher where Trayvon had gone.It wasn’t until a minute later that their altercation took place, when Martin apparently doubled back to confront Zimmerman.this is what the Grand Jury is looking @ </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z3b9t</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T07:25:56+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:18:29+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrnue</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html#comment-480910146</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h5rxy</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>