<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkotq8/post/2012-03-26T15:26:20</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk94tb</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/twm9</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> Sounds like you have a lot of pent up anger along with a lot of misconceptions.

The Jews, more than anyone, deserve a state as we have seen what happens to them when they live at the whim of other nations, be they Muslim, christian, Arab or European.  

"Palestinian" like it or not is a recent national identity.  Prior to the first half of the 20th century, they considered themselves Southern Syrians or simply Arabs under Ottoman Rule.   And, contrary to your "indigenous" belief on the origins of the Palestinians....they are composed of Arabs who migrated from the surrounding Arab countries.  

For example, the Ottomans invited the Zuabian tribe to move into Palestine in the late 1800s.  They also had thousands of kurds and circassians move into the territory of Palestine.  Over 35,000 Syrian Houranian Arabs moved into Palestine then as well.  Even the Palestinian national hero, "Izz e din al Qassam" of whom Hamas' military wing and rockets are named for, was born in Syria.  

Likewise under British rule, thousands of Arabs migrated into Palestine from Egypt, Syria, Jordan, Saudi Arabia, etc.  The numbers were never documented.  Winston ChurchilL, said in May 22, 1939 that the Arab immigration to 
Palestine during the British Mandate was so large that their numbers 
grew in such proportion that even if all Jews immigrated to Palestine 
they could not  that 
number.  In fact, following the formation of the state of Israel, the UN created a special definition of what constitute a Palestinian refugee....anyone who lived in the land for TWO years prior to the war (1946-1948).  If the Palestinians really were such indigenous people, why the "two year" standard?  They should be able to prove centuries of habitation in the land.....Two years is hardly an ancient claim.


The presence of the Jews in the Holy Land goes back more than 3000 
years. In addition to the continuous residence of the Jews in the Holy 
Land throughout recorded history, the repeated genocides, enslavements, 
expulsions, and exiles to which they have been subjected prior to, and 
even after, the formation of the State of Israel, which thinned their 
numbers time and again, have never caused exiled or escaped diasporan 
Jews to forget their history, or to stop considering the Holy Land -- 
where the remains of their forefathers are buried -- as their sacred 
land. The land of Israel (Eretz Y'Isroel) and the city of Jerusalem 
(Y'Rushaloyim) are central to Jewish culture and religion in the 
Diaspora, and  have been. Almost every part of Jewish liturgy 
contains references to the Holy Land and to the Jews' being there and 
returning there.  There are holidays which were celebrated in the middle
 ages in the Cold steppes of Russia which were centered around fruits 
and growing seasons that existed only in The Holy Land. Synagogues in 
the Diaspora are constructed so that worshippers facing the ark, or 
cabinet, in which the Torah is kept, are facing  in the direction of 
Jerusalem.


Now, according to you:
"What Israel has done and continues to do is more than enough to 
de-legitimize it. No other nation comes close ti its record of violating
 or ignoring UN resolutions.

Too bad for you, UN resolutions do not determine the rightness or wrongness of a nation.  The UN has become a forum for the barbarians.  Notice the inaction on Syria where over 7,000 were slaughtered in about a year.  There were hundreds of more resolutions against Israel during the second intifada than against Sudan during the Darfur crisis.  In the Second Intifada approximately 5,000 Israelis and Palestinians died over a 9 year period.   In Darfur 330,000 people died in 2003-2009.  Yes, the UN gave more condemnation to Israel where 1,053 Israelis died and 4,700 Palestinians died in an 8 year period vs Sudan, where 330,000 civilians died in a 6 year period.  As I said earlier, the UN is an asylum run by the inmates.  UN actions neither legitimize nor legitimize a nation.  Another example: even during the Syrian uprising UNESCO invited syria to two human rights board positions.  Truly insane.  



Its occupation of the West Bank and 
arrogant declaration that it owns Jerusalem are actually giant poison 
pills. As it's been said, who the gods would destroy, they first make 
mad. "

Israel claiming that it owns Jerusalem is "arrogant?"  The Jews' connection to Jerusalem predates any other claims by muslims or christians or especially Arabs.  Over 3,000 years of Jewish history is connected to Jerusalem.  In the Jewish Bible,
Jerusalem has many names: Salem (Shalem), Moriah, Jebuse (Yevuse),
Jerusalem
(Yerushalayim), and Zion (Tziyon). The
most common term for the city, Yerushalayim, is mentioned
349 times in the Jewish Bible, while Tziyon is mentioned
an additional 108 times.


Muslims' claim to Jerusalem only dates to around the 7th Century.  When Omar first visited the ruined Temple
mount, after he conquered Jerusalem,  he deliberately prayed south of the ruins of the Temple, toward
Mecca, so that no one should think he was praying in the same direction
as the Jews. 
      The holiest book of Islam
is the Koran, which according to Moslem tradition contains the
teachings of Mohammed. Unlike the Jewish Bible which contains hundreds
of references to Jerusalem, the word "Jerusalem" appears nowhere in the
Koran. All that appears is "al aqsa" which means "the farthest" and has, for political reasons, been used to describe Jerusalem as a consolidation-empire building measure. 

And to talk about Arrogant.....the Muslims built a Mosque over the Jews' most holy site, the temple mount.  Can you imagine what would happen if Jews or Christians built a church or Synagogue over the Kabba in Mecca?  Jews and Christians cannot even enter the city limits of Mecca, let alone pray there or dare I even consider bring in church or synagogue.  Talk about arrogance.  And if you visit the temple mount today, Jews and Christians cannot bring any of their holy items near the mosque or on the mount, pray there, or display their own religious signs....on orders by the Muslim Waqf, so as not to "antagonize" the so easily offended Arabs there.  


As for the Bernadotte assassination...it was done by a faction (Lehi) which was totally disbanded and absorbed into the government.  It was done after Bernadotte was proposing a plan that would favor the Arabs.  Now tell me, if the Jews could absorb and disband Lehi, why hasn't the PA absorbed or disbanded Hamas, Palestinian Islamic Jihad, or the PRC?  

According to you:

"The idea that a "people" as defined by some bogus 
racial-religious-ethnic yardstick can  be the basis of nationhood is an 
idea that should be by now, and especially  after WWII  -- 
thoroughly discredited.  But it lives on in nuclear-armed Israel."

Well, if that is true, it certainly lives on with the Palestinians, a totally invented people who never had an independent religion, language, state, nation, culture of their own.  The Palestinians are no different from Jordanians and in fact share the same tribal ties (families are connected east and west of the Jordan river).  


"When my country decided it wanted large swatches of Mexico, our leaders 
declared this was the natural destiny of the superior Anglo-Saxon race. 
To our disgrace, Hitler admired the way we crushed 
 the indigenous Indian population and smashed our racal "inferiors."  We
 seem to have mostly given up this kind of putrid thinking, but we 
finance it in Israel. "

Wow bravo for the exaggeration and Polemics.  First, the US finances plenty of other countries that you seem to have no problem with - Egypt, the Palestinians, Colombia, and Saudi Arabia (which represses its Shiite minority).  Second, your knowledge of US history is lacking.  The Mexican-American war was not based on "US manifest destiny."  Texas was an independent republic in 1936.   It was recognized as independent by both Britain and France.  About ten years later Texas joined the United States - and clashes began to ensue to to Raids and border clashes and an undefined/un-agreed upon border.  

Israel was attacked in 1948 by the Palestinians, Jordanians, Egyptians, , Lebanese, and Iraqis with forces from Sudan, Saudi Arabia, and elsewhere joining in.  Had the Palestinians not started the war and rejected the partition plan they would have had a state.  There a was no "manifest destiny" nor desire by the Israelis to "smash racial inferiors" - a joke of a claim - over 50% of Israel is composed of Arab Jews (racially Arab).  Israel lost over 1% of its population in that war - proportional higher than any amount the US has ever lost in any war it ever fought.  It almost didn't survive. At the begining of the war it had 3 scrap tanks and no fighter planes, while facing the Egyptian, Jordanian, Syrian, Lebanese, and Iraqi armies all with modern arms Britian and France (including tanks, artillery, and fighter planes).   Hardly a great position to be in to do some "manifest destiny" mission.  


What is most troubling is your double standard.  Both on Jewish nationhood and your desire to criticize Israel for things the Arabs, the US, and other nations have done on a much larger scale...even and often recently.  

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6633si</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/eyjq</id></website><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/national/archive/2012/03/sullivan-j-street-tsa-fallows-rahm-islam-passover-etc/254974/</link><postedTime>2012-03-24T19:24:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T19:26:20+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkotq8</id><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/national/archive/2012/03/sullivan-j-street-tsa-fallows-rahm-islam-passover-etc/254974/#comment-476660414</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zgx5y</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>