<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkzh5b/update/2012-03-25T16:10:20/e9109380f10e0e16a358bdb5dd77fe9433efc52ffde3b62acf567f79b6c14ecb</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>So far, commenters seem to think we all do a good job of accommodation. I'd argue that maybe we do on the small scale, in some places, but not  so much when it comes to larger gatherings.

I'm mother to two special needs children. We have never taken them to a major festival; I've been to one local festival in the time I've been a parent, and only went for the day, even though I was presenting. We've been to Pagan Pride, but being outdoors in a park, it's challenging for us in many ways, and we haven't yet gone and stayed all day.

My son is going to be 4 this summer, and while most of his physical issues are  (to the point that while he's in physical therapy, he's clearly no longer physically disabled), he's non-verbal, and we use sign language a lot with him.  None of our local events advertise sign language interpreting, and most have few kid-friendly events anyway.

My daughter will be a year old later this spring, and she is on the same path my son was at her age - fed via feeding tube, breathing through a tracheostomy, with the help of a ventilator and oxygen.

We travel by stroller (because getting a wheel chair for an infant is about impossible and it would be outgrown before insurance would pay for another). We travel with 100+ pounds of gear for her alone.  Sure, there are strollers meant for -road use, but not ones meant for
  road that will also contain all of the equipment she needs with 
her. In most indoor venues, merchant rooms have narrow aisles - we'd be ok if the room was pretty empty of customers, but during crowded times, we'd never manage our double stroller. Even some workshop and presentation room setups aren't really wheel chair or stroller friendly - chairs go from the front row to the back, wall to wall with an aisle on the wall and in the middle....so you'd have to move chairs to have someplace to be.

We're instructed to be 10 feet from an open flame due to oxygen; neither of my kids tolerates incense well due to their breathing issues. We don't do outdoors in Cold weather, and we have to be cautious about crowded places during Cold and Flu season anyway.

We have a 6 hour  pack for her ventilator, and about the same amount of Battery for our portable oxygen concentrator (otherwise we're carrying 2-3 oxygen tanks for a day trip). Longer than that, and we *need* electricity. Camping is out of the question. Hotel rooms aren't even really set up for this sort of thing - there's just not space in a typical room for all this gear on top of the typical stuff needed for a family of 4.

And all that says nothing of the fact that my daughter's care (like my son's before her) is complicated enough to require nurses to help care for her much of the week and to stay awake with her all night...but frankly, none of our nurses would be comfortable attending a Pagan event, given their religious leanings, so that's not even an option.


For more insight, besides Staff of Asclepius, I'd also suggest reading http://deafpagancrossroads.com/ - Ocean talks about her difficulties in getting interpreters at various large Pagan events, among other things. You'd think it'd be a no-brainer, but it's far more challenging than it should be.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r77me</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lpw5</id></website><link>http://www.patheos.com/blogs/pantheon/2012/03/is-paganism-blind-to-the-disabled/</link><postedTime>2012-03-25T18:16:26+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-25T20:10:20+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkzh5b</id><link>http://www.patheos.com/blogs/pantheon/2012/03/is-paganism-blind-to-the-disabled/#comment-476001526</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/drmng</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>