<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3o9tk/post/2012-03-29T19:40:23</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I was more comfortable coming out to my friends than to my parents. I suppose my mom knew before we lost her to cancer over 9 years ago.

Coming out to my father, though, was.... interesting, since he's 55 years my senior.

in 2008 I started dating a guy, and we'd spend every Wednesday afternoon (my day  in the middle of the week) curled up in my bedroom, watching television or playing video games. Dad would wander past on his way to the kitchen, look in, say hello, and continue on his way, paying absolutely no attention to how entwined our legs or bodies were.

Three months into the relationship I started having seriously bad Nausea. Like, dry-heave in the morning bad (sorry, but this is key to the story). Went to my doctor. Talked to him. Told him about my relationship and about how I had yet to come out to my father. His advice - talk with my dad, since it was probably stress making me ill.

Came home. Told dad that -guy's name- was my boyfriend. His response was, "I had many boyfriends when I was your age." To which I responded, "No, dad, he's my boyfriend-boyfriend. We're dating."

Dad's reaction was what I consider to be super fantastic. When I told him that was why I went to see the doctor, he said he thought I went to the doc because of a heart condition (those tend to run in our family. Oh Joy). I did a comedic death scene, and we've been cool with it since. He doesn't care that his only son is gay.

Now my sister, on the other hand.... um... yeah, haven't told her yet, since we're not exactly close (she lives on the opposite side of the country).

The only time I met with resistance was when I told one of my very religious girlfriends. She told me that it wasn't right, and that she would pray for me. I straight out told her that she needs to stop that, or we couldn't be friends. We agreed, from that point, never to talk politics, or religion, and to go guy-watching from time to time.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66ul2n</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/772v</id></website><link>http://webcomics.yaoi911.com/archive/artifice-page-87/</link><postedTime>2012-03-24T07:02:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T23:40:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3o9tk</id><link>http://webcomics.yaoi911.com/archive/artifice-page-87/#comment-480031267</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzxtj</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>