<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ny14/update/2012-03-29T12:40:36/08edb9ca1d9524c6cdf1daf5dddf632b577aa453963a9b4843afe384dee90117</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34hil</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/y0rgu</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>"the people that end up in senior civil service jobs and the cabinet in 
their 30s are quite obviously the people that who focused 100% on 
getting there from the age of about 16 and that fact makes them almost 
certainly the people that we don't want there. They haven't matured 
since they were in their mid-teens."

I'll make myself unpopular here and say that IME is untrue - the whole civil service is full of people who were 40yrs old teenagers.

It's the most risk-averse, arse-covering, don't draw attention to yourself group I've ever worked with.

To be a tall poppy with any individuality requires enormous office politics skills - 95% get killed Off at the first level of mgt if they step outside the consensus.

It's desperately depressing as many are very clever and hard-working - but spend their time writing incomprehensible wibble policy papers in Whitehall's own private language [I can sound more in-crowd than you], reports justifying why things can't change [that's safe] or dressing up the Bleeding obvious in 7000 words [to make themselves look cleverer than their deskmates].

That's what happens when thousands of people have nothing but bureaucracy to direct their lives.

It's immensely depressing and when politicians are sucked into the same mindset - they are doomed to failure.

I had to LEARN a whole new language/culture when I went from the private sector to the  public - and we joke about the US/UK being separated by a common language...</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z64rh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/xps8</id></website><link>http://www7.politicalbetting.com/index.php/archives/2012/03/29/marf-the-thick-of-it-continues/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T12:00:19+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:40:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ny14</id><link>http://www7.politicalbetting.com/index.php/archives/2012/03/29/marf-the-thick-of-it-continues/#comment-479636226</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6aw8u</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>