<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3bk59/post/2012-03-29T14:53:23</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Spot on!

If - when - the individual mandate is struck down by SCOTUS, it will be a self-inflicted wound for the President.  He was so intent on finding "bipartisan compromise" with the GOP - and so afraid of being demonized as a "tax and spend liberal" - that he took single-payer Off the table before the health care debate even started; and then promptly caved-in on the "public option."

Instead, he bent over, and accepted the "individual mandate" (an idea that the GOP created in 1993 in response to the "employer mandate" contained in "HillaryCare", and championed by the GOP right up until 2009), naively thinking that the Republicans would be accept the olive branch that he was offering.

A robust public option  - "Medicare, Part E" - Medicare for everyone who wanted it - would have passed constitutional muster.  

That was the type of REAL CHANGE that I had HOPED for back in 2008.  

Instead, we got this GOP-lite bill - the ACA - which is really a give-away to the insurance industry, and, which will almost assuredly be struck down by the truly radical Republican majority on the Supreme Court.  It was all so very predictable.

The only silver-lining that might come out of this dark cloud, will be if, after the ACA is overturned, the American People - who truly do want, and NEED, health care reform - will demand the REAL CHANGE that the President should have fought for in the first place.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zzmng</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tsjl</id></website><link>http://truth-out.org/opinion/item/8188-the-supreme-courts-five-hypocrites</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:59:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:53:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3bk59</id><link>http://truth-out.org/opinion/item/8188-the-supreme-courts-five-hypocrites#comment-479757338</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rcq2o</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>