<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msgeag/update/2012-03-27T03:23:06/b526ff6dda4476ec04ed2de3e62088e91aa928e4f4a53dcf3fc1646dc2e40ea4</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>A typical bureaucratic commentary.All GREY !! The company is Bleeding, incurring daily operating losses, and yet to talk of natural retirement timeline of 5 years for reduction of 7500 employees is RIDICULOUS.Manpower is huge, wagebill is huge &amp; yet the CMD is waiting under the banana tree for it to fall in 5 years before he eats it. This is the classic difference between a professional &amp; a bureaucratic management.The former makes events happen, while the latter waits for the event to happen.All leading carriers of the world, who are not in as bad a situation as AI, are taking the manpower related decisions to tame the costs. Why are legacy work practices still followed which have outlived their purpose long back ? Why are retired employees being re-employed on contract ? This a scam, hand in glove with HR, Section Head, &amp; top management ! Deliberately there is no succession plan, to create an indispensability of a retiring person- and then seek his extention. Its a CRIMINAL waste of scarce resources. What action has Mr Nandan taken on it. Expense curtailment. Despite an office order to  all duty tours abroad, and overnight visits in India- how are these openly flouted, and expense incurred. Mr Nandan if you talk of consolidation &amp; setting the house in order, please first cleanse your backyard, Ensure  discipline in complete implementation of rules, particularly those relating to costs, and you will see the results for yourself. This calls for a tough &amp; a hard task master with single minded devotion &amp; committment to generate profits. Waiting for the banana to fall will starve you to death, and the poor banana as well. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l54sa</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ebhf</id></website><link>http://www.livemint.com/2012/03/26205135/Rohit-Nandan--Route-dispersal.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T19:48:20+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-27T07:23:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msgeag</id><link>http://www.livemint.com/2012/03/26205135/Rohit-Nandan--Route-dispersal.html#comment-477252041</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>