<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3k9ju/post/2012-03-29T22:47:47</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Mr. Churchill, in this inter-office memorandum, was not aware "of the slightest 
advantage that has ever accrued to Great Britain from this painful and thankless 
task". But in  public, when Zion was listening, he continued (and to the moment 
of writing this book continues) to applaud the Zionist adventure in a boundless 
manner which aroused the curiosity even of Jewish critics (as will be 
seen). 
     At the time when Mr. Churchill 
dictated this last memorandum his words about "settling the question of 
Palestine at the peace table" were so irrelevant that he might have had humorous 
intent in using them. The issue was closed, for the Zionists had arms, the men 
to use these arms were to be smuggled through Europe from the revolutionary area 
by the West (as shown in the last chapter), and both major political parties in 
England and America were ready to applaud any  of aggression, invasion or 
persecution the transmigrants committed with the arms they had 
obtained. 

     This was particularly evident in the 
case of the Socialist party in England, which at that time was still the country 
chiefly involved in the fate of Palestine.  The Labour party (as it called 
itself) in England presented itself as the champion of the poor, defenceless and 
oppressed; it had been born and bred in the promise of old-age pensions, 
unemployment relief, free medicine and the care and relief of the destitute, 
poor or humble generally.   

     As the war drew towards its end this 
party at long last saw before it the prospect of office with a substantial 
majority.  Like the Conservative party (and both parties in America) it 
apparently calculated that victory was even at this stage not quite certain and 
that it could be  by placating Zion.  Thus it placed at the head of its 
foreign policy the aim to drive from a little country far away some people who 
were poorer, more friendless and longer oppressed than even the British worker 
in the worst days of the Industrial Revolution. 

     In 1944 its leader, Mr. Clement 
Attlee, proclaimed the new, crowning tenet of British Socialism: 


"Let the Arabs be encouraged to move out 
(of Palestine) as the Jews move in. Let them be handsomely compensated for their 
land, and their settlement elsewhere be carefully organized and generously 
financed". 

(Twelve years later nearly a million of 
these people, encouraged to move out by bombs, still languished in the neighbour 
Arab countries of Palestine, and the British Socialist Party, at every new turn 
of events, was more claimant than ever for their further 
chastisement). 

     The British Socialists, when they 
made this statement, knew that the Zionists, under cover of the war against 
Germany, had amassed arms for the conquest of Palestine by force. 

     General Wavell, the commander in the 
Middle East, had long before informed Mr. Churchill that "left to themselves, 
the Jews would beat the Arabs" (who had no source of arms-supply).  General 
Wavell's view about the Zionist scheme was that of all responsible 
administrators on the Spot, and for that reason he was disliked by 
Dr. Weizmann. 

     The reader has already seen, as far 
back as the First War, that Dr. Weizmann's displeasure was dangerous even to 
high personages and it may have played a part in General Wavell's removal from 
the Middle East command to India.   

     The official British History 
of the War in the Middle East describes General Wavell as "one of the 
great commanders in military history" and says Tiredness, caused by his great 
responsibilities, was aggravated by the feeling that he did not enjoy the full 
confidence of Mr. Churchill, who bombarded his Middle East commander with 
"irritating" and "needless" telegrams about "matters of detail".  By his 
relegation General Wavell may have been another victim of Zionism, and British 
military prowess have suffered accordingly in the war; this cannot be 
established but it is a reasonable surmise. 

     In 1944 assassination again appeared 
in the story.  Lord Moyne, as Colonial Secretary, was the Cabinet minister then 
responsible for Palestine, the post earlier held by Lord Lloyd (who had been 
rudely rebuked by Mr. Churchill for tardiness in "arming the Jews" and had died 
in 1941).  Lord Moyne was the friend of all men, and sympathetic to Judaism, but 
he shared the view of all his responsible predecessors, that the Zionist 
enterprise in Palestine would end disastrously. 

     For that reason, and having sympathy 
for suffering mankind in general, he was inclined to revive the idea of proving 
land in Uganda for any Jews who truly needed to find a new home 
somewhere. 

     This humane notion brought him the 
mortal hatred of the Zionists, who would not brook any diversion of thought from 
the target of their ambition: Palestine.  In 1943 Lord Moyne modified his view, 
according to Mr. Churchill, who suggested that Dr. Weizmann should go to Cairo, 
meet Lord Moyne there and satisfy himself of the improvement.   

     Before any meeting could come about, 
Lord Moyne was assassinated in Cairo (November 1944) by two Zionists from 
Palestine, one more peacemaker thus being removed from a path strewn with the 
bones of earlier pacifiers. 

     This event for a moment disturbed 
the flow of Mr. Churchill's memoranda to his colleagues about "arming the Jews", 
and the responsible men in Palestine once again urgently recommended that 
Zionist immigration thither be suspended.  Mr. Churchill's reply (November 17, 
1944) was that this would "simply play into the hands of the extremists", 
whereon the extremists were left unhindered in their further plans and their 
tribe increased. 

     As the Second War approached its end 
in Europe Mr. Churchill's hopes of some spectacular transaction which would 
happily integrate the Chazars in Arabia faded. 

     If his suggestion (that Ibn Saoud be 
made "lord of the Middle East, provided he settles with you", i.e. Dr. Weizmann) 
was ever conveyed by Dr. Weizmann to President Roosevelt, an episode of 1944 may 
have been the result of it.   

     An American, Colonel Hoskins, 
("President Roosevelt's personal representative in the Middle East"; according 
to Dr. Weizmann) then visited the Arab leader.  Colonel Hoskins, like all 
qualified men, had no faith in the plan to set up a Zionist state but was in 
favour of helping Jews to go to Palestine (if any so wished) in agreement with 
the Arabs.  He found that King Ibn Saoud held himself to have been grossly 
insulted by Dr. Weizmann of whom he spoke "in the angriest and most contemptuous 
manner, asserting that I (Dr. Weizmann) had tried to bribe him with twenty 
million pounds to sell out Palestine to the Jews", and he indignantly rejected 
any suggestion of a deal on such terms.   

     Therewith all prospect of any 
"settlement"  and Colonel Hoskins also passed from the story, another 
good man defeated in his attempt to solve the insoluble problem posed by Mr. 
Balfour. 

     Thus, as the war entered its last 
months, only two alternatives remained.  The British Government, abandoning the 
decision of 1939, could struggle on, trying to hold the scales impartially 
between the native inhabitants and their besiegers from Russia; or it could 
throw up "the Mandate" and withdraw, whereupon the Zionists would expel the 
native inhabitants with arms procured from the European and African theatres of 
war. 

     This second great moment in the 
Palestinian drama approached. Mr. Roosevelt had been told by Dr. Weizmann that 
the Zionists "could not rest the case on the consent of the Arabs" but had 
remained non-committal. Mr. Churchill, according to Dr. Weizmann, had 
committed himself, in private, and in 1944 Dr. Weizmann grew impatient 
to have from Mr. Churchill a public committal in the form of an amended Balfour 
Declaration which would award territory (in place of the 
meaningless phrase "a national home") to Zion (in 1949 he was still very angry 
that Mr. Churchill, on the "pretext" that the war must first be finished, 
refrained from making this final public capitulation). 

     Like Macbeth, Dr. Weizmann's 
"top-line politicians" flinched and shrunk as the moment for the deed 
approached.  Neither Mr. Churchill nor Mr. Roosevelt would openly command their 
soldiers to do it and the Zionists furiously cried "Infirm of 
purpose!" 

     Then, Mr. Roosevelt went to Yalta, 
wearing the visage of doomed despair which the news-reel pictures recorded, 
arranged for the bisection of Europe, and at the end briefly informed Mr. 
Churchill (who was "flabbergasted" and "greatly disturbed" by the news, 
according to Mr. Hopkins) that he was going to meet King Ibn Saoud on board the 
U.S. cruiser Quincy.  

     What followed remains deeply 
mysterious. Neither Mr. Roosevelt nor Mr. Churchill had any right to bestow Arab 
land on the lobbyists who beleaguered them in Washington and London; 
nevertheless, what was demanded of them was, in appearance, so small in 
comparison with what had just been done at Yalta, that Mr. Roosevelt's 
submission and some harsh ultimatum to Kin Ibn Saoud would have surprised none. 
Instead, he suddenly stepped out of the part he had played for many years and 
spoke as a statesman; after that he died. 

     He left Yalta on February 11, 1945, 
and spent February 12, 13 and 14 aboard the Quincy, receiving King Ibn Saoud 
during this time. He asked the king "to admit some more Jews in to Palestine" 
and received the blunt answer, "NO". Ibn Saoud said that "there was a Palestine 
army of Jews all armed to the teeth and. . . they did not seem to be fighting 
the Germans but were aiming at the Arabs". 

     On February 28 Mr. Roosevelt 
returned to Washington. On March 28 Ibn Saoud reiterated by letter his verbal 
warning (since confirmed by events) of the consequences which would follow from 
American support of the Zionists. On April 5 President Roosevelt replied 
reaffirming his own  verbally given to Ibn Saoud that: 


"I would take no action, in 
my capacity as Chief of the Executive Branch of this Government which 
might prove hostile to the Arab people". 

     On April 12 he died. This  
would never have become known but for the action of an American statesman, 
Secretary of State James G. Byrnes, who published it six months later (October 
18, 1945) in a vain attempt to deter Mr. Roosevelt's successor, President 
Truman, from taking the very "action hostile to the Arabs" which President 
Roosevelt swore he would never commit. 

     Mr. Roosevelt's  was virtually 
a deathbed one, and another of history's great unanswered questions is, did he 
mean it? If by any chance he did, then once more death intervened as the ally of 
Zionism. His intimate Mr. Harry Hopkins (who was present at the meeting and 
drafted a memorandum about it) sneered at the suggestion that it might have been 
sincerely intended, saying that President Roosevelt was "wholly committed 
publicly and privately and by conviction" to the Zionists. 

     (This memorandum records Mr. 
Roosevelt's statement that he had learned more from Ibn Saoud about Palestine in 
five minutes than he had previously learned in a lifetime; out of this, again, 
grew the famous anecdote that Ibn Saoud said, "We have known for two 
thousand years what you have fought two world wars to 
learn". 

     However, Mr. Hopkins may conceivably 
not be a trustworthy witness on this one occasion, for immediately after the 
meeting he, the president's shadow, mysteriously broke with Mr. Roosevelt, whom 
he never saw again! 

     Mr. Hopkins shut himself in his 
cabin and three days later, at Algiers, went ashore, "sending word" through an 
intermediary that he would return to America by another route. 

     The breach was as sudden as that 
between Mr. Wilson and Mr. House. 

     What is clear is that the last few 
weeks and days of Mr. Roosevelt's life were overshadowed by the controversy of 
Zion, not by American or European questions. Had he lived, and his Pledge to Ibn 
Saoud become known, Zionism, which so powerfully helped to make and maintain him 
president for twelve years, would have become his bitter enemy. He 
died. 
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l52ms</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry2d</id></website><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50458</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T19:24:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:47:47+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3k9ju</id><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50458#comment-480171587</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zd1dw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>