<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwy8iv/update/2012-03-30T10:26:11/b43d0e384de536874b90c1c20b3310bcf7d791cdfa1843af0ba2d30767d74b59</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Now this is how sikh religious body SGPC works. You have goons and immoral people at the top of this body. Whenever there is a mixing of politics and religion that is bound to happen. SGPC is a body which interferes in politics of Punjab and that is where moral down gradation of Punjab started. SGPC is a Taliban or Jamaat-ud-dawaa  in sophisticated form. Sikhism is following the path of radical Islam. Sikhs are emotional people and this religious body is playing with their sentiments and emotions and brain washing some of young sikh's mind. Faith in religion is one thing but whenever a religion start having sentiments that their religion is superior to others, their downfall starts. SGPC  supported extremist elements in sikh community which leads to Bleeding of Punjab in 80s to early 90s. Now, they are instructing Akali dal (who are directly linked to SGPC) to support Rajona. This guy (Rajoana) is a 
killer who killed not only elected CM of Punjab but also 16 other 
innocent people. What about their families? I have a question to all who
 is supporting Rajona what if one of your family members (your father, 
mother, brother, sister, wife or kid) would have died in that blast. 
Would you still ask for clemency? This is not a religious issue but 
issue of justice and closure. Now, some people will start question me 
about 1984 sikh riots. Yes, that riot was also for a short term 
political  and those who were involved should be hanged for killing 
innocent people. There is no two answers about it. These things will 
keep happening in India till these old politicians who will keep 
thinking of short political Gains, and till voters won't be mature 
enough to vote on development and security instead of religious and 
castist emotions. This is a high time that Sikh should delink themselves from these extremist views for the education and progress of sikh community as a whole. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/678s5m</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gidt</id></website><link>http://www.hindustantimes.com/India-news/Punjab/Jagir-Kaur-gets-5-years-in-jail-for-conspiracy-in-daughter-s-death/Article1-833006.aspx</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T12:17:43+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T14:26:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwy8iv</id><link>http://www.hindustantimes.com/India-news/Punjab/Jagir-Kaur-gets-5-years-in-jail-for-conspiracy-in-daughter-s-death/Article1-833006.aspx#comment-480793768</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>