<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/erf7iz/update/2011-12-08T17:42:29/cd9447ea21c0bc29e99cac1ee6356ab7c1c251a1b3c1e649329214a301d6064e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I was Head Boy of the History teacher's school last year and studied for A-level history so I think I'm in a good place to comment on this story.  
One thing that has not been noted is that he was not sharing anything new or exclusive! Any teacher can access past papers; these will show patterns and the 'cycle' that he talks about in the undercover clip. Any teacher with an ounce of sense will Spot the cycle and work out which focus areas are due to come up! Sensibly, they will then focus more on these areas and with any time saved will teach exam techniques. 
Please do not question his honesty and professionalism based on this clip. He is a fantastic teacher; I  say how he was the best I ever had. He  was  willing to talk to me and guide me but NEVER once told me any 'cheats' and Always remained professional and was also one of the most intelligent people you'll ever meet!   

However, there is an obvious issue that needs addressing within the education system regarding the number of exam boards but that is by no means his fault, he's just become a scapegoat for what is, ultimately, the government's failings.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/dmk8jk</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/secondaryeducation/8941589/Exam-boards-WJEC-chief-examiners-caught-on-film-telling-teachers-what-is-in-next-years-GCSE-history-paper.html</link><postedTime>2011-12-07T21:57:06+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-12-08T22:42:29+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/erf7iz</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/secondaryeducation/8941589/Exam-boards-WJEC-chief-examiners-caught-on-film-telling-teachers-what-is-in-next-years-GCSE-history-paper.html#comment-382459766</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rkij8</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-12-07</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>