<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk10l4/update/2012-03-26T12:05:27/d506ded670ce7907dae98e41578304c586a6fe6210c0d9e79d92d1f876138650</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mo8qcr</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Not to sound too harsh, however, I do feel that I need to point out that you are still anew person to this game.  The synergy is not quite fully understandable to you as of yet.  It is obvious, though, that you do like BIG bombs.  This is good, as most people do, I myself included.  But, I recently took a few steps back to look at the overall synergy of a block.  
Take Urza Block (Urza's Saca, Urza's LEgacy, Urza's Destiny)  These three sets let a lot of groundbreaking achievements, but also did this at the cost of losing a lot of players, old and new to the game.  There were plenty of bombs, and plenty of eh, it's okay, but, I wouldn't play it cards.  But at the same time was completely disruptive, and scattered.

Ravnica, Guildpact, Dissention, Was more synergistic, but still pretty scattered.

Zendikar, worldwake, Rise of the Eldrazi, was greatly synergistic, but discombobulated, as ROE felt entirely out of place.  All of the buildup of synergy in the first two sets was thrown out the window in order to make room for ROE and what it had to offer.  This caused a lot of problems for the returning, old and new players alike.  As the synergy of the block was nearly or completely lost on the players.

Scars of mirrodin, Mirrodin besieged, New Phyrexia,  Was the absolute best step in the right direction of synergy, keeping it going, and presenting new cards in the final set of the block.

Now for Innistrad, Dark Ascension, Avacyn Restored.  Wizards, every once in a while takes a step back and reexamines all of the formats.  And to do this, some blocks feel lacking.  But, look at this block as their way of breaking up tension.  Too many Big Bombs all the time equals loss of players, new and old.  However, this not to say that they were trying to deliberately make a crappy block.  I would never say this, as I have been playing MTG for 19 years.  I try to look at things the way Wizards does.  They are trying to break up the current format for everyone's sake.  
Now, the synergy has seemed to a slow buildup.  But, take a closer look.  I beg you.  The synergy is on the different group of peoples in the world of innistrad, and what they have lost or .  The Vampires have evolved into more bloodthirsty beasts than just plain vamps, the werewolves, have gone completely crazy, and the Zombies, and spirits, well, There isn't enough paper or internet space to be able to tell the transformation of these last two groups.  The focus has been on a Night and day theme.  What lurks at night WILL most deffinately hurt you, as will what is in the daylight.

Planeswalkers.  Planeswalkers, Planeswalkers. PLANESWALKERS!!!
Everyone will have their varied oppinions on these newest additions to the card pools.  Some like em hot, some like Cold, some like in the pot completely apart the've been boiled.  However, look for the functionality of a planeswalker that COMPLIMENT your deck, or playstyle.  Me, It don't matter which one it is, I'll  try to find a way to slip a couple into my decks.

Now, for the final acquisition of knowledge.  The reason that wizards has  two cards in this current format, means nothing.  Wizards has   cards.  When Mirrodin, Darksteel, Fifthdawn came out, they had to  the Affinity cards, and the artifact lands because they were too strong.  They completely DOMINATED TWO environments, standard, and extended.  The fact that these two have been Banned so soon, shows that wizards is truely starting to notice thier mistakes, and mishaps sooner.  The reason that they waited so long is because these sets are worked on months, even years, before they even come out.  So there may not be much time for them to catch the overpowered-ness of a card until after it comes out.

Finally, this is a card game, it was made for Wizards to make money, if it wasn't then, the cards would be free, and there wouldn't be any interest in the game.  All games have a price tag.  EVEN, EA sports games.  (Mental note, thank god that I don't play sports games.  They suck compared to real life.)  If you do not want to spend the money to play, then, you don't play.  It's all about supply and demand.
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6mqwfm</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6c9m</id></website><link>http://www.gatheringmagic.com/lingering-souls-and-intangible-virtue-banned-in-isd-block/</link><postedTime>2012-03-20T04:12:34+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T16:05:27+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk10l4</id><link>http://www.gatheringmagic.com/lingering-souls-and-intangible-virtue-banned-in-isd-block/#comment-476496882</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>