<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miyvxr/post/2012-03-22T20:33:56</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Or cocaine, or immorality, or class hatreds, or crop failure, or academic hypocrites, or lung worms, or unions, or  personal hygiene, or Obama/Bush style leadership.   In short, just another academic wank with an agenda.  You don't see England doing the Mayan shuffle or Canada or Japan or even Rome.  What brings down a country are those wonderful 20 things that disallow the industrial revolution and that means sans the Gene Sharp disease.  Here are the first 13 or so I remember from manufacturing history: Note religion CAN BE a strong part of preserving society as shown by asterisks below!
==============================================
Food
Clothing
Shelter
*Peace (no attackers)
*Tolerance (you tolerate the other guy) You don't run the Cherokee  because you fear their printing presses!
*Morality (you can trust the other guy not to steal your tools or stahb you in the back with them)
Technical Publication (you write down how to do things so the tech isn't lost)
Raw Materials
*Preservation of produced items, tools, buildings, etc. no rotting, low humidity, few insects, no freeze damage
*No waste-don't redistribute wealth to wasters, respect things AND people.
Environmental control of people (not Too hot, not too Cold, pain ki77ers/druhgs, television, entertainment,
         comfy clothes, happy foods)
Excess Ag production- you must not tie everyone up making food
*Freedom from disease- by *rote process or druhgs and medicine
Capital equipment-flint arrowheads will only get you so far.
        (sewing machines, metal forming, tractors, plows, Planters, irrigation, transport vehicles)
Water
Power-coal, oil, solar, geothermal, biofuel wood/grassss/dung, electric grid, wind, hydropower, animal power
Transportation
Science-understanding cause and effect, prediction of the future, the poor man's time travel, the dim flashlight! </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yurmm</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yjmx</id></website><link>http://www.foxnews.com/scitech/2012/03/22/did-belief-in-gods-lead-to-mayan-demise/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T17:17:49+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T00:33:56+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miyvxr</id><link>http://www.foxnews.com/scitech/2012/03/22/did-belief-in-gods-lead-to-mayan-demise/#comment-474093119</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c1p95</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>