<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mweicu/post/2012-03-30T08:33:11</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Dirks should be our number 2 hitter, but he will not get it. Jackson has potential and needs to work in more walks, less K's. You put Boesch behind Cabrera, Fielder, Young combo to help clean up... Boesch is a power hitter, Dirks will hit a better average. Avila will most likely not hit like he did last year. He should be at the bottom of the order at 9. Put Santiago and Peralta at 7/8. Raburn is starting to take a dive in his hitting. He will have his moments, but he is not an every day starter. Kelly will be exciting to watch this season. I would like to see Worth continue his tear on the field as well. 

Tigers are getting too top heavy. We need a little more speed mixed in. I am hoping to see Berry in the near future as well as another young catcher to help back-up Avila. I realize Martinez will be back next year, but he can't handle too many games behind the plate. He is pretty much DH duty. I like Santiago as our best choice for 2nd right now, but I would like to see a little more speed in this Spot someday. Perhaps we should start working Worth a little more at 2nd for the time being. I like the idea of Worth as Santiago's back-up over some other players (won't speak their names).</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z9hu0</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lz6q</id></website><link>http://detroit.tigers.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120329%26content_id=27740592%26vkey=news_det%26c_id=det</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:38:07+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T12:33:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mweicu</id><link>http://detroit.tigers.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120329%26content_id=27740592%26vkey=news_det%26c_id=det#comment-480689123</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/go3u8</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>