<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mfu484/update/2012-03-15T17:29:36/8d0ef32e3a7ec8841501941736e6bb93063b38886f34d2c8904e9093793bfb3c</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Both my babies suffered severe acid reflux and this made breastfeeding so hard.  Babies are not stupid and quickly associate feeding as the source of their pain.  With my son (my first) he would break away from the breast screaming and refusing to feed.  Although I had almost daily support from midwives then health visitors for the first few weeks, the problem was not identified very quickly.  They would pop in for literally five minutes, hastily chuck out a few words of advice, rush out a few scrawled sentences on my notes and then dash  to their next appointment.  It was when I finally got referred to a breastfeeding counsellor that she immediately recognised the acid reflux and at last there was at least an explanation for the difficulties.  

The pressure to perservere with the breastfeeding was fairly strong but came mostly from within - I had been so desperate to feed myself.  

I turned to expressing and made myself ill with the 'routine' of feeding, expressing, sterilising.  By 3 months I was ready to give up and actually moved to formula for a couple of weeks.  But felt so guilty that I actually took desperate measures to get my milk back and started expressing again.  It didn't really work as my supply was never the same and by 5 months the formula 'top ups' overtook my supply and I had to admit defeat.  I was so sad and guilty.

Whilst I know the guilt was self-inflicted it had to stem from somewhere and I feel the run-up to the birth plays a huge part in our behaviour as new mums.  All those little conversations with the midwife, the messages in the leaflets you get given, and during the antenatal classes.  The message is conveyed almost in a traditional British 'matter-of'fact' manner:  Ladies, here is your Feeding Priority Order:  (1) Breast.  If failed, move on to (2) Expressed.  If failed, move on to (3) Formula.

It does not surprise me that us Brits are unable to keep up with other countries as we all know that as a nation we work more and play less.  We live to work, whereas other countries work to live.  This evidently has a direct effect on our babies.  My husband was back at work after his two weeks on paternity.  We followed our work and don't live near family.  I was suddenly completely on my own for 9 hours every day and struggled to keep my head above water.  I bet there are thousands of British women in a similar sort of situation.  But it's not like that abroad.  Grandmothers move in, communities rally round with as much help as they can muster, and dads get more time  or enjoy more flexible hours.
 
I also believe that in our fast-paced, high-expectation culture we are gradually losing the mental conditioning necessary to successfully nurse a baby.  The few women I know that have breastfed for more than a few months have the sorts of personalities that are becoming increasingly rare:  calm, placid souls that take each day as it comes, and don't mind not being in control of every little detail of their lives and daily routine.  I try hard to be like that but it is a real effort and my 'get stuff done' persona sneaks its way in all the time.

Anyway, second time around with another reflux baby I have learnt my lesson and only expressed for a few weeks before moving to formula.  The guilt is still there; she is seven months and every time she has the snuffles there is this niggly voice saying 'she would have been better protocted from Colds if she was still getting your milk'.  But at least this time it is calculated guilt, offset against the need to keep myself sane.  

I wish I could Reach out to every woman who is going through something similar to what I went through and just give them a hug on one of those awful Cry Days (when you just curl up and cry all day rocking your sleeping baby back and forth, loving them so, so much but feeling as if you are failing them).

I wish women had more emotional, as well as practical, support.



</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/652gyh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/mxvz</id></website><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/health-news/women-pressured-to-breastfeed-babies-7570366.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-15T00:15:58+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-15T21:29:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mfu484</id><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/health-news/women-pressured-to-breastfeed-babies-7570366.html#comment-466350138</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z8g9j</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-15</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>