<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkbhb0/update/2012-03-26T08:59:13/84c2b2fd2f0697db715f0d696973d4296ad22ae03f9c8f757eb189c8c08a1379</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpvkj6</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hfayg</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>The exact motives behind Godhra Train Burning are known to everyone. May be there is some blackout of Information is your highly developed haryana state. The intention was to take revenge and that' what muslims did.

In the afterward bloodbath, 30 per cent victims were Hindus. So don't make it as only Muslims died. You might not have ever read the newspaper but for your information, from Feb 28,2002 muslims were as much active in violence has Hindus, they were only outnumbered. 

According to Army officials, rioters were protected in the muslim majority areas. To protect rioters, muslims even used lethal weapons against army. The electricity used to be cut Off my the locals to help rioters move away with their weapons. This is the real story.

Only a idiot will compare 
Gaddafhi and Mubarak with Modi. He is democratically elected CM while they were forced upon the people. Both of them ordered killing of at least 500,000 civilians during their rule.

On the other hand Modi is accused of killing 790 muslims. You blame him for not doing enough to save 790 muslims. What about 17,000 muslims who on record have said that Gujarat police saved them from certain death during 2002 riots. Does he deserve credit for that or not??

Gujarat was not the most industrialised state in India. It certainly was among the top 5. But before Modi took over, agriculture growth in Gujarat was around 4.7 per cent. In last 8 years its over 10 per cent.  Take a look at other states that were hast growing 30 years back.  Haryana is all set to lose automobile king title to Gujarat, Punjab is wrecked and Maharashtra is also expected to soon lose the Number 1 Spot as most preferred destination for Industries to Gujarat.

Haryana has largest growth in some sectors but nowhere close to the overall growth figure of Gujarat. And Haryana is the state with highest rate of honor killing. Only state in India where every girl from my village is my sister. What a backward mentality. Haryana is the state that gives most importance to gotra and other nonsense that rest of India has abolished.

By the way the days of Haryana is automobile king are over. Maruti has already planned to run away to Gujarat and most big international automobile companies have come to Gujarat not haryana.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6grj39</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/temq</id></website><link>http://globalspin.blogs.time.com/2012/03/16/why-narendra-modi-is-indias-most-loved-and-loathed-politician/</link><postedTime>2012-03-16T20:05:23+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T12:59:13+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkbhb0</id><link>http://globalspin.blogs.time.com/2012/03/16/why-narendra-modi-is-indias-most-loved-and-loathed-politician/#comment-476375435</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cz3d2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-16</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>