<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwe3tq/post/2012-03-30T08:38:24</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I have an example for you, Sean...when I first joined the "penguins" at my new job in San Diego, I was a transplant from the Phoenix "zoo" with no official title or leadership position, even though I was a team leader at my old job.  I really had no desire to change the culture; overall, it was "pretty good."  I knew the potential was much greater and I set out to feed my family, just like the Ohio penguins in your story.

At first, the other penguins resented me.  I kept swimming, finding new customers.  Soon, our office was filled with penguins who transformed from  in the early afternoon to serving customers until long after sunset.  Our team became the flagship in a company of 4,000 reps who worked in offices all over the country.  Everyone wanted to be a penguin on the elite San Diego team.   There were no boundaries as commissioned penguins and we  levels of pay that far exceeded senior management, which created a new problem at the zoo.

One day, the suits running the zoo decided we were a bunch of overpaid penguins and told us, "monkeys could do our jobs for a lot less money."  So my elite group of penguins built our own zoo and departed to compete.  The suits became jealous and told the penguins who stayed behind that anyone caught saying the name of our new company, "Zoom," would be fired on the Spot.  The orphaned penguins started calling us "Mooz," so they could keep their job at the zoo.  Unfortunately for them, all 4,000 penguins eventually got laid .  7 years later, our penguins are still swimming.  We opened up two other cities and adopted some penguins who lost their jobs when the suits closed all their zoos nationwide.  Now these penguins are working again; they own their own zoos in Salt Lake City and Las Vegas. 

I no longer swim in the San Diego zoo, although I still remain one of the owners on the partner team.  I'm in the Midwest now, searching for a new pool to swim in.  I learned that toxic environments can be changed, not by wearing fancy suits and showing Off corporate name tags.  All you have to do is jump in and swim.  And if management becomes jealous because you're having too much fun and making too much money, jump out of the pool and go build your own zoo.  The world needs more penguins who are willing to swim.  Thanks for a great post, Sean.  You definitely struck my penguin nerve.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66874e</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dx2</id></website><link>http://michaelhyatt.com/how-penguin-leadership-will-change-your-team-culture.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T09:05:48+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T12:38:24+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwe3tq</id><link>http://michaelhyatt.com/how-penguin-leadership-will-change-your-team-culture.html#comment-480693511</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hmjjd</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>