<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mjqrdk/update/2012-03-19T19:56:40/2638f8aba84182155782a0dc0276d8d3399b986367e37c9a59a41b79660943cd</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m93j88</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z8ujq</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Isabelle, Mother Teresa was dedicated and extraordinary, but, as I said in the interview, I did not  find her wise.  Adam's comments below about the service the Missionaries of Charity gave to the poor, under Mother Teresa's supervision, are correct.  The Missionaries of Charity were not concerned with offering optimal care to the poor, even though doing much better was easily within their Reach.

And you are correct, Isabelle, when you say that there are two different attitudes toward suffering here.  This is where faith and reason part ways.  While Mother Teresa's version of Christianity glorified suffering while applying bandaids to big problems, human reason would say that alleviating suffering is more noble than glorifying it.

The media created a picture of Mother Teresa as someone dedicated to alleviating the world's suffering, but she was not concerned with stopping suffering in any sort of effective way.  She believed that by helping people accept their suffering she was preparing them for a better life in a world to come.  I think that this attitude is dangerous.  Even if the Missionaries of Charity have done some good things, I don't think they can be held up as role models in caring for the poor effectively.  

Isabelle, yes, the gospels quote Jesus as saying that a true disciple takes up the cross and follows him.  The gospels also quote Jesus as saying "I came that they may have life, and have it to the full."  "I was hungry and you gave me to eat." "The children of this world are wiser than the children of light."  "Love your neighbor as yourself."  And we could go on.  

I think it's very dangerous to base your spirituality on verses picked from one Spot in the Bible, especially since you can usually find a verse not too far away that sheds light on the same subject from a very different angle.

Thanks for participating in this discussion.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6c6aog</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/b703</id></website><link>http://bigthink.com/daylight-atheism/an-interview-with-mary-johnson-author-of-an-unquenchable-thirst</link><postedTime>2012-03-14T01:46:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-19T23:56:40+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mjqrdk</id><link>http://bigthink.com/daylight-atheism/an-interview-with-mary-johnson-author-of-an-unquenchable-thirst#comment-469513903</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/za6yz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-14</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>