<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ohfz/post/2012-03-29T19:20:48</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39gs2</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Oh yes! They are out to get us because there is money to be made  of getting us! Take the case of one of Huntington Beach PD's  star ticket writers Roman Altenbach. Officer Altenbach is at every award ceremony getting heaps of praise for keeping bad guys  the street, yet he has to make countless illegal traffic stops and falsified arrest reports to achieve these numbers. There are countless stories around town about this particular officer and even his fellow officers are aware of the lies and deceit, yet no one will come forward and put an end to this out of control cop running roughshod on the citizens of Huntington Beach. I heard from one officer that Altenbach has a new wife and home in Yorba Linda, and he really likes/needs the overtime pay that all of his court appearances bring. Here is just one story about Officer Altenbach, taken from Treasure Net online, a forum for metal detector users: "I was out in a park today with a fellow TH'r when I saw a cop eyeballing
 us from the street. This guy was about a 120 yards away. He jumps the 
curb in little police car and proceeds to do a burnout THE ENTIRE LENGTH
 of the field in order to get to us. This field is basically a dirt lot 
with some weeds and is completely riddled with gopher holes. I am 
fanatic about pinpointing and proper digging techniques. This guy tells 
me that we need to get outta here and before I could even get up from 
the plug I was replacing, he tells me again get outta here again. I said
 hold on a minute, first of all there's no sign saying we can't metal 
detect here and you haven't even given me a chance to stand up. He said 
there doesn't have to be a sign there's a municipal code prohibiting 
metal detecting. I said no there isn't because there isn't and he slams 
his car into park and jumps out of the car and stands right over top of 
me pointing at me and says now you really pissed me . I said I pissed
 you Off? How? By telling you that there is no such code. He takes my ID
 and parks his car in the middle of the field for a half hour and 
finally comes back with a ticket for vandalism under some generic code 
saying we had defaced public property. I said ok then point to the place
 where we defaced something. He just smirked and Blushed like a little 
schoolgirl. He looked around and just laughed and said you can TRY to 
fight it if you want. The other guy said hold on I want to get you on 
video pointing to ANY KIND OF DAMAGE other than your burnout tire 
tracks. This guy gets back into his car and blows us a kiss and Burns 
out AGAIN all the way back down the field leaving another set of 
tracks!!! I AM NOT A CRIMINAL AND THIS IS A RIDICULOUS USE OF COMMUNITY 
RESOURCES. This guy is cop in Huntington Beach California and his name 
is Altenbach and his badge number is #1032. I am going to fight this all
 the way". This is just one story of many, on how they are out to get us. They need our money to pay for their ridiculous pay and retirement benefits. They need our money to pay for their ridiculous helicopter program. They need our money to help pay for their disgraced fellow officers legal fees. As you can see, they need a lot of our money!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h2jxo</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/r33p</id></website><link>http://blogs.ocweekly.com/navelgazing/2012/03/huntington_beach_residents_pol.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T01:48:35+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T23:20:48+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ohfz</id><link>http://blogs.ocweekly.com/navelgazing/2012/03/huntington_beach_residents_pol.php#comment-480014690</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>