<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/310642/post/128036343/comment/329519722</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I think there is a plausible reason to believe that Triple H could be jealous of Rock. It&amp;#039;s the end of an , but during that , Rock and Triple H rose to main event status nearly side by side. 
 
Reading through the comments, people are arguing against the claim that Rock was handed the keys to main event status. It is true that Rock was heavily hyped in his debut because of his pedigree. He was a 3rd generation wrestler whose grandfather was revered amongst the Samoan people, and the Samoans were among the most respected and feared guys in the locker room. But the Rock&amp;#039;s beginning push failed miserably. He was booed everywhere he went and then he was thrown in the Nation because they didn&amp;#039;t have anything else for him. Rock got over when he was in the Nation because his Rock character began to develop and his funny insults and witty catchphrases stared to become very popular.  
 
The people who weren&amp;#039;t there can&amp;#039;t understand it. I was in high school at the time, and it was when wrestling was at it&amp;#039;s peak and when wrestling was cool. People were quoting Rock&amp;#039;s catchphrases and talking how Rock was a badass. Then Rock had a ppv match against Shamrock and Mankind. Rock was the heel, but Shamrock and Foley were booed out of the building. People have tried to argue that it was bc the event was in Canada. But that doesn&amp;#039;t jive. The truth is, Rock was getting over the same way Austin got over and Rock was on track to become just as popular as Austin. 
 
Triple H is talented, but 3 of the biggest names in the WWE (, Nash, &amp;amp; Michaels) were constantly talking him up to Vince. When Shawn turned heel after Summerslam 97, he demanded to be allied with Triple H. So Triple H got a big time rub from being with HBK. When Shawn left and Triple H became the new leader of DX, he had to rely on an intense promo from Sean Waltman that cut down Bischoff and Hogan to legitimize the new DX. Eventually, Triple H got his (well deserved) title run. Triple H&amp;#039;s early title runs were not failures by any means. But they were not on the same level as Rock and Austin.  
 
2002-2006 was the dark Triple H . Triple H had just married Steph, and Triple H was in almost every main event program during this Era. During these years, he was accused of burying talent including Chris Jericho, Rob Van Dam, Booker T, Goldberg, and Kane. There were also rumors that Triple H was in Vince&amp;#039;s ear and planted seeds that caused problems between WWE and Rock/Austin. Almost all of the Triple H resentment you see today began during this time frame. 
 
I give this look back at history to show the difference in both wrestlers&amp;#039; rise to the top. People arguing for Triple H ask the question, &amp;quot;Why would Triple H be jealous? He is a talented wrestler, he is a wealthy man, and he will help run the WWE one day&amp;quot; 
 
Here&amp;#039;s why Triple may possibly be jealous of Rock (and to a lessor extent, Austin.) 
 
-Behind Triple H is a man named Paul Levesque, and everyday Paul has to look at himself in the mirror. I personally believe Paul wonders if he would have made it to the top if he weren&amp;#039;t a member of the Kliq. I think deep down he knows he was never the draw that Austin and Rock were. I think he knows that he planted seeds of doubt in the mind of Vince McMahon that prevented Vince from giving guys like Kurt Angle, Chris Benoit, Kane, Jericho, RVD, etc. the title runs they deserved. I believe deep down he was afraid they would prove to be better than him. 
 
He knows he&amp;#039;s not the draw that Hogan/Austin/Rock were.  
 
He knows he&amp;#039;s not the in-ring performer that Shawn Michaels, Bret Hart and Ric Flair were. 
 
He knows he doesn&amp;#039;t have the backstage respect of Undertaker, Rick Rude, or Owen Hart. 
 
Yet the WWE touts him was one of the greatest superstars in the history of the company. I think this eats away at his soul. I believe there&amp;#039;s a small piece of him that believes all of the bad things that are said about him. A piece of him believes he got the top Spot by being the personal valet of the kliq and he got higher by marrying into the McMahon family and that he&amp;#039;s not as good as HBK, Rock, and Taker. If Triple H can turn the fans and the boys against the Rock, it also changes Triple H&amp;#039;s place in history. Rock becomes a jerk, and Triple H becomes the guy who persevered bravely and clawed his way to the very top (The latter story is already the one that WWE pushes.) 
 
HHH doesn&amp;#039;t mind being # 2 on the all-time list behind HBK. But history has been, and is still being, re-written that HHH is the # 2 superstar of all time. Those of us who have followed for many years know that is not the case. Deep down, I believe Triple H knows this as well. 
 
No amount of money or power can make you happy when there&amp;#039;s a piece of you that can&amp;#039;t look in the mirror because you believe the person in the mirror is a fraud. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:310642:128036343</id><idPostId>128036343</idPostId><idBlogId>310642</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:310642</id><idBlogId>310642</idBlogId><link>http://www.lordsofpain.net</link><displayName>LordsofPain.net</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.lordsofpain.net/news/wwe/Former_WWE_Writer_Believes_Anti-Rock_Resentment_Is_Fueled_By_Triple_H.html</link><displayName>Former WWE Writer Believes Anti-Rock Resentment Is Fueled By Triple H</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-01T21:56:51.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:310642:128036343:329519722</id><link>http://www.lordsofpain.net/news/wwe/Former_WWE_Writer_Believes_Anti-Rock_Resentment_Is_Fueled_By_Triple_H.html#IDComment329519722</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T21:56:51.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Former WWE Writer Believes Anti-Rock Resentment Is Fueled By Triple H by SoonerJay</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://intensedebate.com/people/SoonerJay</link><idEmailMd5>f5359f5c55a0c2a1c4ba7e356f7ba662</idEmailMd5><displayName>SoonerJay</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://intensedebate.com/people/SoonerJay"&gt;SoonerJay&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.lordsofpain.net/news/wwe/Former_WWE_Writer_Believes_Anti-Rock_Resentment_Is_Fueled_By_Triple_H.html"&gt;Former WWE Writer Believes Anti-Rock Resentment Is Fueled By Triple H&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>