<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31wmn/post/2012-03-29T16:26:55</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31yos</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Deadly serious, please learn me about my misconceptions however, I may be stupid, but I am willing to learn.

Can doctors cure the common Cold? No, they can treat the symptoms, but the body has to fight  the virus.
Can doctors cure Flu? No they can treat the symptoms, but the body has to fight Off the virus.
Can doctors cure cancer? No they can destroy cancerous cells or remove cancerous cells and hope they don't come back.
Can doctors cure Aid or HIV? No.

I can go on, there are so many diseases doctors can't cure. Let me assure you its 99% your body and 1% doctors. 

Ever heard of placebos? Try looking them up and reading the research on them. The tldr is, its a pill or treatment with no active ingredient, yet it has effects on patients. People are convinced they will get better and they get better not by being cured but by their own body getting better.

Now surgeons, I guess they can be useful, sometimes you need a hole sewn up, or a fleshy thing removed, but doctors, not convinced.

Unless you take umbrage about my comments about dentists, in which case you're just American :P</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ztgyt</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/8hh</id></website><link>http://www.tofugu.com/2012/03/29/why-arent-japanese-doctors-telling-the-truth/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:08:57+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:26:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31wmn</id><link>http://www.tofugu.com/2012/03/29/why-arent-japanese-doctors-telling-the-truth/#comment-479854640</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hn2sc</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>