<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/234352/post/86320894/comment/329726470</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Pitchers and catchers have their bags packed and are ready to report to spring training, so it seems only appropriate to release my Top 100 overall rankings and get the conversation started! These rankings reflect my thought process in a few areas of this season\'s draft strategy, such as focusing on scarce middle-infield positions; enjoying hitters who hit for power while also stealing bases; waiting a good, long time for starting pitchers; flat-out avoiding closers in the early rounds; and, of course, the most important part of any draft, having fun. You have to enjoy not only ranking players, but drafting them. With that, here are my thoughts! For ESPN\'s overall rankings, . 1. , OF, : No suspension? Works for me. Welcome to No. 1, Mr. .2. , 1B, : Edges out the next guy in part thanks to pending third-base eligibility, but also because his lineup is better.3. , 1B, : Of course, it\'s not like he\'ll be bad for his new team, either. It is worth noting, though, that no other Angels hitters made this list. Yep, must have just missed!4. ,burberry borse, OF, : Falls short of 40/40 again,ghd site officiel, but barely. In other words, he\'s legit.5. , 3B/OF, : In 2012, he will lead the majors in home runs. Again.6. , SS, : Might not produce the numbers of other top 10 guys, but consider the position he plays. You don\'t want to get stuck with starting at your middle-infield Spot for you.7. , OF, : A future MVP, and it could be this season.8. , 2B, : Peace of mind and consistency, and the fact he plays second base doesn\'t hurt.9. , SS, : Clearly I have no concerns about him  back strong, moving to third with a smile, stealing plenty of bases, playing nice with new manager Ozzie Guillen, nada.10. , OF, : Must be a major slump pending when he hits only 25 home runs.11. , 2B, Boston Red Sox: Surprise! Position scarcity rears its head to some degree here, but the numbers are there as well.12. , 3B, : Brings the potential for a home run title, and he should add at least 30 points to last season\'s batting average.13. , 1B, : Nothing\'s wrong with him. He\'s still very much coveted,Villboy, but position scarcity works both ways.14. , 2B, : He\'s so injury-prone that he has posted 30-homer, 30-steal campaigns in two of the past three seasons.15. , 1B, Boston Red Sox: He\'s not going to hit 40 home runs, but he\'s still a pretty safe option.16. , OF, Colorado Rockies: Don\'t feel guilty at all that a good portion of his numbers are supplied by a friendly home ballpark.17. , SS, Miami Marlins: Just know going in that he\'s not likely to play in 150 games. We can live with that. The Marlins have three valuable shortstop-eligibles in Reyes, Ramirez and , and they should combine for 120 stolen bases.18. , 1B, Detroit : Upon signing with the , I moved him up more, past Adrian Gonzalez. But upon further review, I think he fits better here.19. , 3B, : The hatred for this fellow is flat-out unwarranted. Look at his 2010 numbers. He\'s terrific and will  back. In fact, quite a few Mets are worth owning (,burberry borse!), though no others made this Top 100.20. , OF, New York Yankees: I thought about pushing him out of the second round, but a 35-homer season with the steals and runs still makes him worth it.21. , OF, Miami Marlins: If you said only two players would hit 40 home runs this season, I\'ll predict Bautista and this guy.22. , OF, : If you ask me who could eventually pull a Matt Kemp and threaten 40/40, I\'d say this guy, although the power isn\'t quite there yet.23. , SP, : Finally, a pitcher. There\'s just too much SP depth to miss out on a top hitter.24. , 3B, Texas Rangers25. , SP, Detroit : Could have the same season but win, what, six or seven fewer times?26. , 1B, New York Yankees27. , OF, Philadelphia Phillies: Seems to me the team\'s new cleanup hitter will put up his best numbers yet.28. , SP, Los Angeles Dodgers29. , 3B, : Really, who is safe to play in 150 games? This guy sure isn\'t.30. , SP, Philadelphia Phillies31. , OF, Texas Rangers: I have no idea how many games he\'ll play, 90 or 120 or 140. But I think he\'ll hit when he plays.32. , SP, : Not exactly a slouch, and still an elite K guy.33. , OF, : Seems a bit overrated to me now that he doesn\'t steal bases. Pence seems more likely to produce the non-Colorado numbers we\'ve come to expect from Holliday.34. , 1B, : A future Votto, and a really safe pick.35. , SP,Shawne Williams Stats, News, Videos, Highlights, Pictures, Bio - New Jersey Nets, 36. , 2B/OF, Tampa Bay Rays: The second base part is really important. I realize I like him more than most, but the 20-homer, 20-steal potential and versatility is nice.37. , 3B, Boston Red Sox: Yes, he\'s not the most durable fellow, but I don\'t know why people think he\'s done. He hit better than .300 the three seasons prior to 2011. Why assume his 2011 season is the new him?38. , SP, Philadelphia Phillies: Hopefully the contract talk doesn\'t affect him negatively.39. , 3B, San Francisco Giants40. , OF, Texas Rangers41. , 3B, Toronto Blue Jays: Yeah,lisser ghd, I\'d say I like this \"future Ryan \" quite a bit. Enjoy him while he\'s playing third base!42. , SP, Los Angeles Angels: Terrific season, but like Verlander, don\'t assume a high wins total.43. , SP, New York Yankees: With him, you probably can assume the wins.44. , 2B, : Not as much power available in drafts as there used to be. Some of it comes with a bad batting average, but so be it.45. , SP, Milwaukee Brewers46. ,burberry sito ufficiale, OF, Cincinnati Reds47. , SP, Boston Red Sox: This year he won\'t have a poor September.48. , SP, Los Angeles Angels49. , 2B, Philadelphia Phillies: Showed he could still run a little, collecting 14 steals (without being caught) in 103 games in 2011.50. , SS, Philadelphia Phillies: Still produces enough numbers to warrant this rank, even if he misses some time.51. , 2B, Cincinnati Reds52. , OF, Atlanta Braves: Others will rank him better, and it\'s not that I foresee a bad season, but there\'s speed available late, so he\'s not a must-have commodity early. Tough to fill a Spot this early with a nonfactor in the power categories.53. , SP, Tampa Bay Rays54. , C, : Yep, he\'s my top catcher. Love the walk rate, and I expect a considerably better batting average.55. , SS, : Won\'t double his home run output, but he doesn\'t need to with all the hits and the 20-plus steals.56. , 1B, : He\'s still reliable, and there\'s no reason to think the run ends this season.57. , C/1B, Texas Rangers: Some will point to his massive second half, when he hit .383 with power, but we can also learn from his first half, when he hit .232. Don\'t pay for the extreme of either half.58. ,Ryan Johnson, SP, Milwaukee Brewers59. , SP, San Francisco Giants60. , SS, Texas Rangers: Like Starlin Castro, he should develop some power. But I\'ll say he doesn\'t  double-digit home runs this season. 61. , SP, Tampa Bay Rays: I\'d say his 2011 numbers are more likely than his 2010.62. , 1B/OF, St. Louis Cardinals: I\'d say his 2011 numbers are also more likely than his 2010.63. , 3B, New York Yankees: What is it about all the hate for the New York third basemen? A-Rod could still hit 30 home runs.64. , SP, Los Angeles Angels: All the facts suggests he\'s safe, considering he thrived in Texas.65. , SP, San Francisco Giants66. , SS, Cleveland Indians67. , OF, Cleveland Indians: Think about how much you loved this guy a year ago today. Hey, he had a rough season. Doesn\'t mean he\'s done.68. ,Nike Mercurial Vapor Elite, SP, Arizona Diamondbacks69. , SP, Arizona Diamondbacks70. , OF,burberry sito ufficiale, Kansas City Royals: Whenever a top prospect struggles for a few years, we\'ll have to remember what Gordon did in 2011. I don\'t think he\'ll do much more this season than he did in 2011, though.71. ,burberry sito ufficiale, OF, Philadelphia Phillies: Didn\'t run as much in 2011, but he remains productive. Watch out for the durability issues and enjoy his cameo on \"Hawaii Five-0\"!72. , RP, Tampa Bay Rays: Meet the AL Rookie of the Year. I generally don\'t talk up young pitchers, but this fellow will dominate.73. , SP, Washington Nationals: Nothing to fear here, other than him hitting his innings limit by September.74. , C, Atlanta Braves75. , OF, Washington Nationals: Won\'t be winning a batting title anytime soon, but he\'s still good for a 20/20 season.76. , OF, Tampa Bay Rays: Hurts the batting average quite a bit, but he still offers a terrific power/speed combo, and he\'s only 27 years old!77. , 1B/OF, Washington Nationals: The power is legit, but that batting average has to drop some, hopefully not more than 30 points.78. , OF, Tampa Bay Rays: I might be overrating him some, but his skill set will translate, and he\'ll run a lot. I say the Rays win the AL East. 79. , OF, Seattle Mariners: Go ahead and give up on this guy, then watch him hit .300 with 40 steals.80. ,ghd diamond version, C, : I\'m not sure who could possibly be disappointed in him still.81. , DH, Boston Red Sox: How many times have you written him ? Power is down across the league, so even filling your DH Spot early with this guy makes sense.82. , SS, New York Yankees: We know many people have written him Off. Of course, I\'m not one of them, but still this is about the latest he has gone in a draft.83. , SS, Chicago White Sox84. , SP, Boston Red Sox85. , SP, Chicago Cubs86. , 1B, Atlanta Braves: Word is he\'s in great shape. Perhaps everyone is in February, but I think he\'ll continue to emerge.87. , SP, Cincinnati Reds: Leaving Petco Park can\'t help him, but he\'s still good enough to succeed.88. , 1B/3B, Texas Rangers: Won\'t supply the home runs, but he\'s safe in batting average, and with that lineup he should knock in 100 runs again.89. , C, : Speaking of batting average ... Yes, he\'s an injury risk, and no, I don\'t think he\'ll ever hit 20 home runs in a season again. But when healthy, what other catcher could win a batting title? Not sure I\'d choose a catcher in the first 10 rounds in a standard one-catcher format,Burberry Lady Bags, but still what a bargain.90. , OF, Baltimore Orioles91. , OF, New York Yankees92. , RP, Atlanta Braves: Ah, a reliever. Finally. I\'m not worried that I won\'t get Kimbrel in any leagues. He\'ll likely go four rounds earlier. Saves are saves, and there\'s much turnover. If we knew for sure he\'d fan a million hitters again, that would be different. But we don\'t.93. , SP, Washington Nationals94. , OF, Atlanta Braves: Well, I\'m clearly buying low.95. , 2B, Milwaukee Brewers96. , SP, Toronto Blue Jays97. , 2B, Seattle Mariners: didn\'t make my top 100, but he didn\'t miss by a lot. And the Mariners have to score more runs this season.98. , OF, Milwaukee Brewers 99. , 3B, Milwaukee Brewers: I\'m not a big fan of him, but he still slips into my top 100.100. , OF, Boston Red Sox: Wow, look how far he has fallen! But consider he could miss a good amount time, and when he returns he\'ll be hitting sixth or seventh.So what do you think? Anyone too high or too low? Who\'s missing? Share your thoughts below, and I\'ll chime in with some more of mine as well. To see Eric\'s full top 100, you must be an ESPN Insider. 
 
[WORDPRESS HASHCASH] The poster sent us \'0 which is not a hashcash value. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:234352:86320894</id><idPostId>86320894</idPostId><idBlogId>234352</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:234352</id><idBlogId>234352</idBlogId><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog</link><displayName>Wanton Wordsmith</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/</link><displayName>The day he went away</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T05:01:09.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:234352:86320894:329726470</id><link>http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/#IDComment329726470</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T05:01:09.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The day he went away by hljfeos2097p</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://nikefrchaussures.com/</link><idEmailMd5>d51388f675db167a99d60462264ee36a</idEmailMd5><displayName>hljfeos2097p</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://nikefrchaussures.com/"&gt;hljfeos2097p&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.wantonwordsmith.com.au/blog/2011/10/the-day-he-went-away/"&gt;The day he went away&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>