<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7ib8/update/2012-03-30T15:33:46/0b0d54d066f2f5ef2ee8544e6f36714cc6b15524db6c628fcc157067c70a0f9e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>While all eyes were on Spain and the eurozone firewall (which is actually exactly where the Germans said it would be before the Eurogroup meeting – i.e. there would be no new money), France has released a lot of statistics that reinforce the view that EU politicians have no strategy to deal with current economic conditions except the usual levers of increasing tax and austerity.

 France was very pleased to announce that its deficit last year was o.1% below target at 5.2%.  However, at the same time its debt increased to a record 85.8% of GDP - a full 25.8% above the Maastricht criteria.

Income and capital taxes have increased by over 10% since 2010, and additional business taxes have been raised by the suppression of reliefs and VAT exemptions.  Social security contributions on employees have increased by over 4%. 
 
Whilst central government is congratulating itself on keeping expenses down and only increasing its debt ‘modestly’, the indebtedness of local authorities and the social security budget ‘has increased notably from the previous year’ as they took out lots of long-term loans at the end of the year.  These plump pigeons will doubtless come home to roost at some point.

Meanwhile, INSEE, the French equivalent of the National Audit Office, hasn’t even bothered to count the billions France has lent to prop up the euro, because like repayments of car-loans to the state, ‘they have no effect on net debt because they affect both the assets and liabilities of the public finances.’  Hmm.  So what exactly do these debt figures represent, then?

Meanwhile the sudden burst in French GDP last month is dismissed in Les Echos as a ‘one-Off’ due to the exceptionally Cold weather; household spending on energy shot up by 11.7% in February because of exceptionally low temperatures.  New car sales have dropped by 20% in the first quarter, and the Salon de l’Industrie is particularly scathing about politicians’ efforts to stimulate the economy – not one presidential candidate has bothered to attend their annual exhibition, yet all profess to be committed to industrial growth.

Plus ça change…</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z3h0n</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/finance/debt-crisis-live/9174995/Debt-crisis-Live.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T07:16:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:33:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7ib8</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/finance/debt-crisis-live/9174995/Debt-crisis-Live.html#comment-481109690</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hahvk</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>