<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw1gpw/post/2012-03-30T23:42:08</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwbul7</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h091e</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>1) No, evolutionists do not hold that is the first stage of evolution. That is the origin of life, something very distinct. They can in fact explain it, as well as replicate parts of it, and provide a reasonable basis for it having happened.

2) Actually, things have added to their genomes and given birth to more complex organisms regularly. This is most commonly seen in things like the Flu virus which produces new strains constantly, as well as drug resistant strains of bacteria and the like.

3) With various colonial organisms, the line between single- and multi-celled organisms is in fact blurred. While the actual transition has not been observed, the evidence to support it having happened exists, rather than the equally unobserved, unreproduced, and unsupported assertions of creationism.

4) As with 2), yes they have. And we actually can see this regularly with mules coming from horses and donkeys. Just because no speciation is happening right at this very moment does not mean it can never or has never happened.

5) In fact billions of mutations are observed constantly. Against with 2) we see this regularly with bacteria and viruses, and we can even observe it with pesticide resistant insects.

6) No, they are called "missing" links because they have not yet been discovered. It may even be they cannot be discovered because their physical forms would not leave fossils.

7) No it isn't. Just because no animals are currently mutating and giving birth across the warm-blooded/Cold-blooded divide does not mean it is impossible. It can easily be seen in things like snakes that related animals can lay eggs that incubate, lay eggs that hatch instantly, or carry eggs that hatch internally and then give birth to live young. Likewise snakes provide easy evidence for variations in carrying and delivering venom, and recent discoveries show connections between venomous snakes and venomous lizards suggesting a different evolutionary relationship.

8) Plants have not needed intelligence and so they have not developed it. Just because a particular evolutionary modification is an advantage for one type of creature does not mean it will be an advantage for all types creatures. Instead plants have developed a large number of variations of their own, including deciduous versus evergreen, perennial versus annual, herbaceous versus woody, and many many more.

9) That is because plants and animals are two different evolutionary branches. Once a branching point is Reached, organisms will not spontaneously flip type. Of course that does not prohibit parallel evolution, and we do actually see things like "carnivorous" plants.

10) Trilobites had a wide variety of eye types among different species. Some had compound eyes, others were completely blind. That a particular eye type was discovered before it was previously expected does not make the principle of evolution wrong, it merely makes the previous expectations wrong. People once believed atoms could not be divided. That did not make molecular theory wrong, it just meant an assumption about a particular unit of the theory incorrect.
Overall you demonstrate exactly why attacks on evolution are so often dismissed out of hand. For the most part you make nothing but wild declarations that are not merely wrong, but actively contradicted by available evidence, and insist they disprove evolution completely, along with a couple of other declarations regarding things that actually have nothing to do with evolution showing that you don't even know what evolution is about to begin with.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67hozm</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ju4p</id></website><link>http://www.breitbart.com/Big-Hollywood/2012/03/30/dukes-schneider-fired-for-questioning-evolution</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T20:55:23+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T03:42:08+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw1gpw</id><link>http://www.breitbart.com/Big-Hollywood/2012/03/30/dukes-schneider-fired-for-questioning-evolution#comment-481497478</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hi7dk</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>