<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk6fzc/delete/2012-03-25T10:44:44</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk6x32</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yss4k</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>...liberals dont like it when you dilute their kool-aid with facts.....The news media does not like to report on such things where someone defends themselves with a firearm...locally look at the story about the grandmother who stopped a robbery....she was mocked by all of the liberals, and the sunherald likely received a lot of grief over it...nationally look no further than Florida and they are cruxifying Mr Zimmerman for using a firearm to stop an assault against him

1. Liberal Democrats Hate Gun Owners


Gun owners, as a general rule, are more conservative and are more likely to 
vote Republican. Gun owners are also more likely to join the Armed forces and to 
give unqualified support to our troops. Gun owners are also more likely to think 
it was a good idea for people like Richard Nixon to go after communists like 
Alger Hiss. Many gun owners supported the Vietnam War. Some of them allowed 
themselves to be drafted and others went so far as to enlist of their own 
accord. These, however, are all things that liberal Democrats despise. If gun 
owners are in favor of these hated things, guns must be very bad.

2. Gun Control as a Means to Attain Political Power

Many misguided people have an honest aversion to guns and would prefer the 
enactment of strict gun control regulations. In this great country they are 
entitled to their opinion and to vote their beliefs. The liberal Democrats know 
this and use these people as a means to win elections.


The liberal Democrats are actually an unholy alliance of single issue voting 
blocs. The liberal Democrats believe that they can win at the ballot box if they 
support the following issues and groups: abortion, homosexuality, affirmative 
action, opposition to school vouchers, anti-religious sentiment, radical 
feminists and big labor unions.


Gun control is just another special interest in their bag of tricks. The best 
example of this is the assault weapons . Every rational person knows that the 
 eliminates certain guns based on cosmetic features. Bayonet lugs and flash 
suppressors do not make semi-automatic guns more deadly or more suitable for 
criminal use! However, the assault weapon  is the ideal wedge to use in a 
Heated political debate. ("My Republican and Libertarian opponents are against 
the assault weapons Ban!")

3. Liberal Democrats Hate African-Americans

Despite their protestations to the contrary, much of the push for gun control 
comes from liberal Democrats who want to keep guns out of the hands of black 
people. Los Angeles, Chicago, Washington D.C. and New York City are places with 
large minority populations and very restrictive gun laws.


Also, the people who push for gun control come from cushy places where 
minorities are not welcome (except as servants). How many working class 
African-Americans hang out in places like Brentwood, California or Beacon Hill 
and Hyannis, Massachusetts? People who do not want minorities to have guns like 
gun control.

4. Liberal Democrats Hate the Constitution 

The Constitution protects the individual rights of individuals and it 
protects individuals from the State. Liberal Democrats hate this. They believe 
that they know what's good for us, how to use our money better than we do, and 
they know whether I should be allowed to carry a gun on my person to protect 
myself, my family and my Synagogue. How else do you explain that liberal 
Democrats find a right to abortion emanating from the penumbra of the 
Constitution, but cannot seem to find any individual right at all in the Second 
Amendment?</body><verb>delete</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r5044</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnde</id></website><link>http://www.sunherald.com/2012/03/24/3840429/coroner-handgun-used-to-kill-child.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-25T04:31:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-25T14:44:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk6fzc</id><link>http://www.sunherald.com/2012/03/24/3840429/coroner-handgun-used-to-kill-child.html#comment-475830795</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/89iry</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>killed</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>