<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mic25g/update/2012-03-22T13:48:35/c669a16736d1595f6cd76d49816dd91c509232250691d895791e41f92409afda</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Heejun needs to go home. It was like watching bad karaoke last night and he is getting worse each week. He does not deserve to be there and especially does not deserve to be going on tour, yet he is because he has some sort of minority vote and he apparently makes people laugh. I think he should start taking this seriously because by being there and messing around he is screwing other people out of their dreams. Sorry for the rant but I don't agree that America is voting to keep him there.

I agree that Jessica is an amazing singer but I also am having trouble connecting with her. I feel that each week she is getting even more disconnected. I want so badly to love her but I just can't. I agree with the B+.

I love Hollie. I think she has a great personality. Sh had a few Spots where she was ever so slightly Off last night but she was still amazing. She sings with loads of emotion. She is my favorite girl and I hope she does something fun and upbeat to show us she does not just do ballads. I almost with the judges would suggest that to her before America gets bored.

Colton was absolutely amazing last night. It was perfect for him and I can feel his emotion in every song he signs. He wants this so badly that it just seeps out of him every time he comes on screen. I hope he stays for a long time.

I also love Skylar. She knows exactly who she is and does not let anyone change her. It's great and she's got an amazing country voice. She has shown that she can sign any song and make it country but still keep it beautiful so everyone loves it.

I hope Heejun leaves as he should have last week.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ymhq2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/mmtc</id></website><link>http://americanidolnet.com/american-idol-2012-top-10-performances-recap/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T02:42:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T17:48:35+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mic25g</id><link>http://americanidolnet.com/american-idol-2012-top-10-performances-recap/#comment-473791829</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>