<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3im0x/post/2012-03-29T21:10:03</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m390au</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Megan,
I still disagree some with your ideas, but not your obviously decent intent. I don't think condemning people's motives or ideas is wrong. I think it's legally unnecessary, usually unhelpful and sometimes dangerous as explained. If those hung at the Nuremberg trials had been proven to all fit into one of two groups (those who exterminated Jewish people out of hate and those who did it out of apathy not wanting to buck the system), I wouldn't have needed to know which group the murderers were in to vote for hanging. Nor would I vote for hanging any of the horrible people who shared Nazi ideas but never Acted on them. International lawyers often claim a need for such categories and seem to like generating them, but I am underwhelmed by what such distinctions have done compared to dealing with behavior. When toothless Klansmen meet in the forest to say ignorant things, there's a reason we start the arrests when they start Burning property or hitting people. Likewise, the hateful comments often made in the church President Obama embraced were not good cause for his or other's arrest. Hate often leads to crime, but the phrase hate crime often misleads. Best wishes to you.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hju4r</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7smk</id></website><link>http://matadornetwork.com/change/gay-mans-death-to-lead-to-anti-discrimination-laws-in-chile/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T23:09:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:10:03+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3im0x</id><link>http://matadornetwork.com/change/gay-mans-death-to-lead-to-anti-discrimination-laws-in-chile/#comment-480100593</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zhb0i</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>