<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwb7tp/update/2012-03-30T21:42:40/43838560e6e1da11532aff47b5d0a61fd943e2fb29a43de0b1f7adb774ae2918</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I  find it hard to get the Simnels right. Either they are too hard or too soft, too small or too big. I remember the Spring of 1972 when we collected a marvelous Bounty of Simnels just outside the village in which I lived in Suffolk. They were growing at the edge of a field, just far enough away from the road to avoid all the usual problems that come with Simnels and passing traffic.

Of course one can grow ones own Simnels but they do require fairly poor soil and not too much water which, in these times of drought, should mean that next year's Simnels should be as good as this past year's Sloes.

Preparation is of course the key. One must soak them overnight to remove the husks and then again for two days in Cold tea (try Earl Grey or Lapsang for an alternative) before adding them to the mix. Weeding out the Garnels is essential as everyone knows. One year I got distracted while someone came to the door and when I returned I continued as though the Garnels had been picked out and the results were dreadful. 

Remember to Turfid the mix well once the Simnels are added and before adding the flour or the Simnels will stick to the other fruit. There is nothing anyone wishes in their mouth less than a Simnel firmly adhered to a tricky bit of raisin, but I needn't point out the obvious.

This year we have enough Simnels to make two cakes, roughly 4lb each so we will be well pleased if they come out. I'm trying a new way of dealing with the Garnels this year. I'm using a ricer as a neighbour said it worked well for her last year. If anyone knows of a simpler method that is quicker than using ones fingers please let me know.
.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6760pk</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/comment/telegraph-view/9176260/A-good-slice-of-simnel.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:39:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T01:42:40+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwb7tp</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/comment/telegraph-view/9176260/A-good-slice-of-simnel.html#comment-481416689</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/eizxn</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>