<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrqwz/update/2012-03-30T12:17:37/176dc23e0c9a0f300e1652a171dd7446bf938c207b57e31f7d3c6478194834d0</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3sbjl</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zywb0</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Thank you for providing those things about Trayvon. My nature craves those stuff. I want to know more about his parents, more about Tracy's fiancee who by default must remain in the background. I am not just satisfied about the crime that has been committed; even though, without which, I wouldn't be needing those biographies in the first place.

From a standpoint of life being a one-time shot; in which we're here to focus-on, and please God more than we focus-on; and help each other find happiness here on earth; we naturally feel that a greater loss has occurred when someone as promising as Trayvon goes so soon. Such an occurrence has the potential for us to lose hope, rather than increase the good that Trayvon stood for, in the best way that we can. I used to view life that way too, but no more.

If we could think from the background that whether or not there is a God, and whether or not this is our first incarnation; we're all here already, and must find the best ways to negotiate this journey called life. We know that it is better to feel happy, hopeful and empowered at every moment; than sad, hopeless and dis-empowered. And with assiduous mindfulness, we really can remain happy and empowered more often than not. I know that with absolute surety, because that's who I have become. And believe me, I had never known anyone to be more dysfunctional, depressed, you-oriented and utterly foolish than myself. Matter of fact; I would bet that God or whatever name we give that power; would not have allowed more than one specimen "as far gone as I was" to reside in each zip code. (lol) 

So, if feeling empowered; all or most of the time, is what we all prefer, then it makes sense to  that any thought or philosophy we daily marinate in, is one that can ignite and maintain feelings of empowerment on demand. It really doesn't matter if we go down on our knees and pray to God, Allah or a stone. When we get back up, we really should feel more happy, empowered and energized. We shouldn't have to fake it until we make it, when dealing with any power called God. And that power should be able to gradually reduce and remove our grief, even for our most beloved loved one.

Every human already fears; or is uneasy about his mortality; I know that. I think that psychiatrists now have a special designation for this universal fear called Terror Management Theory. It seems that fear of our inevitable ending, can stir some people to do evil things. So for that reason alone, I think that humanity deserves a more improved paradigm of life. Obviously; individuals experience different degrees of fear and coping, thus we all don't end up doing evil.

For me; once I started to get a glimmer of the understanding that my life is already eternal; all of the burdens started to leave. Up to that point I would spend hours thinking of how I could execute the plan of capturing, tying-up and castrating the persons who sexually abused me as a child. It would be executed with a Cold dull knife, to prolong their agony. Had I not left Jamaica I probably would've harmed those people. But then again; I was one of those who'd kept those experiences suppressed until I arrived in Chicago in 1982. Oprah came there in 1984 and started talking about such things, and my sleeping memories awoke. I became incensed, and was consumed with thoughts or returning home to exact my revenge. Obviously I didn't. 

In 1984 I was also introduced to the Buddhism that Tina Turner practices. For the first time in my life I heard the idea of life being eternal, and that whatever is happening to us now, is due to causes we made in the past, and our future will  on the thinking we now maintain. Instantly my inner soul connected to that idea. Gradually I accepted the possibility that in a previous life I was the abuser, and that my abuse in this life was reaping what I sowed, to wash-away my sins, and chart a new course for future lifetimes. Still, it was a struggle to let go of the baggage of programmed beliefs that insisted that I remained stuck. 

Today I am no longer a practicing Buddhist. It gave me what I needed to start healing. It was great. I still believe the overall philosophy, but I have moved on. The same way with Christianity. I know without a doubt that a lot of wisdom is still in the Bible. But it has deliberately been corrupted over millenniums, for: racist, political, social and other reasons. The nonsense I find in the Bible outweighs the good, which can be obtained from many other sources or just plain common sense. So to me it serves more to compel the masses into giving up ownership rights to their lives. It encourages naturally You Oriented persons as myself to be even more so. It encourages some to think that wanting to be happy  is sinful and selfish. Many have the ability to not notice the abundant nonsense in the Bible, and thus remain empowered; without having the abundant nonsense seeping into their awareness to contaminate their daily mental state. I do not have that kind of tunnel vision focus.

In any case, from the standpoint of life being already eternal, and that each has been here before and can be here as many times after, as preferred; death is seen as a natural transition, and not a loss. 

That does not mean that one does not still feel the pain from the death of another. The majority of humans are afraid even to consider another possibility, therefore it is natural that the majority of us, still respond as had been done for millenniums. And even for those who've started to think differently; once confronted by the actual death of a loved one, all of what we're trying to make our default, might fail us for a while. We may  just like everyone else, until someone shake us back to the new beliefs that are still there, but not yet fully matured. That very thing just happened when the husband of the woman who brought the world the  died. She too lost it for a while. 

But from a death like Trayvon's, one sees the way that we can all consciously make the world a better place. One life shouldn't have to be sacrificed for the majority to learn lessons that all could learn at once. But that's the way it is right now. And if we're all eternal, then I have to believe that the departed have to have agreed to this situation at some point in time too. We can now decide to test the process, even if we don't fully understand. We can customize the human evolution or heaven in our imagination, with each moment, year, and century of our collective: thoughts, actions and intents. We can commit to multiply the good Trayvon had started, by committing to be good in every way from this moment on. And we needn't worry about being doomed when we don't live up to our own standards, just get back up and start again. We can replace "what ifs" with more "what nows". We can replace "if onlys" with "now I will"

Even though he and his parents were demonstrating how everyone could better serve each other; how many of his peers had followed his suite? How many of his parent's friends were doing what they did? Don't you see that even if guilt is what will now Propel some, many more can now get positively involved, and more communities will be better, thus the world will be exponentially better from those trying to honor Trayvon? And isn't that what we all want? More individuals doing more good as the default condition of life? And if life truly is eternal, then aren't we securing a better world for his return. And while we cannot prove that, wouldn't just thinking about it have more potential for present happiness than worrying if his soul can still be saved by God? 

Would grief not be shorter in duration, and and have less of a destructive impact on our system, if we more easily got ourselves to look at life this way?

So while you still may disagree with me, can you better appreciate where I am coming from? Can you see that I am not coming from a place of coldhearted, uncaringness, but rather from a place where much critical thoughts had gone? </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zq95i</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ewhe</id></website><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/trayvon-martin/trayvon-martin-case-frank-taaffe.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:02:34+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:17:37+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrqwz</id><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/trayvon-martin/trayvon-martin-case-frank-taaffe.php#comment-480909254</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ahv96</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>