<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw1xx7/post/2012-03-31T00:12:26</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I am a licensed clinical social worker, but not fully versed in eating disorders. However, a lot of the research that I'm doing around food lately tells me that processed food w/ MSG, sugar of any kind, (fructose is included), and grains often trigger food cravings, binges, and increase the risk of depression/Anxiety immensely. There's been some talk that how your gut absorbs food directly impacts your neurotransmitters---mind-body link. I'm currently craving sugar like a madwoman, but I know it's roughly equivalent to cocaine in its effects. No sugar/wheat/corn for me! Just gotta get past the cravings first. ;) 

PLEASE don't go raw vegan for very long--we need fats to absorb fat soluble vitamins, and many nutrients are better absorbed cooked. Also, the NIH/Pubmed has shown pernicious Vitamin B12 deficiencies even after years of no longer being vegan. 

Some books that got me very interested in eating for nutrition instead of calories/macronutrients: 
Deep Nutrition &amp; Food Rules by Dr. Cate Shanahan (family medicine), Wheat Belly by Dr. William Davis (cardiologist), and the UltraMind Solution by Dr. Mark Hyman---he comes Off a little quackier than the others. 

If you can, ask your doctor to test your micronutrient levels (Spectracell makes a test) and work with them &amp; a nutritionist to get balanced out. As a nation, we're overfed, undernourished, and putting a bunch of weird chemicals in our bodies that throw our hormones, brains, and weight out of control. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/dtc2f6</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/fv1s</id></website><link>http://www.medicinalmarzipan.com/2011/02/13/body-loving-blogosphere-teen-week-edition/</link><postedTime>2011-12-22T05:11:06+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:12:26+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw1xx7</id><link>http://www.medicinalmarzipan.com/2011/02/13/body-loving-blogosphere-teen-week-edition/#comment-481517907</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-12-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>