<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwiyf4/post/2012-03-31T08:16:15</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw712i</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zsri</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>What you can learn is not pissing  pretty much the majority, and spending a surplus into astronomical deficits with tax breaks.Man, as YvonneofNC correctly stated before, you're "extremely fucking stupid". Seconded.What's your problem with unions? Got a problem with them, RedVoter, because they fight for good working conditions? Did some Teamsters "union thugs" bust up your car with their lead pipes once?Jesus Tap Dancing Christ, dude. And no wonder you're totally clueless about what's going on here. You're from **Idaho**. Not very good optics if you ask me. 

Walker didn't even balance the budget, and that's just the stone Cold truth. I don't understand your asanine and retarded support for the guy. If you sincerely believe that he is balancing our budget, "doing what he promised he was going to do", and is bringing Wisconsin jobs, then you, sir, are MUCH more retarded than you already are.I think Walker's approvals are gonna start steadily goin' down once we start bombarding the TV with ads- like he's been doing since December, running Wisconsin TV stations like they're some sort of Communist propaganda outlet-- I'm serious, he runs commercials at all hours of the day and evening.And when you run a commercial where you smile and say "I didn't destroy your educational system!", you KNOW you and your State Senate flunkies are screwed.And man oh man did I jump for Joy when Pam Galloway resigned like two weeks ago. What a rube, and it served her right.Seriously, RedVoter, what the hell's wrong with you?</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67elyz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ai6</id></website><link>http://politicalwire.com/archives/2012/03/30/what_republicans_should_learn_from_wisconsin.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:01:49+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T12:16:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwiyf4</id><link>http://politicalwire.com/archives/2012/03/30/what_republicans_should_learn_from_wisconsin.html#comment-481782438</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rvsvx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>