<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwea2z/update/2012-03-30T07:45:18/6e54021c4d2abe5bec613a7fa85d8046acfa9f98213a7120ffcc826c7345f5d3</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>What the hell kind of Cry-baby melt-down was this, Stacy?

When you announce to the world that you're quitting blogging because you've failed to bully your way onto a conference panel, and then say within 24 hours that two tip-jar hits have compelled you to quit your quitting...well, you come across as a drama queen of operatic proportions. And possibly an utterly cynical guy who was really just desperate for some quick cash.

This was an astonishing  of self-abasement, because you have now positioned yourself as the blogger who threw that big, fake hissy fit.

Learn from this. You tried your Telford shtick on Hale -- whine and attack in hopes of getting what you want. But it turned out she had more steel and more self-respect than you. I'd say your habit of throwing tantrums when you don't get the gigs you want may well be the primary reason now that you don't get the gigs you want.

You've made a point in the past of Banning commenters who criticize you, saying indignantly that you aren't going to let anyone stay who slags you on your own turf. You've been a dick to Hale, and she's given you a taste of your own medicine, albeit with some sugar. She was still willing to let you attend, even though you slagged her, and tried to put words in her mouth to make her look bad, and made nonsensical claims about having been offered a "scholarship"  to her free event.

</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zkn2y</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6v5j</id></website><link>http://theothermccain.com/2012/03/30/i-write-for-money/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T05:49:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T11:45:18+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwea2z</id><link>http://theothermccain.com/2012/03/30/i-write-for-money/#comment-480651422</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>