<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw9shy/update/2012-03-31T03:36:18/f9c8a009e4dfaaec3ca5035c58b01b4f3fa6e666f16e434ac8a8fdcef8af6360</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwt6gj</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rnyfa</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I do agree with much of what you say, and I am not trying to disagree with you. I'd like to agree. I'm listening. But again you say "Historically this has  been the precious metals especially gold but also silver and for even smaller transactions the base metals such as nickel or copper. "

That is just not so. In many (all? most?) African societies gold was not valued as something for trade in ancient times, so we learn, and in oceanic nations, shells and other beautiful things were used as currency. Who started this thing about gold, diamonds, silver, platinum, and who owns those industries? Which group? And when did that start? See it started by the same group who then went on to create banks, and purchase up all those "commodities". 

There is no use giving value to that which they now monopolize. How about a totally NEW currency, allow me to put forth a new idea:

You said "This "money" is the commodity or good that is completely fungible i.e. is valued by everyone in the market in relation to every commodity good or service and is universally accepted as the medium of exchange, store of value and unit of account."

I'll use that as the basis for putting forth our new thinking to you. Your above statement, while true, could be extended. The VALUE being given, should be given by that community yes, and it should include things like what even a PERSON or ENTITY has contributed to the good and benefit of that society. Via holding power in People's Conferences and nomination (selection/election) of People's Committees of capability of supervised execution of the decisions of the people in the community, the people thus hold political (decision-making and implementation/execution and supervision/monitoring/transparency) authority.

But what of wealth. And what "new" currency. To allocate this again to the old system of fake money, or "precious metals" (why? that is just arbitrary, why LIMIT wealth and then put it in the hands of those who can hoard it, or monopolize it?), instead of this, a new currency is created by the VALUE I mentioned above, and which is decided in those conferences and that community adapts a new ALGORITHM/mathematical formula, let's call it "mathaba theorem":

And this is only a rough first thought, and should be worked upon!

Value of entity = unit green dinar X value factor of service provided in the past, or currently X time scale (day, month, year) X weighting factor

Example. Green Dinars are not paper, gold, or anything else, they are securely digitally or in some other non-manipulative form with clear tracking and verification and security, held in whatever form but can be checked for that account.

Let's say the entity is me. Let us say, I am 48 years old. Let us say that for the last 30 years, I am well known and can be shown to have worked 90% of that time of 12 hours per day, in creating something which was a private bank, that siphoned  the wealth of the community and resulted in suicides, illness, poverty and other ills. 

My Green Dinar account will be: (1 X 0.5 X 365 X 30 X 0.9) X -1000

i.e. 1 unit Green Dinar X half of each day X 365 days X 30 years X 90% of that time multiplied by value factor NEGATIVE 1,000. Thus the VALUE attributed to me by my society, which holds the power and already decided the -1,000 value for bankers who helped no one, upheld the enemy of the people, did not care, benefited from it to factor x or y, etc, thus the value of me is:

MINUS 4,927,500 Green Dinars. I.E. I am in DEBT to society by about 5 Million Green Dinars, if I calculated this correctly.

Now, it is up to society what they do with debtors of over 1 million Green Dinars. Execute them? By what means? Restrict them to the community or banish them, forever or a length of time (in preference to "prisons" which should probably be abolished, that is a subject for another time, insha Allah). Or put them to work to pay  the debt, give them freedom to pay Off within a certain time, to be re-evaluated later?

Or, let us say that for the past 30 years, I was a different person, spending 90% of 12 hours each day non-stop working for awakening to the very democracy which is now adopted, and news media that is now popular and adopted and warned and exposed, spoke truth to power, was abducted, tortured, abused, but my ideas and work has been now accepted world wide and in fact brought about radical changes and helped many of those who wanted change but did not know how to get it... perhaps my value would be:

(1 X 0.5 X 365 X 30 X 0.9) X 10,000 = 49, 275, 000 i.e. 49 million Green Dinars.

Now the airline charges me a ticket to visit France, at 1,000 green dinars, my groceries cost 100 dinars, my house was provided free of charge for life (and that of my heirs) because I started with a credit of over 1 million dinars, get the picture? Instead of being PENALIZED by losing money on things you NEED, you are rewarded, and also instead of being REWARDED for being thrifty, clever, Cold, narcissistic, manipulative, opportunistic, you are PENALIZED.

On the other hand, some very forgiving communities, may just decide, hey we're all average, no one in our community or nation really did anything very great bad or good, or, we forgive and forget all that, and we're going to give EVERYONE a free house, free electricity, 5,000 Green Dinars for each child born, 60,000 GD for marriage, and half the price of each car. And a starting capital of 999,999 Green Dinars for each and everyone. But from now on, the above equations will apply.

To me this is the way forward for a real new world order based on justice and the reward of good, as determined by the needs of society, which holds power, wealth and arms to defend itself from those it banished.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/660mpm</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6ae6</id></website><link>http://mathaba.net/news/?x=630095?disqus</link><postedTime>2012-03-24T20:46:48+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T07:36:18+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw9shy</id><link>http://mathaba.net/news/?x=630095?disqus#comment-481625181</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8nq14</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>