<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qb09/post/2012-03-29T12:03:41</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3v7ls</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/aqh7n</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Hollie's song was a pagent song because she just didn't connect to it in so many ways.   It hurt somewhat knowing her very suburban upermiddle class backround (even leaving asside the british born side of her)

A poor white girl,  single mom with a baby,  probably from the sound of it still going to a few bars and spending her money on cigarettes perhaps...worried about paying for necessities,  putting her child in jeaporody and an icy road in front of her in  a Cold world.   How is Hollie going to bring that home?  Well,  an actor can, but it is a hard role for her to relate to in anymore than a stereo type way... I'm not sure she's even driven through tiny poor white towns in the midwest on her own and had a chance to observe and contemplate the girls who live there,  and how a jacket she wears might be a weeks work.

Then on top of that, you bring religion in.   Perhaps the religion part could fit better at a pagent,  but we all have certain types of faith,  and unless she's in the habit as calling god by name in a Tim Teboe style excercise of faith, there just isn't going to be that "love of god" expressed in the chorus as it calls for to bring that song alive.   With some method  I suppose all is possible but that deep sort of transformation even of faith is a heck of a job to truly carry Off.

Just missing,  turns what can truly be a sublime expression of a very real human reality that exists for many young ladies in position of the girld in the song,  into just a pagent song.   Its the miss that makes it that way.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h0kkl</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q17i</id></website><link>http://www.mjsbigblog.com/american-idol-11-top-9-vote-for-your-favorite-performance-poll.htm</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T02:24:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:03:41+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qb09</id><link>http://www.mjsbigblog.com/american-idol-11-top-9-vote-for-your-favorite-performance-poll.htm#comment-479606822</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cs61</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>