<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tum4/post/2012-03-29T10:06:51</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body> 

I
have to disagree for 22 reasons. http://thelibertyblog.org/tag/rick-santorum/   Rick Santorum will NOT win Pennsylvania in the Republican Primary. 
The
better the Voters get to know him, the less likely they are to vote for him.
The latest poll shows Rick Santorum in a dead Heat in his alleged home state
(Pennsylvania). http://pittsburghlive.com/x/pittsburghtrib/news/state/s_788643.html 

My prediction is that Mitt Romney will win the Pennsylvania Republican Primary.



Rick Santorum's Rhetoric does not conform with the reality
of his record of ever expanding Big Government Spending and Debt, Medicare
Prescription D, votes to raise debt ceiling and against Right to Work,
Earmarks, re authorization of New Deal Era Export Import Bank and so on.Rick
Santorum is a phony. 


There seems to be a collective amnesia about his record. How
does this work?



Rick Santorum is not The Forgotten Taxpayers BFF.


It is fascinating to see how Rick Santorum  clouds the
minds of principled grassroots conservatives who should know better  and
the conventional media which writes narratives without any in depth
research.  



oh well...if you can fool enough of the people enough of the
time, you will do well in the polls. 



What a disgrace to Pennsylvania’s conservative base and what
an insult to Pat Toomey is Rick Santorum wins Pennsylvania.




Compare and contrast Pat Toomey Video (edited) http://paindependent.com/2012/03/video-u-s-sen-pat-toomey-offers-passionate-defense-of-capitalism-at-pa-leadership-conference/ 


</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yhonv</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5wxx</id></website><link>http://www.phlmetropolis.com/2012/03/can-santorum-win-pennsylvania.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T09:03:31+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:06:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tum4</id><link>http://www.phlmetropolis.com/2012/03/can-santorum-win-pennsylvania.php#comment-479513790</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/7iyq</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>