<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi65ll/update/2012-03-22T21:32:10/15f1af53eddd17d801d8745bfdbf810ee5354ee18ac378b1843ec4a23bd097be</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mie30c</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/56eus</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Some flaws and some insights.

1) Climate has changed a lot historically before humans were on the planet.  YES.  But the idea that we have NO idea why this happened is false.

2) CO2 absorbs infra red.  The amount is known, the amount of CO2 is known too.  So it has an absolutely calculable effect on temperature.  We also can account for the CO2 increases in the atmosphere pretty closely by calculating how much fossil fuels have been Burned.  Those calcs are known and dirt simple.  There are many feedbacks, especially with regard to water vapor and clouds that complicate things.  But, you know, I don't blame you for not believing it.  You shouldn't just be a sheep.  But you should read more about it in serious works, not pop media--the more you do the more you will see.  


3) Is the current temperature "optimal" or would warmer actually be better? YOU MAY BE RIGHT.   But we are pretty invested in the world around the current temperatures.  Look at what a wonder modern corn is, and how much of our life Depends on it.  Now imagine a change in climate won't let us grow that.  Our crop lands are limited now--you can't just pick them up and move them, right?  Bummer eh? Can't happen?  Look up pine beetle on google.   Also, look at sea level rise.  Not going to be a problem in Central PA, but in Manhattan and Bangladesh, probably.  

4) Science is not public policy.  You can believe the science and still say that you don't want to spend a dime on it.  That is a perfectly viable position.  There's a thousand things wrong and criminal that cause enormous human suffering in this world that I don't do anything about.  Why should global warming be different?  But the science is actually pretty firm.  

Raise your bottom line.  You can do it.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y6yfa</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yzhh</id></website><link>http://www.centredaily.com/2012/03/22/3135590/realities-behind-the-climate-change.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T05:03:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T01:32:10+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi65ll</id><link>http://www.centredaily.com/2012/03/22/3135590/realities-behind-the-climate-change.html#comment-474123900</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c7rqs</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>