<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/218769/post/127378275/comment/324956718</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Avery isn&amp;#039;t just learning how to shoot.  He is a very good Spot-up shooter who simply hadn&amp;#039;t found his confidence and rhythm until he got enough minutes.  If you read any of the reports on Bradley going into the draft, they ALL note that he is an excellent Spot-up shooter - not just OK, but very good (see DraftExpress, for instance).  He isn&amp;#039;t really a long-range shooter, but the corner 3 seems to be in his 15-20 foot Comfort range.  If defenders shade him to the hoop in order to prevent the back cut, he can sit in the corner waiting for a swing pass.   
 
I am turning into the president of the Avery Bradley fan club.  He can play D like you just don&amp;#039;t see anywhere else.  He pushes the ball up the floor.  He hits jumpers.  He throws down big dunks.  He has a nice raport going with KG.  I hope the Cs hang on to him for the long term, because he is a serious baller.  And he is still really young - just turned 21 in November.  Keep doing it, Avery. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:218769:127378275</id><idPostId>127378275</idPostId><idBlogId>218769</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:218769</id><idBlogId>218769</idBlogId><link>http://celticshub.com</link><displayName>Boston Celtics Basketball - Celtics news, rumors and analysis - CelticsHub.com</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://celticshub.com/2012/03/26/avery-bradley-death-by-a-thousand-cuts/</link><displayName>Avery Bradley: Death by a Thousand Cuts</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:39:52.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:218769:127378275:324956718</id><link>http://celticshub.com/2012/03/26/avery-bradley-death-by-a-thousand-cuts/#IDComment324956718</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:39:52.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Avery Bradley: Death by a Thousand Cuts by CG12</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>f215c4fe4485c5fae14d0acf5c109ef2</idEmailMd5><displayName>CG12</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>CG12 commented on &lt;a href="http://celticshub.com/2012/03/26/avery-bradley-death-by-a-thousand-cuts/"&gt;Avery Bradley: Death by a Thousand Cuts&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>