<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwx9zu/post/2012-03-30T20:57:03</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I kind of believe him. Idk how he did it but heres little story. Im a normal person I just graduated hs a year ago im 19 and i dont do any drugs. I mean.. I smoke bud every here and there but nothing worse than that. But one day I was standing in my kitchen and I waking a pb and J sandwich and I kept feeling the condo building i live in moving as if it was swaying like a tall tower does. But there are only 3 floors and this building is not that tall and its long horizontally. But yeah i finished making the sandwich madd quick b/c i was sketching b/c i felt the building swaying and so i picked up my sandwich(it was on a napkin) and i turned to my right and took one step and next thing you know my sandwich was back where it was before i picked it up and i was like dropped right back where i was standing when making the sandwich... my eyes were open and everything but everything happend fast in a flash. It was like a black flash.. if that even makes sense. everything turned black for a fraction of a second and i standing in the Spot i was in seconds ago and my pb and j was put back. -____- dont believe me if you dont wanna.. but i aint lieing. I've even had an instance where I was in the middle of class and my pencil just rocked forward Off of my desk and my friends were like.. Wtffff o.O</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hgo43</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/u6cr</id></website><link>http://www.worldstarhiphop.com/videos/video.php?v=wshh1458j9ux0P7wVYYD</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T06:48:59+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T00:57:03+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwx9zu</id><link>http://www.worldstarhiphop.com/videos/video.php?v=wshh1458j9ux0P7wVYYD#comment-481384175</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lig02</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>