<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwycz7/post/2012-03-30T10:26:56</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m33zpv</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mvd5</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Your point is valid and well taken. All humans are here to find happiness in whatever we do everyday. Some people seem to be born happy and stay happy. Some have to work hard to find it as I did. There are many right ways, and what works for one may not work for others. Christianity does not work for me, and that's all right, because now I have found what works for me. 

I often think a lot of young people struggle unnecessarily with God fear and confusion, and that it is a sin for them to not be told any other way. So I know I go overboard sometimes thinking that such persons need to be given permission almost, to think another way, or just to honor the opposite of convention, that their gut tell them is right. If Mother Theresa remained committed all her life, only for us to know after her death, that she too had doubts about God, then I believe that the time is way overdue for people to be allowed to hear other ways of thinking. Look at the lines of agony on that woman's face while she was alive. Now we can be sure that they were lines of agony about God. It just did not work for her, but she felt that she had to pretend that it did.  

Something greater came out of you and Dollarbillphil calling me out anyway. I now realize that I truly might have been experiencing something like being high on drugs. I still haven't re-read what I wrote, but I will. I haven't because I was aware of writing some really disjointed stuff somewhere else. When I started reading it over (after posting) I got too stressed because of the way I mangled, jangled and tangled my pronouns and other things.

Its one of those sites where you can't edit after posting so I had to leave it "as is". I believe that the Grio or Discus is becoming that way too, in a more covert way. Here we have the option to edit, but often after editing your comment is not re-posted. So what's the point of leaving open an option to edit, if using it deletes?

When I got in my bed last night, I started laughing uncontrollably. It was a good laugh. I make myself laugh sometimes just to change my mood; as Norman Cousins advised. However, once I became aware of my laughter, I wanted to know what was so funny, and I couldn't figure out why on earth I was laughing. I still don't know. It Dawned on me suddenly that I'd reverted to eating a lot sweet junk, since I realized how poorly the Sanford Police handled this case from the beginning. In the past such a thing would throw me into instant depression etc. thus I would know to stop. This time however I had reverted to those things for at least two weeks, culminating in the greatest amount at one sitting between Wednesday night and yesterday, but I didn't get the usual physical discomforts then depression. 

In the presence of many other healthy habits which I'd developed and stuck with, (to the point where I no longer need to force myself to do them, and apparently even do them without thinking) sugar couldn't overpower me as it did before. That's good; it certainly beats depression, but clearly its nothing I want to indulge. Now I have lost my "destruction indicator" so to speak. We don't need to loose sensitivity to Heat for example; otherwise we wouldn't realize that our finger on the hot stove is Burning, until we smell the odor of barbequed meat.

Now I am understanding what Gary Null or someone else said about sugar, -that it is just like cocaine. I am wondering if the same part of the brain involved in depression, is the same part involved in being high. After-all sugar was the common denominator in these two opposite states, so wouldn't it have affected the same part.? Now I need a Dr. or Nutritionist to explain this to me. Its really exciting! You guys have now initiated this Ah! Ah! moment, which I must explore. So thank you. And now I can really take a break from commenting as Dollarbill suggested, because I really need to explore and understand this aspect of myself. Have a great day!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zq95i</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ewhe</id></website><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/trayvon-martin/trayvon-martin-case-frank-taaffe.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:02:34+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T14:26:56+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwycz7</id><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/trayvon-martin/trayvon-martin-case-frank-taaffe.php#comment-480794487</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ahv96</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>