<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mim55q/update/2012-03-22T17:40:22/b621a308e4b21cc3f41dacb839d38a5df87eab90cbec418c3c7aae917e270582</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miedn1</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cadvp</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>sigh, we have gone over this so many times, Dude, and you still don't understand my point.

First, you think I am impressed when Santos beats the teams in Brazil, with neymar toying with the defenders? you think this is about neymar winning or losing? You think I blamed Ronaldo for anything when Brazil lost the world cup, while he was 21? I did NOT.

Here's my case: Brazil has NOT win the world cup without having the BEST player in the world (C.S. also made this case). Do you not agree? Is Neymar currently the best player in the world? No. Is he close to being the world's best player? No. In MODERN TIME, has a Brazilian become the world's best player in Brazil? No.

I am not expecting Brazil to win the world cup in 2014. So, even if Neymar goes to the world cup (while he plays in Europe), and Brazil still loses, I wouldn't mind. He's still young, and he would learn a lot from the loss. Like I said, Brazil has never won the world cup without having the best player in the world. But, does that mean that we have  won the world when we have the best player? No, of course not. There are exceptions to every rule. But, you tell me, what will be  the difference between neymar moving to Europe this summer, and after 2014? If, as you assume he can Reach his full potential while playing in Brazil, then where is the need for him to leave at all? He should stay then, and let us pray that he will be the first Brazilian player to become the best, while in Brazil (again, In modern time).

If we cannot conclude anything from a tournament, then from what can we make our conclusions from? National teams do not participate in leagues. So, if tournaments (cups) are irrelevant, then there was no need of firing Dunga. There is no need of firing Mano. Who is talking about style? In a world cup, once you hit the knockout stages, then it's "you lose, you go". And, yes, style is going to be VERY important in deciding your chances. The Zico/Socrates generation did not win ANYTHING. Do we play only to play "beautifully", or do we play to win? I never said dunga's style cannot win. But if you're playing crappy football BY Brazilian's standard, and you can't even win the world cup, then what's the point to keep playing the same way. If just because Dunga did not win doesn't mean that the style isn't good, then why not keep it? How many world cups would we have to lose with his style before we change it? And I really don't think Dunga's "combative attitude" created anything, and you cannot prove that either. In fact, Dunga inspired A LOT of respect and discipline from the players because he was so straight minded. The players knew that none of them had a secure Spot. Again, I am not interested in how many games Socrates's team win. History DOES NOT remember that. History remembers trophies (combined with style). And how many trophies did Socrates win? Did they receive a trophy for having won so many games? What is the point of football, anyway?? If you cannot win the most important games, then why does it matter. 

I don't know if you watch basketball, if you do, then Lebron James is a perfect example of what I am saying. GREAT basketball player! He's not only efficient during games, but he plays BEAUTIFULLY!  What's his only problem? he does NOT show up in BIG games! So it doesn't matter how many games he's won. Or, how many beautiful moves he makes. At the end of his career, what will mostly count is whether he has a ring or not. And he knows it! Maybe it's harsh, and unfair, but it's REALITY. Talent is measured by what you do (concretely) with it. What did Socrates and Zico do with theirs? It's not about style. What does that have to do with Neymar moving to Europe or not? And yes, there styles that are more effective against certain teams.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/659h7s</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dd6r</id></website><link>http://brazil.worldcupblog.org/world-cup-2010/ricardo-teixeira-resigns-from-cbf.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-15T23:40:03+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T21:40:22+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mim55q</id><link>http://brazil.worldcupblog.org/world-cup-2010/ricardo-teixeira-resigns-from-cbf.html#comment-473983651</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c3z31</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-15</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>