<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwyea6/post/2012-03-30T10:30:25</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/gt37aq</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> If a parent imposes an unhealthy life-style, including food choices, and that young child became obese, would that parent be Acting in that child's best interests?  

At what point does an unhealthy life style imposed by a parent or parents become parental abuse or neglect?  

Is it abuse or or neglect if the child is 2 or 3 times heavier than they should be?  If the child is unable to walk due to excessive weight?  

Is it abuse or neglect if the child develops significant medical problems?  perhaps diabetes or cardiac disease?

"Childhood obesity however can lead to life-threatening conditions including diabetes, high blood pressure, heart disease, Sleep problems, cancer, and other disorders."

"Due to the rising prevalence of obesity in children and its many adverse health effects it is being recognized as a serious public health concern.[1]"

" Consequences of Childhood Overweight

      Overweight children and adolescents are at increased risk for 
several health complications. During their youth, for example, they are 
more likely to exhibit risk factors for cardiovascular disease (CVD) 
including high blood pressure, high cholesterol, dyslipidemia, and type 2
 diabetes compared with normal weight individuals.4 Additional health complications associated with overweight children include sleep apnea, asthma, and liver damage.4
 Further, overweight children and adolescents are more likely to become 
obese adults. For example, one study found that approximately 80 percent
 of children who were overweight at 10 to 15 years old were obese at 25.4 Another study found that 25 percent of obese adults were overweight 
	  as children.4 This study also concluded that if overweight
 begins before 8 years of age, obesity in adulthood is likely to be more
 severe. Finally, childhood overweight has psychological and emotional 
consequences. Overweight children are at an increased risk of teasing 
and bullying, low self-esteem, and poor body image" http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Childhood_obesity1. Kopelman, Peter G (2005). Clinical obesity in adults and children: In Adults and Children. Blackwell Publishing. p. 493. ISBN 978-1-4051-1672-5.
http://www.ext.colostate.edu/pubs/foodnut/09317.html 


  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/g8r0hq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/h63o</id></website><link>http://sgpaction.com/node/935</link><postedTime>2011-05-17T17:42:33+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T14:30:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwyea6</id><link>http://sgpaction.com/node/935#comment-480797902</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hngsx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-05-17</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>