<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkqebs/post/2012-03-26T01:00:15</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This Outreage is GREAT but Sadly for a not so great circumstance!  The Union Is Great.  Minorities are Really Stepping Up to the Plate and Being Heard!    How Come it was NOT all this Support One Minority to Another 2 Weeks' ago?  Must it be  be negative spin on S**t to make folks stand up and take NOTICE?  F**kED UP!    Now WE got the worst two(s) of the worst as far as black people goes, faces are smashed in as many camera's they can get in front of!    Where was JJ, Sr., for starter last week, when Chicago had 50 Shot &amp; 10 Shot to Death?  Where was JJ, Sr.?   We Sure As Hell Did Not See his Face Smashed in no Cameras When the tally added up to 50 Shot, 10 dead!   People Need to Stop Being  One(s) Sided and Call This S**T Out ON ALL UNFAIR F**KKED UP Situation/Circumstances!  Tonight THUS Far their were 3 killings in Chicago so How B**ches Going to March for Tav'onne When Blood is Spilled out On their Own Streets?  How Do they Protest Another Situation and NOT CLEAN UP THEIR OWN SITUATION(S) AT HANDS?  We Black People! Who think' for ourselves anyway, we know the two(2) Biggest Rat's A/K/A Black Civil Rights Leaders will go ANYWERE A News Camera is Pointed Outwards, we KNOW THAT!  Folk's Wake Up ESPECALLY In Chicago Since We Have the Worst Violence Going Down!  Nobody Is Going to Save US BUT OURSELVES!   As far as Fat Al and JJ, Sr., goes! They'll get their palms greased with a stack of $100.00 to Go Away, this is what they do &amp; Always have, then you got people who got themselves all worked up standing their DUMB aSS'S in the sames Spot their A"ss was standing in with nothing until the NEXT Issue at hand comes to play!  Then After That, Their Dumb ASS's will STILL be standing in the same Spot and JJ,SR., &amp; Fat Al Will Do it ALL over again!  Wake Up People!  BLACK PEOPLE!!!!!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rxjxv</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t26w</id></website><link>http://newsone.com/nation/kirstensavali/joe-oliver-im-a-black-man-and-zimmerman-is-not-racist/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T01:42:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T05:00:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkqebs</id><link>http://newsone.com/nation/kirstensavali/joe-oliver-im-a-black-man-and-zimmerman-is-not-racist/#comment-476226392</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l65uh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>