<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nb8v/update/2012-03-29T13:00:25/72baa3355083d3748957d5e5cf9ee74517f4a2e0d2fe09af3148ded71b1b98c2</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ntct</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/9kc9</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Did you read the Popper article?  Do you understand that even astrology takes an unidentified phenomenon, develops a hypothesis, and then makes predictions?  And that when predictions pan out, that they see that as support of their hypothesis?

Here's another clue - when their predictions don't pan out, they simply come up with some ad hoc special pleading to explain the discrepancy (Mars ascending, or a conjunction of a Comet they didn't remember).  Similarly with catastrophic anthropogenic global warming - data that defies the hypothesis is excused.

When you have a hypothesis that has no clear falsification, you're doing pseudo-science, not science.

"1) CO2 levels would continue to rise unless we do something to intervene."

That could happen with natural global warming, where temperatures drive CO2 levels. 

"2) As long as CO2 levels continue to rise, temperatures will continue to increase."

Falsified by 18 years of stalled temperatures while CO2 continues to rise.

"3) If we look at other planets, the atmospheric make-up of the planets will be largely correlated with temperatures."

False.  Pressure levels are correlated with temperatures.  Note Mars with its high CO2 atmosphere but Cold temperatures.

" 4) If we look at historical data, CO2 levels will mirror temps."

Also false.  CO2 levels *lag* temps.

"The point is, there is a clear falsifiable hypothesis. "

Well, if you accept those as falsifications, then we've falsified your hypothesis.  Now what?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hlxz3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/28/opinion/mann-climate-change-email-attacks/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T12:42:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:00:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nb8v</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/28/opinion/mann-climate-change-email-attacks/index.html#comment-479652280</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/awldj</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>