<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw1fik/post/2012-03-31T00:21:01</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwu9gj</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8nbil</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Your right, my comment wasn't really in answer to your question, it was more just a comment on one aspect of a theme in these comments - there's just so many tiers in this thread of comments, that I wasn't really sure where to place it! Maybe that's just my poor blog commenting etiquette. 

But I don't think it's a question I've been trained to answer. Until recently I avoided topics like this because I felt like I didn't have any answers. I still don't think I do, but I've started to think that maybe questions like 'why do bad things happen' aren't even the right questions to be asking.

In response to the question you posted, in some ways I think you are right - thanking God that he has given me stuff that he hasn't given others implies that he chose me over them to have those things, and why would he do that? And in a way that does relate to the point in my other comment - that we are focussing on the physical and temporary too much.

Rather than thanking God for my house and my job and my safety, perhaps I should be simply thanking God for his goodness and praying that I can unselfishly use my privileged circumstances of being born into a wealthy, safe country to somehow benefit those who aren't.

I don't think God micro-manages, as such. That idea is what drives some Christians crazy I think (in some cases, literally, so much that they think God is telling them what to do in every single situation down to what to spread on their toast for breakfast.)

That would create an impossible life. If we believe that God has an ultimate purpose that he is bringing about, then we would be stuffing it up 1000 times a day, because how could we possibly know his exact will every single second?

I think this can even extend to what we look at as bigger decisions than what to eat for breakfast, to even the job we have or where we live. Though they may seem big to us, I think they are still small to God in the picture of the entire world in the span of eternity. Thinking that every single decision we make is massively crucial is a little bit arrogant. Or maybe more than a little bit.

But at the same time, I believe our God cares supremely for each person individually like a precious child. I just think that care extends far beyond what we comprehend. We use limited analogies, like a parent letting a child experience something negative for their own good, because those are the limited terms in which we live. But I think despite the limitations, we can see the point. God has much more than our temporary  in mind, like a parent for a child, just on a much grander scale than we can comprehend. (Though I don't think that is meant to stop us from discussing it.)

So that's kind of the same point I was making before, but meaning, if we believe in God we shouldn't be thanking him for blessing us with creature , but for his kingdom and ultimate love and purpose which goes beyond the physical.

And really that's all a round about way of saying, I don't really know how God manages free-will vs intervention....but it's sure an interesting topic.

And I'm truly sorry if any of my ideas are terribly one sided or narrow - or at all condescending - that is something I constantly try to avoid but am  aware than I am going to be coming from a western, Christian perspective, and my own family background, and we all inevitably have blind Spots.

And there is Always going to be an insurmountable divide, when one believes there is a God and one believes there isn't, because no matter how hard apologetics tries, I think to be a Christian you can't escape that it is based on faith not incontrovertible proof and concrete answers.

And sorry for this very long comment...</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67anxb</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/qvwn</id></website><link>http://www.jonacuff.com/stuffchristianslike/2012/03/calling-god-by-his-first-name/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T11:04:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:21:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw1fik</id><link>http://www.jonacuff.com/stuffchristianslike/2012/03/calling-god-by-his-first-name/#comment-481523431</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/eu9fc</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>