<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjw7o/post/2012-03-26T14:58:33</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Question:  Everyone keeps trying to throw this particular question out:  What wouldve happened if it were a black person that shot a white kid.. lets examine that for a minute.. If the same circumstances were applicable for this reverse race case (since you all want to make it about race) Would you be defending the black guy?  Would you be scrutinizing every aspect of the white kids existence down to his attendance at school, to why he was wearing a hoodie?  Would you think that in the same circumstance he deserved to die too?? You guys are quick to try to question our motives, but what I see here is no matter what the situation, the black person is Always going to be wrong.  What would really happen in this case would be no support for this black man, no mention of his wounds he suffered.. it would be automatically assumed that since he was black he was naturally the aggressor and the stronger of the two.  You would say how the white kid was the perfect specimen of a human being that did not deserve to be murdered by this black man..  This is an assumption that I can make based on the completely racist comments you are making regarding black people.  

Examine if you will the history of this country and you will see that white people have been some of the most violent people ever!  Hanging, Burning, raping, whipping, shooting, water spraying, all of the above crimes against minorities on a regular basis and getting away with it, as if any of us deserved it.. But Im waiting on that one person to say just how much we did deserve it, which will completely justify my point!! </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r0w00</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/26/justice/florida-teen-shooting-poll/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T16:18:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:58:33+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjw7o</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/26/justice/florida-teen-shooting-poll/index.html#comment-476635672</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z65cx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>