<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/136753/post/26057847/comment/329629128</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>News of collective land to be sold, yesterday, the Shenzhen Luohu District, grass Pu Qingshuihe villagers driving a  of limousines rights, and claimed: BMW! the Southern Shenzhen Urban Planning and Land Resources Committee directly under the Administration of the relevant person in charge confirmed that the grass Pu Qingshuihe Stock Corporation allocation of land. It is understood that the agreement of the Government and the company, this piece of land can only be developed by the village collective, can not develop, nor can it be for sale. If verified these illegal activities, Planning and Land Committee will be severely punished according to the contract, However, in 2007, cooperation company chairman Liang Wei secretly to the above allocation of land to partner companies accounted for only 20% the proportion with two other companies to develop real estate. Leung Wai new admit, he really was caught taking bribes, Luohu People\'s Court also scheduled a crime. But he believes that this was a miscarriage of justice, he does not intend to pursue and apply for state compensation, which does not affect him to continue as chairman and secretary of the community. response to grass Pu Qingshuihe Industrial shares Cooperation chairman Liang Wei Hao car Rights my illegal profit for the villagers is the trouble-making trouble last night, grass Pu Qingshuihe Industrial Stock Corporation chairman Liang Wei response to said this is a bunch of trouble-making stir up troubles in trouble, he has been informed of the villagers drove BMW,louis vuitton pas cher, Mercedes-Benz rights, but with behavior inferior speculation. Last night, the the Qingshuihe street official said, the grass Pu Qingshuihe the villagers have been repeatedly petition. After preliminary investigation, the grass Pu Qingshuihe Industrial Stock Corporation chairman Leung Wai new really is to amend the articles of association, but only changed the Scope of the business. He also confirmed that Liang Wei Suncorp for accepting developer bribery, Luohu District People\'s Procuratorate arrested and prosecuted. But he was released on bail. At present the case to the second trial phase,longchamp pas cher, not yet the final verdict. villagers opposed,mercurial pas cher, in 2007, the Urban Land Authority also issued in accordance with the law But in June this year, Leung Wai new or carrying villagers, without permission to pay the land transfer fees and other costs (32,378,polo Ralph Lauren,334 yuan),lunettes de soleil femme, government land acquisition and the return of the sites in the development of transfer process, a very low price will be worth billions of dollars in land cheap to developers providers. In addition, the villagers also reflected Leung Wai new bribery. accused of cheap land, Liang acknowledged that they are indeed illegal and other companies to develop. Partner companies base is thin, there is no money to develop. They can only sell the land at relatively low prices. They did not convene the general meeting of shareholders and other procedures, but doing so also to the fundamental interests of the villagers, they for the benefit of the villagers. yesterday morning, Luohu District, Shenzhen grass Pu Qingshuihe some villagers have shifted more than ten vehicles, luxury cars, open on the to Qingshuihe street road. Explained to the crowd gathered their own rights, villagers reflect the original Shenzhen Municipal Land Resources and Housing Authority (hereinafter referred to as the May 13, 2005, the two sides signed a compensation agreement, agreed to allocate 50,000 square meters of land north of Xili,louis vuitton pas cher, Nanshan District Liuxian Avenue as the development of alternate land. Agreement,Ralph Lauren pas cher, the allocation of land to enter the market in accordance with the relevant provisions to pay the premium. &amp;#30456;&amp;#20851;&amp;#30340;&amp;#20027;&amp;#39064;&amp;#25991;&amp;#31456;&amp;#65306; &amp;#36817;&amp;#30334;&amp;#21517;&amp;#22823;&amp;#23398;&amp;#29983;&amp;#21463;&amp;#32856;&amp;#22823;&amp;#36816;&amp;#20250;&amp;#36973;&amp;#27424;&amp;#34218; Workers said resign rejected since the cut wrist knife ( Fig &amp;#21021;&amp;#19977;&amp;#22899;&amp;#23401;&amp;#19978;&amp;#23398;&amp;#36335;&amp;#19978;&amp;#34987;&amp;#21163;&amp;#25345; &amp;#19968;&amp;#36335;&amp;#21628;&amp;#25937;&amp;#27809;&amp;#20154;&amp;#29702;&amp;#30572; police criticism, the father of the baby Blushing even said: I remember the police officer told Mr. Jiang said </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:136753:26057847</id><idPostId>26057847</idPostId><idBlogId>136753</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:136753</id><idBlogId>136753</idBlogId><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com</link><displayName>HOCKEYCENTRIC</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-canucks-are-more-than-one-line-and-luongo/</link><displayName>The Canucks Are More Than One Line And Luongo</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T01:36:12.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:136753:26057847:329629128</id><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-canucks-are-more-than-one-line-and-luongo/#IDComment329629128</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T01:36:12.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The Canucks Are More Than One Line And Luongo by sdiyzl63</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://www.sac-louisvuittonpascher.org/</link><idEmailMd5>23f6543da22493700c9ef1aeb7b8f330</idEmailMd5><displayName>sdiyzl63</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://www.sac-louisvuittonpascher.org/"&gt;sdiyzl63&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-canucks-are-more-than-one-line-and-luongo/"&gt;The Canucks Are More Than One Line And Luongo&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>