<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xio4/update/2012-03-29T14:10:01/4f538927e1f974b69a048e7d01cdf431ac25f23d088b19a288f261da12ad87f4</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Learn from populist rule under cronies of Caesar, as opposed to republican rule under Cicero.  Consider police non-diligence in Zimmerman's situation. If primarily driven in respect of connections of his family to the courthouse, then such non-diligence was not primarily driven by racism, but by general cronyism.  It is standing ready to counter sporadic cronyism with mass, unionized, racist cronyism that IS racist! Indeed, pre-organized, pre-meditated racism ... laying in wait for opportunity to spring traps. Thus, Dems pre-organize collectives and victim-mongers to extract doo-dads for followers, while siphoning millions to themselves. Enter pros, to shovel billions out back doors. Pros of populism organize and incite communities to erase boundaries of decency and to surrender individual responsibility to the hollow soul of the international, collective beast. The collective beast is thus tamed to amoral lusts of the most sociopathic and narcissistic of despots.

Plebe-Dems rely on populism among masses, while Patrician-Repubs rely on money and cynical lust for power. An old, repetitive pattern. Soros is simply playing maxi-Crassus to Obama's mini-Caeser. The game doesn't stop, short of everyone kneeling at their feet, as serfs. In effect, Dems --- especially of the Black community --- are used as the tip of the spear for demolishing individual liberty, merit, and responsibility. "Freedom" is conflated with release from individual moral restraint, for everyone to  for every lust --- subject only to veto of reigning despotism.

Even within such a Pandora's box, there remains strong medicine: hope. It consists with an innate, spiritual quality, which utterly defies scientific quantification. Unfortunately humanity tends not to  for spiritual hope and faith until at utmost extremity. Faith is first despised before it's finally resorted to.  That's where we find ourselves. To reduce rampant cronyism to decent good faith, we need to re-learn a few things. Things populists, atheists, and know-it-all-scientists-of-morality utterly despise and degrade.  Stiff necks will prevail until we Reach the end of the road:  to Vomit, fornication, and defecation in the middle of main street ... with children and animals.
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zcxw5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yv37</id></website><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/2012/03/m-the_trayvon_martin_case_and_the_rule_of_law.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T06:17:31+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:10:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xio4</id><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/2012/03/m-the_trayvon_martin_case_and_the_rule_of_law.html#comment-479710242</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/81w8i</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>