<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mss28n/update/2012-03-28T12:18:07/7158af20b77f9228cc1f6ea0cd1071a13c7ef1b5988b565914966fd28e052d39</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I was wondering, has there ever been reports of hooded figures without Red eyes? When I was 6 or so, I was at home, sitting on the stairs while my mum did laundry upstairs. I was looking through the banister rails which are only at the bottom of my stairs, I was looking towards the kitchen door when I saw a hooded figure, it had no face, it was just black and no feet. It just stood there, I started talking to it (apparently) which brought my mother out in concern, thinking I had opened the door to a stranger, she asked me who I was speaking too, being a medical family, wondering if I had kept a hidden Invisible Friend, I turned to her and said "That man there" but when I turned back it had gone. My mum asked had I opened the door and I replied I couldn't  the security latch. Later that day we drove together to pick my older sister up from school and my mum told her I had seen a ghost. I was thrilled, I felt special. For the next several years my house was visited by walking on floorboards, doors opening by themselves and feeling of something pushing into you as you walk past.

I would wake up every night, without fail nearly, and walk out my room, down my landing and into my mums room. I just felt like I had to do it... Like staying in my room wasn't possible.... I dunno if I was scared, but I know I did it, my dad hated it as he had to get up to go into the spare room, spouting "There is no such thing". Thankfully my mother was much more supportive, having seen several ghosts/spirits/entities in her past. We brought in a priest/clergyman who agreed to bless the house, we blessed everywhere, from my attic to my room, to the shed, greenhouse and summerhouse outside (I have a big garden). But the sounds, movement and stuff continued, until it suddenly stopped one day. I don't know if I ever saw it again or anything else... I swear I saw a Henry VIII type figure one night, but that was years after everything stopped. So......

What I saw you ask? I would say a Benedictine Monk with it's hood up... but on reading this.... Could it be a "Shadow Person"? This topic has  sent chills down my spine, I've  been mocked when I tell my tale, but my curiosity has strengthen my Resolve to learn.... I might be 22 in 17 days, but it still scares me. I also have sleep Paralysis due to my ill health and medication.... And while reading during a sunny day is all good, when it goes dark and you're all alone... It's pretty scary.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lli3y</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cd2l</id></website><link>http://mysteriousuniverse.org/2012/03/the-lurking-shadow-people/</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T03:57:19+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T16:18:07+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mss28n</id><link>http://mysteriousuniverse.org/2012/03/the-lurking-shadow-people/#comment-478504028</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>