<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m4x8m9/update/2012-03-02T09:31:00/ccae599b96f554c9f24de9ec734523115ffbb6c9f69d2b733f17cea7b67f3d40</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Thanks Dr. Ritchie for your thoughtful commentary. Unfortunately, this is an old-fashioned witchhunt, and the mob is either misinformed, cowardly, or both. The underlying idea, that physician-soldiers, some of whom have experienced the same type of war-related emotional traumas themselves, have an interest in withholding proper diagnoses to keep fellow soldiers from getting deserved disability pay is just crazy. If that were the case, what's in it for them? Is it their money at stake? Do they get extra pay when they correct a diagnosis? Of course not. All Dr. Keppler said initially, is that the psychiatrists have a responsibility to not be lazy, in essence, and put their signature on a diagnosis that in their best judgment (and judgment is Always involved) is not correct. He used the wrong words to say it, but the alternative to what he was asking for would be to just give a "rubberstamp" to a soldier's recorda and move on. I have nothing to do with the teams involved, but I  have observed Dr.Keppler's work on occasion over the years, and as a result, I've considered him to be the most professional, conscientious psychiatrist I've ever known. I've only seen the team's work up close because I know 2 patients who were seen by them. One patient had reported PTSD, which was strange because he was medically unfit from the day he activated and never deployed anywhere. The other soldier had no physical disability but suffered from somatization disorder. the team urged him to accept this diagnosis because he was unfit for duty and deserved consideration for disability due to the severe nature of his condition, but he would not accept it. As you correctly stated, the victims of this witchhunt are perhaps among the more noble, professional, and highly-trained soldiers in our armed forces. The only interest there can be in persecuting them is to achieve some sort of narrow self-interest. The true story here would be to examine the motivations of the folks gathering the firewood.  The correct action to clear the air would be to re-evaluate the soldiers involved, but it is sad to see really really honorable professionals Burned at the stake for trying to do the right thing.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yjj53j</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tedr</id></website><link>http://battleland.blogs.time.com/2012/02/27/scapegoating-doctors/</link><postedTime>2012-02-27T10:51:02+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-02T14:31:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m4x8m9</id><link>http://battleland.blogs.time.com/2012/02/27/scapegoating-doctors/#comment-454478966</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h9xzf</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>