<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3p6zm/update/2012-03-29T20:13:11/54db7bce580999d918a8fa567784f640a977ac84340a06d1bace383b125c2007</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3jnbt</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/eonhz</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Actually lets talk about energy prices.

Yes, the price of gasoline is up. Lets say you are spending $80 a week to fill your car instead of the $60 a week you were spending a few months. That means you are paying about $80 a month ($20 x 4 weeks) in extra cost to fill you car.

However, this winter we have had record high temperatures (thanks to global warming) and also record low natural gas prices, which has resulted in a much reduced need to Heat your house. Household Heating bills, whether by oil or natural gas, are as much as $200 to $300 lower per month this winter. This means the average household in the Northern part of the country has likely saved as much $600 to $1,000 in home Heating costs this winter. 

So many are spending $80 a month extra in gasoline prices, but are also saving $200 to $300 a month on home Heating bills. Therefore, the average household for many in this country has actually seen their energy costs dropping significantly, despite the higher gasoline price. 

In fact, the $600 to $1,000 of Heating savings this winter for many equals the equivalent of 7.5 months to 12.5 months of the extra cost of higher gasoline prices. 

Net-net the higher gasoline prices are being offset by lower home Heating prices for many and in fact most households budgets are better  and not worse Off at this point, so it is far from clear how much the gasoline price will impact the economy.

***

On another topic:

New CNN poll gives Obama a 54-43 percent lead over Romney, up from 51-46 percent in mid-February.

And Obama has not even really started to campaign yet and if the economy continues to improve, despite what Larry Johnson says, Romney's chances will only diminish.  

http://politicalticker.blogs.cnn.com/2012/03/28/cnn-poll-obama-leads-romney-and-santorum-in-november-showdowns/

From the same poll a very interesting result for this question:

"And, thinking specifically about the economy, which of the following is the most important economic issue facing the country today?"

March 24-25
Unemployment - 37%

Which is down significantly from 

December 16 - 18
Unemployment - 51%

This is very important, as it says that only 37% think that unemployment is the most important economic issue. It also say that 63% of Americas do not think it is the most important economic issue. 

So all this focus on the employment picture may not be as important to voters as many think. I think Romney will need a better message than just the economy.

http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/2012/images/03/29/rel3e.pdf</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zbcjv</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tc48</id></website><link>http://www.noquarterusa.net/blog/66353/obamas-economic-malaise/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:46:30+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:13:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3p6zm</id><link>http://www.noquarterusa.net/blog/66353/obamas-economic-malaise/#comment-480057055</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yrq20</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>