<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m308lc/update/2012-03-30T02:39:45/362c4278571294df1e1039e4798a4dc8176fdcd297aa1f2fb644d138d1bf97ea</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This was a great episode that featured one of the best Leonard Nimoy guest Spots EVER -- even if it was only in voice-over. I absolutely loved the Spock action figure posing gags -- somehow that reminded me of the Family Guy episode with William Shatner and his spastic physical over-. The Spock action figure almost made up for Nimoy not appearing in this episode himself. The only thing that possibly could've made this episode better was if Nimoy had a brief on-screen cameo at the end -- possibly another dream sequence wherein Sheldon talked to Nimoy as Spock.

IMO Sheldon had the A-story in this episode, even if was purely comical and frivalous.

Raj's story was certainly more character-driven and introspective, but since he's my least favourite character (Bernadette and AFF included), I was utterly uninterested in his storyline. The reason is that TBBT has painted Raj into a corner as a sometimes-funny, neurotic, metrosexual, nerdy jerk, who in the first two seasons hooked up with random women through dumb luck, but ever since the characters were paired Off, he became the odd, lonely guy. And the revelation from earlier in the season that he's filthy rich, and his crazy, bitter outburst about not having a girlfriend from last episode certainly hasn't made his character more endearing or sympathetic. So I couldn't have cared less about Raj's dilemma in this episode. Although, the face-palm-inducing, hackneyed cop-out of Howard and Bernadette giving Raj a puppy to placate his loneliness was the worst NON-resolution imaginable!

I enjoyed the Sheldon-Spock storyline so much, I'm going to disregard Raj's storyline entirely and rate this episode: 9.5/10.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ziy1y</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7d9s</id></website><link>http://tv.ign.com/articles/122/1221983p1.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T04:33:53+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T06:39:45+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m308lc</id><link>http://tv.ign.com/articles/122/1221983p1.html#comment-480326547</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hvbmk</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>