<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qaaw/update/2012-03-29T11:29:16/4a5770ed0a2ce269f12aef348f686bc89c620e7819952f9ae3895aa57e782cbe</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>"Islamism is political; it attracts angry, extreme, violent young men from the immigrant underclass who find others willing to justify their Thirst for violence, by using holy texts."

"Islam, in contrast, lacks not just Western concepts of the individual but also Christianity's historic separation of the state and religion."

Ed, first you imply that Islam, in contrast to "Islamism", is not political, and then a few sentences later you acknowledge that Islam knows no separation of state and religion. 

That means that Islam has a large political component, Ed, and no amount of obfuscation in this blog post or your previous one on this subject will change that fact.

In the real world, Muslims hold political views that are largely dictated by their religion. This is not true for members of other religions. 

In all countries with majority Muslim populations jurisprudence is based to a greater or lesser extent on sharia law. Parliaments are full of mullahs, imams and ayatollahs who usually represent the most reactionary forces in the land. They vote down any proposed legislation that might undermine the power of Islam and its grip on the population, or any legislation that might improve the lot of women. 

In ALL Muslim countries women are oppressed, minorities suffer discrimination and persecution, and basic human rights are trampled underfoot.  The 57 member states of the Organisation of Islamic Cooperation have officially declared human rights to be subject to sharia law in the Cairo Declaration of Human Rights. 

If any other political ideology gave rise to so much death, destruction and human suffering, it would be universally condemned in the West. It is only the pathological sense of guilt - assiduously nurtured by the the left-wing media and academia - that pervades Western minds that prevents Westerners from recognizing Islam for the perverse and utterly destructive and totalitarian ideology that it is. 

It is true that honour killings, female genital mutilation and many of the other abominations associated with Islam were practiced in many parts of the world before the advent of Islam and are practiced today in some primitive, non-Islamic cultures. The common denominator, however, is antidiluvian attitudes towards women, and this is encouraged by Islamic teachings. In Islam, primitive male instincts are sanctified and sanctioned by custom and law. 

You, Ed, are like the person who tells the man who wakes up with a searing hangover after a night out drinking that his discomfort is not caused by the 6 pints of beer he quaffed, because wine and whisky can also cause a hangover, and because many of his friends have drunk 6 pints of beer and more in one sitting and have never suffered a hangover. 

With false comparisons (like that, for example, between IRA terrorists and jihadists), a large dose of moral relativism, and frequent distortion of the facts (EDL members are not as ignorant of the real nature of Islam as you believe, Ed), one can fool only those who are already hopelessly deluded.  If you haven't figured it out after the recent events in Toulouse, with the killer Shouting Allah Akahbar as he slaughtered the Jewish children and their father, and the posting of the video of the slaughter on Youtube, with the bloodletting set to the chanting of Koranic verses, it is unlikely that you will ever see the light, even if they come for you some day.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hzyt0</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ms5i</id></website><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/edwest/100147680/how-islam-became-a-scapegoat-for-the-problems-of-immigration/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T14:00:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:29:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qaaw</id><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/edwest/100147680/how-islam-became-a-scapegoat-for-the-problems-of-immigration/#comment-479578390</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/86xtk</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>