<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msshyw/update/2012-03-28T12:36:32/50d729c7d4fd667196b523545b6f4a60f3d71d95bbde22c93b05f009c34c38de</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp34ri</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gksek</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Agreed sir.  Well said.   

The difference in America is that the bulk of the people "do not understand what is happening to them" ( quote from Pravda).

The United States has been slowly evolving into a fascist state since 1917-18 when  the Espionage &amp; Sedition  were passed.  These laws made criticism of the US government &amp; military illegal.  Today its even illegal to Burn the US flag in protest.  In 1948, the president was granted military dictatorial powers with the passage of the National Security , which also established the CIA.  After 9/11 the oligarchs began converting America into a police state.   Although the US still has a constitution, it was essentially scrapped on October 26, 2001 with the passage of the Patriot  and the Homeland Security Act a year later.

At present there is no constitutional law in America.  The president has dictatorial powers to wage unrestricted war whenever and whereever he pleases.  Congress is at the beck and call of the financial cartel, multi-national corporations, defense contractors and the Pentagon.  Citizen issues are an afterthought.  

The media in America is controlled by a very few giant corporations.  All news is strictly 'filtered'.  Only bland stories, issues of little real importance and stories supportive of government policy are published.   IRS statute 501.c.3 provides state revenue to religious organizations in the form of tax breaks, but also restricts clerical rhetoric against American war crimes, political corruption, and cultural debauchery.

Joe six-pack, the average American, is completely ignorant of the implications of these clear and present factors.  Neither does he want to know the truth.  As long as he can watch TV and get drunk he will happily wave his little flag and support the new American fascist police state.   Whatever you do, don't tell him the truth.  He might pull out his Austrian made glock and kill you for attempting to enlighten him.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yvi3c</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/h8a5</id></website><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2012/03/201231995523614214.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T12:10:30+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T16:36:32+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msshyw</id><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2012/03/201231995523614214.html#comment-478521142</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lv2jp</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>