<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3bfe0/update/2012-03-29T14:46:12/77118a41ad276f26cf2b3817bc0750c804b3192f1397a3bcedd6042b4287c436</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Legal, neighborhood watch programs used to be a couple of old ladies with flashlights and whistles. The cops would meet with them, instruct them on what to do if they Spotted 'unusual' activity and how to report it without becoming the story.

Now, for whatever reason, it's become armed confrontations with cowboys shooting at each other and, in the Zimmerman case, a guy who clearly has issues and followed an innocent kid even after 911 operators told him Do Not Follow the 'suspect.' 

If I drive through your neighborhood one night alone in my Jeep looking for an address, am I going to be reported as a 'suspicious vehicle' because none of your 40 colleagues recognizes my Jeep even though I've probably lived here longer than any of you? (61 years) Will I be confronted that night by one of you? Will I have to submit to a line of questioning and detained by one or more of you? 

Or can I just flip you all the bird and drive Off because I'm on a public street, have broken no laws and you guys aren't cops? 

What if I feel threatened by you and your guns after you pull/force me over with your unmarked car? Are your really willing to meet my S &amp; W .44 mag pistol over trying to find an address that night? I'm not the guy you want to harass on public streets because some nosy idiot 'thought' I looked shady.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hk66w</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6rx1</id></website><link>http://www.sltrib.com/sltrib/news/53808907-78/serbeck-campos-advocate-neighborhood.html.csp</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T21:46:30+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:46:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3bfe0</id><link>http://www.sltrib.com/sltrib/news/53808907-78/serbeck-campos-advocate-neighborhood.html.csp#comment-479749643</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gw94t</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>