<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/midvho/post/2012-03-22T19:11:02</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>No I didn't take my aspirin this morning -

a) It seriously reacts with other essential drugs I take and would cause massive internal Bleeding in conjunction with those drugs - if I was so stupid as to believe received wisdom. 
b) People do not all have the same genetic make-up and thus do not all react in the same way to individual drugs.
c) Before I had to take the drugs I now take to keep me alive my reaction to aspirin and other analgesics was atypical. They did not produce the benign reactions in me that other people then showed so it is unlikely that I would exhibit this reaction that medical experts claim is now shown. 
d) I have atypical reactions to other drugs; alkalines such as alcohol burn my skin, reaction is described as very severe; Corticosteroids produce serious reactions ranging from very painful steroid acné to water retention, strong weight Gain, Vision problems, steroid psychosis and arterial lesions; tranquillisers send me into severe Muscle spasms; antibiotics react badly with necessary medication etc, etc

So DON'T self medicate without discussing it with a pharmacist, they usually know more about drug reactions than so-called expert doctors; particularly in the UK. You may just be the one who has a severe adverse reaction and such reactions sometimes don't happen immediately but occur weeks later.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yl70t</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/health/healthnews/9158101/If-aspirin-is-a-miracle-drug-shouldnt-we-all-be-taking-it.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T07:32:55+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T23:11:02+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/midvho</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/health/healthnews/9158101/If-aspirin-is-a-miracle-drug-shouldnt-we-all-be-taking-it.html#comment-474046192</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/61b09</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>