<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m340e6/post/2012-03-29T11:26:16</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I caught the video on MSNBC and the commentary that was going on has pretty much assured I'm not going to be watching MSNBC again.


On the video.  I don't know what to make of it.  The video quality wasn't that good.  If you've ever been in a fight you know that you can take a few hits and be no worse for the wear.  Sure the next day you'll have some bruises.  But you really don't Bleed like crazy unless someone gets a lucky shot in one of the few areas where you're prone to it.  Put it this way, you're eye doesn't turn black when it gets hit, that happens after.  Also the entire hissy fit on MSNBC last night with the morons screaming "why are the searching him now, did they not search him before" was stupid.  You get searched on the scene by the cops, when you are brought to the station and turned over you get searched again!  Every time you change custody or location, they search you.

In other words, the hosts on MSNBC don't know their ass from their elbow about what happens to you when the cops take you into custody, and don't know a damn thing about fighting, boxing, martial arts either.  Instead of fessing up, they just went on wild bullshit and conjectures.  It was hysteria that would make Fox proud.

Far more damning than a video that doesn't prove or disprove anything is the cops own bungling of everything else.  The stories are contradictory, and not in a "two people witness the same set of events and come away with a different interpertation of who started what with who" that's to be expected, but as in nothing matches up at all.  Their story is directly proven to be BS from the actual audio we already have.  I could hazard a guess that the cops written report of the incident might be written Off what Zimmerman said happened with a witness and they just haven't bothered to make sure it matches up with the audio tapes.
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z2z68</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/eyjq</id></website><link>http://m.theatlantic.com/national/archive/2012/03/new-video-of-george-zimmerman-at-the-police-station/255204/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T02:57:23+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:26:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m340e6</id><link>http://m.theatlantic.com/national/archive/2012/03/new-video-of-george-zimmerman-at-the-police-station/255204/#comment-479575954</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zdttq</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>