<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ekyuzt/update/2012-01-19T08:59:32/d711c3b27cf0f1784d028db3fd0588d6edbb42534769795b907910360b3ae7e2</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>CBS what have you done AGAIN? This new format is awful. Get rid of the round table - I don't like listening to the anchor's back! I want to see a face with the voice. The camera hops all over the place and just when you settle your focus on one Spot you move to another. And please, get poor old Charlie Rose a higher table or shorter chair-he's all hunched over like an old man. Erica Hill is still great. Thank goodness you left us one familiar and professional face to listen to. Someone needs to teach Gayle King that constant interrupting is rude. When she asks a question she needs to listen to the answer and maintain her focus on the guest. The new set is too busy and cluttered. It distracts from the news-if you can call it news. I have Always been a big fan of the CBS morning news but since you dumped Harry Smith, Maggie Rodriguez, &amp; Dave Price I have been skeptical. I gave you the benefit of the doubt after that and kept watching but this latest mess is too much. I give up CBS. NBC and ABC here I come. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/di953w</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/eih</id></website><link>http://www.mediabistro.com/fishbowlny/cbs-this-morning-makes-major-changes-to-the-formula-but-do-they-work_b50457</link><postedTime>2012-01-11T19:12:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-01-19T13:59:32+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ekyuzt</id><link>http://www.mediabistro.com/fishbowlny/cbs-this-morning-makes-major-changes-to-the-formula-but-do-they-work_b50457#comment-415315385</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-01-11</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>