<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwr6d9/post/2012-03-30T12:05:59</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3wqo5</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/634h4</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Jean A - Your comments make me shake my head with sadness. You are caught up in the rhetoric Vomited by Palin's lackeys and seem to be unable to evaluate actual facts in order to form an educated opinion. I have to agree with Alex that you seem to not get it - Palin didn't  through 5 institutions unmemorably because she was working so hard to pay her way through school. Such a claim does a real disservice to those of us who fought hard for our educations (I finished at the top of my class in one of the most prestigious colleges in the country. I worked 3 real jobs with babysitting jobs thrown in and received scholarship funds to assist me. I then took a year Off to work and save up money before going on to graduate school at a top program and worked my way through that as well.) I take true umbrage to the insinuation that Palin and I are somehow comparable. She appears to be a mediocre (at best) intellect, both academically and "in the real world". She buckles under any kind of scrutiny and refuses to take responsibility for her own actions and decisions. Most of us have to stand behind our actions and decisions daily and take the spankings when appropriate. I was raised in a politically conservative family and was strongly considering McCain. When he brought Palin on board I was intrigued to learn more about her. Then she opened her mouth and sent me RACING to the Democratic party. Her ignorance is frightening and her xenophobia more so. We might as well invite Le Front National to select a candidate for us. She is a bottom feeder whose most useful skill has been her ability to tap into the fears of Americans and exploit them by encouraging poorly thought out policy and hatred. She uses religion as a guise and abuses people's faith. She is NOT what any forward thinking nation needs. It terrifies me that, in this day and age, little girls are having women like Palin and Bachmann put forward as role models.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6znamb</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/opinion/stanley-sarah-palin/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:15:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:05:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwr6d9</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/opinion/stanley-sarah-palin/index.html#comment-480896666</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zz1j1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>