<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwt1cv/update/2012-03-30T17:01:03/f1d3662fe90f20d985397aa380035783fe595a9f89d9128f6e897645b61dd0d5</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>It almost seems pointless to comment here, given the number of comment, but I need to vent on this latest update about Zimmerman's father bitching about Obama and, well, other black people.

" 'But  when I heard the recording, there was no doubt in
 anyone's mind that that  was George yelling for help.' "

Look out the window, Mr. Zimmerman. There's plenty of people who doubt it's George.



"Zimmerman, a former judge, told reporter Valerie Boey that his son 
was studying criminal justice and hoped to become a judge himself."

I am sympathetic to any parent who dreams big for their kid. But let's face reality, Mr. Zimmerman. Your kid's in his late 20's and can't even follow the simple rules of a neighborhood watch group or comply with a 911 operator's requests. Your kid's just not bench material.

" 'I never foresaw so much hate 
coming from the president, the Congressional Black Caucus, the NAACP. 
Every organization imaginable is trying to get notoriety or profit from 
this in some way.' "

Yeah, those damn black people. Always so sneaky, so opportunistic, looking for an easy dollar. I think you left out something about "reparations," BTW. But sure, of course, your family's not racist.

" 'Currently, 
he's not dealing with it well. I don't know if his injuries are physical
 or mental, but he is not in good shape.' "

Maybe he needs to be evaluated by a psychologist. If he owns up to his wrongdoing and turns himself in, the state will even pay for that evaluation!


" 'I
 wish Trayvon Martin would have been able to do a lot more with his 
life. I hope that my son can go on and do something with his life.' "

At this point, the best thing your son could do with his future is to come clean and surrender himself to the authorities. It would be a good thing--the best thing he could possibility do with his life now. But your delusions about your son's non-culpability aren't exactly helping him take that step.

" 'It's 
just very, very sad.' "

I think you and I have very, very different ideas of the severity of this, Mr. Zimmerman. When my cat died, it was sad. When your son murders someone in Cold blood, then walks free, it's not sad--it is an egregious failure of justice that threatens to integrity of our laws and our society. That's waaaaaay past "sad".</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ev3tz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ydw9</id></website><link>http://motherjones.com/node/168136</link><postedTime>2012-03-18T17:42:35+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:01:03+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwt1cv</id><link>http://motherjones.com/node/168136#comment-481194556</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yuoi2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-18</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>