<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31vtw/post/2012-03-29T16:04:57</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I haven't responded to the latest news about Trayvon Martin as I probably should've.Since his death, more deaths of young blacks followed:

http://www.blackyouthproject.com/2012/03/shooting-death-of-wisc-youth-draws-comparisons-to-trayvon-martin/

http://www.blackyouthproject.com/2012/03/22-year-old-rekia-boyd-killed-by-Off-duty-chicago-police-officer-cellphone-mistaken-for-handgun/

http://www.blackyouthproject.com/2012/03/unarmed-atlanta-teen-shot-to-death-by-private-security-guards/

The bottom line to this ongoing saga is that to be born black in this country is to be a target that must be called out, captured and hunted just for "looking suspicious". In other words the people to watch out for are the ones with black skin and African-like figures. The message being sent is that black people don't have to commit a crime to be executed by police, white people, or even other black people. They just have to "be" black. That is their only crime.
Let's not beat around the bush. Let's not excuse or avoid this any longer. The value of the lives of black people in this nation is severely undervalued. Does it sound Cold and harsh? Yes. But it's true. Sugarcoating it will not make this campaign against black life any better. It's also not wise to avoid this problem and hope that it will go away. 

Already people, mostly white, are making excuses for the deaths of these black youths, or they are trying so hard to present examples of black-on-white crime only as a deterrent to the outrage being felt by the black community. Why? Because they fear and have a deep disdain for black life while placing the lives of whites on a much higher standard. That's why we hear so many people defend Zimmerman and the police. Black lives are dangerous and worthless to them.

I immediately knew that more murders of young blacks after Trayvon will occur. It was something I was not looking forward to, but my assumption was sadly on point. These and other similar murders and the reactions given by the mainstream are proof of society's dysfunctional mindset regarding its citizens of color. To them, we are existentially suspects. We are the problems of this society. And we are the ones that must be dealt with either by imprisonment or extermination. 

If this nation is to survive, it must own up to its problems regarding color and anything not considered "normal" or American. The paranoia of the certain communities run as deep as the scars of living in a white male supremacist nation such as the United States (Yea, I said it!). This nation must get over their collective fears and hatred if it will ever survive. 

By no means is what I said an exaggeration conjured up by some "whining, over-emotional negro who doesn't know any better". This is the truth many members of my and other communities of color know full well. We know the reality of what's going on, and it may be in your best interest to head my warning: If America doesn't confront and correct it's racism on all levels, it will only be a matter of time before the whole nation collapses into itself, and it will have no one to blame but itself. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zhj54</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dhzf</id></website><link>http://colorlines.com/archives/2012/03/kill_at_will_laws.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:39:41+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:04:57+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31vtw</id><link>http://colorlines.com/archives/2012/03/kill_at_will_laws.html#comment-479831686</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mw29x</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>