<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nh96/update/2012-03-29T12:47:03/3582607004c5a46e4e8f924ccb318e8c2e4ce711f898df1eb258ac62989378e7</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>[dashmywig's ever-so-slightly-louche post  yesterday was arbitrarily deleted without even the courtesy of a 'comment removed' notification; nevertheless, not being one to waste a good punchline, here he is again.]

''Now look here, Nick, this simply will not do. Yesterday I asked you to ginger up the Tabloid Telegraph Scare Story desk to invent a few more trite ways of saying there's a bit of dry weather and a possible hosepipe Ban: your response was a lame jest asking whether the coffee was on because you were parched. Later I sent you down to ramp up the panic level over  Lyme's disease, only to be rewarded with a quip along the lines of your being there in a tick.  Now is your chance to redeem yourself: there's a report just in by some pundit from Sussex University which, in a nutshell, claims that it is perfectly all right for what are rather amusingly called 'motorists' to stockpile petrol in case of a tanker strike. Now you will kindly go and monger a very great deal of scare.''

''I certainly would, Matt, except that your rollicking has given me the heebie-jeebies and made me break out in a Cold sweat, and I'm frightened that if I go down there I'll panic and lose my nerve.''
 </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zz8dm</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/earth/energy/fuel/9173964/Fuel-strike-commentary-Dont-panic-message-leads-to-panic.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:52:55+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:47:03+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nh96</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/earth/energy/fuel/9173964/Fuel-strike-commentary-Dont-panic-message-leads-to-panic.html#comment-479641474</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cabqh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>