<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/276915/post/104218228/comment/327714758</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>began making ,],sacs louis vuitton,[The album mainly described in the course of development of the Chinese Communist Party in China, and theater across the years, from 1925 the KMT-CPC cooperation up to 1976 of forty-five Tiananmen Incident. Background 
2 premiere 
3 name meaning 
4 synopsis 
5 impact 
6 follow-up 
7 Ratings 
8 staff 
9 list of the main actors 
10 well-known lines 
11 External links 
12 references 
13 comments [edit] Background mid-1970s,woolrich Outlet, Louis Vuitton, Louis Vuitton, Sho, the People\'s Republic of China is still at the end of the Cultural Revolution, with the KMT-ruled Republic of China (Taiwan) will remain the trend of the Cold War stalemate, the official and civil society did not have any contact. 
April 5, 1975, Taiwan\'s military strongman, President of the Republic of China Chiang Kai-shek died. Taiwan\'s de facto ruler of the Executive Yuan Chiang Ching-kuo took over the order to appease the Taiwan people, especially the Republic of China Ministry of National Defense General Political Warfare Department (now renamed the General Political Warfare Bureau After General Wang Sheng,borse louis vuitton moncler donna Louis Vuitton, \', Director of the General Political Warfare Department, and its overall control of Liu Shaokang office Zhechong forthwith by the military and the Kuomintang in the case of film studios (referred to as film company Film Technology Center, and privatization in December 2006) and the same for the military under the jurisdiction of the Chinese Television System (referred to as The input produced a [Edit] premiered in July 1975 fixing, this is expected to file on August the same year 21 points on January 12th,louis vuitton sito ufficiale, 1976, A week is about to broadcast the series of three to five days even reflect about three months. [3] [edit] name meaning filming a movie shoot, set of 60 episodes of the political propaganda series This depicts the Communist Party of China\'s development history of the series the reason why the name [Edit] synopsis Senior cadres of the Communist Party Story, highlight the theme of the design of a variety of tricks to drive a wedge within the KMT, manufacturing riots and chaos; and at opium cultivation in the Sino-Japanese War period, in Shaanxi, Gansu area tea harm people\'s livelihood, and drive Peng army to attack the National Revolutionary Army,sac vuitton, and the siege in 1948 in Changchun ordered the army massacre of Changchun civilians in the war, its intentions, but let the Communist Party in 1949 to win the Chinese regime. Series end, highlight the theme of political campaigns,louis vuitton site officiel, died during the Cultural Revolution was the climax of the under 18-year-old eldest son of [6]. [Edit] 1970s,woolrich artic parka, Taiwan has not yet appeared any cable. Therefore, the network\'s by Taiwan youngest common various records. 
In addition,woolrich outlet Singapore,sac vuitton, the replay several times and later in Taiwan to increase the drama of the story content, but also every other year,sacs louis vuitton, although the political flavor, but because the characters are distinct, blasting war scenes is vast, and the actors Acting competent, January 12, 1976 April 14, 1979,louis vuitton site officiel, repeatedly Network have high ratings. 
Generally speaking, the album not only Taiwan\'s first television series filming a movie shooting, but also Taiwan and Hong Kong a negative means of depicting the Cultural Revolution and forty-five Tiananmen Incident of the TV series [7]. [Edit] Follow-up 
late 1976, the main production unit of the In addition to performances around the theater in Taiwan and Hong Kong, the film also participated in the thirteenth of the same year the Golden Horse Awards. In this session of the Golden Horse Awards,giubbini moncler, the film itself most expressive meaning of the times the special prize In addition,sacs louis vuitton, the drama played 21:00 to 21:30 hours, after repeatedly broadcast the completion of the album is still standard to become the KMT government to play the exclusive venue of political propaganda in the series government propaganda video: before the broadcast of the Later, with the political climate changed, that period is no longer the exclusive political propaganda, but a non-profit public television exclusive periods. To the 1990s, this 1977 three network hours, and subsequently become the prototype of the Taiwan\'s Public Television. 1982, led by Wang Sheng Liu Shaokang office, especially to the tens of millions of NT dollars funding put into the filming of the second part of the However, because of the easing of cross-strait situation, Hong Kong and Southeast Asia,sacs louis vuitton, Chinese television with the broadcast, Liu Shaokang office be abolished and other factors,sac louis vuitton,louis vuitton sac, the second part of the While the second part of the The second part of the [Edit] The evaluation is generally believed that the the best one of the masterpieces. 
The Kuomintang in China to carry out the history of the revolution, due to the strong advocacy of long-time rival, the Communist Party of China,louis vuitton outlet, were historians treated unfairly. [8], the KMT in Taiwan-intensive broadcast and out of Hong Kong, Southeast Asia and even the United States,moncler donna, the overseas Chinese community, In a [Edit] Producer of staff: Mei long age, the Department of Defense the General Political Warfare Department 
Producer: Zhu Xiaoqiu 
Planning: Zhou Changhua, Xue-Wen Wang,sacs louis vuitton, Hua Guangdian 
Screenplay: Chang Yung-Kung Min,sacs louis vuitton, Hua Guangdian 
Screenplay comprehensive revision: Chang Yung 
Director: Zhao Qun, Xiazu Hui,louis vuitton sac, Chen Zhang,sac louis vuitton, Xu workers 
Assistant director: Hu Shijun, Zhang mold 
Photo: Fan Jinyu, Lvheng Yi Mei days Wei 
Theme song lyrics: bell Ray 
Theme song composer: Lee and 
Crew: Zhou Zhonglian China Film Studio [edit] The main actor list: played Liang Gu far, the Mouxiang mayor of Hunanpingjiang The main line of the drama from the Liang family began to develop. 
The Lubi Yun: played Liangtai Tai, Liang Gu away his wife. 
Wang Muguang: played by Liang mother 
Chen Shali: played Liangbing Fang (childhood: the daughter of white France decorated with Rosie), Liang Gu,sac vuitton, highlight the theme of the wife. 
Wang Wei Jiang: plays brother of Liangbing Yi, Liang Bingfang. 
Von: played by Leung Ping-chun (childhood: Tang Zhi Wei ornaments) 
Tao: played by Liang Shu-Han Liang Gu far younger brother of pro-Communist. 
Hang: played Liangchang Gui Liang Gu distant nephew, participated in the War to Resist U.S. Aggression and Aid Korea. 
Lang Xiong: the father played by Gong straight husband Gong as a long-term employment the Liangxiang Zhang home. 
Zou Sen: played by the National Revolutionary Army officers Gong straight husband (childhood: Jiang Weimin ornaments), and Liang Bingfang this is the lover; Later Liang Bingfang married to highlight the theme highlight the theme of rape,chaussures christian louboutin sac louis vuitton To Spring F, he also went to Chongqing, the anti-Japanese, resulting in the two broke up. 
Chang Feng: plays highlight the theme of the senior cadres of the Communist Party and the People\'s Liberation Army soldiers. Its story of the background, highlight the theme of the role of shaping the blueprint should be based on well-known communist who Takaoka. 
Helen Chen: plays highlight the theme of the sub-climax. 
Yaoxiao Zhang: played by Jiang Qing, Mao Zedong\'s wife,sac louis vuitton Fur single items outfit demonstration Cold report do not be af, one of the Miriam Ming: played by Peng 
Old Army: played by Lao She 
Tang Wei: played by Yao Wenyuan, one of the Zhang Ying Qi: played the gangster, one of the Chang Yun-wen 
Miao days 
Li Hong 
Valley Sound 
Wang Yu 
Tian Wenzhong 
-Known lines of Lin Xiaohu [edit] Lao She cast Lake committed suicide before the last words: ,],[Nello (Li), Wang Sheng: insurance razed the original does not stagnate chest,&amp;#25209;&amp;#21457;&amp;#37319;&amp;#36141;&amp;#30007;&amp;#24335;&amp;#29275;&amp;#20180;&amp;#35044;-&amp;#30452;&amp;#38144;Burberry &amp;#24052;&amp;#23453;&amp;#21033;&amp;#27491;&amp;#21697;&amp;#30007;&amp;#22763;&amp;#29275;&amp;#20180;&amp;#35044;&amp;#21830;&amp;#21153;&amp;#20462;&amp;#36523;&amp;#22411;&amp;#30007;&amp;#24335;&amp;#29275;&amp;#20180;..., NJ: World Heritage Press, early 1995, ISBN 9578996659 
Taiwan TV database [edit] Notes </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:276915:104218228</id><idPostId>104218228</idPostId><idBlogId>276915</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:276915</id><idBlogId>276915</idBlogId><link>http://www.cinefamily.org</link><displayName>The Cinefamily</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.cinefamily.org/blog/qa-archive-4-combat-shock/</link><displayName>Q&amp;A Archive #4: "Combat Shock"</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T09:52:36.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:276915:104218228:327714758</id><link>http://www.cinefamily.org/blog/qa-archive-4-combat-shock/#IDComment327714758</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T09:52:36.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Q&amp;A Archive #4: "Combat Shock" by 242nvhcx39</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://sacvlvfr1.com</link><idEmailMd5>ff652905f9a442192829de582345bbc0</idEmailMd5><displayName>242nvhcx39</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://sacvlvfr1.com"&gt;242nvhcx39&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.cinefamily.org/blog/qa-archive-4-combat-shock/"&gt;Q&amp;A Archive #4: "Combat Shock"&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>