<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms7415/update/2012-03-27T16:19:17/289374fffd42659d779a2cc1bb224dd26c1ef08f1a5b78f8de64b35a95db99f0</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp0fp9</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zdyfg</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Alan Turley's thoughts most closely correlate with my personal experiences of 30 years working elbow to elbow as an ER physician with nurses, technologist, clerks and EMS personnel, in a dynamic tension with patient expectations, administrative short comings and harried, sometimes confrontational,  attendings as we attempt to satisfy all parties while doing no harm, stabilizing the  unstable patients and obtaining a higher leveling care for those requiring it.


Many, indeed, most comments on the inadequacy of our disease oriented system appear to be offered by those not on the frontline of point of care.  No doubt well intended but frequently, sometimes wildly missing the mark, even  lacking face validity.  Tragically I believe this characterizes the majority of those in government who legislate, bureaucrats who write and administer the regulations and organizational executives who implement the rules by which our doctor-patient interactions take place.

There are many insights and effects that can be attributed this causal chain of command.  That any genuinely decisive care is provided is an amazing feat of endurance, Burning out many in the process.  The ER has performed as a safety net, progressively less and less satisfactorily as the now in vogue patient satisfaction scores sometimes reflect.

I cannot speak as directly to other specialties, many if which are also hospital based and nearly all  with one or more hospitals.  Emergency medicine is typically responsible for approximately fifty percent of admissions in addition to its role as safety net.

I believe medical care will continue to consume or account for, if you prefer the economically  correct term, more of our national output until we invest decisively and commit to long term funded basic and applied medical research, including joint MD-PhD programs, that result in a decisive shift from our current halfway-at-best technologies to a preponderance of genuinely decisive technologies.

One measure of success will be a steady, sometimes rapid, decrease in expenditures on catastrophic illnesses.  However, like war and poverty disease will Always be with us, and with it comes an insatiable demand for medical care, now and in the foreseeable future.

In the meantime, if the past is a guide to the future - and occasionally it is not - I am not encouraged that those with an understanding of the complexities of current level of medical care delivery will be in a position to effect the legislation, administration or implementation of medical policies and delivery that currently does little more than reallocate an increasing expenditure of our nation's abundant but ultimately limited resources.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6cwsya</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/qj7o</id></website><link>http://www.kevinmd.com/blog/2012/03/onethird-hospitals-close-2020.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-14T23:02:01+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-27T20:19:17+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms7415</id><link>http://www.kevinmd.com/blog/2012/03/onethird-hospitals-close-2020.html#comment-477734980</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zlvgg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-14</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>