<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9hoxa/update/2012-03-17T02:51:07/8364b77ca4bf4c4d33d3bc4e948b9a423f7365d8f11ef1b1f4c1ecd68d43f3fb</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>You're all missing one crucial issue:
The Palestinian-Israeli conflict is unresolvable. It's not about enemies learning to live in peace and bridge gaps. It's about survival - the Palestinian militants want Israel to dissolve and Vanish.
Should Israel cease to exist just because Palestinians claim to own a land which is NOT theirs to begin with? How far in history should we go to prove they were invading the lands from which they so violently try to hold?
The reason Hammas and Jihadists do not shoot rockets to Tel Aviv (of which they have) is that they know it will bring not a targeted reaction (as happens now), but a full force war. 
A UN worker, who is supposed to report what's really going on, posted recently on Twitter a picture of a Bleeding Palestinian child, claiming it was the result of an Israeli strike... she was caught in a big fat life. Reuters reported it was a home accident (fell from a slide) in 2006!
If the UN allows this to happen without taking any responsibility, can you imagine what the pro-Palestinian 'news sources' are like?
Come to Israel. Visit Tel-Aviv, visit Ashdod, visit Sderot. Then go and visit Gaza. You'll see how far reality is from what you get from your anti-Israeli 'reporters'. 
There are 2 sides to every conflict. The Israeli side is simple: if Palestinians want to live in peace, they should stop targeting civilians and start cooperating instead of spreading lies and hatred. 
What if Israeli civilians would start making their own home-made rockets and shoot back at Gaza, randomly? Would that be a proper response to 130 rockets on Israelis schools and homes? Would that be a 'fair' reaction, or would a targeted assassination of responsible militants be more effective? </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6c9z4c</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/h7jj</id></website><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/infocus/2012/03/violence-flares-up-between-gaza-and-israel/100263/</link><postedTime>2012-03-14T16:24:35+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-17T06:51:07+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9hoxa</id><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/infocus/2012/03/violence-flares-up-between-gaza-and-israel/100263/#comment-467576821</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-14</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>