<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mlz60a/update/2012-02-20T11:21:24/1b06a6056c70ecddf55e59dd595164f0cdae9721bb98128dce6e734459b5090b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>What a mess- I liken it to traversing a mine-field on a pogo-stick. You might get to your destination, but there's a great chance of getting blown up en route. 

My feelings about this whole mess are mixed. Perhaps a bit of history will clarify things. 

I was stationed in the Bay Area in the early 80s while serving in the USAF. I was in my early stages of exploring my Pagan path, and somehow came across one of Z's Dianic groups via a science fiction convention and Marion Zimmer Bradley's group. They were mixed in with MZB's people in the East Bay. I had been sexually assaulted, and they- and Z's "Holy Book Of Womens Mysteries" helped me to heal from that particular trauma. I also went through what I now call my Angry Militant Feminist stage. Mary Daly, Z Budapest and other feminist authors stoked that fire. 

My very brief  interface with the Dianic group did not end well, though. Once I got my head back and started feeling human again, I was told that my energy was 'too masculine' and that I was not doing myself any favors by serving in the military. I was urged to stop being a servant of 'the patriarchy', and urged to leave. When I chose to reenlist, I was asked to leave the group, and was shunned. I left for my next base shortly thereafter.

I bear no ill will towards them for this action. If this is an example of fundementalist feminist sepratist orthodoxy (and to my mind, it is), they're doing it right- even if it rubs some people wrong. Some women need separate spaces to heal, and some women choose to remain in that space.  But with 30 years of hindsight behind me, it is also clear that some get stuck in the militant zealot (patriarchy victim) stage. I outgrew it. I am no longer a victim, or even a 'survivor'. Wisdom, experience, and genuine compassion have replaced my zealot militancy. I am a human being, soveriegn and complete. I own my life- the good things and the bad. My righteous anger of that time served to Burn Off the crust of hate and fear, and instead of getting stuck there, I moved on. I won.

They have their holy places. I have the multiverse. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yu5u19</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lpw5</id></website><link>http://www.patheos.com/blogs/pantheon/2012/02/should-there-be-freedom-of-religion-within-paganism/</link><postedTime>2012-02-20T15:40:19+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-20T16:21:24+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mlz60a</id><link>http://www.patheos.com/blogs/pantheon/2012/02/should-there-be-freedom-of-religion-within-paganism/#comment-444086029</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a6jli</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>