<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m33qzb/post/2012-03-30T00:47:15</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3iedo</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a8s1u</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>My ex-husband tried to use autism to overturn custody of our son (but not our disabled daughter....).

First of all, I need to disclose that I was granted Full Custody in our Final Decree. My ex was RELENTLESS in his obsession to overturn that custody.  Part of WHY I got full custody was because my ex was diagnosed by a court-appointed psychologist (as part of creating the Parenting Plan) as being "overly involved with our son, to our son's - and MY - detriment."  Overly-involved is an understatement - he was OBSESSED with him... to the point that, he didn't like what the psychologist said in the court report - so, he hired a PSYCHIATRIST to "evaluate our situation" after the divorce.  He forced me into counseling, with him, through the courts - AFTER the divorce. "For our son's sake."  He manipulated the shit out of me through the justice system, long after our divorce.  

This psychiatrist eventually acknowledged that it was my ex, not our son, that was in desperate need of his help.  And once he decided that my ex had a "Narcissistic Investment in our son" I was finally able to stop the madness. You see, the good doc finally started listening TO ME, and called our sons school counselor. And all hell broke loose - for my ex.  

She informed him that prior to beginning each session with him (at the beginning of third grade) that my son would ask her why "he didn't get his treat for being a good boy coming to see her".  After the third session, she wondered why he was in counseling; she asked him about the "treat for going to her." He said that his dad gave him treats before his "talk doctor" visits. Our son was evasive at first, but finally told her that my ex was feeding him a big bag of Skittles before each and every meeting with the psychiatrist. My ex  made 11:00AM appointments - 3 hours after breakfast, 1 hour before lunch.  And our son would miss the mid-morning snack at daycare because dad picked him up at 10:00AM.  Imagine: a bag full of Skittles on an empty tummy. 

Not surprisingly, our son  Off the walls while in the doc's office. Once the psychiatrist figured out what was really going on (he was being played by my ex...) he issued the report about my ex's Narcissism, and what he was doing to do in order to "create" conditions for an Autism diagnosis (so I would be shown as an unfit mother, as I insisted our son DIDN'T HAVE AUTISM).  My ex dropped that shrink faster than a hot rock. 

But its stuff like that getting in the way of Autism diagnoses. Its an extreme story, I know - but I think he got the idea "online" from a Father's Rights group.  So every time I hear a discussion about autism, the hair on the back of my neck stands straight on end. And I Shiver with the memories... just wanted to share that.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zefie</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/hxgv</id></website><link>http://politicalgates.blogspot.com/2012/03/palling-around-with-radicals-and.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T08:29:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T04:47:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m33qzb</id><link>http://politicalgates.blogspot.com/2012/03/palling-around-with-radicals-and.html#comment-480255358</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8ilnx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>