<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms7und/update/2012-03-27T16:26:24/5a03e5aafc1fbd0b3cc594104bfa99a4353ef9428ba8bb0c0c3225987fed1ac0</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>In the past I have used mostly pills and such, but when hangovers  seem to happen more often and the bodys age is not able to take it anymore I realized how dumb it is to poison your body even more after you poisoned it with alcohol. So I sought out natural ways to cure a HO. 
By logic something that re-hydrates you, takes out the toxins in your body and something that takes out the swelling of the brain resulting from Dehydration should do the trick. So I tried several things that now allow me to recover much faster and that with advancing age. 
Mexicans taught me about what they call "suero", translated a serum. It is Apple Juice or Apple Soda and Topochico Mineral water.  have some in the fridge on weekends. The electrolytes such as POtassium in apple juice do the trick it seems. Sugar helps too, but normally sugar makes you crash later. As do sugars in Coke and other sodas. 
If potassium and other eloectrolytes are the key, then Coconut water is also a good choice and so I have been drinking that sometimes. Has worked so far. 
Recently I discovered a japanese drink called UKON power, a Turmeric extract drink of 3.4 oz that so far has worked every time. It has artificial sugars but the main thing seems to be Turmeric. 
If the head pounding is heavy Ibuprofen is my choice since it is anti-swelling and as some person wrote below the swelling of the brain is part of the problem. 
And then water to get you to go so you can expel toxins from your body in the way it is supposed to happen. And eat liver and kidney friendly food the next day. Fat and drugs such as strong pain killers absorbed through the liver, will just make your liver more work and hence make you pay each hangover after a 20 year lease. 
The best way of course is to drink the good and expensive stuff, so you have purity in your drink and a limit on your wallet that will also limit the amount. But that is like not having sex because you can get pregnant or get STDs. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l1y82</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rp9l</id></website><link>http://blogs.houstonpress.com/eating/2012/03/the_hangover_guidebook.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T15:02:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-27T20:26:24+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms7und</id><link>http://blogs.houstonpress.com/eating/2012/03/the_hangover_guidebook.php#comment-477741320</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>