<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0amo0/update/2012-03-31T15:06:56/bc456d1bd00d69390f511cebae31f7088db705056c505acc002b312922364d9c</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I must be an outlier, given that I am anti-abortion, yet pro-choice. It's your unconscious mind, you deal with the consequences. The fact is that a life is lost whenever an abortion occurs. As long as people are brave enough to deal with this fact in an open and honest way, then I have no problem taking their pro-abortion stance seriously. Sheesh, my ex-wife and I even had an abortion once, so it's not like I'm entirely ignorant of both sides of the argument. Of course, I didn't know she was sleeping with two other people at the time. Small wonder why she didn't want the Headache.

I find it a little odd that people don't talk a whole lot about the fact that unmarried fathers in Alberta and British Columbia have practically zero parental rights. American and Canadian women flock to these places to subvert the parental rights laws in their usual place of residence. Fortunately, the courts in the US are now punishing people for this, reuniting children with their fathers and uniting kidnappers with fines and jail time. I'm pretty sure that this criminal behaviour is why some people don't take the militant pseudo-feminist movement seriously. "What's yours is mine and what's mine is mine" is a bit ... tyrannical, if you ask me.

Anyway, thanks for sticking up for everyone's rights... when it serves your public image, that is. I'll Always look up to you for sticking it to those who rape, kidnap and extort. /me rolls eyes.

As for the people talking about violence, my lovely ex-wife also gave me a lovely third degree Burn scar. It was not known to me at the time that she also abused her ex-boyfriend of 10 years. As you can see, you really have no idea what you're talking about in general. I told the police about it. They deferred the charge to a later date, to see if "things would work out for the best". That's hilarious. Ahh, to be born with a penis. Oh well.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67wed9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/agg8</id></website><link>http://boingboing.net/2012/03/31/army-of-volunteers-politely-ca.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T17:25:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T19:06:56+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0amo0</id><link>http://boingboing.net/2012/03/31/army-of-volunteers-politely-ca.html#comment-482106563</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gp0b3</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>