<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mww8ab/update/2012-03-31T12:16:03/5ae20354c404eec29d70162274f09637cbdba2e8fc344894d007887d4fda5fbe</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4w8e</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rpg2l</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I'm sorry.  For all of his authority and ability to Reach a very broad and large audience, he did LITTLE but appeal to everyone....neither hot nor Cold.  

WHY will the black and white pastors (especially the black) STOP ENABLING the raciast idiots like Sharpton, Jackson, NAACP, Black Panthers, etc etc. by not unashamedly stand up and be a real voice of truth so that those that still LISTEN to these devil inspired race-baiters hear TRUTH coming from the man of God????

SERIOUSLY..."Let It Go" sounds like nothing more than a soft message to add to his book collection.

Mr. Jakes, we have real problems, serious ones and if your idea is to go asoft-pedal YOUR VERSION of the truth, you have done NOTHING to help this nation with the great tools you have been given.

Where are the John the Baptists?  Where are the Elijahs?  Where are the MIGHTY MEN OF VALOR THAT ARE BOLD AND UNASHAMED TO NOT BOW TO THE COMPROMISE we see all around us???  When God has to send 'conservative men and women' in the media to tell the truth, because the "fat and happy" preachers are to COMFORTABLE to tell the truth when we need them to be 'black and white' and not TIP TOE AROUND SPEAKING GREY, then we are in real trouble......and that is where we are now, we are in real trouble.

Jakes, why won't you tell the TRUTH to blacks about Obama?  Do you REALLY BELEIVE THAT, that is NOT part of your job?  Do you really beleive you are not required by heaven to be one of the voices to REALLY SET THE CHRISTIAN BLACKS in this nation FREE, by telling the truth and getting rid of the garbage they have been fed for way too long?  Who????? WHO WILL STAND IN THE NAME OF JESUS BY THE POWER  OF THE WORD OF GOD AND say these evil men are liars?  That they are evil?  That SOCIALISM AND ABORTION AND TURNING YOUR BACK ON ISRAEL IS SIN??????  IT IS SIN.  IT IS AGAINST THE GOD OF ABRAHAM ISSAC AND JACOB.  IT IS AGAINST THE GOD OF T.D. JAKES.

WHY MR. BISHIP WOULD YOU BE SILENT??  YOUR SILENCE IS AN ALLEGIANCE TO THE FALSE GOD TRYING TO DESTROY THIS NATION, AND GOD'S PEOPLE.

PLEASE SOBER UP, WAKE UP AND TAKE A STAND. TELL THE TRUTH.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67y3t8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/n7fc</id></website><link>http://www.charismanews.com/us/33110-td-jakes-talks-forgiveness-in-trayvon-martin-case</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:47:31+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T16:16:03+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mww8ab</id><link>http://www.charismanews.com/us/33110-td-jakes-talks-forgiveness-in-trayvon-martin-case#comment-481959130</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7i02</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>