<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xb70/post/2012-03-29T13:58:30</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3n27b</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>This is why parents who can have moved their kids out of district, the same goes w/ great teachers and principals. Many have moved to suburban districts or private/charter schools because they're allowed to have more control over their classrooms when it comes to behavioral issues, not to mention have to worry about dealing with every person who screams that little LaQuande or Santo is getting the short end of the stick because of their socio-economic status. I've met many parents of different races, creeds, ect.. who've moved out of DISD who tell me things like this have become a true distraction and lessens the quality of education for their kids...

I hate saying this, and i'll catch Heat for it, but the DISD reminds me on the whole as a noisy, unkempt road-side zoo. Its a place where young parents who are barely into adulthood themselves either by age or maturity dump Off their unruly little troublemakers, saddling decent teachers with ever-increasing homerooms making them into proverbial cage-cleaners and the zookeepers themselves(i.e. principals) end up taking a lackadaisical approach to running their campuses by either ignoring serious issues or just plain giving up. In other words, they punch a clock for a check and thats about it...</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zruzp</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rpfn</id></website><link>http://blogs.dallasobserver.com/unfairpark/2012/03/another_dallas_isd_teacher_sus.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:01:14+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:58:30+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xb70</id><link>http://blogs.dallasobserver.com/unfairpark/2012/03/another_dallas_isd_teacher_sus.php#comment-479699423</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hywi</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>