<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzbjq/post/2012-03-30T14:37:26</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwhabn</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dsvwh</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>It's refreshing to hear from someone who has first-hand experience of the oppressiveness of political Islam. Melanie Phillips published an excellent book called Londonistan that underscores the point you make. Muslims who moved England to escape the repression in their countries of birth are horified to discover that the British government is allowing the most radical Islamists to enter the country and promote the very repression from which they fled. She positis that the strategy is to appease the Islamists in hopes allowing them to express their extremism verbally will in some why prevent them from "Acting out" in the form of terrorism. Basically, the same strategy was being followed in France and we can see where that got them. The fault lies with the West, which has lost confidence in the values that made it great. There is too much hand-wringing and apologizing for the excesses of the past, something the Islamic world never does. This Paralysis has created a vaccum into which the Islamists, aided by useful idiots on lthe eft, have taken up residence. Tragically, truly moderate Muslims, those who respect and wish to be a part of the cultures they have adopted, are robbed of their voice and marginalized while the British and European governments fete extremists who, while usually stopping short of endorsing the tactics of al Qaeda, nonetheless share Bin Laden's ultimate goal, the re-establishment of the Caliphate and the eventual domination of sharia Islam across the world.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67ajwk</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cusm</id></website><link>http://www.rawstory.com/rs/2012/03/30/french-police-swoop-on-suspected-islamists/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T11:15:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:37:26+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzbjq</id><link>http://www.rawstory.com/rs/2012/03/30/french-police-swoop-on-suspected-islamists/#comment-481052863</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a9kkg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>