<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw26h7/post/2012-03-30T03:05:59</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>THE ISRAELI ATTACK ON THE USS LIBERTY THAT KILLED 34 SERVICEMEN INJURING 170  

At 
              0800 hrs, 8 June, 1967, eight Israeli recon flights flew over 'Liberty,' 
              which was flying a large American flag. At 1400 hrs, waves of low-flying 
              Israeli Mystere and Mirage-III fighter-bombers repeatedly attacked 
              the American vessel with rockets, napalm, and cannon. The air attacks 
              lasted 20 minutes, concentrating on the ship's electronic antennas 
              and dishes. The 'Liberty' was left afire, listing sharply. Eight 
              of her crew lay dead, a hundred seriously wounded, including the 
              captain, Commander William McGonagle.

            At 
              1424 hrs, three Israeli torpedo boats attacked, raking the Burning 
              'Liberty' with 20mm and 40mm shells. At 1431hrs an Israeli torpedo 
              hit the 'Liberty' midship, precisely where the signals intelligence 
              systems were located. Twenty-five more Americans died.

            Israeli 
              gunboats circled the wounded 'Liberty,' firing at crewmen trying 
              to fight the fires. At 1515, the crew were ordered to abandon ship. 
              The Israeli warships closed and poured machine gun fire into the 
              crowded life rafts, sinking two. As American sailors were being 
              massacred in Cold blood, a rescue mission by US Sixth  carrier 
              aircraft was mysteriously aborted on orders from the White House.

            An 
              hour after the attack, Israeli warships and planes returned. Commander 
              McGonagle gave the order. 'prepare to repel borders.' But the Israelis, 
              probably fearful of intervention by the US Sixth Fleet, departed. 
              'Liberty' was left shattered but still defiant, her flag flying.

            The 
              Israeli attacks killed 34 US seamen and wounded 171 out of a crew 
              of 297, the worst loss of American naval personnel from hostile 
              action since World War II.

.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z95eo</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yjmx</id></website><link>http://www.foxnews.com/world/2012/03/29/israel-braces-for-arab-protests-on-friday/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:22:00+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T07:05:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw26h7</id><link>http://www.foxnews.com/world/2012/03/29/israel-braces-for-arab-protests-on-friday/#comment-480383619</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/819ym</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>