<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpp3hx/delete/2012-03-22T02:20:41</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Most of what I read here is and should be  Critical of the EPA, most certainly a Rogue Agency as is the Dept of Ecology in the State of Washington.  The reality that absolute power corrupts, absolutely is so true.  These agencies clearly resonate with most of us in the Rural Areas of this Country......We owe this nonsense with respect to Wetlands to George H.W. Bush, with his "No Net Loss Of Wetlands" this was the Executive Order gave the EPA as well as the Corps of  Engineers way to much power.  

What we have here are agencies that have been taken over by Radical Environmentalist, those with the intent of turning the USA into Big Box Urban Communities.  If you all recall, the Spotted Owl, that one cost entire communities their livlihoods, displacing families, forcing Logging Families into extinction...

Teddy Roosevelt in the early 1900's, said; "Behind the Ostensible Government, sits Enthroned a Government acknowledging no allegiance and owing No Responsibility to the Peopls"  A Runaway Bureaucracy then and now a Bureaucracy Out of Control.  Unionized and thumbing its nose to the public and those paying Taxes and thus their salaries.

Let's not forget the EPA and the Endangered Species Act, Wow, here's another example of just how foolish it all is.  We see Tens of Millions of Dollars being spent to enhance Habitat, however after over 20 years of Blunders, results are still indecisive.  When Queried, the so called experts can only say they need more timne and of course more money, but in the mean time,  these nitwits still intend to restrict land use at all levels...

Bottom Line, unless our Elected Officials get a grip on this, we the American People will lose.  The ability to own land of any size, farm land is of course Bottom Land, Rich and yes mostly Organic, add Irrigation and guess what, you now have a Wetland....If you'll notice our Dairies have been forced out of our Communities to the more desolate areas, away from Rural Urban areas.  

A VOTE for Obama is a Vote for Socialism and more Regulation and More Regulation and yes,  More Regulation...More Bureaucracy and yes, More Bureaucracy, more Government and More Government Employees Unionized that can never be Fired for Abuse of Power. :-( </body><verb>delete</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dpk1n</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/21/us/scotus-property-rights/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T15:01:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T06:20:41+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpp3hx</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/21/us/scotus-property-rights/index.html#comment-473368377</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zd24r</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>killed</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>