<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m33uux/post/2012-03-30T00:55:28</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m37jjh</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> I could not disagree more with this assessment of hot 26or Bikram Yoga; if only half of this was true, thousands upon thousands of Bikram yoga practitioners (or Hot 26 as it is also called) would be injured, ill or hospitalized as the practice has been in the US since the 1970s and is worldwide. After 15 years of practicing and teaching Hot 26 yoga, I can say that I have seen and heard more anectodal evidence of "things getting better" from students than in any other yoga form I practiced and taught in the 25 years prior to my hot 26 yoga affiliation (yes, I have been doing and teaching yoga for 40 years). If you hydrate well and follow the teachers instructions, you will not get injured. I have had students tell me that the Hot 26 Yoga series has helped with migraines, high blood pressure, diabetes, high cholesterol, vertigo, lupus, fibryomyalgia and more.  Scientifically proven? No. 15 years of personal experience with hundreds of students? Yes. Most people don't get this: its NOT just the Heat of Hot 2 Yoga that heals; its the Tourniquet Effect of the 26 poses, whereby circulation is squeezed  and released in a rush of oxygenated  blood. After 90 minutes, the 20 poses have applied this Effect to all parts of your body, internal and external, for full-body benefit." Milder format?" That;s another Hot 26 Yoga Secret: when your body is so perfectly worked, your mind is released and this practice is actually highly meditative. Try 3 classes and report back!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hvnez</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/jc5c</id></website><link>http://www.bocamag.com/blog/bikram-vs-hot-yoga/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T15:38:49+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T04:55:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m33uux</id><link>http://www.bocamag.com/blog/bikram-vs-hot-yoga/#comment-480260865</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>