<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9i2j4/update/2012-03-18T09:40:47/b68544604d470652fe2d88be776a09e5e77a48f137bed9c42f0e72306155560a</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9cpcx</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/e1gb2</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>First of all, skippy, you can ask that question. And you know what? The person you ask it of can tell you to buzz Off and mind your own business. If he doesn't want to answer, you don't have the right to chase him down liike a psychotic horror movie villain and shoot him for that!


As for the rest?

You don't have self defense after 1) calling the cops and being told to stand down. 2) Following the suspect anyway, and not considering the fact that you are a man following someone who a) might be dangerous--according to your own description of him, or 2) doesn't know you from Adam and might--MIGHT--think that you are some creepy pedophile/mugger/bully/murderer/psycho/serial killer, and not react too kindly to your pursuit of him. He might even, oh, I don't know RUN AWAY FROM YOU.3) To compound your stupidity, you chase the guy, somehow catch up with him and lo and behold, it's the kid's fault that this strange guy has come upon him--WITH A GUN, and you have the audacity to be shocked that this scrawny kid might not be happy at your sudden proximity and fights as if his life is on the line, although why you get so close to him when you have a gun is unclear.4) Poor baby, you allegedly (roll eyes here-we have no way of knowing if this is how it went down since the other guy would very soon be DEAD) get your butt kicked by a scrawny kid (roll eyes some more) that you've scared the daylights out of for no reason but because you're a sociopathic weirdo, and 5) rather than taking your lumps like a man, or thinking, hey--maybe this is getting out of hand, you 6) Pull out your gun and shoot the kid.I'm trying to see the self defense here. Come on, where is it? Cough it up!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/65ocgh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yzhx</id></website><link>http://www.miamiherald.com/2012/03/15/2696446/trayvon-martin-case-give-do-public.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-16T01:18:56+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-18T13:40:47+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9i2j4</id><link>http://www.miamiherald.com/2012/03/15/2696446/trayvon-martin-case-give-do-public.html#comment-468333918</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6iz4q</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-16</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>