<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/312236/post/127908609/comment/328344575</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body> on what rooms you're talking about and what type of fixtures you have.  In the kitchen you want lots of light, so if you only have a couple of light fixtures use 100-to-150-watt bulbs.  For bathrooms, 60-watt or 75-watt bulbs will usually do.  If you have lamps, make sure you check them to see if they have a maximum wattage rating (I have a couple of 3-way lamps that have a maximum of 150 watts, so I use 50-100-150-watt 3-way bulbs).  Lamps that you intend to use as a light source for reading should be at least 100 watts, but "effect" lamps can go as low as 25 watts, Depending on the desired effect.  If you have chandeliers, ceiling fans with light fixtures, or small light fixtures in hallways, you will probably need special bulbs.  Best bet there is to take one of the bulbs out and take it with you to Lowe's or Home Depot to get replacements.  In terms of brand name, the most common are Philips, Sylvania, and GE.  I've had good luck with Philips but GE bulbs seem to Burn out quickly.  No idea about Sylvania.  Good luck!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:312236:127908609</id><idPostId>127908609</idPostId><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:312236</id><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><link>http://www.denpdf.com</link><displayName>denpdf.com</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.denpdf.com/light-bulbs-light-bulbs/</link><displayName>light bulbs- light bulbs?</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T09:40:59.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:312236:127908609:328344575</id><link>http://www.denpdf.com/light-bulbs-light-bulbs/#IDComment328344575</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T09:40:59.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on light bulbs- light bulbs? by sarge927</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>4130ad4601e919e2a8ed58fa2f50b1b4</idEmailMd5><displayName>sarge927</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>sarge927 commented on &lt;a href="http://www.denpdf.com/light-bulbs-light-bulbs/"&gt;light bulbs- light bulbs?&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>