<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mion68/update/2012-03-23T22:20:01/fb840f8fc538fe8ce00a2d39943966b45a2f32394e5032daf744cd4779fb9a72</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Hooray, finally someone who isn't head over heels uncritically in love with this movie. I've had it up to here with glowing reviews and everyone jumping on the "amazing" bandwagon. I went to see the movie expecting nothing, as I haven't read the books. But being a sci-fi buff, I was completely openminded and hoping for the best. It didn't take me more than a few minutes to become really annoyed at the pretentious, constantly shaking camera work. I mean come on, how hard is it to show a  of a person or an item in someones hand, without having to shake the image so violently, that you can't focus on what's in the frame. I can somewhat accept it as a "clever" way of obscuring the violence since it's apparently such a big deal with kids killing kids these days, but it was completely overdone everywhere else in the movie. The simple task of Katniss pulling back her bow and aiming it at an animal, was inexplicably intercut to smithereens between more than 10 different shaky shots of her from every angle. Like a really bad music video made by a director without any sense of orientation. Why this overkill of annoying shakiness? By mid movie you could predict every time the next shaky 'bender' was approaching - and every time the action Heated up to somewhat interesting, it was reduced to an incoherent blur, where you had no chance of following who did what to who?

I'm sorry, but I left the theater feeling as if I had just watched the worst movie of all time. Not even Jennifer Lawrence's good  or the occasional sweeping sci-fi vistas can make up for more than two hours of crappy camera work.

And don't get me started on the flawed logic in many scenes. Worst example: Let's go blow up the supplies to annoy the boys... oh, never mind. Apparently - for some odd reason - they've mined their own supplies, so we can just set them Off. Easy peasy. WTF??

And absolutely no setup as to what society we are in, other than some vague suggestions later in the story. It's just too quick'n easy hack work.

This whole thing is so poorly executed, shot and edited, that I have a hard time believing thsi is the same guy, that gave us Pleasantville and Seabiscuit??
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/667p70</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/drg8</id></website><link>http://www.firstshowing.net/2012/review-the-hunger-games-is-fine-sci-fi-that-couldve-been-better/</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T21:03:53+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-24T02:20:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mion68</id><link>http://www.firstshowing.net/2012/review-the-hunger-games-is-fine-sci-fi-that-couldve-been-better/#comment-474984362</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>