<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw0g79/post/2012-03-31T13:14:41</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>lets try again

WARNING..Due to it's structure, this post is a bit long, but it's an easy read of about 10 minutesFor you who still think that Islam in any form isn't potentionaly dangerous allow me to share some facts with you...I have checked these numbers / accusations; and they're Spot On...Please copy-n-paste this info to read later and share with others---A-F-T-E-R --you do your own research....Wikipedia can verify the Muslim percentages around the world for you.Enjoy !...(Note sarcasm)From Dr. Peter Hammond's book: Slavery, Terrorism and Islam: TheHistorical Roots and Contemporary ThreatIslam is not a religion, nor is it a cult. In its fullest form, it is a complete, total, 100% system of life.Islam has religious, legal, political, economic, social, and military components. The religious component is a beard for all of the other components.Islamization begins when there are sufficient Muslims in a country to agitate for their religious privileges.When politically correct, tolerant, and culturally diverse societies agree to Muslim demands for their religious privileges, some of the other components tend to creep in as well.Here's how it works--&gt; As long as the Muslim population remains around or under 2% in any given country, they will be for the most part be regarded as a peace-loving minority, and not as a threat to other citizens. This is the case in:United States-Australia-Canada-China-Italy-Norway--------------------------------------------At 2% to 5%, they begin to proselytize from other ethnic minorities and disaffected groups, often with major recruiting from the jails and among street gangs. This is happening in:Denmark-Germany-United Kingdom-Spain-Thailand-----------------------------------------------From 5% on, they exercise an inordinate influence in proportion to their percentage of the population. For example, they will push for the introduction of halal (clean by Islamic standards) food, thereby securing food preparation jobs for Muslims. They will increase pressure on supermarket chains to feature halal on their shelves -- along with threats for failure to comply. This is occurring in:France -- Philippines --Sweden - Switzerland -- The Netherlands --Trinidad &amp; Tobago At this point, they will work to get the ruling government to allow them to rule themselves (within their ghettos) under Sharia, the Islamic Law. The ultimate goal of Islamists is to establish Sharia law over the entire world.-------------------------------------------------When Muslims approach 10% of the population, they tend to increase lawlessness as a means of complaint about their conditions. In Paris, we are already seeing car-burnings. Any non-Muslim action offends Islam and results in uprisings and threats, such as in Amsterdam, with opposition to Mohammed cartoons and films about Islam. Such tensions are seen daily, particularly in Muslim sections in:Guyana -- India --Israel -- Kenya --Russia--------------------------------------------------After Reaching 20%, nations can expect hair-trigger rioting, jihad militia formations, sporadic killings, and the burnings of Christian churches and Jewish synagogues, such as in:Ethiopia-----------------------------------------------------At 40%, nations experience widespread massacres, chronic terror attacks, and ongoing militia warfare, such as in:Bosnia --Chad --Lebanon-------------------------------------------------------From 60%, nations experience unfettered persecution of non-believers of all other religions (including non-conforming Muslims), sporadic ethnic cleansing (genocide), use of Sharia Law as a weapon, and Jizya, the tax placed on infidels, such as in:Albania -- Malaysia -- Qatar --Sudan-----------------------------------------------------After 80%, expect daily intimidation and violent jihad, some State-run ethnic cleansing, and even some genocide, as these nations drive out the infidels, and move toward 100% Muslim, such as has been experienced and in some ways is on-going in:Bangladesh --Egypt -- Gaza -- Indonesia -- Iran -- Iraq -- Jordan -- Morocco -- Pakistan -- Palestine -- Syria -- Tajikistan -- Turkey -- United Arab Emirates----------------------------------------------------------100% will usher in the peace of 'Dar-es-Salaam' -- the Islamic House of Peace. Here there's supposed to be peace, because everybody is a Muslim, the Madrasses are the only schools, and the Koran is the only word, such as in:Afghanistan -- Saudi Arabia -- Somalia --Yemen Unfortunately, peace is never achieved, as in these 100% states the most radical Muslims intimidate and spew hatred, and satisfy their blood lust by killing less radical Muslims, for a variety of reasons.'Before I was nine, I had learned the basic canon of Arab life. It was me against my brother; me and my brother against our father; my family against my cousins and the clan; the clan against the tribe; the tribe against the world, and all of us against the infidel. -- Leon Uris, 'The Haj'It is important to understand that in some countries, with well under 100% Muslim populations, such as France, the minority Muslim populations live in ghettos, within which they are 100% Muslim, and within which they live by Sharia Law. The national police do not even enter these ghettos. There are no national courts, nor schools, nor non-Muslim religious facilities. In such situations, Muslims do not integrate into the community at large. The children attend madrasses. They learn only the Koran. To even associate with an infidel is a crime punishable with death. Therefore, in some areas of certain nations, Muslim Imams and extremists exercise more power than the national average would indicate.Today's 1.5 billion Muslims make up 22% of the world's population. But their birth rates dwarf the birth rates of Christians, Hindus, Buddhists, Jews, and all other believers. Muslims will exceed 50% of the world's population by the end of this century.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67cbs9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/opinion/sick-israel-iran/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T12:55:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T17:14:41+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw0g79</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/opinion/sick-israel-iran/index.html#comment-482010182</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/avyfh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>