<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwlynx/update/2012-03-30T12:50:18/8bb24b052e620cdd5f82c26b02ada2a9caddfcba220d7fea3c917ff7366f5707</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwdk9c</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6epzj</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Of course you will be reading ant-B.N.P. articles, there are plenty of those around, a lot of them sponsored by other parties who seem to be terrified of the B.N.P.. If as they claim, that the B.N.P. has been written Off, what are they so scared of? Is it the fact that the B.N.P., along with other websites, are still in a position to get news accross that certain people would rather not have the public know about? Believe me there's plenty of that about.

If you want to see some real fascists in action then take a closer look at the U.A.F.. This is an organization of thugs who pose as anti fascists but in reality are the biggest fascists in the land.

Their main targets are organizations who exercise their right to freedom of speach. But if the UAF doesn't agree with what is being said then it's on with the bully-boy tactics in order to break up legal gatherings using force if need be. 

Hitler had such an organization often refered to as the Brown Shirts. The main difference with the UAF is that they are just a bunch of scruffy yobs who will do anything for their masters. It's interesting to note that our Mr Cameron was a founder for this organization of yobs. Some people refer to the UAF as the United Association of Fascists, much more accurate.

As for myself, I will keep on supporting the B.N.P. because I don't want any part of the other parties who are leading this country to disaster. My father fought in both world wars and my brother fought in W.W.2 for this country. I myself was a bomb armourer in the RAF in the 50s and 60s, hardly a job for cowards or the Faint hearted. Whether the BNP ever get to power will really be of no concern to me as at 73yrs old my time is now limited. 

But through the B.N.P. I see a glimmer of hope for future generations. I believe in Nick Griffin because as a man of the legal profession he could have made himself a tidy living without all the hassle of being leader of the B.N.P..
That's what I call dedication.

I could go on forever but I like to flick through different political sites. That and my gardening amongst other things keeps me active. So thanks for the blog. It's now time to visit an Australian site who's web master keeps me informed of what's going on in Oz and much of the rest of the world.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zh93e</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/travelnews/9173906/Stansted-baggage-handlers-to-strike-over-Easter.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:39:24+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:50:18+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwlynx</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/travelnews/9173906/Stansted-baggage-handlers-to-strike-over-Easter.html#comment-480942453</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cqovu</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>