<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ixac/update/2012-03-29T21:32:22/42f5896aed2400881f3175c1e1775ab91161f824179863888c0d27e1e1e0411f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Carbon insulates us from the void of the universe. It keeps much of 
the energy we receive from the sun contained on the planet. As the 
amount of carbon in the atmosphere grows, the ability of the earth to 
emit the Heat back out into the void decreases. 



An analogy would be a house that  has its heater on, but the 
house's insulation continues to thicken and increase its R-value, 
preventing less and less (relative) energy from leaving the house.


As the heater runs, the house's energy increases. The insulation will
 let more Heat out as the energy increases. So as the insulation 
increases (more carbon), more Heat is contained in the space. The amount
 of Heat released will also increase, but this will be dependent on the 
relative increase in internal Heat in the house and will Always be a 
fraction on the internal increases. 



Here is the crux of the matter. It takes us relatively little time to
 remove carbon from the earth and put it in the atmosphere. The process 
carbon requires to get out of the atmosphere and back into the 
boisphere/geosphere/hydrosphere takes approximately 5,000 years on 
average. 


Don't take my word for it. Learn for yourself. Assuming understanding the issue is part of your agenda. 
  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hlxz3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/28/opinion/mann-climate-change-email-attacks/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T12:42:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:32:22+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ixac</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/28/opinion/mann-climate-change-email-attacks/index.html#comment-480117495</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8klwj</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>