<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4bna/update/2012-03-30T17:49:19/e76d041224c07beecd76b88bb451ad307e4ecb52afec194ad0c928d841799185</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I have worked in veterinary medicine for 6 years.  I Always knew I loved animals, my first best friend was my grandma's poodle mix.  Finding that I could do it as a career (vet tech) was like having my birthday candle wish come true!  It absolutely breaks my heart when I hear people say "you guys don't care about animals."  Really?  What about the times I've come down to the clinic at midnight because I can't sleep knowing "Pebbles" is so sick she might die overnight and I just can't let her die alone.  Or when I get called in at 2 in the morning and have to leave my daughter whose been sick with Fever to see "Snowflake" on emergency and then be told "I don't have any money to pay", keep that up and I won't have any money to pay the APS bill or my mortgage or the Dr. bill for my daughter who has to be seen at the ER.  I love my job and I'm doing it because I love animals.  I can say I'm guilty of paying on client's bills (and let me remind you, those city employees who go around to all the parks and empty the trash cans make more than I do) and every pet I own I've rescued (4 of them have been work that come home with me).  Look me in the eye knowing just this little bit about what I do and tell me again I don't care about animals. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/dia1cl</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/bhxi</id></website><link>http://www.askavetquestion.com/why-are-vets-so-expensive.php</link><postedTime>2012-01-10T19:52:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:49:19+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4bna</id><link>http://www.askavetquestion.com/why-are-vets-so-expensive.php#comment-481239217</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-01-10</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>