<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msybei/update/2012-03-27T10:55:51/2e158b3d61e782d4d1ce0e83f163fe0c26dc25c4d2e0dc680b5483bf630b0c2c</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Since Hubbard took to the sea to stay out of the law's Reach when the Heat was on, it's not unfathomable that Miscavige couldn't do the same -- and take The Hole and RPF with him. The Freewinds might not be the ideal choice, as there's only limited space in the engine room to operate a major gulag. (besides, the screams from all those beatings might risk upsetting the well-heeled passengers above) 

If I were Miscavige, what would I do? Well, putting on my 'evil' hat for a moment ... I think I'd buy an old freighter ship, register it in some obscure African country (under a newly created front-group name, naturally) and then stuff all the prisoners in the cargo holds and steam away.

I don't know what international law might have to say about running a private 'prison ship' in international waters, although I do recall plenty of discussion about this strategy as the US military's preferred option if their existing beyond-the-law prisons at Guantanamo and Bagram were ever forced to close.

The other legal advantage is that if and when people die at sea (whether from denial of medical care, excessive beatings, etc) there's no clear-cut legal authority to conduct investigations. I don't recall the nation of Liberia ever investigating *any* of the rapes and murders that occur on the many cruise ships that fly its flag. 

As the screws continue to turn ever-tighter on Miscavige and his illegal operations, I think at some point he'll come to a point where he'll be forced to face up to the law ... or perhaps flee to the sea and continue the abuses unabated. Maybe, just like Hubbard, he'll take the 2nd choice.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lnxd2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rpyi</id></website><link>http://blogs.villagevoice.com/runninscared/2012/03/scientology_concentration_camp_the_hole.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T12:05:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-27T14:55:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msybei</id><link>http://blogs.villagevoice.com/runninscared/2012/03/scientology_concentration_camp_the_hole.php#comment-477459606</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>