<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3wzd4/post/2012-03-30T01:49:55</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3yv7n</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zh6z8</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>There is NO law that states that parents should read the STUDENT'S handbook even though they were provided a copy. It's the students who are provided with the handbook not the parents. Maybe next time schools can provide "Parent's Handbook". A student that tries drugs is both brave and stupid. one can never tell if a student is using drugs unless they show up in school high ,if he/she is positive when a drug test is conducted or if he/she is caught on the Spot. drug usersdoesn't kiss and tell.

So what if the student uploaded her picture? according to the article her facebook account was PRIVATE so does this mean that the STC goes around hacking students facebook accounts? before facebook and twitter almost EVERYONE had multiply accounts as well as friendster. Kids aren't really an expert when it comes to knowing what's right or wrong? so are you saying that adults are  right? I'm 22 years old and in the eyes of the law i'm considered as an adult but still i make mistakes and i'm 22. Anyone can make mistakes be it a minor or an adult. 

If ALL parents allowed their kids to smoke and drink at super young age then ALL parents then they would all be in jail right now. " Schools can only interfere if  the parents are doing NOTHING or is the cause of the  negative change in the student be it mentally or emotionally. Of course you wouldn't die if you don't get to drink or smoke but the fact that the student was with her parents when the picture was taken means her parents are supervising. No decent parent would allow their kids to get drunk Off their ass right in front their faces or pose nude online. STC is a school for rich kids, no one can deny that, so when the family of s student decides to go on a beach outing, they would go somewhere classy where there are also rules when it comes to swim wear, bikinis are accepted so are tankinies or one piece swim suites but right now you can hardly find a one piece swimsuit that isn't sexy. if attempt to swim in t-shirt and shorts the establishment would throw you out. For a school to dictate what a student should wear or do in a FAMILY AFFAIR is NOT RIGHT!  when a parent enrolls their children in a certain school they don't give up their rights as parents and their family's privacy to the school authorities. 

maybe STC should make their rules more specific so that this kind of incident would't happen again. :) 



</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l0h0l</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q15f</id></website><link>http://newsinfo.inquirer.net/168441/high-school-girl-banned-from-graduation-over-facebook-bikini-photo</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T00:11:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T05:49:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3wzd4</id><link>http://newsinfo.inquirer.net/168441/high-school-girl-banned-from-graduation-over-facebook-bikini-photo#comment-480295314</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zl09g</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>