<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mku7hs/post/2012-03-26T10:20:11</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkxkti</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lx0pm</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Wow, you took that as implying that Big Oil was killing alt-energy?  When the author came out and simply stated several times that it would be *market forces* that would ultimately drive us away from oil-based fuels and towards alt-energy?  Way to see exactly what you expect to see; selection bias strikes again!

Also, way to put quotes around "global warming" -- allowing us all to keep pretending it's a "myth" when we see all of the predictions of anthropogenic climate change (a more correct term, since global warming allows the obstinate or willfully retarded to say stupid things like "it's Cold today -- global warming is a MYTH!") are coming true.  Essentially the hallmark of a good scientific theory -- solid predictions which are coming true -- is insufficient for those who refuse to believe that "global warming" is actually occurring (and has been for quite some time) and won't believe it's true until we've razed the planet and torched just about every ecosystem in search of just one more drop of precious, precious oil.  Oops, there's MY bias showing...

About the only part of your reply I agreed with was the sigh about the anti-nukes people.  Despite the fact that nuclear power is still one of the cleanest and safest sources of large scale on-demand power available, with the potential to give us an ACTUAL bridge to wind/solar/wave power, the anti-nukes crowd is so scared of radiation and the handful of actual disasters and the myriad of hypothetical disasters that they enable the every-day destruction wrought by the oil/gas/coal industries.  Nuclear ain't perfect, but it's a damn sight better than COG-fuel, and it just might  us over until the last few economic pieces of the puzzle pan out and we can move over to alt-energy for good.

By the way, don't put too much stock in the "on demand" power thing. One of the biggest potential shifts with alt-energy is the move to *local* power production.  Doing this removes a TREMENDOUS amount of grid stress (well, technically ALL of it if we ever moved over to 100% localized production, but I'm not sure that day will ever come).  Coupling localized production with the rather dramatic advances in energy storage tech -- think Batteries, but I'm betting on supercapacitance (see articles in advances in supercap in Wired right now) -- and localized (house by house, or neighborhood by neighborhood) energy production becomes not just a possibility but an economic inevitability and a HUGE game changer that is literally right around the corner (think 10-25 years max).  And yes, in THAT market, Big Oil IS the blocker, since they're doing everything except give away a free Escalade to keep people addicted to their products.

So yeah, mixed bag in your response.  Big Nukes needs a bit more love from the "hippy" crowd.  Global warming doesn't need "quotes," but it probably needs to stop being called "global warming" (note the APPROPRIATE use of quotes, there ;) to take one more toy away from the science-denier crowd.  And finally, output variability is not a blocker to alt-energy; it's just one more technological hurdle to be overcome, and it IS being overcome rather rapidly, in parallel with dramatic improvements in the economic viability of sun and wind power (at least... haven't read much on wave/geothermal lately...)

And all of that is pretty much just a TL/DR version of what the author said.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rp6ay</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lka7</id></website><link>http://www.wired.com/underwire/2012/03/alt-text-energy-innovation/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T10:34:14+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T14:20:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mku7hs</id><link>http://www.wired.com/underwire/2012/03/alt-text-energy-innovation/#comment-476424356</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lhlxz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>