<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkyp57/update/2012-03-25T09:06:09/76acf62d1e5338a32a9a5068664f8dd3565e827b2d5d491420d86b8a533fa2ef</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I am so Glad I asked! Thanks for the answer. Of course, the very idea of donning a hoodie and taking an internet-ready snap-shot of myself makes me queasy, though I had not explored why. 

I get what you're saying, and I believe it is true. We have a problem as a society, though: The majority of people lack the ability to explore issues critically but also have a Burning desire to join with such protests movements which seem to be the only outlet for their emotional responses to these sad events. Thinking is out; feeling is in. There has been for some time a disturbing (to me) trend in American society of people loudly mourning people they don't even know, of actually summing deep emotion for utter strangers because it is COOL to do so. It is cool to mourn Treyvon (not his fault); it is apparently NOT cool to protest in support of the three women who were raped at gunpoint in their student housing complex at Lander University in SC three days ago. How do I know? It didn't appear on YouTube.
Your essay makes people angry. Good. It appears to strike a nerve that you question that "liking" something or donning a hoodie and taking a picture of yourself qualifies as real social action. It makes people very grumpy indeed.So, grumpy people, let us consider this: Gun ownership is at all time highs in the United States, right now; and gun-oriented video games are being produced in record numbers and possessed by record numbers of Americans. Their average age is 37, their average race is white, their average sex is male. Perhaps a discussion of white male rage would be in order? Because just as no one can wear Treyvon's hoodie, no one can walk in George Zimmerman's shoes either.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ra5a4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/l7r5</id></website><link>http://chronicle.com/blognetwork/tenuredradical/2012/03/the-power-of-the-hoodie-or-the-paradox-of-the-political-meme/</link><postedTime>2012-03-24T22:57:30+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-25T13:06:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkyp57</id><link>http://chronicle.com/blognetwork/tenuredradical/2012/03/the-power-of-the-hoodie-or-the-paradox-of-the-political-meme/#comment-475788975</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lj56l</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>