<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkhhmy/update/2012-03-25T14:44:40/d4b0a4a6aa8ad7f6baf884e0f92e4926c2d2850002da82b08db1a3ba1872af51</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miqoei</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>CR:

I think you've provided some very good insights here. So, thank you.


I'm not certain that Mr. Kwon was the first NJ Supreme Court nominee has been defeated in committee or by the Senate advise and consent function. Between 1844-1947, I believe the state Supreme Court members were appointed by the Legislature and the Governor. So, they may have held very Heated battles which are now lost to history.


That said, I do believe Mr. Kwon was the first nominee who has been rejected since the 1947 state Constitution. Thus, it's a first for the modern state Supreme Court.


Either way, it is new.


Likewise, when Governor Christie did not reappoint Justice Wallace to the Supreme Court in 2010, that was also the first time since 1947 that a sitting Justice's term had expired and his or her tenure was denied.


That, too, was new.


(There are instances sine 1947 where a sitting Justice did not seek reappointment, as with former  Justice Rivera-Soto. I believe there is another who may have passed away while on the bench. I believe Chief Justice Hughes and Chief Justice Zazzali were both forced into mandatory retirement in their first term. Those of course are fundamentally different reasons not to have one's term renewed).


As to Mr. Kwon and the leaking of his confidential application documents (if indeed that is what happened), I agree in large part. That is unfortunate and disgraceful. How much will it chill disclosure when leaks such as that become commonplace? Will some highly capable potential nominees refuse appointment because they do not wish their personal and family lives to be the political football?


That said, I believe a nominee's family, business, and personal matters can become be subject to the Senate Judiciary's Committee consideration. The information or evidence uncovered by the Committee does not have to meet the standards of court to secure an indictment, be submitted as evidence, or satisfy the burden of proof for the court. Certainly, that opens the Senate's process to evidence which would not stand judicial inquiry. That's quite ironic, actually, when appointing a Court justice.


But, in my view potential nominees should be given both the maximum scrutiny permitted under the law and the minimum amount of security and confidentiality required to  it is a free and open process before the public. Under that view, to scrutinize one's family would not necessarily be out of bounds. To do so may be politically dirty and morally unhealthy, yet it may still produce a rewarding result to Ensure the Court is free from the taint of impropriety (perception is as good as reality) and is as pure as the driven snow.

Still, I am still disturbed by your allegations that a potential nominee's privacy and trust in the process was violated by leaks and unlawful disclosures of his confidential application materials.


I cannot say I know best how to tread between complete disclosure and maintaining confidentiality.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yiysg</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zumc</id></website><link>http://www.politickernj.com/node/55773</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T23:08:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-25T18:44:40+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkhhmy</id><link>http://www.politickernj.com/node/55773#comment-475954965</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z6n8w</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>