<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mknn5g/update/2012-03-26T04:52:39/3c4e0d106e39d29508c80fcc6000729ce5e0636cb14185ec9d3cad10266b2293</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Just wanted to write a few things. First thanks to Eddie.. Your site has been the backbone of my recovery. The comments, the archives, the topics. Everything. Now I understand and know why NC is so important. Over the last 2 years my ex left me more than 6 times for days on end and then came back. The last time he left was 6th Feb. He has since spent the last 2 months on and  trying to get back in my good books as well as doing everything in his power to hurt me. He is a piece of work.. when I cave he leaves again. He is a massive game player and seriously needs help. He has issues! All this time I have been reading everything and trying every site known to man on how to get ur ex back etc.. This weekend however something inside me clicked. It was my sons 11th birthday and we have just had the best weekend of our lives. My son is going to be the centre of my world and every bit of energy I possess is going to be given to him. It  was anyway but even more so now.  Its never going to work if I take my lying two faced waste of space ex back. I actually wrote to a agony aunt in a national newspaper 2 days after he left. I totally forgot about it but On saturday night I was reading said paper and omg my letter was printed. I nearly Fainted, I was so shocked that it could come on a weekend when I was experiencing totally new feelings and ideas about this break up and how I should live my life. She basically told me what I already knew. This guy is a loser. I need to get my dignity back and start living and thats exactly what I plan to do. Ive finally blocked him on Facebook. Im actually excited about the future.. Nothing is written in stone. Life changes on a daily basis and Im not going to waste another second hanging onto the past when my best days are probably yet to come so thats something to look forward to as well. Hang in there everyone. Keep moving forward, dont look back. It sucks when you cant let go because your too busy waiting for the impossible to happen. Im finally letting go and it feels like a massive weight been lifted  my shoulders. Never thought I would say that! Keep going people! When the pain, the cries, the tears and suffering has Reached a limit, that is when you will know in your heart and your head that you come out as a strong person.  Rock bottom is where I was at, I have had to force myself to get over him and its the hardest thing ive ever done. Im still healing and will be for years to come and still love him totally and utterly. As each day passes that fades a little bit more and it hurts. Its painful... Embrace it and you will soon be on the way to a better happier life as really it does get easier... Hang in there everyone. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/5ue3j5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gz5e</id></website><link>http://lovesagame.com/no-contact-help-how-to-fight-the-urge-to-contact-your-ex-part-3/</link><postedTime>2011-04-16T08:19:25+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T08:52:39+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mknn5g</id><link>http://lovesagame.com/no-contact-help-how-to-fight-the-urge-to-contact-your-ex-part-3/#comment-476290517</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-04-16</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>