<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/136753/post/22410048/comment/330016653</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>students to eat Lancai: Zunyi, Guizhou to the east primary school students accused of eating Lancai. The morning of October 13, Zhonghua Road, Zunyi eastern basic school some parents ascertain namely a car has started corroding vegetables louis vuitton outlet, was actually prepared to do to the students at midday to eat vegetables. Rage, the parents migrated them Lancai middle of the street, Because of dissatisfaction with the attitude of the school, pile up parents gathered at the school gate. Afternoon spaccio woolrich, Zunyi City Honghuagang government held a reception meeting, conference communications, said the school headmaster to be dismissed by far louis vuitton outlet, canteen ordered to stop. parents of the students stopped to eat Lancai be stacked on the roadside after a crowd of Lancai users to provide to elementary school students eat Lancai Dongfeng buy Lancai the babies  friends to provide remind students to eat Lancai core According to 13 am, Zunyi Road louis vuitton outlet, east China school some parents find that a car has started rotting vegetables, was actually prepared to do to the students at noon to eat vegetables. Rage sac Louis Vuitton sacs louis vuitton students apt dineeateat, the parents moved them Lancai middle of the street, Because of dissatisfaction with the attitude of the school, scale up parents gathered at the school gate. Afternoon belstaff borse louis vuitton World of Warcraft Guide apt Ha, Zunyi City Honghuagang government held a press conference woolrich channel woolrich parka uomo &amp;#20064;&amp;#36817;&amp;#24179;&amp;#20250;&amp;#35265;&amp;#24847;&amp;#22823;&amp;#21033;&amp;#24635;&amp;#32479; 2011-06-0, conference communications louis vuitton outlet, said the school principal to be dismissed on the Spot, canteen ordered to stop. students to eat Lancai incident: a hot car Lancai minority parents 13 &amp;#26085; &amp;#26089;&amp;#26216; approximately 8 pm, some parents send their children to Zunyi City, Guizhou Province, Dongfeng primary school, I saw somebody send food to school, the parents of curiosity to open the pocket dish installed and found the children cooking the food is so frightful - streaming green pepper has decomposed liquid; eggplant has Danian; cabbage cabbage entire others scrape the surface of the outer leaves the recess of the putrid leaves; meat flesh ... ... the first slot vexed parents ambition Lancai tear louis vuitton outlet, the requirements and principals gathered by the school gate one explanation. [flash] player.youku/player.php/sid/XMzEyNTM1OTAw/v.swf [/ flash] students to eat Lancai video 8 am that day, wind in front of primary and secondary schools, gathered a large sensitive parents. The ground in front of parents, was intercepted just piled a lot of vegetables: Black was only half of the peppers, the tomatoes have broken skin in Tangshui, dark cabbage, tofu acid issue ... ... a parent that morning around 7:50, they accidentally discovered the car conveyed to a school cafeteria food sacs louis vuitton, is the slot head meat. Some parents are very angry after informed, the school will move to rotten vegetables middle of the street in front of the Chinese way, and presently preoccupied hundreds of parents gathered, guiding to disruption of transmission to North China. students to eat Lancai dissatisfaction: compel children to eat low-quality school lunch in the field, Dongfeng Primary School Yurong Tang louis vuitton outlet, trying to approach an knowing by way of regrets, to appease the matter, but the parents We do not adopt. Yurong Tang attempting to move out on the streets of rotting vegetables, live, by their parents to stop. children to eat these Lancai understand how long to eat. , desperation, they began to pay in October. approximately 10 am, because of dissatisfaction with the school\'s treatment attitude sacs louis vuitton, angry parents gathered to continue to the streets, two-way traffic disruption Lawrence North China, mustered a massive number of local police and other officials to preserve order; Honghuagang Committee Secretary Wang Jinjiang louis vuitton outlet, head of water in such cozy scene sac vuitton louis vuitton sito ufficiale &amp;#22799;&amp;#23041;&amp;#22839;&amp;#26053;&amp;#28216;&amp;#26223;&amp;#28857; &amp;#22799;&amp;#23041;&amp;#22839;, listen to their opinions, we mortgage to Zunyi Municipal Government 16:30 Honghuagang District School Board will hold a press conference informed of the incident site the results of progress sacs louis vuitton, until 12 o\'clock noon, the parents ahead being dispersed. stopped at their parents later the stack stacked ashore the roadside Lancai users to provide peppers decaying flowing liquid; eggplant has Danian; human scraped cabbage all the rest of the altitude floor of cabbage dishes bang rotten leaves; pork meat is the first slot ... ... to students collection of food Lancai because also many parents and onlookers, cordoned Off after police arrived to provide users eat Lancai students gathered in the east primary in front of parents and community users to provide treatment: removal canteen principals ordered to stop yesterday p.m. peuterey sito ufficiale louis vuitton sito ufficia, Honghuagang informed at the press conference spaccio woolrich, east Primary School Yurong Tang , was on the Spot removal, school canteens have been closed down correction, acceptance test to be resumed until the opening meal. Honghuagang Education Secretary Zheng Jianxin louis vuitton outlet sacs louis vuitton, said the school canteen treatment In 2006 sacs louis vuitton, the education sector has been disallowed to do a small dining table louis vuitton outlet sac vuitton sac vuitton Gaddafi escaped to carry large quantit, but of parents is not convenient, only restore. Honghuagang Vice Mayor Zhou Yu-hsin spaccio woolrich, the same day, they have sent 10 working groups sacs louis vuitton, the region\'s 64 school canteens to start checking. testified Honghuagang has established a working group to investigate the episode, the quality of the dishes tested spaccio woolrich sacs louis vuitton Review New York stock [mart;ma, combing parents\' opinions and, whether feasible in today\'s announcement of the results. friends of the students eat Lancai hot: # to the students to eat Lancai #: (^ o ^) / Ergu: this phenomenon in a crowd of Guizhou primary and secondary schools is widespread, with the fuel, the ingredients have some problems in terms of quality, teachers silent resentment, sorrowful ah sacs louis vuitton! hope this accident by the national authorities to take to rectify this phenomenon, so that our children\'s health growth! corruption away from the pedagogy sector, gives the children a pure land. # # apt the students apt eat Lancai: immediately this thing everywhere. This no only harm the growth and development of children\'s health sac Louis Vuitton gaddafi has occurrence feasible whereabouts of the mys, but also deprived of the teacher and the child\'s luncheon damage period, but likewise peeved the parents, the community of teachers, confrontation among the educate is really more than a stone carving. These corrupt president is abominable! # # Lancai students to eat: pigs feeding while the child louis vuitton outlet sacs louis vuitton, the parents Dang Houshua: disallowed to do a small dining chart is a headless policy spaccio woolrich, which a city family to the parents to work children to cook? now numerous schools in the 3 o\'clock on the school, seem to decrease the burden on students sacs louis vuitton, but in reality is to get parents Dang Houshua, not path most parents pick up their kids, had to bring their children to personal small dining table, is called what? authorities issued the plan while the brain short-circuit it? people absence to do the school canteen, but it tin not be fed to children for an pardon because pigs sacs louis vuitton, reducing the burden does not advance from school at last. you assist, oppose, alternatively wait and see, does not matter sac louis vuitton louis vuitton sito ufficiale hawaiian [scenery;lan, amuse share your opinion </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:136753:22410048</id><idPostId>22410048</idPostId><idBlogId>136753</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:136753</id><idBlogId>136753</idBlogId><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com</link><displayName>HOCKEYCENTRIC</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com/the-hockeycentric-top-10/the-hockeycentric-top-10-things-the-nhl-does-best/</link><displayName>The Hockeycentric Top 10: Things The NHL Does Best</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T14:50:20.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:136753:22410048:330016653</id><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com/the-hockeycentric-top-10/the-hockeycentric-top-10-things-the-nhl-does-best/#IDComment330016653</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T14:50:20.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The Hockeycentric Top 10: Things The NHL Does Best by ndhbwu1268</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://sacslvfrance2.com</link><idEmailMd5>35e93ae5dba8c6c4c013eda89fd6fa5e</idEmailMd5><displayName>ndhbwu1268</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://sacslvfrance2.com"&gt;ndhbwu1268&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.hockeycentric.com/the-hockeycentric-top-10/the-hockeycentric-top-10-things-the-nhl-does-best/"&gt;The Hockeycentric Top 10: Things The NHL Does Best&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>