<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzmbj/post/2012-03-30T14:18:14</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>What are the options for those of us with casein allergy? Ghee or should we use just the coconut oil? Would bone broth be permitted as it would seem like an ideal way to heal any gut issues simultaneously. 

I don't want this to sound disrespectful but one trend I am noticing in the Paleo/Primal blogosphere is the majority of them are written by men attesting to the myriad of benefits of  the lifestyle all sporting there six pack photos to back it up... Don't get me wrong I think it is great. I have eaten VLC Paleo for two years problem is NO WEIGHT LOSS...I don't think I am alone when I say this....most of us 40 year old Paleo women would like to know why this is not working for us despite following everything we are told. I have tried exercise vs. no exercise. VLC to some Paleo carbs. Dr. Kruse's Leptin Rx for over 6 months and most recently his Cold Thermogenesis all with no results. Yes, I have had my hormones tested and they really weren't that out of whack. Dr. put me on some bio-identical progesterone cream and I literally Gained 3 lbs in 5 days.....no thanks. What the hell do us Paleo women have to do to lose weight? 

I think it would be most interesting for one of you to take someone like me who represents a good portion of the Paleo forum community and hack me...that would be truly helpful. There are so many Paleo woman out there that are just completely frustrated and tired of searching for answers. Just my two cents and again no dis-respect intended.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ywngqd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ngem</id></website><link>http://www.bulletproofexec.com/rapid-fat-loss-protocol/</link><postedTime>2012-03-07T17:20:58+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:18:14+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzmbj</id><link>http://www.bulletproofexec.com/rapid-fat-loss-protocol/#comment-481033251</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-07</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>