<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6icu/update/2012-03-30T11:45:53/8257ae4f800a29ec0b879ac2cb88bff78a4de9fdb06cf85c224fdae07804fd3a</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Taken individually, I think I preferred the bright psychosis and dark calm of the previous episode, if only because Jeff's subplot seemed too much of a step back character-wise. As some other commenters have pointed out, why are we back with super-egotistical Jeff from Season 1? The jokes were funny; the only way I can embrace the new focus on his ego is that we're just seeing how inconsiderate Jeff still is outside of the group – but him not noticing Annie Sneezing just seems Off. Good joke, but at the expense of where (I thought, anyway) Jeff was now.

However, if only because of that amazing trailer, I'm sort of seeing this second half of the season as the show dipping its toe (okay, jumping right in, really ...) into examining and playing with "pay channel cable" season-long arcs. So we're going to have a coup by a truly mentally ill former Spanish teacher, simmering tensions in the best relationship on television, hilarious social commentary on the Citizens United aftermath via fast-food chains instead of political candidates, and god knows what else.

So I was slightly let down by this one, but ... overall, I think this is going to end up being more ambitious than season two's experiments in the sense that it seems to be ... a subscriber channel cable series filtered through Community. Maybe.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z9yyj</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/digital-exploration-of-interior-design,71200/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:30:35+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:45:53+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6icu</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/digital-exploration-of-interior-design,71200/#comment-480875747</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h8qrp</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>