<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwqvko/post/2012-03-30T18:36:52</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Everything  on the rules of the state in which you win the lottery.  In my state, the only info the state is required to release to the public is the winner's name, city of residence, the amount of the jackpot, and the name of the store where the ticket was purchased.  All other publicity (press conferences, holding up big checks, photo sessions, etc.) may be asked of winners but not required of winners.

Lottery winners tend to be their own worst enemies.  They brag to buddies, live large, and generally paint targets on their own backsides.  If anonymity is what you desire and you happen to live in a state like mine, it's easy enough to achieve.  If I won the big one, this is what I'd do:

1)  First order of business is to place the "unsigned" ticket in a safe deposit box at your bank.

2)  Second order of business is to file for a legal name-change.  If you're really "John Parker," change your name to "Bill Smithers."  Name changes take between 60-90 days to finalize and you have 180 days in which to redeem your ticket.

3)  When your name change is finalized, take your name change order to your motor vehicle department and get a new license.  Most such requests are either done on the Spot or take a week.  Also, send a copy to the Social Security Administration so they know.

4)  When you get your new license, open up a bank account in a bank with which you currently don't do business.  Get their bank routing number (and your account number) since lottery agencies prefer wiring your winnings to a bank.

5) If the lottery agency allows for it (mine does), redeem your ticket via Registered Mail.  There's no point in actually "showing up" at an office since you'd have to wait two weeks for them to "verify" the ticket anyway.  NOBODY gets a check/payment the same day they redeem a ticket.  And besides, when jackpots get big, news entities hire "stringer" reporters to hang out at lottery offices - waiting to pounce on you with cameras, microphones, and questions.

6) Every con artist and charity (and whoever) will be looking for a "Bill Smithers" who, for all intents and purposes, only exists on paper.  Once you receive your wired winnings at your "Smithers" account, wire it again to your "Parker" account - closing your Smithers account afterward.

7) Tell your attorney you had a "change of heart" about your name change ... and file papers to reclaim your old name. 

8) Once you reclaim your old name, let Social Security know and get your driver license changed again.

9 Then, the most important advice of all.  KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT !!!

Don't hire a financial planner.  Online courses available from Boston University and elsewhere offer financial planning training.  Assuming you're trained to give good financial advice, chances are you'll get better advice than if you asked an "expert" (like Bernard Madoff) who might not have your best interests at heart.

If you want to be "charitable" to friends, relatives, or charities later, have your attorney set up a blind-trust account that will keep your name   ... calling it, for example, The Northwest Charitable Trust.  NEVER lavish friends, relatives, or charities with gifts that reveal your name.  You'll likely regret it later.

Off pulpit (snicker).</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67zp9x</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6tdd</id></website><link>http://www.csmonitor.com/USA/2012/0330/Note-to-Mega-Millions-lottery-winner-Beware/(page)/2</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:40:40+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T22:36:52+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwqvko</id><link>http://www.csmonitor.com/USA/2012/0330/Note-to-Mega-Millions-lottery-winner-Beware/(page)/2#comment-481278520</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hzu0r</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>