<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwljzq/update/2012-03-30T13:12:47/94cc5a1921bfe48d35db631375567752b9578d03cde30256daa59f8d5c37545e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Justice Scalia
challenged  the constitutionality of the
individual mandate in the AFTA, by asking 
AG Verrilli to identify the Limiting Principle. If the government could
pass a law requiring individuals to buy health is insurance, what principle
exists to limit their power to pass laws that require an individual to buy any
other product, such as broccoli? The 
great English libertarian, John Stuart Mill answered this  question 
in his 1859 essay On Liberty. Mills' famous Harm Principle declares that
the state can  interfere with an
individual's right to do (or not do) as he pleases only if such action causes
harm to others. A law that penalizes an individual for not buying broccoli does
not pass this test. A law requiring individuals to purchase health insurance
could meet this test on two counts. First, the uninsured place a financial
burden on those who are insured and that without universal enrollment under a
larger tent, programs like Medicare will be unsustainable. These topics  has been discussed at length. A second reason
is that the uninsured are reluctant  to
seek or unable to access timely medical care during the early stages of
illness. If you doubt this,  try showing
up at your local hospital with a Fever, without proof of insurance, and see how
quickly you receive treatment compared with someone who is insured. Events over
the  last twenty years shows that the
rapid spread of pandemics  begins with individuals who do not receive the
required medical intervention in time, leading to the death of thousands. Harm
to others could be the result of an individual harmful  or the result of
many individuals each engaging in some Act which by itself might not cause
great harm. One person failing to pick up after his dog in a park may not cause
much harm, A thousand people doing the same thing would be  very harmful to others.  One uninsured citizen   may not cause harm to others. Thirty million
uninsured citizens is surely harmful to a nation dedicated to the life, liberty
and pursuit of happiness of all citizens </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67cc84</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/opinion/dorf-supreme-court-health/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T12:27:37+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:12:47+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwljzq</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/opinion/dorf-supreme-court-health/index.html#comment-480965563</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zl6n0</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>