<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/312236/post/127907488/comment/328334329</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Here we go--this is from way back in 1993 (issue #5!) This is a great recipe, but I will say that all that turning is unnecessary, in my opinion. It\'s guaranteed to mess up your clothes and really isn\'t worth the trouble...but you can decide that for yourself. Brining is definitely the way to go; the turkey stays really juicy and flavorful. 
 
The Best Oven-Roasted Turkey with Giblet Pan Sauce 
 
(Serves 10-12) 
 
--1 turkey (12 to 14 pounds gross weight), rinsed thoroughly, giblets and tail removed 
--2 pounds salt 
--3 medium onions, chopped coarse 
--1 1/2 medium carrots, chopped coarse 
--1 1/2 celery stalks, chopped coarse 
--6 thyme sprigs 
--1 bay leaf 
--1 tablespoon butter, melted, plus extra for basting 
--3 tablespoons cornstarch 
 
Place turkey in a pot large enough to hold it easily. Pour salt into neck and body cavities; pour salt all over turkey and rub into skin. Add Cold water to cover, rubbing bird and stirring water until salt dissolves. Set turkey in refrigerator or other cool location for 4 to 6 hours. Remove turkey from salt water and rinse both cavities and skin under cool running water for several minutes until all traces of salt are gone. 
 
Meanwhile, reserve liver and put giblets, neck and tail piece, 1/2 of the onions, celery, carrots, thyme sprigs, and the bay leaf in a large saucepan. Add 6 cups water and bring to a boil, skimming foam from surface as necessary. Simmer, uncovered, adding liver during last 5 minutes of cooking, for a total of about 1 hour. Strain broth (you should have about 4 1/2 cups); set neck, tail, and giblets aside. Cool to room temperature, and refrigerate until ready to use. 
 
Heat oven to 400 degrees. Toss another 1/3 of onions, carrots, celery and thyme with 1 tablespoon butter and place in body cavity. Bring legs together and perform simple truss [here\'s what it says to do: Using the center of a 5-foot length of cooking twine, tie the legs together at the ankles. Run the twine around th thighs and under the wings on both sides of the bird, pulling tightly. Keeping the twine pulled snug, tie a firm knot around the excess flesh at the neck of the bird. Snip Off excess twine.--These days a lot of turkeys come with a \"hock lock\" that holds the legs together, so this step may not be necessary.] 
 
Scatter remaining vegetables and thyme over a shallow roasting pan; pour 1 cup reserved broth over vegetables. Put perforated cover on roasting pan; set a V-rack (preferably nonstick) adjusted to widest setting on top of cover. Brush entire breast side of turkey with butter, then place turkey, breast side down, on V-rack. Brush entire back side of turkey with butter. 
 
Roast for 45 minutes. Remove pan from oven (close oven door); baste turkey with butter. With a wad of paper toweling in each hand, turn turkey, leg/thigh side up. If broth has totally evaporated, add an additional 1/2 cup stock to pan. Return turkey to pan and roast 15 minutes. Remove turkey from oven again, baste, and again use paper toweling to turn the other leg/thigh side up; roast until meat thermometer stuck in leg pit registers 165 degrees, about 30 to 45 minutes. Breast should register 160 to 165 as well. Transfer turkey to platter; let rest for 20 to 30 minutes. 
 
Meanwhile, strain pan drippings into a large saucepan (discard solids) and skim fat. Return broiler pan to stove and place over 2 burners set to medium Heat. Add 3 cups reserved broth to the broiler pan and, using a wooden spoon, stir to loosen browned bits. When pan juices start to simmer, strain into saucepan along with giblets; bring to boil. Mix cornstarch with 1/2 cup Cold water and gradually stir into saucepan. Bring to boil; simmer until sauce thickens slightly. Carve turkey; serve with gravy. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:312236:127907488</id><idPostId>127907488</idPostId><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:312236</id><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><link>http://www.denpdf.com</link><displayName>denpdf.com</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.denpdf.com/cooks-illustrated-does-anyone-have-a-recipe-for-roasting-a-whole-turkey-from-americas-test-kitchencooks-illustrated/</link><displayName>cooks illustrated- Does anyone have a recipe for roasting a whole turkey from America's Test Kitchen</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T07:35:57.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:312236:127907488:328334329</id><link>http://www.denpdf.com/cooks-illustrated-does-anyone-have-a-recipe-for-roasting-a-whole-turkey-from-americas-test-kitchencooks-illustrated/#IDComment328334329</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T07:35:57.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on cooks illustrated- Does anyone have a recipe for roasting a whole turkey from America's Test Kitchen by Leslie D</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>827c13e07b5e688ab996fa42f0bf7fd0</idEmailMd5><displayName>Leslie D</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>Leslie D commented on &lt;a href="http://www.denpdf.com/cooks-illustrated-does-anyone-have-a-recipe-for-roasting-a-whole-turkey-from-americas-test-kitchencooks-illustrated/"&gt;cooks illustrated- Does anyone have a recipe for roasting a whole turkey from America's Test Kitchen&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>