<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwdq12/post/2012-03-30T10:01:00</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I guess the government thinks that Veterans, excuse me, "Working Age Retirees," can be bought  with a few beads and moldy wool US blankets.
 In 1979 Beaverton, Oregon USMC recruiting office, begged me to enlist in the Marine Corps. Back then the Country was still suffering psychologically from Vietnam, Jimmy Carter had screwed Desert 1 up royally so it can be said that prospective enlistees were not exactly beating down the recruiters door.
 I was told by Sgt, Chuck Towls that if I completed 20 years or more of honest and faithfull service to the Country and the Marine Corps I and my family would receive life time free dental and health care.
 Basically this boils down to me and my wife because our children are all grown now and do not fall under our insurance plan in which we pay premiums, and co pays.
 As a young impressionable young man, enlisting into the Marine Corps which to me was the most honorable branch of service on the entire earth, and Sgt, Towles was a direct representative of the Marine Corps, I took his word as bond, and I agreed to enlist.
 I loved the Marine Corps with every fiber of my being, I loved the field, the camaraderie, and belonging to the best fighting organization that had ever been created.
 My wife shook her head in disbelief, of my blind loyalty and obedience. In 1979 TRUST was my core believe in the Marine Corps and I carried that through my career.
 By God I was going to uphold my end of the agreement that I had made with the US government, and there was not going to be anyone that would tell me any different. Not even my wife.
 I did every thing that was requested of me, I went on every overseas rotation without complaint. As an Infantryman, the field was my home and sanctuary. I felt like superman and nothing was going to stop me.
 Now 12 years after my retirement. My body is wracked by severe Arthritis, and Hearing loss, four injured disks in my back, and a bunch of other maladies that doctors are trying to figure out. I guess Lex Luther and his Kryptonite has caught up with me.
 Tricare not so much for me, I receive much of my care through the VA despite what people say has given me excellent health care, if you don't mind waiting for months for an appointment.
 It is my wife I am worried about. I dragged this poor woman across the globe over 2.5 times. Each time as the dutiful Marine Corps wife she did so without question or complaint, even though she wanted to, God bless her she never did, not until the end of my career when she said, "Dad, if you have to rotate somewhere again, you go, the kids and I will stay here and wait for you.
 My wife became part of the Marine Corps as if she had enlisted. And as I roamed across the world and fought in one war, she kept the family together by herself, and having to deal with a teenager who was just figuring out what those two things in his pants were for. And for that I owe my wife everything.
 My wife to expected the US government to uphold it's end of the agreement despite it's denial that the recruiters never said no such thing, like life free health and dental care.
 Now that I have become politically aware, I must admit to, what my wife was telling me all these years. You know what it feels like having everything you believed in for 20 years just suddenly come to an abrupt stop and realize that it all was a lie. The honor, the trust, the belief in the very system that is responsible for who I am today, just ripped out from the center of my being.
 My own government and the Marine Corps filled me and others up with a bunch of bullshit, just so the system could get 20 or more years out of us, and then cast on onto pile of busted and broken bodies, while they troll the Halls of high schools looking for young and strong, idealistic kids like I was.
 Hmm. You know something, A thought just popped into my head. This is how the American Indian must have felt after the government made promises to them.
 Well at least back then the horse hair US blankets didn't have the stink of double-dealing as they do now.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z4hmt</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry2d</id></website><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50524</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:03:24+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T14:01:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwdq12</id><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50524#comment-480768912</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ajm56</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>