<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwo2xv/post/2012-03-31T05:13:36</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>

To be an American patriot means to love Liberty, however
that’s not in today’s definition. It’s amazingly discouraging to see what is being
argued in the name of patriotism. 


 


If you don’t support funding for undeclared and illegal
wars, you’re frequently being labeled as unpatriotic. 


If you don’t support flag-Burning amendment to the
Constitution, you’re said to be unpatriotic. 


Not being blindly obedient to the state or simply to
challenge the power of the state is considered unpatriotic. 


 


It is readily assumed that unquestioned loyalty to
government is synonymous with patriotism. 


Others, though, believe that a good patriot is one who is
willing to stand up to his or her government when the rights of the people are
being abused and when the government pursues bad policies. 


 


True patriotism requires supporting the people even under
dire circumstances and threat of government punishment. Great danger is
imminent when any criticism of the government is considered unpatriotic.
Patriotism never demands obedience to the state but rather obedience to the
principles of Liberty.


 


Quite often when we listen to demagogues in Washington
stating their views on patriotism to garner support for more and more
government meddling, we are reminded of the Samuel Johnson regarding
patriotism. Patriotism, according to Johnson, “is the last refuge of a
scoundrel,” and there are quite a few of those in Washington. The arrogance and
manipulation of naming a piece of legislation that severely undermines the
Fourth Amendment and calling it the Patriot  says it all.


 


Call it patriotism and opposition disappears. It’s easier
to go along than do the work to explain the hypocrisy of the process.
Politically, it’s  tempting to take the easy way out and appear to be
doing the right thing and do it with “patriotic” enthusiasm—even if the
opposite is being accomplished.


 


Just think about how many lies Americans have been told
over the years to rally their support for lost causes once military hostilities
start. The propaganda and lies accelerate to prevent the people from failing to
support the effort, even with great economic pain. Logic does not work; false
patriotism does.


 


Patriotism is to Always support the cause of Liberty and
it turns out governments over the ages have notoriously been the chief abusers
of Liberty. The original American patriots declared independence from an
abusive government.


 


The aphrodisiac of power overwhelms many well-intentioned
individuals who go into government with high ideals. Championing change as an
outsider is easily morphed into a patriotic fervor to protect the state once
the politicians become part of what they previously argued was the enemy. It’s
a powerful argument for not giving power to elected or unelected officials,
since so few remain diligent defenders of individual rights.


</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67z8ea</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yjmx</id></website><link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2012/03/30/army-reserve-reprimands-soldier-who-spoke-in-uniform-at-ron-paul-rally/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:06:27+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T09:13:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwo2xv</id><link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2012/03/30/army-reserve-reprimands-soldier-who-spoke-in-uniform-at-ron-paul-rally/#comment-481677316</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cy38r</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>