<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m370y7/update/2012-03-29T07:55:52/e36de6018a55e8fb7760bd787bc4c51d37caa33a187e05a41dc67f9b1510ca35</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>You have geothermal right now, and have had for twenty years, if it is cheaper why are you paying the highest rates in the country? Are you being ripped Off? You think that is going to change? Explain why?  If they won't give it to you cheap now what makes you believe they are going to give you cheap power ever? They have you as long as you are tied to that grid and they will never give you cheap power the grid is expensive to maintain and inefficient who do you think is going to pay for it? Solar works particularly when you pay 44 cents a KWH. Do you know in the mainland they pay 11 cents for that same KWH in some places and even they are going solar. Read the articles and come to the meeting this Saturday at 5:00pm at the Pahoa community center there will be a lot of people there on solar talking about how they do it for less than you pay right now. You want to pay go ahead but we will not let you destroy Puna because your to stubborn to get a solar water heater. Almost 40% of residential electricity is to Heat water. Your being played like a fiddle.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r2xxz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f2ph</id></website><link>http://www.hawaiitribune-herald.com/sections/news/local-news/helco-courting-geothermal.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-24T22:20:20+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T11:55:52+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m370y7</id><link>http://www.hawaiitribune-herald.com/sections/news/local-news/helco-courting-geothermal.html#comment-479436099</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8ekr5</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>