<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mszoh0/delete/2012-03-27T15:41:44</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msle2h</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5dv0k</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>The most consistent hate-mongering bigot posting in this forum (PostSilenceShhh) continues to inflame utilizing hate-speak and baseless rhetoric. Others follow suit. None value the tenets and protections of the Constitution. 

Don't be fooled by the empty calls for Zimmerman's arrest and justice. This is a call for the lynching of a man in Cold-blooded, hate-based revenge. 

If Zimmerman did do what the mob is accusing him of, he should be brought to face the charges. If he was, in fact, defending himself from a beating, then let those details be the guide. 

Unfortunately for Zimmerman, a fair approach to this cannot and will not be taken as the civic leaders will cave to the threats made by Sharpton and is ilk.  Listen to the language being used in the crowds. All of it is highly (understandably) emotional yet none of it truly wants the scales of justice to be incorporated. Listen to what they call justice. A bullet to the head of Zimmerman is justice? Perform some simple Google searches and you'll see the Bounties that are placed on Zimmerman's head. That's justice?
This is being escalated to be used as some sort of race war. The division grows wider by the minute.</body><verb>delete</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lhef8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnmp</id></website><link>http://www.thenewstribune.com/2012/03/26/2083609/vigil-held-in-tacoma-for-trayvon.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T04:21:57+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-27T19:41:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mszoh0</id><link>http://www.thenewstribune.com/2012/03/26/2083609/vigil-held-in-tacoma-for-trayvon.html#comment-477700919</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5dv0k</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>killed</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>