<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34wwa/update/2012-03-29T11:25:55/e9309df5607e76ce76b61f6cca9852d95a224643f8ed5fe9bab62970521619be</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I think its kind of sad that she tries to quote Stanhope to make him out as the bad person and pass herself  as a god sent humanitarian white knight for the good of the people. She was the one who talked to that guy that was terminally ill and had nerve damage that made him a quadriplegic or whatever he had and he had no hope and lived a life of endless pain and then she wrote that she didn't believe he deserved the choice to have assisted suicide to end his own life when he himself could not. I believe she said something like: "He should hope and pray to magically get an infection and die a slow even more painful natural death."(?) Remember, this is a person who is trying to fool you into believing she is a humanitarian. Now shes writing articles on people doing the exact same thing she is and poking fun at them laughing while they sit trial for a stupid pathetic laughable crime. Can she possibly be anymore hypocritical? Shame on her for agreeing with the censorship of free speech.  She deserves far more then to "be called a four-letter word by a stranger." She is a sick monster that wants to "terrorize the weak, insult 
  the strong and desecrate the 'nearly' dead." People like her are ruining the world. What idiotic writer advocates against free speech? Le lollercopters! Surely you jest madam. The stories and information posted on the internet are artistic works of fiction and falsehood. Only a fool would take anything posted here as fact. Who cares if someone called you a name or said something that made you get upset. They are only words. If my words upset you please write about me as well (I could use the youtube subscribers!) Maybe they don't have sticks and stones in the U.K? We don't need sheriffs to police the world. People like her need to grow up. She is a threat to human rights and the freedom of expression. Shame on you for calling yourself a writer, a creator! SHAME!! When someone says something morally disgusting that's practically a thought crime against humanity that involves the outright inhumane torture of human beings, they deserve a verbal trashing like Stanhope delivered.  Hell they deserve far worse then that. I agree with Stanhope, in that someone who outright spits in the face of someone in endless pain deserves the wrath of an angry god. The kid she is talking about was just being a stupid kid as kids are. The difference is that he wasn't serious and was just messing around and making bad word choices and failed his recovery and  even more stupid, but she is 200% serious that human beings don't deserve their own sacred right to control their own life and death. That's what makes her sickly disturbed and anyone that defends her viewpoint is sick as well. That is Stanhope's commentary intent, to point out the fact of how much empathy she lacks while wearing her guise of an angel, when in reality she is pathologically evil. The bad bad no no words she received are well deserved. Perhaps in the best of light, I could say that she is childish and unaware of the universe around her and maybe she has never had to watch someone she really loved in real never ending agonizing pain suffer in her life.  Hopefully, when the day comes and she has to watch one of her loved ones (or hopefully herself [THE IRONY]) Bleed out and their eyes go Cold and blank, then maybe she'll understand and have some respect for people who wish to commit suicide, since they are the bravest people in this world, maybe sometimes misguided, but unlikely in the case of extreme pain and terminal illness.  Hopefully I'll be there to say "How does it feel to wish to die with all your heart and soul and nobody would grant your wish?" Then as she starts to fade away, the pain finally unhinging her bouncy door spring on life, the last thing she'll see is me zipping down my pants revealing my glistening neon green man thong with the words "Party Analmal" etched on the front mocking her clouded milky eyes glazing over with a tiny glimmer of hatred and malice. Then perhaps her skeletal veiny dust hand will shakily raise itself to slap helplessly several times against my muscular leg meat, a final  of defiance of not only me but to that of an uncaring world as her eyes search frantically and meet those of the nurse or various street drekhead that I have paid  in advance look away and leave indifferent to the crime that has befallen her in their midst.  Finally, after her cackling bellow of death and farm buying, her body now having become an empty vessel of meat and guts, ill just zip my pants back up and leave having done nothing but succeed in trolling her into thinking in her dying moments that I was going to molest her helpless corpse. I would then leave feeling content, that justice and balance had once again been achieved in the world,  and as I stepped out into the bright Sunlight, from the darkness of the old folks home or hospital or dark crackhead/junkie/misfit Les Misérables-filled alleyway, I would have only two things on my mind: Doug Stanhope, and a ride 
home.
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ho3p5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/twitter/9171470/The-curse-of-the-internet-trolls.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T20:06:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:25:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34wwa</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/twitter/9171470/The-curse-of-the-internet-trolls.html#comment-479575657</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzcm2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>