<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpeqtz/update/2012-03-21T08:26:16/e7b5e40ef97eb063c9cdfff556e69ae3a1d36df6f85090233083be810171943c</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp8ov5</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mm5lf</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I am so looking forward to your three or four or even maybe five articles about the evidence Sheriff Joe Arpaio and his Cold Case Posse collected and evaluated determining thus far that the computer generated birth certificate of April 27th is a forgery and more importantly that the Commander in Chief's Selective Service card is a forgery also.  Sheriff Joe has much more to disclose in the coming weeks, part of which will be the fraudulent SS# and the fact that we need to see the Occidental College records to determine what most know that Barry Soetore was a "foreign student" thus not eligible to be POTUS, it is impossible for him to be a "natural born Citizen."  

William you mentioned the purchase of the Slice of land next to the Obama home (it is not officially his home on the deed) that was purchased with a criminal"s help.  You may be surprised to know that the land was purchased with a fraudulent SS#.  Does Harrison J. Bounel ring a bell. The non-existant person is using the President's SS#.  At this point one must ask are all journalist brain dead?  

Here is a Conservative scandal to work on William.  Ben Shapiro from Breitbart has made deal with Sean Hannity so they can both do the same thing you have begun here.  Hannity made the deal with a hand shake and promise that he would NOT mention the evidence collected by Sheriff Joe Arpaio.  Shapiro was interviewed by a Radio Host stating he would not be looking at any of the Sheriff Joe evidence even if it were a slam dunk.  

William, you should take each piece of evidence and write a detail story as to why you believe the evidence provided leads you to believe there have been crimes committed.  That may take you more than 4 or 5 articles.  A post like this one although eyeopening to some are all legal associations (with the exception of the land deal given the fraudulent SS# and phony tax records) and will have no impact on this election.  However, the criminal activity would force a resignation and a brokered convention in Charlotte.  You my friend could become the journalist of the century given this would be a story about the biggest Constitutional issue in athe history of our Constitution and this is not an exaggeration.  Go gettem William.     </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dv4wv</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yv37</id></website><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/2012/03/m-baracks_people.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T06:04:49+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-21T12:26:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpeqtz</id><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/2012/03/m-baracks_people.html#comment-472277282</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/du9d6</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>