<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mku02u/post/2012-03-26T10:58:31</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkxkzc</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Radon precursors to earthquakes have not been believed by the mainstream scientists since the 1980s.  It was one of numerous ideas that could have worked, but in practice don't.  Radon detection was supposed to be a proxy for deformation, which we can now measure directly with instruments such as GPS that were not nearly as precise in the 1980s.

Further Guiliani misused radon, as he didn't understand how it was supposed to work.  He was predicting events as distant as half way around the world as well as nearby.  The place he predicted an earthquake, another town, did NOT have an earthquake, and I think his spurious prediction had expired by the time the real earthquake struck.

The website you cite for information on AGU also cites the website "Earthquake Warning Research", which gives credit to Charlotte King with her Headache Headache precursors, magnetization of iron by earthquakes, and other nonsense, undermining their reliability.

In fact, AGU does not develop early warning systems, and hence could not invite him to help, they talk about issues of the day at conferences.

Many people tried to find out on what he was basing his prediction, and did seek him out to try to clarify the situation, although I remember nothing but scorn from those who found out.

However, he probably did use more than one van.

If you can dig up more details of the alleged AGU endorsement, I'd be Glad to look into it, but I'm sure they did not endorse his prediction OR methods.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6mxooc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/v0v0</id></website><link>http://cms.pnsn.org/cms/blog_posts/48</link><postedTime>2012-03-20T05:55:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T14:58:31+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mku02u</id><link>http://cms.pnsn.org/cms/blog_posts/48#comment-476449799</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/e5g7z</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>