<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3wxrg/post/2012-03-30T02:04:36</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3b93c</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Growup. RomneyCare will work for Massachusetts because they are one of the most highly educated states with the lowest number of uninsured, highest rates in the entire country.
Obamacare will bankrupt states like Texas, New Mexico, and Mississippi, with ten times the poverty rates, and other Cold hard epidemiological facts, that are not politically correct for Mitt Romney to use in defense of RomneyCare:

 Poor populations, such as Texas and Mississippi, have far, far higher incidence of behavioral related morbidity and mortality. Which is a fancy way of saying they have far more people killing themselves with food, cigarettes, alcohol, drugs, firearms, and high risk sexual behaviors. Far more heart attacks, joint replacements, strokes, cancers, Alcohol and drug related car wrecks, violence, HIV, premature births with babies in neo intensive care..
You get the picture.
States have two big budget items: Medicaid and Education.
Obamacare mandates massive increases in Medicaid, so these states, many already  at the bottom of the 50 states on education, will have to literally decimate education to pay for all this health care. And/or they will increase taxes.
But wait, didn't Obama say if you made under $250k your taxes wouldn't go up? Nice trick, huh?
There is a reason the Framers of constitution limited Federal power:To prevent the Feds from enacting one size fits all laws that work well in some states (Massachusetts) but would be very detrimental to other states.
There is no better example of federal over Reach than Obamacare.
Either repeal it, or strip it down to it skeleton and rebuild it in way that give states back the necessary power to craft their own solutions.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z7g7z</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/opinion/barnes-health-care-reform/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:39:48+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T06:04:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3wxrg</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/opinion/barnes-health-care-reform/index.html#comment-480304481</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dp4d5</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>