<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3umcq/update/2012-03-29T15:08:07/a2eee773af84d93f6c81eabf3399d8080a2e63f7d8af806b4ea9592bf7054db9</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Due to the media coverage everyone automatically thought this guy Zimmerman was guilty. They initailly reported the guy was a 5'10 250  and they made Trayvon to be this tiny kid. Turns out that Zimmerman is 5'8 170 pounds and Trayvon was 6' 160 pounds. Trayvon was 4 inches taller and about the same weight. Check out the police report to confirm these measurements. Everyone makes it out to be that Zimmerman ran this kid down and just shot for no reason. A witness has already come forward and said that they saw Trayvon beating Zimmerman up. There are other facts that haven't come out so at this point all this racial comments are crazy. Just because one guy was white and the other was black doesn't mean that it was fight based on race.
What i think happened was as follows, Zimmerman Spots Trayvon and thinks he looks suspicious. He follows him after being told not to by the police which was a mistake. But what he did is not ILLEGAL. He lost him initially but for some reason Trayvon came back and confronted him. At this point I figure Trayvon saw a small white guy get out of the car and said to himself I can take this guy if i need to so he went and confronted him. He had a choice either walk away and call the police or confront him and he chose the latter.Unfortunately he never figured that the little white guy had a gun. This goes to show that you never know who you are dealing with or what people mindsets are so its  better just to walk away from a confrontation. If Trayvon was so scarred why didnt he just run and get to a safe place? Why did he tell his girlfriend Im not going to run from this guy after she told him to do so? Because he wanted to be tough. Look at his facebook ics. The kid has his shirt  throwing gang signs. It was simply the wrong place at the wrong time.
I do think that there should be a trial and it should be decided fairly. But all this racial black and white stuff  is absurd. When Zimmerman calls 911 for the first time he is asked if teh subject is black or white and he responds by saying he doesn't know. Later he says that he is black. That means that he wasn't going after this guy cause he was black. He was just Acting suspicious. Many facts are right in front of everyones eyes but people are choosing to not see them.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ztxr5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/us/florida-teen-shooting-sanford-divided/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:29:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:08:07+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3umcq</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/us/florida-teen-shooting-sanford-divided/index.html#comment-479772847</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zhrfl</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>