<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nnzr/update/2012-03-29T12:57:42/e9e49468b1ec286b775e87fba7a50f6d07aff63e861ef8378392f63ec9c9c21d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>my guess is you are not making class-time attendance a necessary pre-cursor  for academic success.  I'm not talking about making attendance mandatory, i'm talking about making it worthwhile to the student to actually attend class instead of just following the material on their own.  It's easy to write Off the issue as student apathy but the real issue for a long-time has been staff apathy, you need to look at what you can do as an instructor to make class-attendance a more engaging and worthwhile affair.  Education has become progressively more and more dumbed down leading to apathy among the students.  In classes that did not count for attendance i would often miss as much as a 1/3rd of total class-time and still ace the course because teachers did not make class-time a necessity, I could get all the information out of the textbook so sitting in a class as the teacher dumbed down their lecture to make it accessible to even the slowest students was an agony that I was all to happy to skip out on.  The state of higher education in this country is a joke, the Cold hard truth is you had no students show up on time because they think your class is a joke, there may have been some apathetic students no doubt, but the majority of them just didn't see your lectures as crucial educational instruction.  It is your job to make them see your lectures as important not their job to attend lectures that they aren't receiving the type of instruction they feel entitled to.  Student's nowadays are a lot better informed going into college, the internet has a wealth of information and delivers that information at incredible speed, you cannot compete with the internet at producing information.  Your job is to add a human element to education and that needs to be a legitimate reason to attend class.  Your class attendance is far more of a reflection on your own teaching methods than general student apathy.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lag3n</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/l7r5</id></website><link>http://chronicle.com/blogs/onhiring/apathetic-students/30657</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:15:55+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:57:42+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nnzr</id><link>http://chronicle.com/blogs/onhiring/apathetic-students/30657#comment-479650115</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzy2m</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>