<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwfuc6/post/2012-03-31T01:31:48</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>let me explain what is curse of being no 1 test side-
Courtesy article written by Mr Anupam Mukherjee in jan 2012

 Sportsmen are known to be superstitious but this really is stretching it a bit too far.  Hushed voices in the corridors of uncertainty are revealing that the race to the world number one Spot in Tests has been called Off. Teams like South Africa, Australia, and Sri Lanka, formerly vying for that coveted crown in Test cricket, are now reportedly happy with being just number two. 

The reason for this sudden change of heart is a rumour doing the rounds that the world number one Spot is cursed.  
Even the two erudite Michaels — Atherton and Vaughan — were overheard comparing it to the mythical poisoned chalice, where the person drinks the wine thinking that he’s becoming the king, but is actually swallowing down what will eventually end up consuming the consumer.  
The signs are there for everyone to see. On day one of the first Test between England and Pakistan, the newly crowned world number one team was bundled out for a measly score. And very few Indians can actually forget what happened to the previous world number one when they played England not so long ago. 
The similarities don’t end there. India lost Zaheer Khan on day one of the first Test. England lost Tim Bresnan before he could even board the flight. India lost Yuvraj Singh midway through the second Test. England almost lost Ian Bell before the first ball was bowled. Bell may have delayed the curse but he could not deny it, failing to score a run during an inning that brought back memories of 2005. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67xf24</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/y62v</id></website><link>http://www.espnstar.com/cricket/international-cricket/news/detail/item778638/Broad-injury-creates-selection-dilemma/</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:26:48+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T05:31:48+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwfuc6</id><link>http://www.espnstar.com/cricket/international-cricket/news/detail/item778638/Broad-injury-creates-selection-dilemma/#comment-481566502</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>