<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ubkc/update/2012-03-29T15:28:02/d5f8d9e355dd2c381b67e11e23a39410535f35b49b22397f1393e558b133e604</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3bw2q</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/fips</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Naval warfare and ground warfare aren't exactly... analgous.  And the comparison to the recent land-locked insurgencies in Iraq and Afghanistan is more than a bit questionable in my book. The battlespace is quite different, as is the threat, as are the behavior and characteristics of the enemies.         

As you pointed out, there's very little 'recent' naval combat history in the last 30 years or so to support either of our arguments - although the Brits and Argies might disagree considering May is 30th anniversary of Falklands.  

However, I believe there is still a bit more applicable naval history to support my theory.   If one looks back to naval warfare in WW2 the commander who could complete the 'detect' and 'identify' portions of the kill-chain first had a tremendous advantage (see Midway, Coral Sea, Phil Sea, Atlantic.)  One could also see the very same pattern in the Falklands War and (in theory) the Cold War.  Detection + Identification = Death.

ISR is a tremendous multiplier in naval warfare.  And in terms of technical specifics, BAMS has both a radar (detect) and an EO/IR (identify).   It can also go down to 'low altitude' - kind of an important attribute for takeoff and landing.

Please note that I'm not advocating completely shutting down the ship production and cranking out only UAVs.  We need ships to do all the things than only ships can do - boardings, platforms for maritime , etc.  I think you've well over-interpreted my argument. 

I am advocating a balanced look at the merits of ISR versus low-end ship force structure.  And when I say low end, I very much mean LCS.  I  think we're actually in agreement as to what a modern frigate can do.  I also think we could use more frigates - which provide both presence and warfighting utility.  

Unfortunately, the Navy's not at all interested in building frigates!!!  They are interested in building LCS which is in effect an overpriced cutter, designed to operate in an environment where it has no hope of surviving, nor providing much warfighting utility.  The best LCS is going to be able to do is a bit of presence and ISR, and maybe take on a pirate or a cabin cruiser full of girl scouts on equal terms.  In an actual war, it will likely be shunted aside so it doesn't hurt itself.

I'll trade an LCS for additional Airborne ISR any day of the week.  I'd much rather have another BAMS orbit up in the sky surveying vast tracts of ocean and cueing my ships which can actually do something about it (i.e. DDGs), vice a bunch of hapless little crappy ships putzing around with radar and binoculars.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zc7wg</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/54so</id></website><link>http://www.informationdissemination.net/2012/03/brand-new-approximately-300-ship.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T06:07:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:28:02+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ubkc</id><link>http://www.informationdissemination.net/2012/03/brand-new-approximately-300-ship.html#comment-479793279</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/w1pv</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>