<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39ctu/update/2012-03-29T17:20:34/c0f17d192f4207e0d847ac0c1a4c8d070bfd386002fca79cd606e3fc385fb235</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xkna</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z6kn2</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>The possibility that fish with better land mobility were favored by natural selection due to shrinking water habitats is certainly not a theory. It is just a hypothesis and not necessarily the one favored by the scientific community. There are quite a number of selection advantages for fish that can survive on land, notably escaping from predators. There are still fish today with varying degrees of land mobility and survival time out-of-water, suggesting the advantage is marked. I've never heard it phrased "dry pond" before. I know pithy titles can be a fun way to popularize science, but perhaps "drying pond hypothesis" is better. That makes it clear that, if true, this process would have taken many generations.

I would not put myself at an expert level, but I am fairly well informed in the history of Christianity and its texts. To be honest with you, I had a Cold when I wrote the previous entry and had just had some NyQuil. My original point stands, but I did leave out the apocryphal texts of early Christianity. Also, I think "left-wing" scholars is an unclear term. Do you mean secular scholars? If you are talking about scholars who are not inerrantists, then you put pretty much all of them in the "left wing" category. That is a term better suited for political ideology, not scholarship.

I am well aware of the possible dates of each gospel. We can say pretty confidently that Mark was written first and that it was written about three decades after Jesus' death, when, we can be pretty sure the apostles and just about everyone else who could remember Jesus was dead. When I said that mark does not mention the resurrection, I meant to say he doesn't mention any appearances of Jesus after his death. The evidence shows overwhelmingly that Mark 16 originally ended with the empty tomb and an angel(?) declaring that Jesus rose. The deceptively translated NIV and probably the NASB say Jesus "is risen." But you need only grab a dictionary of ancient Greek to probe that translation incorrect. Everything after the Tomb is said to be added to Mark over one hundred years later.

It is strange that you would qualify the first 300 years as a reasonable time frame for source material. This in a time before the invention of paper (except in isolated China) provided a convenient means of recording information. Not that it would have mattered, since all of the apostles and surely most of Jesus' followers were illiterate. And with much shorter life spans, eye-witness accounts disappeared in far shorter time than now. So the most important witnesses never had a chance to write the information down and after three hundreds years, a dozen generations must have passed. You should be focused on contemporary documentation of the resurrection. But, of course, you can't because there isn't any.

And even if we extend the dates for our sources to one-hundred years(though we really shouldn't), all of the texts are by Christians. And the facts and opinions they contain vary wildly. Why would many early Christians reject the bodily resurrection if the evidence was so good? And even in the canonical gospels there is little agreement on the details of the resurrection story. That does not bode well for its authenticity.

You really don't have the right to claim any evidence whatsoever for the resurrection. There are no contemporary accounts. There are no contemporary records. There is no archeological evidence. The earliest accounts are written decades or more after the events by people who were not there and they do not agree on key details. There is evidence that early Christians questioned the validity of the bodily resurrection and they were in a much better position to judge than we were. You accept the resurrection on faith alone. Please be honest to yourself and others about it.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66buws</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6qc0</id></website><link>http://communities.washingtontimes.com/neighborhood/higher-things/2012/mar/24/planet-apes-are-we-just-higher-animals/</link><postedTime>2012-03-24T05:58:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T21:20:34+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39ctu</id><link>http://communities.washingtontimes.com/neighborhood/higher-things/2012/mar/24/planet-apes-are-we-just-higher-animals/#comment-479908139</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zgvcl</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>