<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miryz8/update/2012-03-22T23:16:24/0766fe814d7a43927037735ce252dd6e6adc95125fd28fcbfaafda35944e495f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I am definitely following my passion and loving it!!  My husband suffered from the debilitating affects of type 2 diabetes.  In 2002 he was on 43 units of insulin, weighed 280 pounds (he is 5' 10"), had severe painful neuropathy in both is feet.  He suffered from neuropathy for over 15 years and was on a strong pain medication.  He could not walk more than 75 feet without sitting down.  He had profuse Night sweats from low blood sugars.  He had psoriasis that made his elbows like heavy sandpaper.   i told my grown children that in 6 months I would be pushing dad around in a wheelchair.  He was angry, irritable and wanted to do nothing all day.  I had lost him emotionally, physically.  I lost my best friend even though he was still physically here.  I loved him but didn't like him anymore.In late 2002, I read a book that put me on the path of research and study about diabetes.  I came up with a program that changed our lives.  Within 3 months my husband came Off of all insulin (has never gone back) , within 9 months he lost 80 pounds (lately he lost another 20 pounds making it a total of 100 pounds lost), his neuropathy is gone, he has eliminated pain medication (Neurontin).  He has been in 2 5K races and walks 2 miles 3 times a week.  Psoriasis is gone.  Night sweats gone.  Sleep apnea and snoring - gone.  Best of all I have my husband back.  Happy, full of energy, full of life.He and I teach classes where ever and whenever we can about How We Beat Diabetes.  We recently created a DVD of our classes and we have that 2 DVD set for sale on our web site. We were invited to The Ohio State University School of Medicine to share our story and give the opening to Gary Taubes ( award winning author of Good Calories, Bad Calories as well as Why We Get Fat and What To Do About It as well as his New York Times article in 2001 What If Its  All Been A Big Fat Lie). A doctor from the Cleveland Clinic talked to us about our story and said this is a story that must be told.  He was instrumental in getting us on Channel 3 news a few months ago.We want to share our story of hope and new life.  Our web site shows the remarkable changes in my husband.  I followed the same program and lost 40 pounds.  After my husband came back to me, I got back into life too.  Check us out at http://www.marythediabeteslady.com</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yjx2a</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ut7f</id></website><link>http://www.andyandrews.com/blog/3-questions-for-turning-your-passion-into-a-career/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T20:41:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T03:16:24+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miryz8</id><link>http://www.andyandrews.com/blog/3-questions-for-turning-your-passion-into-a-career/#comment-474177098</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>