<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwwu1s/post/2012-03-31T12:47:58</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Good morning Cheryl and Pepper!

I read through all of your posts and responses on this thread. Kudos Melissa! You are a champ! 

Cheryl, first take a deep breath, blow it out long and slow. You are a great doggy momma and you have some excellent help! You're doing fine. Pepper has a number of issues, it's going to take time to work them out. There won't be a quick fix. BUT every little improvement that you can make will make a positive difference. 
In the toxically injured world, we say, "Slow is fast." So you'll want slow down on changes. You've been changing Peppers food to better quality... That will almost  trigger a "cleansing crisis." that could very well be the reason for the Itching. It would help him if you sprinkled 1/3 of a capsule of spirulina or chlorella over his food, at least once a day. If you can get Toxin Free from agapenutrition.com, And sprinkle the same amount over his other meal each day that will help. 

We want to control the cleansing crisis, so that the release of toxins doesn't overwhelm the system and cause damage. So make dietary changes slowly! Melissa's advice on this was very good, though you may find it necessary to slow waaaaaaaay down.

 It is not a good idea to use antihystemines to deal with the Itching. They are an additional toxin. FYI oral infant formulas often contain higher doses of active ingredients, as they figure that not all of the Meds will make it into the child. Yeh, that one shocked me too, when I first learned it. 

So, what can you use? Epsom salt baths. Daily for a week, and he should be rinsed after he comes in from his walk. Dr. Karen Becker DVM, has some articles on healthypets. mercola .com (take out the spaces) type "Itching" into her search box. She recommends a number of recipes to soothe Itching skin. You might find a lot of helpful articles on Peppers various problems there. 

One other small thing I'd like to see you change right away... Don't use greenies dental bones. If I'm remembering correctly there were some issues with those... I personally wouldn't give my pet anything with a colorant in it. Colorings are toxic, unless food sourced. I recommend raw antlers, raw bones or the dental bones on mercola's site.

Melissa has given you some very good information and guidance. However, She and I have different beliefs when it comes to pest management. I don't wish to confuse you as you've expressed that you are already feeling overwhelmed. I don't use any toxic substances. It takes a lot of courage and faith to step away from chemical treatments. You have already expressed "fear that he won't be protected." And this may not be something that you can handle, right now. I'm going to share my protocol, because I know that pesticides (flea &amp; tick, worm meds,) are toxic and harm our pets. Its very hard, when you live in the south, to do this with out fear. I should tell you that my son moved to Texas this last year. They recently had their spring hatch for fleas... The house he bought was loaded, and the fleas hatched out in droves. He used this protocol, and reports "no more fleas." He's currently keeping 3 dogs.  I'll have to post it in a subsequent entry, as Disqus and IPad have issues. I can't paste in, past the first six lines or so.

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ylta4n</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ukja</id></website><link>http://www.dogfoodadvisor.com/dog-food-reviews/blue-buffalo-freedom-canned/</link><postedTime>2012-02-05T13:40:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T16:47:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwwu1s</id><link>http://www.dogfoodadvisor.com/dog-food-reviews/blue-buffalo-freedom-canned/#comment-481987184</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hzpmw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-05</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>