<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw3xul/post/2012-03-31T11:50:58</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3yjtc</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I have had a lot of crazy sleep/dream experiences. I think that this whle process is something thats  come pretty naturally to me however it was mor semi-lucid cus i never took FULL contrlol of the dream. A lot of times i got nervous as i also felt i was never going to wake up. Sleep Paralysis also was something i used to experience.  To put it lightly, it used to scare the crap out of me. I got to the point to where it would happen to me a couple times a night. I used to wake up gasping for air from trying so hard to just wake up and move my body. Its something thats very hard to explain but if you've been through it you know. Back to the lucid dreaming though. I never realized how many other people experience this and in a way i rejected it and this is why i never got the best out of it i could. I would find that a lot of times i would wake up in my room and see myself still sleeping. This would freak me out and i would go into my mothers room and ask her for help but she could not hear me. This was  a problem for me in my dreams. I found i could not communicate with others. The dreams were not Always bad like this though. They got bad when i started going through rough times. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/mq28l6</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/uxes</id></website><link>http://robinnixon.com/thejourney/why-you-should-learn-to-lucid-dream</link><postedTime>2011-10-28T08:34:59+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T15:50:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw3xul</id><link>http://robinnixon.com/thejourney/why-you-should-learn-to-lucid-dream#comment-481937880</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-10-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>