<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwbpoo/update/2012-03-30T22:10:08/f9403f10b680b790e4e33be29d88443c1c5127f372e4bd830f440ceaebc09df9</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The thing is, the Rock in his 'few' years in wrestling has achieved MORE than Cena has in his 10 years or so in WWE. No matter what he says can change that fact, the Rock like so many others like Stone Cold, Triple H were part of the attitude , the highest peak wrestling has ever gotten. 

If you asked a non-wrestling fan who they would support between J. Cena and The Rock: Most would point to the Rock. Yeah, he didn't use The Rock alias in his movies after a while but it's understandable, he wanted to establish himself as an actor and not this dumb wrestler who thinks he can . 

Btw, i don't care if John Cena "supports the troops" and i don't care that he is in the "wish a foundation" whatever BS. First, support the troops, most of us outside US, rather have the troops go where they're from. As for his charity work, good for him, to be honest, i don't care if a celeb gives a kazillion dollars to help with welfare. It's good if he does, it really is but you know, if you really wanted to give, you don't need to parade around town saying "yeah, i gave man". 

BUT regardless, that should not be a thought with his wrestling gimmick/persona, i know it's hard not to but it shouldn't. It's a character build around the wrestling world and should be kept in the wrestling world. 

John is an idiot, i thought he was an idiot when he first mention the Rock in the Sun wrestling radio show, i thought he's an idiot now. I am no hater and i am no mark either. 

Btw, wtf happened to wrestling? i tune in after the "summer of punk"(died very fast IMO) and notice the last good match was between CM Punk and J. Cena at the PPV. that was good i admit, other than that, i got bored. BORED. 

There is no more confrontation, the feud looks like something a girl would watch on some soap opera. that's disturbingly true too. 

I thought i outgrew wrestling at first, but i was excited when the Rock came back, when CM Punk started "pipe-bombing" on the mic with a shoot. 

When i watch the old days, i KNOW, that wrestling won't be that again, whether it was the cartoonish and or outlandish characters of the 80s to the ruthlessness of the attitude Era. 


Now that i am done ranting here, i am going to watch football and when i say football, i meant soccer for you US dudes. Good luck, somebody PM me if wrestling actually becomes interesting again. :D

</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6769x0</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cq26</id></website><link>http://www.wrestlezone.com/news/252267-cena-continues-to-rip-the-rock-why-he-called-out-wrist-notes</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:27:01+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T02:10:08+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwbpoo</id><link>http://www.wrestlezone.com/news/252267-cena-continues-to-rip-the-rock-why-he-called-out-wrist-notes#comment-481435228</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7tgi</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>