<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0g0qn/update/2012-03-31T19:45:04/6d402adcdafc49746f0026ab120d5a3f8c79d400f9d25e2a7a9160c24286e1f1</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0g4k2</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l8x3c</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I appreciate the civil response. That is a change. In fact I DO KNOW how much responsibility you have and appreciate it. As for more than I can imagine? Sorry, you'd lose on that one. I spent many yrs in a comparable, if not more responsible position and have moved on way past that now. But it really doesn't matter. 

I also know what you make (your range) and while everyone thinks they are worth more, we are in a new economy now and all of us are taking hits. I've also met a number of those that serve and I'm sorry to say, I'm not all that impressed. (I've also met some that REALLY IMPRESSED me, but all have an entitlement mentality unlike any other I've seen.)

I've also been in any number of Burning buildings/vehicles. I've suffered extensive 3rd degree Burns twice, and minor Burns several other times doing rescues, usually in advance of FD and Always without benefit of breathing apparatus. It just had to be done and I was there. 

I offer no explanation for the numbers and I give the Star ZERO credit for reliability, but their salary numbers don't have their spin on them. They are just numbers reported by the city. 

I appreciate what you and your brethren do. I've been on the receiving end of services several times, but I've also been the one that's had to clear the way for them on many more occasions. It is unfortunate that anyone needs to make cuts, but it is reality and needs to be faced by all. Fireman are no more immune then anyone else. I've got many friends still on the PD who have been feeling the pain for years with no significant end in sight. Personally, the only increase in my income in 5+ years has been from additional sources of income. I'd LOVE to see $100 an hour again, but doubt I ever will, at least not without a career change. 

DO be safe. I'm painfully aware of what can happen in the blink of an eye.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zjb9e</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnmb</id></website><link>http://www.kansascity.com/2012/03/29/3523208/fire-department-takes-76-million.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:55:06+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T23:45:04+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0g0qn</id><link>http://www.kansascity.com/2012/03/29/3523208/fire-department-takes-76-million.html#comment-482329136</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gl53l</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>