<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/187348/post/127720081/comment/329252462</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>microphone crack! yo just heard bucks call to whoo kid.....personally I think he desrved to get booted cuz he bit the hand and was poppin Off about not getttin enough money whebn 50 bailed him outta tax evasion and dude just kept spending frivolously like an idiot. but unlike game he was affiliated with the group b4 get rich even dripped....and he was on that album. so I say if he&amp;#039;s really down and learned his lesson like he says let him back in the group. 50 should keep it on the low and debut the reunion on his new album....Bloodhound 2! but fuck game that dude is such a bitch fake homo promotin all this gang shit that he aint even about, goin on radio sayin 50s beefs aint his when 50 fukin made him....buck went at whoeva went at 50 unlike game, he was loyal...just dumb with his money. buck was not only on 50s first commercial release he was on the only 2 g-unit albums....unlike game who was not on any of those 3 albums. dre put game in gunit to sell the album and 50 gave that dude Heat....documentary was pretty much fill in the blanks, all those beats and features. so yeah, bring back buch but fuck game! buck was a real g-unit member game was a poser.  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:187348:127720081</id><idPostId>127720081</idPostId><idBlogId>187348</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:187348</id><idBlogId>187348</idBlogId><link>http://hiphopgame.ihiphop.com</link><displayName>http://hiphopgame.ihiphop.com/</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://hiphopgame.ihiphop.com/</link><displayName>javascript:commentaire_d(16382)</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-01T14:00:33.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:187348:127720081:329252462</id><link>http://hiphopgame.ihiphop.com/#IDComment329252462</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T14:00:33.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on javascript:commentaire_d(16382) by bddatt</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>7e873aa67e05b362eef84c716c89d0d2</idEmailMd5><displayName>bddatt</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>bddatt commented on &lt;a href="http://hiphopgame.ihiphop.com/"&gt;javascript:commentaire_d(16382)&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>