<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mik5rb/update/2012-03-24T04:38:49/e5a906ca9228a92aa003fdb27e461b4fe0829feef2f18abfb524075540144218</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The way some people talk (jarmolkiewicz) its as though modest pensioners have been protected from all the financial ills of the country when that simply isn't the truth.

A Pensioners 'basket' go costs to live is vastly different than those at work and rarely has items that can be dispensed with to save money. Food, Heating and housing are the primary items of expense NOT expensive fashion statements like  or foreign holidays which can be trimmed back.

The tax perk of a higher personal allowance stood at 50% more for someone 65 or over in 2010/2011 but last year that differential was reduced to just over 20% when the allowance was raised for non pensioners but frozen for pensioners. Next year it will be the same and by letting this allowance whither we'll see less income than before.

Added to this we'll see in 2016 a two tier state pension where existing pensioners will get around £125 per week whilst new pensioners get £140.  Thats a disparity of £730 per year that will occur Depending on the day your were born and hardly fair or just.

Oily Osborne lies through his teeth when he proclaims simplification is his game not vindictiveness but when we have two state pension regimes, how can that be simpler.

Its a callous attack on OAP's unable to make further savings as they don't splurge on luxury items like the younger generation and he'll rue the day this comes to pass.  


</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6do3pr</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ms5i</id></website><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/finance/ianmcowie/100015750/budget-2012-pensioners-to-pay-3-3bn-more-tax-for-chancellors-simplicity/</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T14:17:46+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-24T08:38:49+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mik5rb</id><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/finance/ianmcowie/100015750/budget-2012-pensioners-to-pay-3-3bn-more-tax-for-chancellors-simplicity/#comment-475103650</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5jzhy</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>