<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0f6ca/post/2012-04-01T21:51:03</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Klym, you are SPOT ON when you write about needing to just  your deluded co-worker/friend.
I find this the VERY MOST DIFFICULT part of "passing" for a Believer in the Bible Belt. 

Like most ExChristians, I can't bring myself to say empty words, but I can't find anything to replace them with either, so I usually end up playing along because I know it is the only way this weak minded soul can deal with a reality they want to deny.

I hate myself for patronizing Believers when they are in so much pain, but I feel like it is better to tell a dying Christian that he is about to see HIS GOD, than spend his final seconds telling him he is going to go black and cease to exist. Who wants to be hated for THAT? "First do no harm".

I am a coward, but I guess mama raised me better than to grind my heel into someone's pain, just to make a point. So what if people want to believe that "angels will convey them Home"? So what? AS LONG AS THEY DONT MAKE IT A LAW SOMEWHERE THAT I GOTTA BELIEVE THAT NONSENSE.....being a delusional **INDIVIDUAL** is not against the law.

NOW THE CHILDREN WHO WERE HURT in this tale? I would handle them all together DIFFERENTLY! I would advocate for them as a Guardian Ad Litem and drill their abusers in the A$$ in court. And I might even make sure that the victims didn't find Comfort in prayer, but respect them enough to acknowledge that they survived and it was all due to their own strength.....and that I will walk through FIRE to protect them in the future.

I am rambling, but I loved your essay and find so much fidelity with your struggle to relate to folks who----on the outside---look perfectly normal---and whom you clearly respect. That is until they open up their mouths and spew forth the Bible Babble.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/672way</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/768</id></website><link>http://new.exchristian.net/2012/03/where-was-god-when.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T10:28:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T01:51:03+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0f6ca</id><link>http://new.exchristian.net/2012/03/where-was-god-when.html#comment-483229261</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>