<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/eyo259/update/2011-12-04T19:54:43/8d386c2d1f5f06aa9af559595c4b5fa2c87fbe1002907997f9df59824ee43be6</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>A couple of points:

Most members of the military are simply doing their job and following orders.  Like the rest of the brain-washed masses in America, they think our nation is a force for good in the world.  They don't see our leaders as the criminals they truly are.  Well, many do now.  The ones involved in the fighting.

Anyway, the point I'm trying to make is this...

The elite explorers, rulers, politicians and other "leaders" of society have  taken advantage of their citizenry and still do today. It doesn't matter if you're talking about British colonialism, American "capitalism" or Ottoman confiscation... there has  been a small group of wealthy, elitist f*cks that have enslaved their people and forced them to ravage and/or conquer another group of people (who were already enslaved by their own group of rich elites).

When will the people of the world stop arguing over capitalism vs. socialism, west vs. east, U.S.A. vs. the "terrorists", left vs. right, liberal vs. conservative, jews vs. the rest of us, BLAH, BLAH, BLAH?? When...

It is... and  has been... the people vs. their rulers. When we, the people, figure that out... then the game will change. Until then, wealthy, immoral, power-mad elites will  rule the world... and  have "the people" under their thumb.

And they will Always use DIVISION in order to maintain their rule. To keep us all at odds with one another... so we don't try to blame them when the s.h.t.f..

Why do you think Obama vilifies "the rich" so much... when HE is one of them? So in the end... you won't go after the ruling class... just the business people... like they are doing in Britain right now. Burning down ordinary mom and pop businesses because it's all the fault of "the rich". You should be after the Queen's head instead.

Btw...

Vote for Ron Paul 2012
He doesn't want you to be his slave</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/c02cwb</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/znv4</id></website><link>http://topdocumentaryfilms.com/iraq-secret-war-files-wikileaks-special/</link><postedTime>2011-02-25T18:43:03+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-12-05T00:54:43+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/eyo259</id><link>http://topdocumentaryfilms.com/iraq-secret-war-files-wikileaks-special/#comment-379220138</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/518ux</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-02-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>