<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3bnua/post/2012-03-29T14:40:48</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xffm</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/812i5</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>You ask why people hate Christians, first  I do not hate anyone, religion does not give you merit your actions do. I also will state that I am an Atheist. I can hover give you insight why. You start by using your definition of a Christian, which for the most part I would accept that many of your faith believe, you should follow, but that is a flawed argument. You have only one requirement (most denominations) and that is accept Jesus as your lord and savior, and that he died on the cross so that your sins may be cleansed. That is not why people hate Christianity however, but this line I could truly say would give me a reason to dislike you as an individual "
I believe it is because they are told untruths by those that are so full of self that they cannot admit the existence of a creator and want to drag as many down with them as they can". You are assuming that there is a  plan to "take down the good little Christians". Have you ever thought that this is offensive to someone that doesn't believe? I mean seriously you don't know a thing about me yet you assume that I have a Secret Evil agenda, when in fact sir you could be farther from the truth. I can't brag to much about myself but there is one thing I can tell you and feel 100% accurate about  is that I am a good person, I love life, my fellow human, I am a great father, I even work in social services so that  I can help people, besides the time that I volunteer at the local lodge, help my neighbor with a project, or feed the stray cat that no one cares for, I am a truly good person. I can tell you this as well I have read the Bible in fact that's why  I do not believe, there are so many things that I find immoral, and to be blunt, amazingly hard to believe. I have also read several other text  from other faiths as well as Christian apologetic books. I can tell you this as well. Atheist outscored all other faiths in knowledge of the Bible. It was done by a Christian research center (pew research) and it shows clearly that Atheist know their Bible. Don't believe? simply search "who knows the bible pew research.  Look at your own words man, objectively and see for yourself why people get upset with Christians, besides the fact that you insult peoples morality and intelligence indirectly, the choice you give me is. God loves you, now follow him or Burn for ever. Sounds more like an ultimatum to me.
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zh26v</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yjmx</id></website><link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2012/03/29/taking-liberties-arrested-for-reading-bible/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:06:50+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:40:48+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3bnua</id><link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2012/03/29/taking-liberties-arrested-for-reading-bible/#comment-479743741</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ggeoz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>