<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/273926/post/128035511/comment/330018257</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Hehe, I do love using the KIND name in a punning context. 
 
As I said to Maria below, it&amp;#039;s too easy to forget that this bug has taken its toll on my system and just jump back into things (not that I did that...ahem).  It has left me pretty exhausted, but at least I appear to be sleeping more than I have in ages.  I&amp;#039;m still tired though, but I suppose that&amp;#039;s to be expected. 
 
You were not misuderstanding at all: you&amp;#039;re Spot on.  I was expected to complete things early to compensate for supervisor 1 taking ages to complete their marking and/or feedback (and said feedback Always came with a very condescending attitude...)  The thing that prompted my total meltdown over the PhD was being given feedback on a chapter a month late, then being expected to write a 2-4000 word report for my mid point assessment ALONG with another chapter that I had pre-written, but never received feedback on.  I had no idea how to complete the report and should have had 2-3 meetings back in March relating to the whole thing, but instead I was just told to look at the website guidelines, which were in themselves out of date.  Oh, and I had precisely a month to complete all of this AND revise for the assessment.  That just tipped me over the edge and was completely unnecessary.  Sorry, rant over! 
 
Thanks so much for your faith in me - I&amp;#039;ve been trying to gather evidence all day for my appeal.  There are more holes in the University&amp;#039;s case than a Swiss cheese, but usually it&amp;#039;s the Big Guys who win in these situations.  I just want some acknowledgement of fault on their part and the lies written/spoken about me in their withdrawal letter to be...err, withdrawn! 
 
xxx </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:273926:128035511</id><idPostId>128035511</idPostId><idBlogId>273926</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:273926</id><idBlogId>273926</idBlogId><link>http://www.almostovernow.com</link><displayName>http://www.almostovernow.com/</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.almostovernow.com/2012/04/cruel-to-be-kind.html</link><displayName>Cruel To Be KIND</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T14:53:16.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:273926:128035511:330018257</id><inReplyTo><link>http://www.almostovernow.com/2012/04/cruel-to-be-kind.html#IDComment329681793</link></inReplyTo><link>http://www.almostovernow.com/2012/04/cruel-to-be-kind.html#IDComment330018257</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T14:53:16.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Cruel To Be KIND by ~Jess~</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://intensedebate.com/people/jasriana</link><idEmailMd5>a61b886cd0fd5d3193b712a5ac03b21e</idEmailMd5><displayName>~Jess~</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://intensedebate.com/people/jasriana"&gt;~Jess~&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.almostovernow.com/2012/04/cruel-to-be-kind.html"&gt;Cruel To Be KIND&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>