<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwluvy/post/2012-03-30T13:07:53</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Just read Laura Stack's article re:ROWE.  With Best Buy announcing closure of another 300 stores, maybe ROWE is NOT the end-all-be-all she believes.  With all the overhead savings allowing people to work from home (do employers pay for the internet access they require?), reduced sick pay (hey, sick employees can work at home instead of not coming in and infecting coworkers) etc., it seems like just another productivity expert's take on how to reduce costs of paying those pesky employees that businesses unfortunately require to make them money, along with how many billions it costs business to allow employees to chat about non-work-related topics at the office.  Think of all the pay reductions that we can now "allow" since employees don't need money to drive in to work, all the time saved not driving to work that can now be used productively for corporate benefit!  A Brave New World indeed.  Let's not forget that power corrupts, and management does not Always make requests of employees that can be carried out in a timely manner with the resources provided.  Is it now the employee's responsibility to provide any missing resources regardless, presumably at their own expense??  (Someone WILL do that unless proscribed, meaning all MUST do it or get terminated in order to compete.)  ROWE, right?

Perhaps adopting some of the spirit of ROWE at the office (something along the lines of extra credit) without going overboard would produce meaningful improvements for BOTH employee and employer without Burning out and over-stressing the employees.  Just don't throw out the baby with the bathwater, Laura.  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ednrw0</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/nz7i</id></website><link>http://www.growthink.com/growingyourempire</link><postedTime>2011-08-04T16:12:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:07:53+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwluvy</id><link>http://www.growthink.com/growingyourempire#comment-480960441</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-08-04</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>