<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpym4d/update/2012-03-21T10:50:20/1314c9088cc387bb2fb3cca61f556b9285d0511d0febf19b18a0d769d1d13378</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Good lord.  Do we not study our history at all?

Originally the VP was the candidate who had finished second in the previous Presidential election, leaving political rivals sharing these two top Spots.  This was changed in large part because our own history taught us that it is wholly destructive to have a VP who has a vested interest in undermining the credibility of the President.  As VP under John Adams, Thomas Jefferson's anonymous undermining of his President was so bad that he legitimately could have been prosecuted for treason were his behaviors know to be from him.  And yet we are going to shove some sort of "balance" down our throat by forcing a President to choose a VP from a party with differing views?  Can you imagine any Republican as Obama's VP?  He would have to choose between undermining his President as he serves in his administration or be seen as a toady to the other side.  Can we imagine Obama doing anything other than marginalizing his VP even more than that position already is?  It belies the lessons of history and totally misses the mark on what the real problems are....

We don't live in a "Democracy."  We have never lived in a "Democracy."  In fact during the debate over the Constitution our founding fathers warned REPEATEDLY about the dangers of Democracy, of the "Tyranny of the Majority."  We live in a Constitutional Republic, and the fact that more people don't know and acknowledge this (including well educated and very worldly-experienced retired CEOs) confirms the reasons why it is so necessary to stick to our original government's construction.  By guaranteeing individual liberty and limiting the Scope of government our Constitution makes the potentially "destructive" and "baneful effects" that comes with the unavoidable pursuit of power through party organization much more narrow.  How can we be forced to succumb to tyranny if our individual rights are guaranteed by the Constitution, irrespective of the parties involved?  And yet we keep giving up our rights bit-by-bit, in fact sometimes in whole chunks....

The dysfunctional nature of our government can't be saved through"bipartisanship"; we have never been a "bipartisan" country, rising above partisan designs.   Ever.  Even Lincoln had to face a bitter political election in the middle of the civil war, from one of his own Generals, no less.  To think this is the route to prosperity is a fool's errand.  No, the path to American greatness is a return to a respect for the guarantees of individual liberty granted us in the Constitution.  Without that it won't matter if tyranny comes from one party, the other, or both.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6defu8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnmb</id></website><link>http://www.kansascity.com/2012/03/20/3503088/as-i-see-it-irv-hockaday-on-remaking.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-20T21:31:47+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-21T14:50:20+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpym4d</id><link>http://www.kansascity.com/2012/03/20/3503088/as-i-see-it-irv-hockaday-on-remaking.html#comment-472401728</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cmviz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>