<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ykwl/update/2012-03-29T02:33:31/1e221f751905dbb6e69c7739bafe86c36552b1392643aeaf89506b9566158e4e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msp6zb</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8buii</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>That's part of the problem. Whites look scared. Clueless white parents teach their children non-violence and John Lennon philosophy. Jive-happy minorities used to fear the icy white man. But we've thawed out and become huge pussies, for the most part. I'm a smaller guy (though I do work out and stay in shape). I'm wiry and lean and not physically imposing and I never will be in terms of height and body size. It's just not in my genetics. But a lot of what I do to keep from being walked on comes from my face and mannerisms. Older white men who grew up in an age where men were still taught to be men seem to pick up on my mannerisms (which are "old fashioned"). I think the issue is that white men are too comfortable. They are too relaxed. Hell, their styles and mannerisms are soft. They want to be everyone's "friend." There's nothing wrong with the warm heart. But the warm heart shouldn't show itself to everyone because most people are not going to return it in kind. The altruistic white man just doesn't seem to see this. And the racially conscious 'groid (all 'groids are racially conscious) uses this to his advantage. The white "man" today is caught  guard by the negro's "hard" posturing because you can't go from goof-shit to Mr. Serious on the Spot. But the negro is, generally speaking, more bark than bite. So don't let his bark  a foothold on you. Your cred is gone if you're goof-shit guy. Goof-shit guy is actually INVITING trouble. And goof-shit guy is an intolerable hand for us whites to play in a mixed society where racial dick swinging is ubiquitous.

This doesn't mean to behave stupidly because the negro is violent and can't think of the future. But keep a poker face. Keep a suspecting face. Keep a face that says to the world "I just generally disapprove."  It goes a long ways toward making up any inches in height or any mesomorphic features your body may lack.


Darky can see how goofy white 'boys" are by their faces. If you maintain a sense of stoicism (which is the true Euro sensibility), don't be afraid to keep your eyes on the darkies because when you look away first, you affirm their dominance and they do pick up on that. Man, do they ever pick up on that.

I've actually found that growing my facial hair out has only helped with this effort of self-assertion. It's a male sex characteristic you likely have that they almost Always lack. And there's really nothing artificial about this. I'm not trying to be something I'm not and I'm not suggesting that you play dress up. It's just a matter of white men understanding what it is to be a man even if you're not the biggest dog in the fight. Look mean. Think mean. Be "mean." And be prepared to accept the consequences of being a man (if you do find yourself in a situation that you cannot avoid). The psychology of this is truly "liberating." And for Chissakes, every white needs learn how to use a firearm, particularly if he is any type of husband and father. The world (particularly our society today) is mean. We have to survive it.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hc70w</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/e57v</id></website><link>http://www.alternativeright.com/main/blogs/zeitgeist/why-we-don-t-care/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T04:33:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T06:33:31+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ykwl</id><link>http://www.alternativeright.com/main/blogs/zeitgeist/why-we-don-t-care/#comment-479151876</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yu1bg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>