<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkuy6w/post/2012-03-26T10:08:21</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkxjb7</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a6vd2</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Ad-v, you're not likely to be sifting through maps and menus during a Heated moment, obviously there will be a pause option if you want to pause, it's not going to be like Dark Souls where pausing is considerred for the weak lol. That being said, in Burnout I constantly glance over at the little map in the corner to look for turns and such, completely ignoring the road whilst I'm driving with no crashes. But if I'm say at the top of a building looking out and want to know where to go, I can glance between the map and the scene and figure out a route much quicker than loading the map, looking at the route, closing the map checking in game, going back to the map etc etc.
As for them being further apart, not such a significant amount. It's not like a head turning amount it's a single glance down with your eyes. I guess it partly Depends how quick your eyes are, but I really can't see it being a massive problem. My controller it usually resting around by my knees as I sit on the sofa, directly below the TV anyway.

I know the devs want their games to sell, but a lot of them are excited about this kind of streamlining. I think people are worrying too much, if it were detrimental to the game they wouldn't do it. This is their chance to get a whole new audience of people who weren't lucky enough to own a Wii and a HD console on board their franchises now, they need to make a good impression just as much as Nintendo do with the machine itself. It's in both parties interest to make these titles work as best they can, especially these launch/early titles!

as for the shovelware, I don't think they need ditch it, it obviously sells to a lot who must enjoy it or they wouldn't keep buying it. And companies like Ubisoft seem to make plenty from it which allows them to fund Rayman Origins and work on beyond Good &amp; Evil 2. as long as the other titles are there too, nobody's forcing you to play the shovelware. I have 40 odd games for my Wii and I love them! If I'd dismissed the console simply because the other stuff that doesn't interest me was there too I'd have missed out big time. I don't get this mentality, both Xbox and PS3 have their fair share of titles that don't interest me, yet I have both and enjoy many games on them.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6roxgc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7d9s</id></website><link>http://wii.ign.com/articles/122/1221572p1.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T09:53:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T14:08:21+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkuy6w</id><link>http://wii.ign.com/articles/122/1221572p1.html#comment-476416474</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g9z1c</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>