<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/136753/post/39305688/comment/329397305</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>; ; are several ways to change the skin of impurities Ginger  in addition to acne the scar to before going to sleep with finger pressure on the scar at 15 minutes, then washed  the next morning, a week, you will find this method to deal with acne scars is very effective. magic index: &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9734; effective index: &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; to face horny in the face to sprinkle a little white sugar, then gently rubbing half a lemon skin, can go dead skin and reduce the sun Burning sun mark. magic index: &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9734; effective index: &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9734; homemade the toner lemon juice add a little cucumber juice can be made into a natural toner, but must pay attention to durability, oh. magic index: &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9734; effective index: &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; growth of eyelashes drink the leftover tea and let cool before going to bed the next morning, use a cotton swab moistened eyelashes. can achieve the effect of eyelash growth. magical index: &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; effective index: &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9734; go horny elbows, knees, heels part talc gently rub  age darkening of the skin of the body serious when coated with petroleum jelly, cover with a bandage night. magical index: &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; effective index: &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9734; the bruise disappeared , fall bruise a large piece of ugly and disgrace how do? Cooked eggs, peel and tumble in the bruise on it soon disappeared, but do not eat eggs. magic index: &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; effective index: &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; the &amp;#9733; eliminate dark circles preparation of Cold water, milk and paper towels, first in Cold water and fresh milk in a 1:1 mixed, and then the tissue wet eyes attached to the lower half of 15 minutes, you can eliminate annoying black eye. miraculous index: &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; effective index: &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9734; go black nose raw eggs close to the shells of the layer of film the whole peeled  and attached to the nose. Such as dry after peeled , you will find black specks on the magical index: &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9734; effective index: &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9733; &amp;#9734; the treatment freckled little recipe 1 fresh carrots provision broken Ji Zhi, take 10 -30 ml morning and evening after washing face painting, to be dry, wash. In addition,Hermes Kelly handbags, daily drink a glass of carrot juice, can whiten skin. 2, lemon juice, mix juice, add sugar moderate drinking. The lemon contains a lot of vitamin C, calcium, phosphorus, iron and other. Drink lemon juice not only beautify the skin, and also to make melanin, the role to freckle. 3, a daily cup of tomato juice or eat tomatoes, has a good effect to prevent freckle. Because tomatoes are rich in glutathione, glutathione inhibit melanin, the pigment so calm diminish or disappear. 4, when the wash water and add 1-2 tablespoons of vinegar,Hermes Birkin, reduce pigmentation. 5, eat a vitamin C and vitamin E, can be achieved freckle role. 6, with a clean eggplant skin attaining, after a period of time, a small Spot is not so obvious. your bags under the eyes NO daily life, if a good attention to health, work and rest appropriately, do not stay up all night and to  adequate sleep, can delay the bags under the eyes. one night before bed if the viscous fluid in the vitamin E capsule right now skin coating and massage for four weeks, to receive good results in elimination of the lower eyelid to reduce aging. two, before going to bed now posted in the fig of the skin or cucumber , stick with it can be received to reduce the cosmetic effects of the lower eyelid. Can also use papaya and mint dip in hot water made into tea, Liang Liang, often coating on the skin at the moment. three, with some cream or oil on the face, hitting the facial parts of the fingers facing up, with particular attention to the weakness in the skin around the eyes focus on tapping. Usually free to pull the lower lid should be avoided or its outward hyperextension. diet often chewing such as carrots and celery or gum. Usually still need to eat some colloid, high-quality protein, animal liver and tomatoes, potatoes, food, attention to a balanced diet can do this part of the new cells to provide the necessary nutrients and also benefit from the elimination of the lower eyelid. five, to treat the lower eyelid, it was often used in foreign countries Chamomile, high-quality tea or rose sub, as well as with castor oil or olive oil Heated wet compress 15 minutes to several hours a day, the bags under the eyes of these material help to solve now appear in the capsular bag. easily have white skin 9 the trick skin smooth, white, female,  enjoyed special treatment, because the uniform and the white skin, to better bring out the features of bright moving. Acquire a certain amount of know-how, you can easily have a white skin, and enjoy her superiority. whitening , by no means unnatural bleaching purpose is to actively avoid the skin to produce Spots and make skin healthy, distribution of natural Xi Jie gloss. Therefore, in addition to the scorching sun need to strengthen the sun, all year round, the need for whitening work against different UV. Below we provide several whitening tips. 1, if not necessarily have to go out, to avoid to go out in the morning from 10:00 to 14:00, because the sun\'s UV rays are the strongest, most powerful damage to the skin. 2, each exposure to , you should use sunscreen products, but every 2-3 hours, then rub. In addition, even the same in the water will Burn, so like swimming or diving,Hermes Birkin bags, use sunscreen of SPF possessed waterproof effect. 3,Hermes Handbags, as long as the engaged in outdoor activities, regardless of how the sun and the extent of the home should be the first body rinse. Easy movement after cleaning the body, and foam with warm water rinse, then rinse with Cold water, and can wipe some of the body skin care products. Or with a towel wrapped ice, iced in the Heat of the skin, slow down the hot and uncomfortable feeling. 4, watermelon rind ice in the sun red skin. Natural watermelon rind contains vitamin C, can be calm, moist skin; natural aloe vera have the same effect, remove the middle of aloe mass deposited in the skin, anti-inflammatory effect, but also has a cool refreshing function, improvement of skin redness. 5, relieve physical and mental tension. The pressure of life will bring the discomfort of the skin, and long-term pressure on the skin needs special care at night listening to pleasant music, good whitening maintenance and purification of the mind, relieve physical and mental fatigue in the music of nature. 6, do not intake of foods containing artificial food additives. The organs of healthy people to maintain normal metabolism, so that the smooth discharge of melanin. Too many artificial additives in food can cause the burden of the internal organs, resulting in pigmentation, the formation of dark Spots, freckles, etc.. 7, not all of the degree of skin anti-Japanese sun. Usually white skin, dark skin easier to get a sunburn, according to the length of time he will stay in the case of UV irradiation to select the appropriate SPF sunscreen. 8, UV long-term exposure can cause cataracts or chronic ophthalmia, even damage the cornea. The method of protection is to wear a UV filter: transparent or dark color filter film. Eye sunscreen and cosmetics around the eyes to avoid damage by the sun. 9, before the sun to avoid taking certain hormones, drugs or saccharin after exposure to ultraviolet, these ingredients can cause skin melanin to deepen. Also, before the sun is best to avoid the lemon, celery, cucumbers and other vegetables attaining, because these fruits and vegetables contain some ingredients can easily lead to inflammation of the skin after sun exposure. Pears lungs and phlegm, Apple Diarrhea and nutritious. cucumber effective Weight loss, inhibit cancer kiwi. the tomato blood to help face the lotus root Chufan wonderful hangover. qi orange phlegm, kidney warm leek knee waist. radish addition to Flatulence digestion, celery can cure high blood pressure. the diuretic row toxin cabbage, cauliflower eat less cancer. melon swelling diuretic, green beans detoxification high efficacy. the fungus to engage in cancer casual blood stasis and kidney swelling yam consumption. kelp iodine loose silt Results mushrooms contain cancer cells. pepper to fend  the Cold and dampness, onion spicy ginger for Colds. fish Pig complement milk, liver goat liver good eyesight. kidney waist eating walnuts, dates Jianshen Spleen eat. governance hypertension: Reference (1) 30 grams of banana peel, dried decoction to drink 3 times a day, a month effective. (2) Apocynum with traditional Chinese medicine, the open water to drink, 15 grams a day, half bear fruit. (3) Ginkgo biloba 15 g per day,Hermes Kelly, with open water to drink, half bear fruit. governance hypotension: 20 g licorice, cassia twig, cinnamon, 40 grams of the above drug combination to take a week when the tea brewing. lipid thick governance: Reference (1) medlar 10 grams, polygonum multiflorum, Cassia tora, hawthorn and 15 grams, 20 grams of Salvia water, twice a day, four cycles of healing, (seven days for a course). Reference (2) hawthorn, Ginkgo biloba. Gynostemma 15 grams, make some tea. Even serving four courses (half a course of treatment) face black star (freckles): $ coriander (aka cilantro), Jiantang a day, wash three times, a course of treatment to cure. governance sweat. odor: white radish boiled Washing the feet every night for 30 minutes, even wash half cured. beriberi the: pound leeks, boil water ten minutes feet once a day, every 20 minutes three days dig up the roots. neurasthenia governance: floating wheat of 50 grams, 24 grams of hay, jujube 20 grams, 30 grams of Semen mixed. Decoction once a day, half cured. established governance Toothache: liquor twelve, 15 grams of rosin, soak 2 hours after the cotton touched alcohol on the Toothache Department, clenched. 5 minutes hurt, Qi Qing insects fire Cold. Share cure Toothache the: ant nest of brown sugar, two against two bowls of water and fry the remaining half a bowl of the patient to drink three decades hurt. governance stomatitis the: dried watermelon rind the Feng Chaojiao, a little ice pieces into powder and mix with honey applied to the lesion, special effects. governance rotten mouth: the concentrated tea water, add a little salt, and then used to gargle three times a day to five, 30-Day cure. governance pharyngitis: kelp washed, blanched out, sugar, salted after eating three times a day, each 30 grams a pair. Light, two pairs, to pay to dig up the roots (a pound of kelp, a pound of sugar). otitis media governance: leek root one or two smashed out of water, add a little borneol, ear drops, special effects. cure tinnitus and deafness: Wuji a male, sweet four pounds, cooked hot food, ate five, special effects. Colds: a coriander, light blue even have five, ginger 10, decoction, add brown sugar, one or two hot clothes twice a day, one day cure. the governance migraine: right amount of raw carrot juice, Usage: supine into the nose, pain in the left Note right, right pain Note the left, the magic of the ice sheet some even better. Headache: Angelica 4 grams, 2 grams of borneol, 2 grams Asarum, involved in research into the flour the paper tube to put the powder Burning, with smoke inhalation (nerve Headache) cure Dizziness Headache: Astragalus . Gastrodia one or two each, stewed yellow hen eaten, ate three cured. cure hemorrhoids: skin one or two nitrate Huaimi half a catty. Boil water Washing, twice a day, seven days to cure. governance Yin Yang anal Itch: vinegar 500 grams, salt 5 gram hot wash three times a day. treatment of epistaxis : (1) left nasal Bleeding from the right ear, blowing, blowing from the left ear, right nasal Bleeding, immediately stop the Bleeding. (2) ash blown into the nostrils stand only (male female hair, female parent fat) can eradicate head Fever. governance rhinitis : Xanthium 30 grams and lightly smashed into the spoon, add sesame oil 50 grams Boiling will Xanthium slag remove droplets nose a day, 3-5 times. the governance glaucoma: sunflower plate (seeded) 3, cut half of the oral administration of the decoction of the crushed other half of the fumigation eye a half months to cure. governance eye tears. keratitis: , fish gall bladder, eye, three times a day, half cured. fast Beauty: three eggs, wine foam, sealed 4-7 days, egg white painted face every day, seven days a surface such as snow. acne governance: dandelion 2 two boil water to drink, one day a pair, half cured Governance hand, foot and cleft: appropriate amount of gall into powder coated bovine bone marrow or alum Shihlin tone seam in five days to cure. governance Spots: Angelica half a catty, boils water bowl, wipe the affected area with this water, a half effective governance shoulder week inflammation: one or two of the ginger, taro two pound peeled rotten drunk, loaded with bags Haotie affected area twice a day, four cycles of healing (seven days for a course). governance cholecystitis: 30 grams of corn, dandelion, capillaris 15 grams. Decoction three times a day a month to cure. the rule gastroenteritis: papaya 100 grams, 100 grams of lentils, watered down beans to eat cooked soup, twice a day and a half eradicate. the rule gastroenteritis: papaya 100 grams, 100 grams of lentils, watered down beans to eat cooked soup, twice a day and a half eradicate. treatment of rheumatoid arthritis: two bubble pepper white wine 2 pounds, bubble wash the affected area after seven days, three times a day, Half Moon to cure governance bronchitis: fried peach, white pepper, and the branches , ether and 25 grams of crushed broken face, egg reconcile Nanzuonvyou attached to the soles of the feet at eating eggs. One a day, seven days effects. governance gallstones: 10 g Gallus gallus domesticus, drying into powder, blunt boiled water three times a day a month to cure. governance kidney stones. urethral stones: walnut, crystal sugar 20 grams, 50 grams of sesame oil, warm water, one day a month to cure. cure stomach ailments : blood WULINGZHI 25 g Yan Hu Su,Twelve constellations of the funny language, Xiang Fu bergamot 20 grams each, nard 15 g water. One a day, half cured. bloating stomach full governance: black and white ugly drying into powder, blunt boiled water, 3 times a day, each 10 grams, seven days to cure. limbs Numbness in governance: of ginger, garlic, 20 g, 100 g chopped mixed with vinegar, add water, a bowl of fried open Washing the affected area. (1) wash your hair, put a little salt in the water can also prevent hair loss. (2) wash your hair with vinegar, can make hair floating along, easy to take care of both the efficacy of dandruff. Particularly suitable for the hair after the perm. (3) on the toothpaste when brushing your teeth, plus a little Minnesota, brush three teeth as white as jade, natural shedding of teeth rust. (4) put a few  of tea a day chewing in the mouth three times, it will give you mouth to keep the fragrance, three days later to remove Bad breath. (5) after the walnuts over the fire pan on the pain of teeth, bite, so a few times and never Toothache. (6) sleep mouth with orange peel, one containing 15 minutes, spit it out 3-5 times a day can cure snoring teeth. (7) a day sooner or later Chili a swallow slowly, hold for 3-4 days, the inflammation of the mouth immediately improved. (8) with white radish skin affixed to both sides of the temple posted 20 minutes per night, can cure migraine. (9) the big light blue chopped on the small cap, small cap before going to sleep to put the pillow you can sleep peacefully for several days to cure insomnia. (10) fell injuring tendons after leek mash, less urine, swelling can be attached to the wound a few hours to a little boy, three days later back to normal. (11) each port with an egg facial, an hour later, washed with water, such as can often wipe, skin is more tender. (12) orange with a white silk Many oranges are orange on the white silk In fact, there is rich in flavonoids, beneficial to the body. (13) from 8:00 to 10:00 and 4:00 to 7:00 is the best time of the health of the sun. (14) the best time for tea health meal one hour after. (15) 3 minutes after a meal and gargle, brush your teeth the best time. Come to a warm water bath (35 &amp;#176; C to 45 &amp;#176; C), to sleep at night (16) a day, make the body\'s muscles, joints, relaxation, blood circulation, help you fall asleep. (17) after a meal 45-60 minutes, the rate of hourly 4.8 km walk for 20 minutes, the Heat consumption of the largest, most conducive to Weight loss. Two hours after a meal and then take a walk, would be better. (18) evening exercise is most beneficial. (19) eyedrops upward slightly when the mouth so that the eyes on the chaos will not blink. (20) eye into small dust, close your eyes and Cough hard a few, the dust will be out of their own. (21) just a mosquito bite is finished, coated with soap will not Itch. (23) If the inflammation of the throat, gums, and in the evening to eat watermelon cut into small pieces, dipped in salt, remember it must be at night, when the symptoms will be alleviated next day just fine. (24) eating smelly things, such as garlic, tofu, eat a few peanuts like. (25) flowers when a drop of detergent in the water drop can be maintained for several days. Summer (26) feet sweat easily, feet can cope with sweaty feet a day with salt. The anti-insomnia (27): less before bedtime talk too much, avoid drinking tea before going to bed not Dayong brain, can be used hot water and vinegar and feet. (28) hands easily become dry and rough, hand soak with vinegar 10 minutes to skin care. Tofu friction face a few minutes every morning (29) a month, the face will become very moisturizing. (30) bag on the stain, you can use cotton dipped in the wind spirits wipe. hair: hair perm - avocado hair perm process will take away the water and oil of the hair, the hair becomes dry. Mature avocado contains 30% of the precious vegetable oil - oleic acid, play a role in protection of dry hair. The brain : excessive use of excessive brain - banana brain lead to vitamin minerals and energy deficiency, in addition to the tired brain, but also often feel depressed. The supplementary bananas provide the necessary nutrients and to mitigate the negative emotions. With the brain due to excessive consumption of a variety of vitamins, nutritionists, adding that the Centrum multi-vitamin tablets. eyes: excessive use of eyes the - papaya , for a long time staring at a computer screen or TV screen, and excessive use of the eye, the retinal photoreceptors rely on key material consume a lot of vitamin A, the eyes feel dry, pain, photophobia, and even vision loss. At this point you need to consume a large number of vitamin A can provide the Fan papaya. With special effects. gums: Bleeding gums - kiwi gums healthy and vitamin C are closely related. The lack of vitamin C in human gingival become fragile, and often Bleeding, swelling, and even lead to loose teeth. The vitamin C content of kiwifruit is the most abundant fruit, so the fruit is most beneficial to gingival health. efforts of cherry pipe heart: history of heart disease - high the grapefruit cholesterol serious impact health, in particular, a history of heart disease should pay more attention to control body cholesterol levels. Grapefruit is the fruit of the medical profession recognized as the most therapeutic efficacy and the valve contained in the natural pectin can lower cholesterol, and prevention variety of cardiovascular diseases. lung: long-term smoking - the grapes long-term smoking lung accumulation of toxins, function is impaired. The active ingredients contained in the grapes can improve cell metabolism rate to help the detoxification of lung cells. In addition, grape also has expectorant effect and can alleviate respiratory tract irritation, Itching and other symptoms caused by smoking. muscles: muscle strain the - pineapple , muscle strain after inflammation, blood circulation, pain, swelling of the injured area. Pineapple contains bromelain components have anti-inflammatory effect, can promote tissue repair, but also speed up the metabolism, improve blood circulation, rapid swelling is the body most in need of to fruit. skin: it is easy to wrinkles prevent wrinkles - mango the if skin collagen elasticity. The mango is the best fruit to prevent wrinkles, rich in beta-carotene and unique enzymes to stimulate skin cell viability, and promote waste discharge, helps to maintain collagen, elasticity, effectively delaying the appearance of wrinkles. blood: lack of oxygen - the Cherry fatigue and blood iron content in most cases to reduce, not getting enough oxygen and poor blood circulation. Eating cherries iron supplementation, which the rich content of vitamin C can promote the body to absorb iron to prevent iron loss and improve blood circulation, help help to resist fatigue. feet: athlete\'s foot trouble - lack of vitamin B1 the orange body prone to athlete\'s foot trouble. This case, the most suitable choice of oranges, which are rich in vitamin B1, helps glucose metabolism, the effective prevention and treatment of beriberi. This case, the most suitable choice of oranges, which are rich in vitamin B1, helps glucose metabolism, the effective prevention and treatment of beriberi. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:136753:39305688</id><idPostId>39305688</idPostId><idBlogId>136753</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:136753</id><idBlogId>136753</idBlogId><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com</link><displayName>HOCKEYCENTRIC</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-philadelphia-flyers-must-find-a-goaltending-fix/</link><displayName>The Philadelphia Flyers Must Find A Goaltending Fix</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-01T18:19:50.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:136753:39305688:329397305</id><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-philadelphia-flyers-must-find-a-goaltending-fix/#IDComment329397305</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T18:19:50.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The Philadelphia Flyers Must Find A Goaltending Fix by bm8vne4vt</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://hermeshandbags-sale.com/</link><idEmailMd5>d5822e0c2ffaaba5fe4f7fc4b792d912</idEmailMd5><displayName>bm8vne4vt</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://hermeshandbags-sale.com/"&gt;bm8vne4vt&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-philadelphia-flyers-must-find-a-goaltending-fix/"&gt;The Philadelphia Flyers Must Find A Goaltending Fix&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>