<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk1hld/post/2012-03-26T11:25:15</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>New details and info, according to Orlando Sentinal:  

"With a single punch, Trayvon Martin decked the Neighborhood Watch volunteer who eventually shot and killed the unarmed 17-year-old, then Trayvon climbed on top of George Zimmerman and slammed his head into the sidewalk several times, leaving him bloody and battered, authorities have revealed to the Orlando Sentinel.
&lt;i&gt;snip&lt;/i&gt;
There is about a one-minute gap during which police say they're not sure what happened.

Zimmerman told them he lost sight of Trayvon and was walking back to his SUV when Trayvon approached him from the left rear, and they exchanged words.

Trayvon asked Zimmerman if he had a problem. Zimmerman said no and Reached for his cell phone, he told police.

Trayvon then said, "Well, you do now" or something similar and punched Zimmerman in the nose.

Zimmerman fell to the ground and Trayvon got on top of him and began slamming his head into the sidewalk, he told police.Zimmerman began yelling for help.

Several witnesses heard those cries, and there's been a dispute about from whom they came: Zimmerman or Trayvon.

Lawyers for Trayvon's family say it was Trayvon, but police say their evidence indicates it was Zimmerman.One witnesses, who has since talked to local television news reporters, told police he saw Zimmerman on the ground with Trayvon on top, pounding him and was unequivocal that it was Zimmerman who was crying for help.

Zimmerman then shot Trayvon once in the chest from very close range, according to authorities.

When police arrived less than two minutes later, Zimmerman was Bleeding from the nose, had a swollen lip and had bloody lacerations to the back of his head.

Paramedics gave him first aide but he said no to going to the hospital. He got medical care the next day.
&lt;i&gt;snip &lt;/i&gt;
He had been suspended from school in Miami after being found with an empty marijuana baggie. Miami schools have a zero-tolerance policy for drug possession.

"http://articles.orlandosentinel.com/2012-03-26/news/os-trayvon-martin-zimmerman-account-20120326_1_arizona-iced-tea-suv-unarmed-black-teenager</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rxhlr</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tz1k</id></website><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/will-cain-takes-on-cnns-don-lemon-lz-granderson-over-racial-aspect-of-trayvon-martin-case/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T01:10:59+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T15:25:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk1hld</id><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/will-cain-takes-on-cnns-don-lemon-lz-granderson-over-racial-aspect-of-trayvon-martin-case/#comment-476468360</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/07k6</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>