<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mibvpq/update/2012-03-23T14:47:02/4fab96dde2842cba46fb78a5a45d743a4d5de052e9d7cb5a4cf62ec8d34e2f99</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I commend Mr. Friedersdorf for dipping a toe in a pool that most left-leaning 
writers won't even venture near, but he undermines his own credibility with 
observations that prove dubious and/or hypocritical in the Cold light of reality.  

For example: 

1. Friedersdorf: "Obama supporters are under no illusion that his policies are going to bring about an earthly paradise. He hasn't attempted to sell them that way." 

Oh, please, Conor! Are we not talking about the same Obama who, as a presidential candidate in 2008,  uttered such soaring rhetoric as "generations from now we will be able to look back and tell our children that this was the moment when ... the rise of the oceans began to slow and our planet began to heal." 

Yes indeed, and if that's not a big enough  of pie-in-the-sky on your plate, dig in to his 2009 U.N. speech in which Obama declared his commitment to "a world without nuclear weapons."  (No word on whether he expects to  that goal before or after he rids the world of poverty, hunger and disease with a wave of his mighty hand.) 

* * * * * 

2. Friedersdorf: "(A)s Communism and centrally planned economies became increasingly discredited even on the left ..."

Communism, discredited on the left?? I'd say the trend is moving in the exact opposite 
direction.  

Three easy examples: 

(1) The "One World Working Together" rally on the National Mall in 2010, which featured Communist Party USA right alongside such fellow sponsors as the NAACP, the AFL-CIO, the Sierra Club and the National Education Association.  

(2) Shortly after becoming president of the AFL-CIO, Richard Trumka helped rescind a provision that  Communist Party members from 
becoming officers in the union. 

(3) Democrat Congressman Danny K. Davis of Illinois, an Obama ally, recently accepted a Social Justice award at Communist Party USA's Chicago headquarters ... presented by the pro-Marx group People's World. 

Doesn't exactly conjure up memories of Joe McCarthy, does it?   

* * * * * 

3. Friedersdorf:  "the right, which is good at producing content that sells to the shrinking base ..."

"Shrinking base"?? A January 2012 Gallup poll found that 40% of Americans describe themselves as conservative, 35% as moderate, and 21% as liberal. Moreover, Talkers magazine's survey of the most popular talk radio programs finds Rush Limbaugh, Sean Hannity, Michael Savage, Glenn Beck, Mark Levin at the top of the list. I don't think any Air America Radio hosts qualified.

Come to think of it, the fact that Levin's book debuted No. 1 on the Times best-seller list would seem to suggest that either his base is anything but shrunken ... or that his audience includes more than just right-wingers.

* * * * * 

4. Friedersdorf: "Conservatism is as rife with such Acts of tribal loyalty as any other network." 

Whatever the validity of this statement, it amounts to a petty charge of  "You guys a're just as bad as we are." 

I mean, he's already acknowledged that "right-leaning books aren't given their due in academia or the left-leaning media." Why not take his fellow lefties to task for consistently treating conservative literature with the kind of shun that would make an Amish parish proud? Instead, he  simply says, "Their [conservatives'] beef is legitimate" -- which hardly conveys the kind of critical energy that he unleashes on Levin's book and conservatives in general. 

* * * * * 

5. Speaking of which, why was this story headlined, "Why Mainstream Media Ignores Conservative Bestsellers"?  Friedersdorf invests considerably less time, space and effort exploring that question than he does enthusiastically critiquing "Ameritopia" and the conservative movement.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6m6bfq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/eyjq</id></website><link>http://m.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2012/03/why-conservative-bestsellers-are-widely-ignored/254692/</link><postedTime>2012-03-19T19:19:40+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T18:47:02+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mibvpq</id><link>http://m.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2012/03/why-conservative-bestsellers-are-widely-ignored/254692/#comment-474699943</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/tsfe</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-19</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>