<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkhsjy/post/2012-03-25T15:31:05</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I learned about this from a lady whose family is from there.  You can see she's distraught and she wasn't even born during this.  She lives on the forgotten borough of NYC and I learned about it back in the early 90's.  She wanted all of us to pick up and go with her and her family and open businesses there.  That's the first time I also heard about Rosewood, FL with a slight mention about an old babysitter I had in Miami who, when I would return to that area and see her in 1999 she would tell me all about the movie and that she was one of the kids in the swamp.  MIND you, she NEVER saw the movie but she could tell me incident by incident EXACTLY what occured.  This is how I know Singleton kept as close as he could to the story.  She was an old lady telling me this.  It struck me that as she watched me as a scared kid running from domestic violence from my beloved home Harlem she was also traumatized much worse living in Miami and not the town her people built up because of crazed Whites, out of their minds.  I had seen the movie so you know how you have to go and meditate after you see it to cool down.  (steam coming from ears, you know the deal).

So, when reading up in the 90's about Negro Wall street and being stuck here in Northern Mississippi, outerboro of NYC that has a problem being part of NY where they give Black people hell for living in places named after big slave masters in this NYC (Dongan Hills) I of course lent my books out and never got them back because once people get hold of the story it takes time to go back to it and then you want to look at the book, then put it away for a time because it's traumatizing.  Well, it's time to heal that and build up again. 

Right now I'm poor as a church mouse but I'll see my way clear to scrape a few dollars and send and I'll tell EVERYONE I know about this.  

If the producers are reading this I want them to know that on 9/11 I was on a ferry for the first plane strike but the second one I was on the 18th floor at the edge of Manhattan 5 blocks away from 9/11 when the second one hit.  A week later when were allowed back into the office, of course everyone's in shock and of course the inevitable racists are going to say "how dare they do this to our nation."  I had to tell them this isn't the first time it was done and I mentioned two violent episodes in this nation the first of which was maniacal Whites getting in planes and throwing malatov cocktails from above at the residents below because they were too  Black and successful and when "settlers"  Burned out Native Indian teepees and then shot the poor people as they ran away from the smoke inhalation.  

I was of course laid  in 2002 cause they couldn't deal with me nor could I stomach them.   
They still see red when I bump into them but I couldn't contain myself I just can't let White folks think their ancestors would good people who came her peacefully.  They weren't, they were murderous, blood thirsty, jealous, destructive individuals and as a group they are like a plague of locusts.  Now they're gentrifying. 

Time to build up, time to kick out the foreign owned corner stores, time to kick the Asians out of the hair business and shame on any of us for buying foreigners no tasting salty fried chicken.  We need to show that when we buy any little thing from these foreigners, especially from the Arab/Middle Eastern world, 2,000 years of hateful history stains each and every transaction.   Light skinned Egyptians hate us over there and deny that the original people there were dark with no crinkly hair.  If they hate us there, they hate us here.  Same for India, etc.  Turn this mess around.  

I'm searching for grants, angel funds, etc. and once i start my own businesses I'll be starting angel funds and businesses as schools so that others can be trained to do this.  I will NOT be a CJ Walker to an Annie Malone who showed Walker how to do it and then gets all the accolades.  Time for that type of BS to STOP.  

Daily I see two high schools near me full of Black kids spilling out onto my neighborhood where they buy up pizza from 3 parlors, fried chicken from two foreign owned places, 10 candy stores, a donut shop, an Italian bakery, 2 sandwich shops, 2 drug stores, 2 99cent shops, and 4 laundromats and not a one will hire a Black child EVER.  

Being in my current situation I have seen things I've never seen before and one of them is the eagerness to learn about not only how to run their own businesses but why we're taught to  WORK for someone rather than RUN/OPEN our own.   Our folks are ready.  We're tired of seeing the gentrifiers buy what we couldn't buy and ears perk up when the Black history of slaves and how they celebrated Emancipaton day on the Manhattan facing waterfront here in 1827 and how our ancestors walked all the way from Bullops Point in old Richmondtown to where the ferry is now.  That's a long damned walk and they did it in fear of being enslaved again.  

This borough has a lot of provincial people here but now they're really getting tired of the way things are and ready to make some changes.  We were enslaved in Port Richmond from the 1600's virtually the same time we were building the walls on Wall street during the dutch  so of course when whole Mexican towns decide to take it over and  like there's a turf war, we should have a problem.  We built that area (now lead infested) for free.  This is before Sandy Grounds Settlement. 

We were lynched in Snug Harbor.  These things have to be rooted out and to complete the picutre.  Harlem I love you and miss you but if Columbia is going to put a 7 story deep underground biohazardous lab on top of an active fault line that Harlem does indeed have, there may be a time when we'll all have to run!  

Remember, Harlem didn't happen to us, WE happened to IT.  We also happened to Negro Wall Street and if from the random conversations I see from Blacks and Browns living under siege in low cost housing and greedy Whites working hard to push us out is any indication, were going to have to band together and save ourselves.  See, even with money we cannot move back en masse to former settlements downtown in what was once Little Italy, Chinatown, and on Mercer,  Spring and Broome Streets and if we try to re-establish the old African Theater on Mercer street near the old One-Mile Stone Inn we can have triple the cost of sale but denied the ability to purchse;  we can't go back there!  Not in large groups anyway.    
 
Any White person possessing the cash can go back to any old part of NYC we USED to be in.  

When they all get bored with each other, cause despite how different and creative they think they are, many are just alike, they're going to go looking for something else with some more flavor.  This time though, they've really taught us who they are.  Just talk to the Black folks of Fort Greene and Bed Stuy now.  Them White folks sittin' on the A train can't wait to get rid of us. It's the best lesson about we could ever learn about who they really are and how their ancestors behaved.  In this time however the world is changing and this time, when the worst of them comes to push once again, they're going to get a shove they never expected.  When people are just tired and beyond tears and hurt, things change.   The next revolution will NOT be televised.  

This goes for every other town too.  We know the deal.  

Will be looking forward to this documentary and hope it expands to telling in depth stories of other settlements, towns (over 16) and extends to Canada and Central/South America.   Have to connect all the stories including the disaster that is now in the old rich areas of Africa.  We put this stuff in cars at the expense of people that look just  like us.   From here to Nigeria to the untold stories of the Latin world where Blacks in Columbia are being pushed Off mineral rich mountain land and threatened with execution.  Time for an international movement.  From Oklahoma, to DC to Trenchtown, the violence, poverty, murders, and how it makes us turn on each other can be undone.  Tell the stories here, start the economic movement here and toss any good for nothing con artists and let's make real changes in earnest.   No time to go after White folks either.   

Let's get a plan together, identify the disruptors and toss em out or play with em and turn this situation where foreigners can get loans and help but not us around.  We buy groceries from stores that don't source food from Black farmers.  Take control of this NOW.  

Trust me, I'm dangerous with a lottery win!  I have no time for mansions unless I can turn it into a school, shelter, etc.  Love and peace y'all!  

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yj0cv</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t26w</id></website><link>http://newsone.com/nation/dlchandler/hyati-the-legacy-of-black-america/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T20:59:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-25T19:31:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkhsjy</id><link>http://newsone.com/nation/dlchandler/hyati-the-legacy-of-black-america/#comment-475980309</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mrsn9</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>