<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwuglu/post/2012-03-30T22:33:30</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>These renovations were also made in the complex I live in.  While I love the new kitchen, my issue with these new kitchens and bathrooms is the money it cost to do the renovations.  I've had things in my apartment that have desperately needed fixing for years (very drafty doors and windows mainly) but have been told "we don't have the money to fix things like that".  Heat is included in my rent, and if any tenant goes over the allotted amount of fuel, we have to pay the extra.  I wouldn't mind that if I didn't have to vacate my living room every time the wind blows because an actual breeze can be felt coming in through the windows in the living room because the insulation has deteriorated so bad.  I would have GLADLY gone without the new kitchen, bathroom and laundry room I got in exchange for a warmer, safer apartment.  The renovations they have made were cosmetic, and not necessary.  But many of us have to blow through our fuel very quickly because much needed renovations can't be done because there is no budget for it?  Please tell me how that makes any sense.  And no, we can't complain to Housing.  I tried and Always get told "Sorry, blah blah, no money to fix that, blah blah".  Ask questions before you judge and accuse.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67tckz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dngw</id></website><link>http://bangordailynews.com/2012/03/30/news/bangor/bangor-housing-renovation-upsets-some-tenants/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T23:54:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T02:33:30+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwuglu</id><link>http://bangordailynews.com/2012/03/30/news/bangor/bangor-housing-renovation-upsets-some-tenants/#comment-481450199</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5wzqx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>