<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mid3ji/post/2012-03-22T19:49:41</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mimkbl</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6gykb</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> I heard them too and was surprised.  I thought the MHM was going to be in Foley square though.  I had just dropped by the park after a job interview to see the Occupiers, see who has reappeared, whose been arrested and check for the usual disruptors (one was there but very quiet).  
  During the protest I heard some OWS people making chants and have to say that it was out of place since it was so difficult to hear the people speak in the first place.  I had to leave early as my feet gave out in those shoes.   to see the signs, etc. but it's time to make demands, tighten up the message and so on.  I like the idea of dissent against a corporatized gov't and political process and pushing the idea of breaking the hold of the hidden power structure that's done so much to damage our lives but when I mention that slaves built the wall on wall street and that Zucotti Park stands on the Spot where the first slave rebellion was planned there in 1711 and tell them that as angry as they are, people of color have been hammered by the system created to benefit Whites who go of to gentrified apartments, it's still not enough.  
    For Black folks there is work to do outside of OWS.  There are anti-dissent police and gov't agents trained to come in and undermine groups like this.  When I come around there I know what I'm in for but just because some don't understand that doesn't mean that other knowledgeable people of color shouldn't appear there and be a thorn in their side.  Our physical presence there coupled with intelligence is only irritating to the wrong people.  You don't ask permission to be there you just get in and take over and put your message out there.
   It's also good to know what they're up to next, how they think.  Apparently wherever minorities are, especially poor ones, is now the Spot to gentrify.  Right now its cool to pretend like what they're doing is perfectly fine behavior but it won't Always be.  Our numbers are growing and we have a long memory.  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yu8jb</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t26w</id></website><link>http://newsone.com/nation/elonjameswhite/how-occupy-wall-street-co-opted-the-million-hoodie-march/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T17:05:59+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T23:49:41+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mid3ji</id><link>http://newsone.com/nation/elonjameswhite/how-occupy-wall-street-co-opted-the-million-hoodie-march/#comment-474068730</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mrsn9</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>