<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/212653/post/71547994/comment/329368677</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Baby Fever natural prescription (old Chinese recommended) 
to the baby Fever natural prescription old Chinese : when the baby is sick with Fever, easy not to eat the baby antipyretics,Hermes Bags, and do not transfusion! Baby Fever when Chinese medicine, told me as long as you give the children lose a liquid, the child was sick most of 1-1.5 months,Hermes Birkin bags, should the reason for the degradation of immune function. Tell you that the mother a prescription for Fever, is when the baby is sick, an old Chinese medicine given. Parsley to the leaves remain 3-4 root stems and roots of turnip 1-2 tablets, 2-3  of ginger, add rock sugar boiled for 15 minutes. Cooked in the back of the hand to try the baby to drink is not hot baby sweating Fever . . an old Chinese recipe: pears lungs and phlegm, Apple Diarrhea and nutritious. Cucumber effective Weight loss of kiwi fruit inhibit cancer. the tomato blood to help face the lotus root Chufan wonderful hangover. Qi orange phlegm, kidney warm leek knee waist. radish addition to Flatulence digestion, celery can cure high blood pressure. Diuretic row toxin cabbage, cauliflower eat less cancer. swelling diuretic melon, green beans detoxification high efficacy. Fungus to engage in cancer casual blood stasis, kidney swelling yam consumption. kelp iodine loose silt Results mushrooms contain cancer cells. Pepper to fend Off the Cold and dampness, onion spicy ginger for Colds. fish Pig complement milk,Hermes Kelly handbags, liver goat liver good eyesight. Kidney waist eating walnuts, dates Jianshen Spleen eat. treatment of hypertension: (1) banana peel 30 grams of dried decoction to drink 3 times a day, a month effect. (2) Apocynum with traditional Chinese medicine, the open water to drink, 15 grams a day, half bear fruit. (3) Ginkgo biloba 15 g per day, with open water to drink, half bear fruit. Governance hypotension: 20 grams of licorice, cassia twig, cinnamon 40 grams, more than one drug mixing to take a week when the tea brewing. governance lipid density: the (1) medlar 10 grams, polygonum multiflorum, Cassia, hawthorn, 15 grams, 20 grams of Salvia water, twice a day, four cycles of healing, (seven days for a course of treatment). (2) hawthorn, Ginkgo biloba. Gynostemma each 15 grams, make some tea. Even serving four courses (half a course of treatment). face black star (freckles): Yuan coriander (aka cilantro), decoction, wash three times a day, a course of cure. governance sweat odor: the white radish boiled water Washing the feet every night for 30 minutes, even wash half cured. beriberi: pound leeks, boil water ten minutes feet once a day, every 20 minutes, three days dig up the roots. treatment of neurasthenia: 50 grams of floating wheat, hay 24 grams, jujube 20 grams, 30 grams of Semen, mixed. Decoction once a day, half cured. the Toothache: liquor two rosin 15 g,The firefly \'s life , love and transformation, and soak two hours after the cotton touched alcohol on the Toothache Department, clenched. 5 minutes hurt, Qi Qing insects fire Cold. cure Toothache: ant cellular brown sugar, two against two bowls of water, the remaining half a bowl of fried patient to drink, hurt in three decades. governance stomatitis: watermelon rind dried, the Feng Chaojiao, the ice sheet a little into powder, mix with honey applied to the lesion, special effects. governance rotten mouth: with concentrated tea water, add a little salt, and then used to gargle three times a day to five times, three-day cure. treatment pharyngitis: kelp wash , blanched to remove the sugar, salted after eating two, three times a day for each 30 grams a pair. Light, two pairs, to pay to dig up the roots (a pound of kelp, a pound of sugar). governance the tympanitis: leek root 2 smashed out of water, add a little borneol, ear drops, special effects. cure tinnitus and deafness: Wuji a male, sweet four pounds, cooked hot food, ate five, special effects. Cold: coriander and a light blue even have five , ginger 10, decoction, add brown sugar, one or two hot clothes twice a day, one day cure. governance migraine: the amount of raw carrot juice usage: supine into the nose, pain in the left right note, right pain Note left, the magic of the ice sheet some even better. Headache: Angelica 4 g, 2 g of borneol, 2 grams Asarum, research into the flour involved in the paper tube to put the powder Burning, with smoke inhalation. the governance Dizziness, Headache (nervous Headache): Astragalus Gastrodia one or two each, stewed yellow hen eaten, ate three cured. cure hemorrhoids: skin one or two nitrate, bud half a catty. Boil water Washing, twice a day, seven days to cure. governance Yin Itching anal Itching: vinegar 500 grams, salt 5 gram hot wash, three times a day. treatment of epistaxis: (1) the left nasal Bleeding from the right ear, blowing right nasal Bleeding blowing from the left ear, you can immediately stop the Bleeding. (2) head Fever ash blown into the nostrils stand only (male female hair, female parent fat) can eradicate. governance rhinitis: Xanthium 30 grams, lightly smashed into the spoon, add sesame oil 50 grams Boiling will remove Xanthium slag, with oil droplets nose, a day 3-5 times. treatment of glaucoma: 3 sunflower plate (seeded), cut half of the oral administration of the decoction of the crushed other half of the fumigation eye a half months to cure. administering eye tears. keratitis: fish gall bladder, eye, three times a day, half cured. Fast Beauty: three eggs, wine foam, sealing the 4-7 days, egg white painted face every day, seven days a surface such as snow. cure acne: dandelion 2 two boil water to drink, one day a pair of half cured. Governance hand, foot and crack: gall amount into powder, bovine bone marrow or alum Shihlin tune smear crevices days to cure. governance Spots: angelica half a catty, boils water bowl, wipe the affected area with this water, half bear fruit. governance shoulder Zhou Yan: Ginger a 2 taro twenty-two, peeled and smashed drunk, loaded with bags Haotie affected area twice a day, four cycles of healing (seven days for a course) . governance cholecystitis: 30 grams of corn, dandelion, capillaris 15 grams. Decoction three times a day a month to cure. rule gastroenteritis: papaya 100 grams, 100 grams of lentils, watered down to eat cooked bean soup twice a day and a half eradicate. treatment of rheumatoid arthritis: pepper 2 two soak liquor 2 pounds, bubble wash the affected area after seven days, three times a day, half cured. cure bronchitis: fried peach , white pepper, and the branches,Hermes Kelly, ether, 25 g crushed broken surface, the egg reconcile the, Nanzuonvyou attached to the soles of the feet at eating the eggs. One a day, seven days effects. treatment of gallstones: 10 g Gallus gallus domesticus, drying into powder, blunt boiled water three times a day a month to cure. cure kidney stones, urinary tract stones: walnut, crystal sugar 20 grams, 50 grams of sesame oil, warm boiled water, one day a month to cure. cure stomach ailments: blood WULINGZHI 25 g Yan Hu Su, Cyperus bergamot 20 grams each, nard, 15 g water. One a day, half cured. governance bloating stomach full: black and white ugly drying into powder, blunt boiled water three times a day,Hermes Handbags, each 10 grams, seven days to cure. governance Numbness of the limbs: ginger, 20 grams each of garlic, chopped 100 grams mixed with vinegar, add water, a bowl of fried open Washing the affected area. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:212653:71547994</id><idPostId>71547994</idPostId><idBlogId>212653</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:212653</id><idBlogId>212653</idBlogId><link>http://www.ourartcriticism.com</link><displayName>Our Art Criticism</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.ourartcriticism.com/contemporary/the-relevance-of-critical-theory-to-art-today/</link><displayName>The relevance of critical theory to art today</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-01T17:26:25.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:212653:71547994:329368677</id><link>http://www.ourartcriticism.com/contemporary/the-relevance-of-critical-theory-to-art-today/#IDComment329368677</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T17:26:25.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The relevance of critical theory to art today by ef7ji7nr</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://hermeshandbags-sale.com/</link><idEmailMd5>96a64324f22b2c912bc43c9442b84105</idEmailMd5><displayName>ef7ji7nr</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://hermeshandbags-sale.com/"&gt;ef7ji7nr&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.ourartcriticism.com/contemporary/the-relevance-of-critical-theory-to-art-today/"&gt;The relevance of critical theory to art today&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>