<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwr721/update/2012-03-30T12:11:44/ad99d24fd06de5e7ad7380847c60f3a315bf87f1d5a04758e07840ae7e659ca7</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwdhtx</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lj73r</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> the efficiencies are quite ok and at 85-90% (pumps and turbines and the guttery around Heat up and consume energy )

but the expense is of course the investment in infrastructure which Always gets whispered away like "1 time expense which they are not"
it requires a lot of energy to make cement and concrete. a LOT.
A hoover dam is there for decennia 50years, but it needs a lot of repair all the way. it is a bomb as well, terrorists will flock around those dams to see how to break them, no difference with nuclear, you'ld have 24/365 security and police army around them.

oh and it STILL does not fix the transport problem: we hv now a star network from power stations to urban centres. this buffering of energy adds a dimension in complexity as these will become a set of nodes elsewhere in the landscape, away from the urbans away from the stations away from the windmill parcs just, you know, somehwere jollifully elsewhere. As long as wind is just a parasitic disturbance in the star network this gets ignored. At the moment wind is more of a disturbance than the original star network can handle you need massive re designs

wind energy will not save a molecule of CO2 in its whole lifespan, and thats under the assumption the climate does not change. if the climate changes, the wind will blow too hard or not at all in the wind optimised wind parks, and the windmills will NOT turn, and instead of a green dividend this parcs become a huge carbogenic spill</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z63l9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ms5i</id></website><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/jamesdelingpole/100148065/what-pastygate-tells-us-about-camerons-conservatives/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T12:22:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:11:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwr721</id><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/jamesdelingpole/100148065/what-pastygate-tells-us-about-camerons-conservatives/#comment-480902856</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cnd4t</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>