<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jybe/update/2012-04-02T02:56:42/9381cf4675848138ee14fd9792f43f9043517cf17abd9e9bbab51dea2fe8b7f9</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The  life is terrible.  Double the  by increasing its surface area to the most of the rear face and add a slight increase in average thickness by filling the phone body to the same uniform thickness overall, instead of just the camera hump and the fat ass.


The 16GB HSDPA+ model is too small for programs, data and local storage of multimedia data.      Provide for more storage, via a micro-SD card slot or offer a 32 + 64GB internal storage model.    I'm already out of space and I don't have all my music. 
The RAM usage by lots of applications resident services (which cannot be stopped) requires 
Double or Quadruple the current 1GB RAM to 2 or better still 4 GB.

The  covers hooked slots on the bottom of the  door are a design defect.   They can be hard to Align and can break. Remove them and replace with the same snap-to-fit all the way around.

Go for the proper RGB display, instead of Pentile.  The image quality difference is noticeable compared to an iphone 4.

Go for a higher performance processor GPU/CPU pair as the display can be jerky.  Go hard or go home.  Quad core, maybe. But definitely bump GPU performance by a factor of two at least.

Place the speaker on the *bottom* of the phone, not the back!  (seriously, who let that get past user experience testing?!). Also, make the speaker able to be LOUD.   Its currently simply not loud enough for situations with even a little ambient noise.

The camera is inferior compared to almost any other phone with a backside-illuminated sensor. Seriously, why put an inferior image sensor in, but have great camera *software*?!   Go for a decent backside 
illuminated sensor this time - lots of camera phone shots are of poorly lit, ad-hoc shots. It's the WHOLE POINT of phone cameras and poor Light sensitivity lets this function down.add water-resistance coating FTW.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6v730h</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/y2ru</id></website><link>http://www.engadget.com/2012/04/01/how-would-you-change-samsungs-galaxy-nexus/</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T11:13:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T06:56:42+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jybe</id><link>http://www.engadget.com/2012/04/01/how-would-you-change-samsungs-galaxy-nexus/#comment-483321966</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yu907</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>