<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m33cz7/post/2012-03-30T00:16:06</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>http://phoenixpreacher.net/?p=11670

Just reading around the meta and eureka, connected dots. Here is just one link but there are plenty in the comments.

 Why the big deal on Harriet's comment? Why the sudden coincidental "blog comment moderating" focus from other blogs around the NC/Reformed meta? 

Mark Driscoll. 

Since Petry, the former fired Elder/former lawyer, story came out-- some  29 churches are not happy. Some are even leaving the network. Ergo, it is being swtiched to Chandler. All to stop the possible Bleeding of members or churches leaving the network.  They want the blogosphere quiet about this and the post interviewing the W. Europe  29 guy could have become a bit embarassing if any uncomfortable questions asked.  (Of course it is being spun that Driscoll leaving was planned all along but that would not explain Mark's announcement a  month or so ago he had to come back and get things in line there. But now, he is leaving to focus on ministry at MH? A bit flighty.) Driscoll is stepping away to stop the Bleeding fast.

Seems the guy running  29,   Thomas, was the point guy for taking Petry down. there is documentation with him using  29 email.  So, he is "going into another ministry" and not going to Texas.

Sojourn in Louisville has a letter on it's site saying it is leaving  29 to become church  dated March 28. Of course, they still love Acts 29.  

Will no one out in celebrity Christian land be Driscoll's Nathan? Must we all pretend this is not rearranging deck chairs on the Titanic?</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hwpq6</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/jrkj</id></website><link>http://peterlumpkins.typepad.com/peter_lumpkins/2012/03/below-is-a-post-by-harriet-petersen-harriet-is-among-the-kindest-mellow-southern-baptist-bloggers-period-yet-recently-s.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T01:13:37+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T04:16:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m33cz7</id><link>http://peterlumpkins.typepad.com/peter_lumpkins/2012/03/below-is-a-post-by-harriet-petersen-harriet-is-among-the-kindest-mellow-southern-baptist-bloggers-period-yet-recently-s.html#comment-480234615</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzvot</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>