<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzzz0/post/2012-03-30T14:26:44</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>While I think it's unfortunate that Soundtrack appears on the same week as 'Norm the Movie', its real faults are in its execution. Although it's a decent read, it is frustrating. And I think the issues are universal to amateur scripts (what separates amateur from professional/polished scripts)

-The entire story and plot rely only on the premise to hold our attention. Meaning: very little actually happens. It is simply a story about a problem, and talking about the problem. In the hope that that the writing (action blocks, descriptions, character traits, dialogue) is sharp enough to keep us engaged with the plot, when in fact the issue is that there is no plot. Ian is not active and there are not enough things around him which are active.

    -Ian has an issue (which begins when he falls on his head). He has a problem to overcome (impress the producer) while dealing with the issue, when he's put on the Spot (the audition). It goes horribly, but then he's given a 2nd chance. Thus, what may appear to be (or was intended as) the break into  II, is simply a continuation of  I (nothing's really happened, except to continue things as they are. He hasn't been forced into a dilemma/paradox, he hasn't lost anything, he hasn't won anything). 

    (-Compare that to The Hitman's Bodyguard, where  II begins when Kiernan and Bryce have to team up. They make an active decision, which leads to more action.)

Again, I think this a very universal issue with amateur scripts (even my own. Actually, 'especially' by own!). We have an idea (a premise), and only want to harp on how great/innovate that premise is, instead of using it to manufacture creative ways in &amp; out of the problem. That way the characters are taken on a journey (so is the reader/audience.)

-In addition, like most amateur scripts, Soundtrack simply use Act breaks/plot points to divy out information peace-meal; like the writer is afraid of exposition, and wants to keep us hanging on. (One of the major issues with Trees, from a few weeks back.)
    -Why not explain who Kaitlyn is to Ian right away?

    -While Ian's problem is directly related to his goal (getting the job), it's not related to a character trait/fault ("Oh Dae Su talks too much"....)

    -Why not simply explain who/what the job is right away?

    -If Ian really needs money, he could sell the ring. The opening banter/exchange with Kaitlyn is too long. They argue and indicate character traits, but nothing really happens. Nothing's decided, changed, etc..

I think that was the remarkable element of The Disciple Program and The Hitman's Bodyguard. They take a problem, write themselves into an impossible situation, and then come up with innovative ways out of them (whereas an amateur script such as Soundtrack, simply 'punts' the issue). </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/676vh6</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cj6q</id></website><link>http://scriptshadow.blogspot.com/2012/03/screenplay-review-soundtrack-amateur.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:12:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:26:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzzz0</id><link>http://scriptshadow.blogspot.com/2012/03/screenplay-review-soundtrack-amateur.html#comment-481042043</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hruar</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>