<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msn1df/delete/2012-03-27T21:34:12</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpz9w3</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6gxg9</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>MARTIN WASN'T in flight. According to the police report, if you'd get the fuck Off of wikipedia, zimmerman was on his back being beaten when he fired the shot. A witness confirmed that a man in red (zimmerman) was getting his "ass kicked". The witness ran upstairs to get a better look when he heard 1 shot, when he got to the window zimmerman was beginning to get up and martin (unfortunately) was on his back in the grass right next to zimmerman. This man has a record against the police do you really think there is some sort of cover up? they released him because the grass stains on his back and the wounds on his face and the back of the head (where witnesses said they saw martin smashing zimmerman's head against the ground) all pointed to self defense. Martin didn't have a scratch on him. Zimmerman tried to walk away. REGARDLESS of what might have been said between the two why the fuck would you attack a 250lb fat guy at night if you didn't have some sort of "i can kick anyone's ass" mentality? i don't care about Trayvon's grades or his school activities. The kid assaulted a man and got shot..legally. A black radio announcer like a week after this brought up a story and a good point. Two black teenagers followed a younger white 14yr old home from school and doused him in gasoline and lit him on fire (he survived) then the radio host played the news audio clip. They never mentioned the color of any of the kids..just that they were teenagers. The kid that was Burned later reported that one of the kids said "Burn white boy". If THAT had been two white kids Burning a black kid there would have been riots. I swear racism is turning around in places. All the Jesse Jameses and NAACP members don't give a shit about Trayvon...they don't care about black or white or anything in between...the only color they see is GREEN. </body><verb>delete</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dydud</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q905</id></website><link>http://patdollard.com/2012/03/did-george-zimmerman-complain-about-fucking-coons-in-911-call-before-killing-trayvon-martin/</link><postedTime>2012-03-20T23:56:47+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T01:34:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msn1df</id><link>http://patdollard.com/2012/03/did-george-zimmerman-complain-about-fucking-coons-in-911-call-before-killing-trayvon-martin/#comment-477975481</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>killed</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>