<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwnmq1/post/2012-03-30T19:23:12</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I think this is what will happen: Breaking news
WWE thought The Undertaker vs HHH was NOT gimmicky enough so the rules are as follows: 
It
 is 60 minutes No DQ a referee will be at hand at all times to count the
 pins falls in this case Shawn Michaels this will have no effect on the 
outcome of the match. In addition a pole suspended from another pole 
directing in the center of the ring. Every time a wrestler Bounces of 
the ropes hard enough to make the pole fall down on it's own accord a 
sedated dog is chained to the opposing wrestler's corner maximum 5 dogs.
 If a wrestler is thrown over the top ropes to the floor he must take 
all the dogs in his corner and walk them around the perimeter of the 
arena. For every piece of dog shyt stepped on by the wrestler he will 
receive a potato. When the 60 minutes have elapsed the potatoes are 
taken back to the locker room where a makeshift kitchen has been 
constructed. The wrestlers must wash,peel and cook their potatoes into 
home fries/chips whatever you want to call it and will then be consumed 
by Mick Foley. The viewers at home will be treated to one continuous 
shot of Mick Foley eating all the prepared potatoes finally Foley stops 
to catch his breath/wipe his beard. As this happening a match will take 
place back in the ring to keep the live fans occupied. Once all the home
 fries/ chips have been consumed the results will be written on piece of
 paper and will be put into a sealed envelope and be given to the 
referee. Foley will neatly fold the envelop twice place it in his back 
pocket to see it crack open on a toilet seat. As soon as this happens a 
timer will begin counting down as the two wrestlers take turns hitting 
each other over the forehead barbed wire baseball bats and Bleeding each
 other on camera. This will continue for ten minutes or until or the 
floor has an even coat of blood over the entire carpet. After this has 
phase of the match has been completed the wrestlers will make their way 
back out to the ring where two more special guest referees will be 
added. The third one can be chosen at will but the second one has to be 
Shawn Waltman NOT X Pac 123 kid but Shawn Waltman. Each of them will 
produce a coin shaped with the face of Vince Russo's face on the head 
side and a picture of Vince Russo testicles on the tail side. The 
wrestler with the most cuts in his forehead has to call the subsequent 
coin toss and the winner of the coin toss will recieve a Number 1 
contenders match for the US title however the loser has the option of 
producing a gun and shooting his opponent in the face. If this option is
 taken then the wrestler can cover his opponent for the pinfall and 
claim the No. 1 contender Spot for the US title himself. Hopefully 
you'll enjoy that version of Undertaker vs HHH at Mania.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67vv1g</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/e1x9</id></website><link>http://www.wrestlinginc.com/wi/news/2012/0330/551250/edge/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T23:15:30+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T23:23:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwnmq1</id><link>http://www.wrestlinginc.com/wi/news/2012/0330/551250/edge/#comment-481313076</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/llgel</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>