<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3km7d/post/2012-03-29T22:12:13</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3o4a0</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8e0e9</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Great post. 

My dad taught me gun safety as well and I taught my children. They enjoy target practicing now and we do it often at our camp. We bring a bunch of bricks which give a nice  of red dust when they get hit. They like the .22 best as do I for target shooting. I  felt safer knowing me and my siblings were safe and protected with dads firearm and that was way before the doctors started pushing heavy narcotics for Headaches and muscle aches and the bath salts. My children told me when they got older that they  felt safer on our excursions when they knew I was carrying which is basically all the time, unless I have to go to court or the federal building. 

Our closest call was on a Sunday afternoon after church. My dad had to shoot a dog that kept coming around the house that was a threat to others as well as some of our livestock. The dog chased my brother into the house while dad was in his study. The dog wouldn't leave the front door and Acted very threatening so dad killed it. Come to find out, we learned the dog was a stray and it had bitten a kid about a week earlier and the kid had to swim across a portion of the lake to get away from it. 

It's interesting that we take after our parents the way we do as a scoiety. That is what concerns me about the children today. Many parents have no business raising children.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6znuio</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dngw</id></website><link>http://bangordailynews.com/2012/03/29/health/math-and-myth-of-guns-and-safety/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:43:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:12:13+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3km7d</id><link>http://bangordailynews.com/2012/03/29/health/math-and-myth-of-guns-and-safety/#comment-480146516</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8meq4</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>