<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwhiym/delete/2012-03-30T14:01:24</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw8oay</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/eiq9x</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>"The guy comes in here, clearly in violation of all the rules..."- slabbie. well then, what are the rules to ganging up on and insulting other posters hmmm? lets see: per Current...

Be respectful.

		Everyone is entitled to an opinion. Remember what we all learned in  kindergarten? Treat others the way you'd like to be treated.

Take a deep breath.

		Things can get Heated. If you think you might be getting too worked
 up, take a second to think about what you'd like to say before you 
post.

Keep an open mind.

		Be open to learning from each other. Differences of opinion help broaden perspectives, and you might be surprised by the things you can 
agree to disagree on.

*Personal attacks.

		We can't  agree on everything, and that's fine. But stick to 
debating the point, not attacking the other person. 

*Ganging up/Harassment.

		Everyone is entitled to an opinion. Harassing or ganging up on 
those 
who disagree with you is not cool. Why not give our "Good ideas" 
section another read?

*Being a hater.

		Hate speech, racism, and bigotry are unacceptable. Remember, just 
because someone disagrees with you on an issue doesn't necessarily make 
their statements hate speech.

*Posting private information.

		Posting emails, private messages, addresses, or other identifying 
information about others is not okay. Let other people decide how much 
of their information to share, and when to share it. If it's not in 
their Current.com profile, then they probably don't want to share it 
here.

In addition, posting inappropriate content regarding Current TV 
personnel is considered in violation of our guidelines and will be 
removed in accordance with our Terms of Use.

* guilty parties- slabbie, FOK, ckay, jeannie, Olbermann himself, ozzie, flute....hell, i should have just listed ALL of the Olbermann "fans". would have saved me some time. 

anyway, WHY arent these repeated offenders BANNED?? they are guilty of MORE infractions than ALL of HC, the studd muffin Jay, Unicon, FormerlyLib etc. COMBINED. ahhhhh, progressives with their hypocrisy and selective "moral outrage"...


		
		
</body><verb>delete</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zjd12</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/vr8i</id></website><link>http://current.com/shows/countdown/videos/robert-reich-assesses-whether-occupy-wall-street-has-succeeded-in-changing-the-dialogue-on-wall-street</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:31:06+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:01:24+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwhiym</id><link>http://current.com/shows/countdown/videos/robert-reich-assesses-whether-occupy-wall-street-has-succeeded-in-changing-the-dialogue-on-wall-street#comment-481015915</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzowx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>killed</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>