<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwvjbw/post/2012-03-30T16:17:12</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7gfh</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lxu6q</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Many true believers in Cold fusion don't see any categories other than "doubter" and "open-minded."

I am not a doubter. I wouldn't be hugely surprised if someone managed to get Cold fusion or LENR working. But it won't be Rossi. Rossi is a transparent fraud. If you are seriously hoping he's not, go buy a lottery ticket - it's more likely to pay Off.

Any professional who's in the Cold fusion field who doesn't know Rossi is a fraud is a fool. Anyone who thinks he is, but is pretending he's not, is a liar. (Some may be lying for a seemingly good purpose - hoping they can develop convincing results themself before Rossi's fraud sets the field back another decade.)

Any outside observer who doesn't know Rossi is a fraud is self-delusional. This is the human condition. 

It's annoying for those who are not deluded on this topic to be lumped in with "doubters." If there was less of that going on, then people might be more willing to engage with the appropriate, scientific attention - which includes skepticism.

So unless I've misunderstood you, people like you are making a substantial contribution to keeping scientists away from the whole LENR field. Congratulations.
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zgwpu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/1ld</id></website><link>http://nextbigfuture.com/2012/03/brillioun-energy-closing-to.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T08:05:40+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T20:17:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwvjbw</id><link>http://nextbigfuture.com/2012/03/brillioun-energy-closing-to.html#comment-481152490</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/agfva</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>