<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m33jdt/post/2012-03-30T01:02:28</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I just currently sold my ps3 and i loved it. But im looking at going to xbox now, ps3 use to be cool but since they went down a few months ago they have changed alot of things. Now the online play is like with xbox u have the free one and the pay for one. The pay for one you get tons more free stuff plus i imagine a better online gaming exp. With xbox you get the same thing, the free games and demos, but you also get reward points for completing challenges that you can use in the store. I think the lagging and hacking issue is worste on ps3 then on xbox. I played mw3 on my buddies xbox daily and we never had lagging or ghosting problems.  But I come home and the game was unplayable. Ps3 is more of an entertainment counsle to play blu-ray and stuff like that. But xbox is the better counsle for streaming like netflix. Ps3 has a music channel but it suck, xbox now has Iheartradio and a ton of other aps that their starting to come up with in the last 6 months. (march 2012) When we originally got the ps3 we wanted a xbox but couldnt find any so went with ps3, either way i still Burnt a ps3 up and was Burning my second one up, i still have a warranty on it so if it does mess upo ill just replace it for them. But im sure id have done that with xbox to, even though ive heard newer ones dont have as many problems as before.
The problem with ps3 internet is that is supports G networks while most of your routers from cable companies and that people buy are N network since thats what took Off oin the last few years. And since xbox started with that they dont have to make changes while ps3 would have to. 
Straight out if your into computer stuff and like getting into the op systems of things then ps3 is for you. There is a whole nother universe with it that you can do. But if your looking for a plug and play gaming counsle and dont mind not having button hole veiwing graphics then xbox is it for you. Alot more family games and if your married thats a plussince problay your wifedont like fps lol.
But me writing this article has actually helped me make a decision, i think im going with xbox, with the recent changes and additions that they have made, it seems like the better choice, worser comes to worse alway return it.
The changes are a big thing for me i've had ps3 for 3 months and the only changes they've made is making you pay for more stuff so at least for 3 bucksa a month i get a better online experience.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/5wh0ue</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7d9s</id></website><link>http://gear.ign.com/articles/111/1116182p1.html</link><postedTime>2011-05-09T23:04:29+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T05:02:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m33jdt</id><link>http://gear.ign.com/articles/111/1116182p1.html#comment-480265505</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzjfb</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-05-09</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>