<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tedy/post/2012-03-29T09:34:28</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3v4cg</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lmftq</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>The haves will  strenuously attempt to make sure that the have nots never get whatever it is the haves already have. What do you think will happen to my three children if I am allowed to marry the man I love in a 5 minute civil ceremony? I have already told them that I stand a good chance of Burning in Hell for all eternity and by the entranced looks on their faces, I can sense that unlike most if the information I have imparted to them, they are fervently hoping that the my Burning in Hell for ever item is accurate. It seems a bit harsh for the occasional hugs and kisses and frisky diddling that Herbert and I exchange in the privacy of our bedroom, but if that is what the all knowing, universe creating omnipotent God who sent to earth his only begotten son who never married but insisted He loved us all requires, then so be it. The Amendment is a petty piece of spitefulness. Do you seriously want me to teach my children that although the North Carolina Constitution claims that all people will Always receive equal treatment under the law, it will be better if heterosexuals can be treated more equally than homosexuals?</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6za15k</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnmo</id></website><link>http://www.newsobserver.com/2012/03/29/1965824/time-factors.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T04:15:51+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:34:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tedy</id><link>http://www.newsobserver.com/2012/03/29/1965824/time-factors.html#comment-479491785</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rxlmo</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>