<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5s3ias/update/2011-08-28T12:20:17/5bcbc1f683424677c40300c351b5938050150d8c94884b43cdfdad4b1f420f6a</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5s3a6e</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a0gst</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>lhill1
 
Thank you for your comment.  I visited Singapore, in the 1960’s, on r n’r from Borneo, whilst serving in the Royal Marines, at the time of their independence from Malaysia, and was later, based at Simbang for a year before we pulled out. None of us thought that they could survive as a nation.  How wrong we were.  The tallest building then was the North Bridge Hotel.  I visited fifteen years ago whilst working at kertih in Malaysia on the design and construction of an ethylene jetty, for Penta Ocean of Japan, we had an office in Singapore at Pasha Pajang. What a transformation, the North Bridge Hotel is now dwarfed by surrounding infrastructure.  They have progressed in exactly the opposite direction to their now declined former colonial masters.  
 
They indeed had Lee Kwan Yew, no waffle, no bull$h1t, no seventeen years of accountants and lawyers sucking money for committees for Crossrail,  they got things done. But Lee Kwan Yew has an answer for corrupt politicians.  It was called Changi Jail. There were bars on the windows, and the door didn’t open for a very long time. Entertainment would be the chirruping of  crickets at night, and the annoyance of flies by day.   Air conditioning provided only by the outside environment filtering through the gaps  between the bars. Two settings hot at night and hotter by day.   Our corrupt right honourable liars get a peerage.  If I had my way, it would be a pierage Off the end of the pier. I would happily provide the concrete wet suit for free. With no raw materials other than fish, Singapore must be efficient to prosper.  Their education and health system makes the British look like dinosaurs. I visited again five years ago (Shell Island), more of the same remorseless progress and true growth.  But they have leaders, many of them scientists and engineers, not rubbish.   I am now working in Lagos, Nigeria. The country is in trouble, but the kids here speak read and write better English than most of British youth, with not even a tenth of the money spent on the education experienced by British kids.  Something is very wrong, and I do not think that the political class of today have either comprehension of the problems, or the capability to fix them.  Given their lousy calibre, I doubt if they even care.
 
I bet you are Itching to get back to Singapore.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/en1py0</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/politics/conservative/8727056/Whats-the-Tory-partys-verdict-on-the-Coalition.html</link><postedTime>2011-08-27T18:07:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-08-28T16:20:17+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5s3ias</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/politics/conservative/8727056/Whats-the-Tory-partys-verdict-on-the-Coalition.html#comment-297191012</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cro36</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-08-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>