<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3j685/post/2012-03-29T18:19:24</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fq0m</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ym5c9</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>
They are sooo irresponsible. We planted a flag and on their land which obviously made it our land. Then they offered to share the land and we signed treaties to share the land. Now we ignore the treaties and now we make them prove it is their land in our courts. We are so smart and they are so irresponsible.


And we made up some perfectly good laws for them to follow.  The Indian  
is so good, that we have kept it around for about a 130 years. South Africa 
liked it so much that they studied it when setting up apartheid. Our 
system is still here and apatheid is gone so our laws must be better.

They are so inept too. After 130 years of trying to get them to 
give up their culture, stop speaking their language and follow the 
Indian . They could not get it done. 

And we should we give them money? I mean really...we rounded them up, forced them Off what is clearly our land and made them stop using it to making a living. We made them stop their way of governing themselves and looking after themselves. We took their kids away and Burned down their villages. We forced on to welfare, broke just about every promise we made.  Its not our fault. That's for sure.

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zxr5p</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/4r1e</id></website><link>http://news.nationalpost.com/2012/03/29/budget-2012-federal-canada/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:11:18+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:19:24+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3j685</id><link>http://news.nationalpost.com/2012/03/29/budget-2012-federal-canada/#comment-479963308</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h1l1y</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>