<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw5f2n/post/2012-03-30T06:17:04</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Wow, what an episode. Now maybe we can put the whole "let's kill Klaus" thing to rest. I hate feeling conflicted, and now I don't have to. Thanks to the release of the synopsis for Heart of Darkness, I pretty much guessed that if one Original dies, their bloodline dies, too.  Who wants to bet that Damon, Stefan, Caroline &amp; Katherine are all of Klaus's vampire bloodline? That would be a really cool way to end the whole "Kill Klaus" thing, forever;)

Regarding Original Vampire Bloodlines: I am so happy that part of TVD mythology is that if the fount of the bloodline dies, so does the rest of vampire kind. You guys know what that means, right? It means that EVERYONE needs to be worried about Esther. I mean, really worried. If she comes back attempting to kill her children, everyone has the potential of being toast.....by everyone, I mean not only Klaus &amp; the rest of his family, but Damon, Stefan, Caroline &amp; Katherine. I'm foreseeing a HUGE team effort (meaning Team Originals &amp; Team Mystic Falls) to make sure this doesn't happen. We have four Original Bloodlines left, let's keep it that way;)

BTW: for those of you complaining about this season: I want you to think about what you learned tonight regarding the bloodlines and think about what Ester wanted to do. She wanted to turn all of her children human and then kill them. Now, think about what that would mean for your favorite vampires......Way to go writers for tying things together nicely;)

 I'm going to vent my spleen a bit here and I'm thinking back to Season 1 when I do this. Did anyone think it took way to long for Team MF to consider helping Damon? Remember when Stefan was held by the tomb vamps? What did Damon do? Did he do everything he could to get his bro back? Yep, he did. Now, that being said, this is not an insult to Stefan....I agree with what Stefan said to Elena......Damon would want them to follow through with the plan. But, if Elena THOUGHT that it was the wrong thing to do, why didn't she grab Caro and go get Damon back? I mean, Klaus won't let any harm come to Elena...and Caro? All she had to do was shake her tail under Klaus's nose and ask him for a favor......he would've granted it. As mad as he is right now, I do NOT believe for one minute that he would harm one hair on Caro's head...and Bonnie? Back down on the least favorite characters row. I didn't feel one ounce of pity for that one...

Moving on: That was so bad ass when Stef showed up to get Damon. Klaus put new words into torture, doesn't he? He not only believes in torture...he believes in visual enhancement;) I have to say, he made a pretty gory visual point tonight and I can see why he earned his reputation as the biggest, baddest vamp around.  Thank God Klaus pointed out to Stefan that all of Stef's anger has been pointed in the wrong direction. It's about time somebody did, after all, compulsion aside, Stefan made the choices he made and now he has to learn to live with them.

Now, we know Finn was an Original....did you guys see how Klaus was throwing his ass around at the beginning of the episode? Ha! Just pointing that out;)

So Kohl is watching Jer? LOL.....Klaus hasn't just been Burning drawings, he's been busy of the last couple of days. Sending Kohl  to keep an eye on Jer, gathering blood from his siblings, tracking down Finn, kidnapping Bonnie.....yeah, Klaus has been real busy. He was lining all his ducks up and he wasn't taking no for an answer.

Now, about Elena: I have nothing to say about her other than how could any Damon fan want Elena with him? I mean seriously....

And Ric's alter ego hid the last stake......I knew those damn herbs wouldn't work. He's still in serious trouble and the gang really needs to help him......although, if they keep putting it , it may be to late.

Now it's time for another two week hiatus. Loving this season. Loving the Originals (more on Bex later), and loving Damon &amp; Stefan. Also, loving how the story lines are coming together. I see now why Julie Plec said that a decision is going to have to be made by Elena.....I just don't think that decision is going to be to chose one of the boys....I think she's going to have to make a different choice. Until next time....Cheers:)

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zfyfg</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lhxx</id></website><link>http://www.vampire-diaries.net/tv-series/reaction-post-poll-vampire-diaries-the-murder-of-one-ep318</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T23:30:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T10:17:04+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw5f2n</id><link>http://www.vampire-diaries.net/tv-series/reaction-post-poll-vampire-diaries-the-murder-of-one-ep318#comment-480589220</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cbsco</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>