<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/190966/post/103524633/comment/329627479</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>We and baeing all &lt;a href="http:\/\/www.chanelsalesonlineoutlet.com\/" target="_blank"&gt;Chanel Bags Sale&lt;/a&gt; know that a genuine Chanel Handbags - &lt;a href="http://www.chanelsalesonlineoutlet.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.chanelsalesonlineoutlet.com/&lt;/a&gt; designer &lt;a href="http:\/\/www.chanelsalesonlineoutlet.com\/" target="_blank"&gt;Chanel Bags&lt;/a&gt; handbag is &lt;a href="http:\/\/www.chanelsalesonlineoutlet.com\/" target="_blank"&gt;Chanel Bags&lt;/a&gt; very expensive.&lt;a href="http:\/\/www.chanelsalesonlineoutlet.com\/" target="_blank"&gt;Chanel Handbags&lt;/a&gt; One is for its materials. They use high quality leather or canvas which should be free of damage. The attached hardware such as the lock has the best quality.The second is for its workmanship. The seams of a real designer bags are actually sewn and not just glued together. High quality zippers, snaps and latches are also used. The lining is well made and sewn into place without wrinkles. The third is for its standing. But a bag of more than a grand is still quite a strong pill for most ordinary people. However, there are some very well made replica handbags which cost much lower or even half price of the real one. In fact they are so well made that it may be tough for the untrained buyer to Spot a replica bag.First, quality replica bags are made of the same leather and canvas that are used to make real designer bagsSecond, high quality replica bag has all of the marks of good workmanship that mentioned above.Third, you will also find the designer&amp;#039;s logo attached to the replica bags. In many cases, it will take a very well trained individual to tell whether or not the logo on your bag come from the original designer.Forth, a real designer bag has a production number stamped inside to Ensure that the bag is an original. It will let the buyers to know that the bag was made with caution. But you will also find a unique number inside the well-made replica bags. These bags were also made with care and caution,Messenger Chanel Black embellished flowers and used are an amazing design option for Spring season. Pink and red, dark and Mulberry coloring mixture are exceptional and bag and feminine bow details, unquestionably include festive touch. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:190966:103524633</id><idPostId>103524633</idPostId><idBlogId>190966</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:190966</id><idBlogId>190966</idBlogId><link>http://www.cp-africa.com</link><displayName>CP-AFRICA.COM</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.cp-africa.com/2011/08/12/why-every-nigerian-on-the-internet-should-start-a-blog/</link><displayName>Why every Nigerian on the Internet should start a blog</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-20T05:32:06.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:190966:103524633:329627479</id><link>http://www.cp-africa.com/2011/08/12/why-every-nigerian-on-the-internet-should-start-a-blog/#IDComment329627479</link><postedTime>2012-03-20T05:32:06.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Why every Nigerian on the Internet should start a blog by uvfoukhanf</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://www.chanelsalesonlineoutlet.com/</link><idEmailMd5>6c3ed99bfe17b928f537b132e389b3f5</idEmailMd5><displayName>uvfoukhanf</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://www.chanelsalesonlineoutlet.com/"&gt;uvfoukhanf&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.cp-africa.com/2011/08/12/why-every-nigerian-on-the-internet-should-start-a-blog/"&gt;Why every Nigerian on the Internet should start a blog&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>