<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34y5j/update/2012-03-29T10:46:15/9fddea26d627d71e81aa3646772682f6f8bbc8589c25adea74d737559fa231f5</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3cdh5</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Spot on. Joe Arpaio is a bigger shitbag than Corsi, and basically all he did was regurgitate Corsi's bullshit and pass it Off as his own. His "investigation" is basically a desperate attempt to hold on to power, becase the support of the "birther" crowd is about all he has left. I have family in Maricopa County who are very conservative and used to support him, but even they have had enough of his bullshit and are now saying they will vote him out next election. Arpaio is a half-senile 80-year-old man who got elected and got to stay in office because of gimmicks like making his jail inmates live in tents in the 115-degree Heat, wear pink underwear, and eat half-spoiled food. When illegal immigration became a huge issue he started running "sweeps" to round up illegal immigrants based on such flimsy evidence as letters written by supporters claiming "there's too many Mexicans in my neighborhood, they're all illegals I know it!!! Come and get them Joe!!!" Now his empire is crumbling; his office was found to have misspent more than $90 million, the nastly little former county attorney who helped Joe launch baseless investigastions against his political foes is about to be disbarred, and his deputies failed to investigate more than 400 sexual assault reports (including many against children) in a community called El Mirage that was under his jurisdiction. He probably launched the birth certificate "investigation" because the Justice Department is suing him Federal Court on charges of egregious racial profiling, and there are criminal investigations going on as well. It is only a matter of time before Joe gets perp-walked, and his jails are put under federal receivership because of several cases where inmates have died brutally and needlessly at the hands of his goon-squad guards. For more on what a piece of garbage Joe Arpaio really is check this out: http://www.phoenixnewtimes.com/arpaio/

Arpaio is no better, and probably worse, than Corsi, They're both shitstains on the ass of the universe (if I may borrow a phrase), who just can't stand the fact that we have a black president (like all birthers).</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6loggm</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/nequ</id></website><link>http://www.metalsucks.net/2012/03/27/dave-mustaine-strikes-again-i-know-president-obama-was-born-somewhere-else-than-america/</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T18:01:27+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:46:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34y5j</id><link>http://www.metalsucks.net/2012/03/27/dave-mustaine-strikes-again-i-know-president-obama-was-born-somewhere-else-than-america/#comment-479542203</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>