<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qubv/post/2012-03-29T12:04:38</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I am a retired RN,  my last position before retiring was a Nursing Supervisor in the EMERGENCY ROOM so I've had  a little bit of  practice working on people with broken noses, including one of my own kids and 2 grandkids. 

1. They Bleed like a stuck pig and that blood DOES spurt out uncontrollably. 

2. You WILL get one,  maybe both eyes blackened and sometimes swollen shut.

3. The nose is Always packed and taped if not splinted. 

4. You cannot look down!  The blood will rush into your face and you will experience a LOT of pain. That's why you see so many with a freshly broken nose tilting their head slightly up, it relieves the pressure therefore calms the pain somewhat.  Especially if the break is just a couple of hours old. 

Also, my oldest son is an Emergency Room Physician.   I spoke to him last night and asked if he had seen the video of Zimmerman at the PD and he said yes.  Before I could ask about the broken nose story he told me, there is NO WAY IN HELL that man had a broken or even fractured nose.  

As for the damage to his head.  It to will Bleed a lot. IF there was a break in the skin, and he was treated at the scene by EMS, they WOULD have covered it, either with a bandage and tape or possibly a 'butterfly" tape to hold the skin together.  NOTHING THERE. 

That video along with his statement and that of the police SHOULD make one thing crystal clear to EVERYONE.    HE FUCKING LIED. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hwjdr</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cusm</id></website><link>http://www.rawstory.com/rs/2012/03/28/surveillance-video-shows-no-blood-or-bruises-on-george-zimmerman/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T01:09:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:04:38+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qubv</id><link>http://www.rawstory.com/rs/2012/03/28/surveillance-video-shows-no-blood-or-bruises-on-george-zimmerman/#comment-479607640</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5nvx3</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>