<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/179861/post/43238200/comment/327691190</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>,chaussures armani homme Shen Xin letter stated,chaussure armani, from 2007,chaussure armani jeans, Shen stone, the spirit of problems, once pesticides liquor to drink,Sac Armani, but fortunately we found in a timely manner, and sent him to the hospital. more than two months after discharge from hospital also eat more than a month of medicine,Armani Jean, found that his situation is more normal,t shirt armani, stop the medication. Chen Jupiter At present, the local police had contacted a psychotherapist to red to do psychological counseling. edition News in cooperation with the Southern TV,montres armani homme, news, please pay attention to today 21:30 Southern Television recalled the incident scene,veste armani homme, the red can not help but Shiver: He said someone, and then close the door, I think,armani montre homme, wanted to rush out to him ill, but his hand grabbed his neck, and warned me to keep quiet, I  \'Help\',armani costume, he would punch Shen Shi-Jin hit my eyes,Armani Femme, I almost Fainted in the past. , a stab wound to her left hand, she did not know what time to be chopped. Shen: think .... . Unexpectedly suspect after you hear the second tone gunshots suddenly turned, waving a machete toward the firing Feng captain cut in the past. Feng captain calmly at gunpoint the suspects,armani montres, to the thigh. in mind: Why do you want to rape people little girl? seeing the suspect rushed to the front of 5 meters, Captain von decisive shot, hitting the suspect right leg,veste armani, but the suspect actually did not fall,parfum armani homme, but continue to stand waving the machete resisting arrest. Shen: her grandmother came back to knock on the door, I worried about being discovered. Shen: I hope a good life after his son, a non-smoker, the two do not drink,montre armani femme, do not like your father ... Here, Shen Shi gold, bowed his head, the sound becomes very small, and softly sobbing, calloused hands clasped, reluctant to speak. Raised his head and after about two minutes, his eyes red. Detention center, police officers brought him back to the prisons,costume homme armani, the moment into the prisons,costumes armani, he suddenly back looking up at the sky. Perhaps for him to breathe free air again has become unreachable. Shen: I have drunk Dizziness brain up, a moment of weakness,montres homme armani! See a little girl at home, you want to hug her. the town of Chau Tsai gold farm village public security officer confirmed that the Shen Shi gold, indeed history of mental illness,robe armani, usually there is no petty behavior. Two years ago but began gambling lottery, originally a small savings all to the cleaners,armani paris, people in the village was originally heard that he had a mental illness will be wary of him, but since he entered the the Huaiji hospital back,costume armani, do you think his performance is normal, a little let down our guard, he would end up dry so hurt hain\'t. Qiu, deputy director of turned on Feng captain said: smoke, Qiu, deputy director of a sudden one  to seize the suspect\'s right hand,armani lunettes, von captain immediately rushed to seize the suspect\'s left hand,armani chaussure, the two together to the suspect will be pressed to the ground,armani homme, rounded up the police immediately rushed up, the suspect under control, and handcuffed. The violent criminals captain fired shots victims of a Poverty and ill health girl leave psychological shadow: the door did not dare to enter in mind: Do you want to say your son? ,armani montre, stone gold (hereinafter referred to as : a kind of local white wine, alcohol content: 28 degrees,sac armani, the police later identified half a bottle of about two), feel dizzy and want walked around, walked, we came to the door of that family. in mind: Why did you kill her grandmother? carrot and stick press down on suspects set the target, and an Interpol went over to persuade the suspect did not think that would not said they endured a stick. Interpol had stepped back, who knows the suspect thought Interpol are afraid of him, actually raised the stick and machete to catch up from the Interpol. Feng captain immediately took out his pistol to the to Tianming a shot. According to the town of Chau Tsai gold market village party secretary about victim is a low household in the village,montre armani homme, near grandmother rescue the father of the red (a pseudonym) bilateral cataract blindness, the tragic death of the mother 10 years ago,montre armani, his brother\'s mental development problems,armani, and only has to take care of their siblings great grandmother is a complete labor. Unexpectedly,blouson armani, this time grandmother but criminals hacked them a the situation worse. just assigned tasks, they received intelligence of investigators: The suspect hid in a Long Neck Dagangshan fruit trees. The Feng captain led team immediately rushed to the dragon\'s neck Dagangshan team is divided into an encirclement, slowly near the location of the suspect. Suspects perceive the police to round up,Armani Montreune, suddenly jumped out, waving around a 50 cm long wooden sticks, did not bring the shields and other protective equipment. about 11:30 that day,chaussures armani, we suddenly received Chau Tsai station calls, said two people in the local chop wounds to the murderer at large. He said in the report to the competent criminal investigation Chiu,armani femme, deputy director of the criminal investigation of more than 20 police officers immediately drive Chau Tsai town rushed to the more than 10 kilometers away. On the road, Captain von team is divided into three groups: first group of crime scene investigation and evidence collection,armani france, the second group along the suspect escape route tracking, third group dispatched to the suspect home. grandmother restrained rape was hacked to death toward the muzzle rushing has been to supervise operations in the next Qiu, deputy director of then suddenly Shouted: suddenly a drink actually takes effect, the suspect in the hands of scared about to throw away the machete. Qiu, deputy director of then put on a soft tone: suspect has been family sent to hospital for compulsory treatment in three columns emergency dispatch Shen: My wife and 12-year-old son was reading the fifth grade. Shen: I was very sorry for them one. Reporter: So you now how to do? Shen: do are already done, only waiting for legal decisions ... in mind: Do you want son? history of mental illness addicted Mark Six 18 February, the police Shen Shi-Jin sent to the Third People\'s Hospital of Zhaoqing City do spirit of the forensic results are not yet announced. &amp;#30456;&amp;#20851;&amp;#30340;&amp;#20027;&amp;#39064;&amp;#25991;&amp;#31456;&amp;#65306; montres homme armani Three suspects in theft of mo blouson armani 5 men robbed and raped two women we ralph lauren Understanding Why Men Leave - Signs He Doesn&amp;#8217;t Want to be With You </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:179861:43238200</id><idPostId>43238200</idPostId><idBlogId>179861</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:179861</id><idBlogId>179861</idBlogId><link>http://blog.foodnetwork.com/healthyeats</link><displayName>Healthy Eats</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://blog.foodnetwork.com/healthyeats/2010/07/09/ask-he-is-flaxseed-worth-the-hype/flax-seed-good-or-bad/</link><displayName>Flax-Seed-Good-or-Bad</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T08:58:04.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:179861:43238200:327691190</id><link>http://blog.foodnetwork.com/healthyeats/2010/07/09/ask-he-is-flaxseed-worth-the-hype/flax-seed-good-or-bad/#IDComment327691190</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T08:58:04.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Flax-Seed-Good-or-Bad by nisifi32ap</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://www.sacarmani.com</link><idEmailMd5>9af2f341aa4653127b729ea57c11d1a6</idEmailMd5><displayName>nisifi32ap</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://www.sacarmani.com"&gt;nisifi32ap&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://blog.foodnetwork.com/healthyeats/2010/07/09/ask-he-is-flaxseed-worth-the-hype/flax-seed-good-or-bad/"&gt;Flax-Seed-Good-or-Bad&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>