<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/312236/post/127908676/comment/328345318</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>If you\'ve never seen it, check out the \"Cubing a Round\" episode of Good Eats.  Lots of awesome recipes for using top round. 
 
In particular, Alton\'s Country Style Steak recipe is to die for.  Check it out here: 
 
2 pounds beef top/bottom round, trimmed of excess fat 
2 teaspoons kosher salt 
1 teaspoon freshly ground black pepper 
3/4 cup all-purpose flour 
1/4 cup vegetable oil or bacon drippings 
2 cups chicken broth 
1 teaspoon dried thyme 
 
Preheat the oven to 300 degrees F. 
 
Cut the meat with the grain into 1/2-inch thick  and season on both sides with salt and pepper. Place the flour into a pie pan. Dredge the pieces of meat on both sides in the flour. Tenderize the meat, using a needling device, until each Slice is 1/4-inch thick. Dredge in the flour again and set aside. 
 
Add enough of the vegetable oil or bacon fat to just cover the bottom of a 4 to 5-quart Dutch oven set over medium-high Heat. Once the oil begins to shimmer, add the steaks to the pan, being careful not to overcrowd. Cook until golden brown on both sides, approximately 2 minutes per side. Remove the steaks to a plate and repeat until all of the steaks have been browned. 
 
Remove the last steaks from the pot and add the chicken broth and thyme and whisk until the liquid just comes to a boil. Return the steaks to the pot and make sure they are all submerged in the liquid. Cover the pot and place it in the oven on the middle rack. Cook for 1 1/2 to 2 hours or until the meat is tender and falling apart. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:312236:127908676</id><idPostId>127908676</idPostId><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:312236</id><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><link>http://www.denpdf.com</link><displayName>denpdf.com</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.denpdf.com/round-steak-recipes-any-good-beef-round-steak-recipes/</link><displayName>round steak recipes- any good beef round steak recipes?</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T09:00:26.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:312236:127908676:328345318</id><link>http://www.denpdf.com/round-steak-recipes-any-good-beef-round-steak-recipes/#IDComment328345318</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T09:00:26.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on round steak recipes- any good beef round steak recipes? by Justin B</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>19399ed6402d11e5db023bfab363e8e5</idEmailMd5><displayName>Justin B</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>Justin B commented on &lt;a href="http://www.denpdf.com/round-steak-recipes-any-good-beef-round-steak-recipes/"&gt;round steak recipes- any good beef round steak recipes?&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>