<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miqz76/update/2012-03-23T11:53:11/7e6b0ee1e0734bc5654e56ee8a1fe40509e5a22049bcc40d95a1e34db3f73479</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Sigh, a couple of years ago 6 black men raped and tortured a young teenage couple for days cutting Off the breasts of the girl with a knife, raping her many times. The boy, if I remember, was forced to watch and then mutilated. The victims were a young teenage white couple on a date. My point? Where was the outrage on this one. I didn't hear Sharpton and Company complaining then despite the utterly horrific manner of the crime. I can cite countless similar crimes. Crime is crime, why must these idiots bring race into everything? I am so sick of the race card I could Vomit. In fact, one could argue it is so old it is actually garnering racism in and unto itself. Get a life and move on. Grow up. Your skin color is not your problem, it is your attitude and expectations. Obama is a symptom of a disease, not the cause. That this man is our president show just how low the culture has sunken. I am so disappointed that the first black president was a man like this. Instead of a Clarence Thomas or Thomas Sowell, Alan West, we get this man. The antithesis of a leader...</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66djb5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yv37</id></website><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/blog/2012/03/obama_if_i_had_a_son_hed_look_like_trayvon_comments.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T15:10:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T15:53:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miqz76</id><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/blog/2012/03/obama_if_i_had_a_son_hed_look_like_trayvon_comments.html#comment-474556870</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mmn7o</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>