<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ps2v/post/2012-03-29T20:50:15</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3pnlq</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yoc8t</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>DLBRT..thanks for checking that out and do you agree as well that what Vigue has said publicly doesn't jibe with this statute?

So you recall anything about the public debate or testimomy when this bill was passed in 2010?

  It seems to have been designed and tailor made to create the stautory authroity for this proposal before there was any public mention of the proposal.  I had hoped that we did not yet have statirtoy authority so that we could have a fuller discussion of issues and implications .  For example our statute does not address fair wages or apportion responsbility n the event of default or provide adequately for any public scrutiny at all.or require any comparative bids .  It allows a negotiated sole source process.It is all strictly between the DOT Commissioner &amp; the Legislature.  Is that how you read it too??

Intersting to note that a 2006 study by UMaine for DOT, which cincluded a chaper on public private partnerships specifically advised against  highway ifrsatructure and stressed multi modal projects.

Also at the DOT site at the history page on  the Esat West Highway, interestingto note Angus King, like the DOT was not keen on further purusing an East West toll road.

And this vivtory lap with our DOT Comissioner and David Cole in tow in Canada????

I thnk we should all push to Close up some of these loop holes.in the statute and put the Spot light on the DOT Comissioner.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6znkpa</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dngw</id></website><link>http://bangordailynews.com/2012/03/29/news/down-east/canadians-told-east-west-highway-through-maine-a-gateway-to-opportunity/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:52:51+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:50:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ps2v</id><link>http://bangordailynews.com/2012/03/29/news/down-east/canadians-told-east-west-highway-through-maine-a-gateway-to-opportunity/#comment-480085072</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hxvr9</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>