<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4a3m/post/2012-03-30T17:19:57</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>LeBron and DWade need to put on a full court press for Steve Nash. They need to bring him to Miami and treat him to an entire week of sun and fun. Talk about getting the ball WHEREVER they want. Top 5 "smartest" point guards in the history of the game. Shoots an unbelievable percentage as a guard. The ultimate court general. The biggest no brainer I've seen in years. Chalmers is good and getting better, but even he'd have t realize this is "Steve Nash". But Mario wont. He literally thinks he's the best player on the team. But you can't worry about that when you can get a talent like Nash. My only concern is that it'll take the ball out of LeBron's hands. DWade has finally learned how to play without dominating the ball. Can LeBron? If he could, then the Heat would be unbeatable. Especially in the pick and roll. Heck, pick and roll series after series with LeBron at 6' 8" picking and rolling or popping and Nash running the show. Back one foot  Nash to follow LeBron, and he'll sink the jumper consistently as he's Always done. Double up on Nash and LeBron rolls to the basket and will get a dunk half the time like Amare used to get. It would be SCARY!!!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zp54z</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yzhx</id></website><link>http://www.miamiherald.com/2012/03/29/2722049/suns-steve-nash-says-he-would.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T03:24:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:19:57+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4a3m</id><link>http://www.miamiherald.com/2012/03/29/2722049/suns-steve-nash-says-he-would.html#comment-481212475</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/y3cyj</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>