<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3x3ys/update/2012-03-29T14:13:04/1f7184d1158ac923d3114c05af9d6d6a8bec3547c602819635d2e79054b6adfd</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3vcfd</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>God may not answer you in the time or in the way YOU think He will or should. The enemy does'nt want you to find God. He will try to tempt you and confuse you. The word of God is living and active. If you didn't want to be helped you would not post this.I want to let you know that you are not alone! Jesus did everything for you! He paid the price for you to have freedom and a New life in Him.
God is the provider (Jehovah Jirah), you think that it is your job that is providing for you, but ultimately it is God who allows you to have a job, be healthy enough to work, etc.
At the age of 25, I was engaged to be married. I had a full time job, my fiance' was finishing up college. I became ill, and within a period of 6wks was bedridden for 7 mos., my insurance company dropped me. I could not drive a car, do laundry, wash my hair.
I had severe pain, Muscle spasms, fatigue, low blood sugar, Fever, insomnia. We were married, after 2yrs, we were married, but with much stress. The thing that changed was our decision to rely completely on God. Even though we did not know my diagnosis, we chose to get married. Many people, including our pastor, told him not to marry me because I was so ill.
After 3yrs. I was diagosed with Lupus and Fibromyalgia. Neither one of these illnesses have a cure. Two years later, we discussed getting a dog, my husband didn't think I was well enough to even handle having a dog. We did get one, and God taught us unconditional love with him, he had epilepsy. 
I had made a vow to God that no matter how hard it got, or how much pain I was in I would never give up on life and have faith that God is our provider. He is the one who would decide if I was healed, or if we would ever have children. I was told I would never have children, because with Lupus you would miscarry.
At a women's retreat at our church 8 yrs later, God through, circumstances, His word, and the topic of our study (Psalm 139) He knows your name.
I felt that the Lord was leading me to trust him and get  of the 5 medicines I had been on for 8 yrs to cleanse my body to prepare for pregnacy.
Two weeks later, he named my child, Micah (means, Who is a God like you)  We began praying about all of this, it was not an easy thing to trust that I really knew what was happening, but I began to half and quarter pills. After 3 months, I had some routine blood work done. I was informed that all of the blood work-4 tests needed to be postive, were clear! I was told that this would be a great time to become pregnant, because apparently my Lupus was in remission. We became pregnant around Thanksgiving. We were due August 19th, I went into preterm labor 5 1/2 weeks early. I had him in 6 hours, He looked full term! No signs of prematurity! The lungs were completely developed! 
MY doctor could not believe he could look so old and be 5 1/2 weeks early!
Later I found his scripture Micah 7:18 that states his name meaning, "Who is a God like You."  He was born on 7-18-1999!  So how is it that we who do not know the future, worry. And God who knows all things, we have a hard time trusting Him!
I know have 3 boys  ages 12yrs, 10 yrs, and 7 yrs.  I am completely healed of the Lupus. I have had fibromyalgia for 22yrs. But God is faithful@6d54d58f1949ba23304f7ec008df0154:disqus   
We are now in full time ministry and yes I sometimes get tired, in pain and overwhelmed, but I am so Glad that I trusted God with my future! Please be encouraged! God is not finished with you YET! Trust him with all your heart! Learn from others trials and from your own. Never give up! The Lord is able to do exceedingly, abundantly more that you could ask or think!! Blessings to you and your family. There are people who care! Glorify the Lord with your life! God loves you and will meet your needs, if you trust in Him!
Brenda B.
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/8oo9nc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/e7xn</id></website><link>http://www.familylife.com/site/c.dnJHKLNnFoG/b.6235823/k.809F/FamilyLife_Today.htm</link><postedTime>2010-11-08T23:42:25+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:13:04+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3x3ys</id><link>http://www.familylife.com/site/c.dnJHKLNnFoG/b.6235823/k.809F/FamilyLife_Today.htm#comment-479713460</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2010-11-08</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>