<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk9tcs/post/2012-03-26T13:34:09</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>If this case had been one of two drunks fighting in a bar and one shot the other one during the fight, would the shooter not be arrested?  In this particular case the circumstances are quite different of course, stalker stalks innocent person and shoots him.  Whether or not the stalker (who was committing the initial aggression) was "confronted" by the unarmed victim seems almost irrelevant.  Nobody set the victim up as a DECOY to Zimmerman's profiling, and I find cognitive psychology's "blink" type explanations to be a cover up for the fact that racism exists and that it is: generated by members of society in a variety of ways, upheld by the disparities and injustices for which there have never been reparations, and televised to people here constantly.  The harder work of anti-racism extends beyond the legal system, beyond "dialogue" which is sometimes reduced to so-called whites talking about their racial Anxieties, becoming defensive and telling us how hurtful it is to be called a racist; beyond a civil rights , since all  should be civil rights .  Other terminology can be used to replace "civil rights" since that has been appropriated for a US nationalized feel-good mentality that negates the reality - and in this case brutality - of ongoing racism.
The other thing that bothers me about this case is the Skittles and Arizona Iced Tea.  Is this an ad during a movie or a story about the degree of denial of racism that leads to situations like this one?  Can someone just call it candy and a non-alcoholic drink?
Finally I think this case should include not just an indictment of Zimmerman - a man who made a mistake for which he should be arrested and which will no doubt be carried with him throughout his life, but an indictment of this country.  I hope the rest of the known Secrets are let out.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66m1nk</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/l7r5</id></website><link>http://chronicle.com/blogs/brainstorm/walking-while-black/45078</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T14:16:03+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:34:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk9tcs</id><link>http://chronicle.com/blogs/brainstorm/walking-while-black/45078#comment-476566556</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g04l4</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>