<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mstw44/update/2012-03-27T18:30:04/c24754e861097e64c1e5cff33587917530b524472e3845301d6bdb28977c3a40</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mshrd3</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yc7h1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I have not read the article yet, so I am just going by this article. It says she was put on a Weight Watchers type diet for children. I don't know how much you know about WW, but it is really about learning to eat more nutritiously and about portion controls. Its not really a diet, because no foods are Off limits.  Weight Watchers also incorporates exercise into your Weight loss plan, so they are actually teaching you how to eat healthy and the importance of exercise in that healthy lifestyle.

I agree that 7 year olds don't need to start worrying about how much calories might be in a hot chocolate, but that is hopefully where the mom can help out. When I was growing up, if I wanted junk food or soda, I had to ask my parents permission first. Sometimes they would say it was okay, other times they would say no and have me just drink water instead and a healthy snack. It was never about the calories or fat, just that it wasn't healthy to eat it all the time. I understood this, and I never felt shameful about wanting to eat unhealthy snakes. I just knew that it wasn't something I could have all the time.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lfnbo</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/twef</id></website><link>http://www.thefrisky.com/2012-03-27/the-soapbox-a-former-fat-kid-responds-to-the-vogue-mother-who-put-her-7-year-old-on-a-diet/</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T16:02:29+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-27T22:30:04+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mstw44</id><link>http://www.thefrisky.com/2012-03-27/the-soapbox-a-former-fat-kid-responds-to-the-vogue-mother-who-put-her-7-year-old-on-a-diet/#comment-477848826</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/atch1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>