<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwicl0/update/2012-03-31T08:03:15/ce07368ca79cf517b7ccb1799f4a28d5cb278d1d1e865e4826c27e6984c7ae7f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Obviously the list is all opinions, however, I don't have a problem with the Master Sword being #1.  A bit surprised.  Although it is "just a sword" in how it's used in the game mostly (minus controlling time, and various other applictions), you should look at the importance of the sword first to the game.  There is only one Master Sword, how it was forged and passed down through time, and the symbol of good conquoring over evil.  All this embodies this sword, not the hero of the game who changes (not in look or shape much, but not the same person).  Sure, it doesn't do anything supernatural or exotic.  It's not the weapon I would take with me if I were fighting firebreathing possessed aliens or even walking down my street to look tough.  I'd rather have something that was a one and done weapon that could be fired from a mile away.  Those weapons are everywhere, and not unique one of a kind weapons.  The Master Sword doesn't roll Off an assembly line in the Legend of Zelda, It can't be replicated.  You usually have to work hard to get it when you play the game and it makes actually getting it satisfying and rewarding.  These are the reasons I can see for putting it #1, although I could see other ones at that Spot as well.  It is a matter of choice, but to say it shouldn't be #1 is not giving the Master Sword enough credit.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ycqrsu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/vo5m</id></website><link>http://www.ign.com/top/video-game-weapons</link><postedTime>2012-01-23T21:20:27+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T12:03:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwicl0</id><link>http://www.ign.com/top/video-game-weapons#comment-481774211</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7fhc</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-01-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>