<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi6ech/post/2012-03-22T21:36:29</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpkmbp</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zdaa2</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>The real issue was your attacking those of us who're pro-lifers as supposedly uneducated and ignorant!  I'll not accept your attempts to change the subject - it's a typical Communist tactic!!!

Next, as to evolution and religion being mutually-exclusive or not (which they actually ARE as we then make God and the Bible to be liars!):  beyond a certain common set of rules and principles, techniques and other such things, what is education really for?  No human mind can EVER know everything, and even if all 7,000,000,000 brains currently on this planet were combined, there  will be something lacking.  Also, even if we knew all the facts of the universe, all the innumerable planets, galaxies, solo-stars, black-Spots, etc., &lt;b&gt;has any of that knowledge changed basic human nature???&lt;/b&gt;  Surely the answer is a resounding &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;NO&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;:  as long as you have wars, famines, diseases and people looking down upon others for one of so many reasons beyond counting (some of them downright frivolous!!), we'll ALWAYS have misery and unhappiness!!!!

And as to science supposedly being impartial:  I can assure you that in the end, whenever you have men involved in the process, it's categorically IMPOSSIBLE!!!  Anybody and everybody sooner or later will torpedo the process at least for a time - and what's the point of a perpetually-changing, mutating, self-rejecting (in the end) process of a knowledge database?

[Another reason against evolution is that then so many life-forms - ours included - are then meant to die out and repeat a cycle of newness, maturity and extermination.  That is totally contrary to the tenets of Christianity when it comes to Mankind.]

As to the devil fooling us:  why would he bother planting the evidence?  PRECISELY as part of his cheating us!!!  It's all part of his plan - and God Has Let him because, much as He Wants us to come to Him, He DOESN'T want us to do so as automatons!!!  He Wants us to do so of our own free will, making as fully-informed and loving a decision as possible.  We're not meant to be His Robots, ever!!!!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6m3nbw</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/1to1</id></website><link>http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/im-going-to-kill-our-baby-a-fathers-worst-nightmare</link><postedTime>2012-03-20T14:52:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T01:36:29+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi6ech</id><link>http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/im-going-to-kill-our-baby-a-fathers-worst-nightmare#comment-474126169</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l2i7j</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>