<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miy9bo/post/2012-03-22T20:58:21</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Nogar, you are right, George Zimmerman is not White, he is Latino.  I stand corrected from my original post.  However, I still think that although tragic and that Zimmerman should be prosecuted to the fullest extent of the law we as African-Americans need to do a self-evaluation.  We need knowledge of self more than ever during these times not coming together and walking around with some damn Skittles bag.  If we are going to come together right now let this be the catalyst for another movement of doing right and living right.  We are  marching some damn where and putting faces on T-shirts and calling up either Al or Jesse to say a few words.  Nothing against either of those brothers but let's change the trend of the knee jerk reaction.  I live in Chicago and dozens of Trayvon's get killed every other weekend during the summer by Blacks.  Do you hear about that?  Probably not because at that point they are just a number or a 2 minute segment on the evening news.  It is happening all over this country without marches or articles such as this one being written.  If we are going to ride by any means necessary then let's ride until the wheels fall Off for our race.  Obama, is not our savior and nor are Whites.  If that was gonna happen it would have happened already.  Stop blowing up the Spot because a non-white killed this young boy.  We live in a country that has very lenient gun laws and an astonishing crime rate.  The death of any innocent person whether they be a child, adult or senior citizen is wrong.  But a million hoodie march while carrying skittles accomplishes what for our race in the long run?? As I said before, I don't want us to just win the battle I want US to win the war.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dwohe</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t26w</id></website><link>http://newsone.com/newsone-original/ldavenport/trayvon-martin-emmett-till/</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T18:46:07+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T00:58:21+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miy9bo</id><link>http://newsone.com/newsone-original/ldavenport/trayvon-martin-emmett-till/#comment-474106132</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yj6uk</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>