<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwjw42/post/2012-03-31T05:09:01</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Let me tell you about women. There are MANY good ones, but the MAJORITY of them  are sluts and bitches. This is just a simple fact. My generation (currently 18-30) has the most whores. I discovered this in college. Almost every girl I dated wanted to fuck me on the first date. I never even had to ask or make an effort to convince them to bang me; it was  their idea. Women today are so loose with twats it’s a joke. Sadly, most of them had boyfriends or were involved with other guys when they decided  on my cock. You see, women love to shop not only for shoes, but also men. Like trying on different pairs of heels at the mall, they will string along a couple of guys at a time to see which one is the best fit and will benefit them the most. If the new exciting pair they bring home that evening lets them down or leaves their ass they can Always fall back on the other ones in their closet. 

I know this one woman through a friend that stays in an abusive relationship because she wants security. The man she is with is an alcoholic, ugly, out of shape, and abusive (punched her in the face). But guess what. . . . . He's got a lot of money and a great job. She wants so badly for him to marry her, but he doesn't have any interest in doing so. Her reasoning is that if they get married and it doesn't work out, she will get half of everything. 

I use to believe that women needed to be respected and treated well, but my whole perspective changed after I started dating. These bitches are not like the picture of women that my Mom painted when I was young kid (sweet, caring, kind, pure, loving). Young women today are as Cold as fucking ice. Their characteristics and personalities are that of which you would expect to find in a man but only worse. Thank you Feminism! I would never marry one of these no good whores, let alone bring a child into the world with one of them. I say just fuck them and forget them. Leave nothing behind except your wad. (Make sure its in her mouth though. If the bitch gets pregnant your life will be over).


</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/d2gdpo</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/1nh8</id></website><link>http://www.menarebetterthanwomen.com/every-woman-is-a-cheating-whore/</link><postedTime>2011-11-25T22:47:28+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T09:09:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwjw42</id><link>http://www.menarebetterthanwomen.com/every-woman-is-a-cheating-whore/#comment-481674600</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-11-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>