<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkogwz/post/2012-03-26T15:09:28</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>That is one of the sickest graphs I have ever laid eyes on. Reminds me of the NY Jets franchise a few years back. As "they say", you can't start the recovery process until you have hit rock bottom and are able to admit to yourself where you're at and the only one to blame is you. Are we at rock bottom yet? Or is that bottom line with the 20 next to it actually rock bottom? Don't let Comolli see it. His head will explode.

We're at the tail end of a long season. The players are mentally tired and the only thing we're playing for is pride. No chance for 4th, the only meaningful target from a financial perspective. And maybe in the players heads too. We're playing for the Liverbird on the shirts boys, respect and a decent league position. It has to be enough this year. The FA Cup semis I know we'll play our asses .

I still feel in my gut that a goal scoring striker, one or two more decent additions, Lucas back, a better attitude and complete focus will get us competing for the CL Spots again. We already have in place the makings of the best defense in the league ready for next year. (Reina, Jonno, Kells, Skrtel, Dagger, Coates, Enrique, Carra) That's obvious to us all. Just need to find those goals and that creative/inspired touch. Suarez could be good for 20 goals next season if he goes on a run. We just need Andy to step up and pick up a top class striker to add say 10 goals. Then Andy and the new guy are competing for starts and the best one gets them. In a league as competitive as the EPL, you just have to lose focus for an instant to end up in a nosedive.

That graph parallels my drinking. Started downhill on the 3-1 loss to Bolton January 21st and went Off the cliff on the 2-1 loss to United on Feb 11th. I'm in denial too along with the coaching staff. 
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6la5p4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/y675</id></website><link>http://liverpool.theoffside.com/premier-league/liverpool-on-relegation-form-in-2012.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:14:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T19:09:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkogwz</id><link>http://liverpool.theoffside.com/premier-league/liverpool-on-relegation-form-in-2012.html#comment-476645414</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>