<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwlcyd/post/2012-03-30T12:42:16</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>You say I'm Cold and it's true. 
My heart lies sleeping beneath the dirt, swaddled in a blanket of winter's snow. 
Do not try to hasten the spring. A snap thaw would flood us both and leave the ground ruined and rutted, unfit for the tender shoots of my heart. 
All things have a season and spring must come gradually, slowly and patiently. 
The cheerful song of birds must fill the cool air before the crocuses will shoot up and raise their silky flags to greet the rebirth of life. 
Until then, I sleep underground, wating for warmer weather, storing my reserves jealously, holding tight to the hope of spring and new vigour. When the rains have washed away the dirt and ice of winter, Joy will return, and openness. 
There is hope in the thaw and a warning too. Wait for spring and roll in the soft grass of summer, but watch for the autumn. 
Prepare your farewells against the coming frost. As sure as winter turns to spring, the long days of summer will fade into night and my heart will once again rest beneath the dirt and that gentle blanket of snow.

Why do you grasp at the fading rays of summer's sun? You cannot stop the sun from setting. Do not weep or mourn the loss of warmth from my heart. 
Is it not my singular charm to be like the first flush of spring? The spectacle of my bloom cannot last. Would you wish me to be a woody shrub without any show or splendor just so you can stay by my side? I cannot be evergreen, that is for someone else. 
I am a spring flower. Would you change my nature? Would you hate the very ephemerality that is the essence of my heart? 
I store away my energies for a long life of brief blooms. It takes a patient gardener to love me. One who will soak up all my beauty and enjoy every day of my short visit and then wish me well with a tender kiss and a promise to meet again.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67e2bd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/n4i5</id></website><link>http://thewritepractice.com/spring/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T14:47:21+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:42:16+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwlcyd</id><link>http://thewritepractice.com/spring/#comment-480934268</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>