<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwg2au/update/2012-03-30T06:38:24/cb16eba5a25a3a0fb52b7051e612ed716c4678c81d541cdc62a0692c394d01f2</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3w5pj</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zyzm2</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I think a lot of people I know who are not lawyers or law students know about the Military Commissions ....

I think Andrew Koppelman defined the idea of a living Constitution best.  He said that the Constitution is not the precedents, nor is it the text of the document but rather it is a set of rhetorical norms themselves in tension with eachother, unstable, and changing over time.  I like this definition.  I think it is a very accurate description of Constitutional law at least in my opinion as an amateur historian.  At least it adequately describes the way, say, first amendment protections changed during the McCarthy  in response to government abuses.  Sure the court threw out older precedents and adopted newer protections but we are all more free given that distributing the Communist Manifesto can be seen as an invitation to overthrow the federal government.

I think the problem with your line of reasoning is that one recurring theme-- one rhetorical norm if you will, and one which even Sotomayor and Kagan have stood behind in some cases, is that our federal government is supposed to be one of *limited* and *enumerated* powers, but the commerce clause has already morphed into something very much like a general police power, and the courts have to find some way to limit it.

My preference would be for the courts to say "the commerce power's jurisdiction ends after the purchase is made and goods are delivered" but that would be horribly disruptive, and would involve throwing out a large number of precedents.  It would however save the mandate without turning this into a general police power.  However given that no court wants to do something that disruptive, it seems to me that Kennedy's formulation, that this is a significant change in the relationship between the federal government and the citizens and therefore requires steep justification is the correct one.

Let me put it this way.  Congress says "if you are a sex offender and you cross state lines in interstate commerce you must register as a sex offender."  The travelling across state lines subjects the individual to jurisdiction in law beyond the terms of the actual commerce, so this nexus is on-going.  Similarly they say "if you buy a gun that has ever travelled in interstate commerce, you may not take it within 1000 ft of a school."  Again, this means that the gun is forever under federal jurisdiction once it has ever travelled in interstate commerce.

If those two laws are Constitutional, and if (as I contend the court ruled in Morrison and Lopez), that Congress cannot simply mandate that everyone go get, say, a Flu shot, then it seems to me that Congress can still say "if you buy a Flu shot, you must use it."  However, if Congress can *also* say "you must buy a Flu shot" then this distinction is meaningless.

So I don't think it is a matter of throwing out existing precedents.  I think it is a matter of realizing that this a case that does involve rhetorical norms that are in deep tension with eachother, and that the court has to find some way to Resolve them.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zieyv</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/okle</id></website><link>http://volokh.com/2012/03/30/citizens-united-or-kelo/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T04:28:26+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T10:38:24+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwg2au</id><link>http://volokh.com/2012/03/30/citizens-united-or-kelo/#comment-480603515</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ymqmf</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>