<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/323728/post/127798188/comment/327570437</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>First of all thank you for the clarifications. Now to your latest reply:&#13; 
&#13; 
&amp;quot;NO! The main point of the Open Letter, as I just said was to complain to Fox News about needlessly preempting the show for news alerts that weren&amp;rsquo;t news. Moving the show had nothing to do with it. How much plainer can I make that?&amp;quot;&#13; 
&#13; 
Like I said I am going on memory. I saw something on Big Hollywood about moving Red Eye to an earlier time slot. (and I now see it was John Nolte who wrote that, so that, I grant you, is a mistake on my part).&#13; 
&#13; 
&amp;quot;AdventurePic is a total jerk. I&amp;rsquo;m not surprised you got here with negative opinions about me or my blog, given he was the source. But again, you made lots of judgments about what I&amp;rsquo;ve said and how I&amp;rsquo;ve said it without bothering to look at the context, or to note that some of the stuff you claimed I said was actually me quoting the guys.&amp;quot;&#13; 
&#13; 
Well the context of his retweet inferred that he agreed with you. It wasn&amp;#039;t a negative opinion. I agree that he&amp;#039;s a jerk but he seriously hates Red Eye fans and idle curiosity made me wonder what he so liked from this conservative blogger. I&amp;#039;m not saying that as a reflection on you, which if that were my intent would obviously be both inaccurate and unfair, but that&amp;#039;s how I got here.&#13; 
&#13; 
&amp;quot;I don&amp;rsquo;t take Gutfeld all that seriously. I think he&amp;rsquo;s hilarious. I think baiting the Dalai Lama was hilarious. My point was that you can&amp;rsquo;t go around complaining people are mean on Twitter when one is oneself &amp;hellip; mean on Twitter, whether in an effort to amuse people or not.&amp;quot;&#13; 
&#13; 
Well there, we disagree. I don&amp;#039;t think he&amp;#039;s being &amp;quot;mean&amp;quot; to be &amp;quot;mean&amp;quot;, he&amp;#039;s being &amp;quot;mean&amp;quot; to be funny. The people he complained about in the podcast were not being mean to be funny, they were being honestly mean. I see a difference between the two. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:323728:127798188</id><idPostId>127798188</idPostId><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:323728</id><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><link>http://www.chrisisright.net</link><displayName>Chris Is RIGHT</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/06/29/red-eye-in-which-i-get-off-the-short-bus/</link><displayName>Red Eye: In Which I Get Off The Short Bus</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-07-08T11:03:00.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:323728:127798188:327570437</id><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/06/29/red-eye-in-which-i-get-off-the-short-bus/#IDComment327570437</link><postedTime>2011-07-08T11:03:00.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Red Eye: In Which I Get Off The Short Bus by TomGMS</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://twitter.com/TomGMS</link><idEmailMd5>aaa0b4463622ae706036118057dd6eaf</idEmailMd5><displayName>TomGMS</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/TomGMS"&gt;TomGMS&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/06/29/red-eye-in-which-i-get-off-the-short-bus/"&gt;Red Eye: In Which I Get Off The Short Bus&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2011-07-08</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>