<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi65xe/update/2012-03-22T21:32:43/18a5d2bbbe172bf10d41ce8b1ff1f30faaa40cc20bb0373d0d69f79157f94f70</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I haven't read the review yet or the comments, sorry. 

I had to make a liquor run immediately after this episode (which drove me to drink, or actually we were just out but whatever). As I was driving on those lonesome, rainy country roads, hoping I didn't hydroplane, crash into a tree, and die, I couldn't help but think how annoyed I was by this episode, and I downgraded it a little more just now after I got back.

The stuff in the middle with Jeff and his transformation into narcissistic Hulk was the schlockiest, most irritating thing I might have ever seen on this show. The Dean reduced to a quivering mess on the floor and flopping around like a horny fish at the sight of Jeff in aviators as well as Chang's thought bubbles as he dreams up his child army were both irritatingly schlocky as well. I know that the latter two are the most gimmicky characters on the whole show, so I could overlook their actions, but when the cartoonishness is starting to Bleed into all of the characters this much it's worrisome to me. @Semi-bored Torontonian had some really great thoughts about that trend last week, but this episode brought my fears about it full force.

I don't blame the writers for going to the well of Jeff's neuroses for story; it is ripe and disturbing and has produced some really great episodes. But we've seen his issues with narcissism play out in much funnier and more satisfying ways in other episodes. Here it just fell completely flat. If I were grading the episode based on this arc alone, I would probably give it a D.

But then there's Troy and Abed's stuff. I liked Troy's taking the reins and trying to steer his friend out of trouble. The push and pull of trying to be Abed's friend and engage in all this childlike stuff is being done really well, I think. I liked how their peace is immediately made uneasy by an incomplete  best friend handshake. I liked Abed's weird trip into the Dreamatorium (Hot. Hot hot hot.) There were many other funny little moments at the Bar Mitzvah and in poor Pierce's constant struggles for any kind of affirmation. And while I didn't like the essence of Jeff's story much at all, I did enjoy the interactions it provided for him and Britta, and another opportunity to show Off her psychology smarts. I thought this all was A- material. 

In conclusion, really weird episode.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yk4a1</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/contemporary-impressionists,70958/</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T00:30:37+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T01:32:43+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi65xe</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/contemporary-impressionists,70958/#comment-474124218</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6f1fd</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>