<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nhsr/update/2012-03-29T12:47:20/604a1789e4bcb71e5725a82d975115c49c0fcf18991495bce2192ca6a589c644</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34n9q</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I agree with you! My vegetarian friends absolutly love eating with me and my family because I respect their journey!!  I love the challenge of making sure my vegetarian friends have plenty of protein and iron-while making them moan in delight over the meal!  Our D.O.P. for my Food network show Fixing Dinner, is vegetarian.  Lisa can attest---I would take great Joy in bringing her food to set on occasion. 

I say the above because I get the impression that you think I am targeting vegearains ---not at all!  In fact, I have met many pain-in-the-butt Carnivore dieters over the years that won't shut up about how many inches they have lost on their belt----as they scream out their praises all the way to my migraine Headache! 

The purpose of my blog is to open the conversation and support exactly what you just said! Your journey is your journey!  Your friends need to respect yours and you theirs! When your carnivore friends ask you if you're still vegetarian---you should;t need to feel like a criminal and nor should they! This will open up great conversations! 

A great example for me would be when one of my staff noticed how many vegetables I eat.  she said, you could be vegetarian could't you?  My reply, well you see how much spinach I eat, right? For what ever reason when I'm dragging my butt, my body is telling me to have a steak! And after I do, I just feel well! I'm more alert, I feel happier!

On my journey I used to eat red meat at least 4 times per week-but now maybe only twice!  Do you see what I mean? Right now it seems to be a battle!  ---and I beleive it's the battle that's keeping us from progress!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zyace</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/nl3f</id></website><link>http://www.positivelypositive.com/2012/03/29/the-food-journey/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T10:35:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:47:20+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3nhsr</id><link>http://www.positivelypositive.com/2012/03/29/the-food-journey/#comment-479641691</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzmps</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>