<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miooq6/update/2012-03-23T22:45:44/3913f96f135538b587287b49ba200f5ee5fd60b238d847010874c8b8490b3f07</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I spent YEARS travelling the Sheppard subway user--as a rider I  appreciated that I NEVER had to stand but that also reflects its weakness.

Even people living at the stops don't take the subway!!!! An 'environmentalist' socialist friend of mine LIVES and WORKS within a FIVE minute (on either end) walking distance from two subway stops along the Sheppard line and yet this person never takes the subway to work. This person also drives into downtown Toronto rather than take the subway, EVEN IF THE DESTINATION IS NEAR A SUBWAY STOP (I wish I were making this up but I'm not :( :( :(.

I've been on Queen on occasion. I now live near a subway stop along the Bloor-Danforth line and I know precisely WHY I live near one--it's the neighbourhood that's got me hooked and the fact that I can and DO go everywhere by foot or by transit, north, south, east, west! It's not an arduous process to go in any direction which is why I left Sheppard (I love Agincourt but I just couldn't see raising a family there).

I've looked at the maps for all these areas and Sheppard doesn't have the same geography as does the Danforth or Queen street!

The Sheppard subway runs 300 m to 800 m north of the 401 and if it were extended along the rest of Sheppard would run just as close to the 401 along much of its length. If you've spent any time along Sheppard as a transit user you'll know that the 401 is a COMPLETE barrier for north-south transit and pedestrian travel.

The Sheppard line can ONLY service people living NORTH of the line. People living south of the 401 are effectively cut  from the subway and I experienced that the hard way &lt;grumble&gt;.

There are other natural barriers NORTH of the Sheppard line that prevent people from readily accessing the Sheppard line. Roads are not on a grid pattern which means walking is an arduous process. And, even if you do live near Sheppard "as the crow flies" the windy (not the weather kind ;) roads can double your walking distance.

It's not at all that people hate Scarborough.

I've got a really soft Spot for Scarborough--I started my career there and still try to get back as much as I can but I also don't understand the insane proposition of putting a subway line beside a 16 lane highway when the line simply wouldn't be viable, and may not even be viable 50 years from now.

We're not EVER going to get rid of the 401 so that massive barrier to community building will  be there which means that any extensive subway development along there will require constant subsidies from riders in the rest of the system or from tax payers in general.

As it stand each station along Sheppard requires $10 million/year in subsidies ($5 to $8 per trip). 

That's half a billion dollars every decade! Increasing the length of the Sheppard subway will only increase the number of subsidised stops required since there will only be a bit of an increase in ridership above what additional stops would capture but not at all enough to make the subway self-sustaining.

Instead we--as a CITY--would be better Off using that $50 million per year to expand subway transit capacity in areas that CAN sustain subways. As more people across the city use transit pressure would mount to provide Scarborough with LRTs along far more routes than just the SRT and Sheppard (my vote would be McCowan or Brimley).

I'd dearly love to return to Scarborough some day in the future but not along Sheppard--I just can't stand the 401 and the only way that's going to happen is if new LRT is built out along streets like Markham or Brimley (which I hope will happen some day).</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ykmko</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zsj8</id></website><link>http://www.torontosun.com/2012/03/22/doug-ford-rails-against-lrt-supporters</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T00:11:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-24T02:45:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miooq6</id><link>http://www.torontosun.com/2012/03/22/doug-ford-rails-against-lrt-supporters#comment-474995062</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/esswq</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>