<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwvggf/post/2012-03-30T15:47:29</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I blame women!&lt;blockquote&gt;Women Voters Can't Help Fawning Over Sexist GOP
'We Should Know Better, But There's Just Something About Its Unflinching Misogyny,' Says Gushing Female Populace

WASHINGTON—Saying they know its no good for them but they just can't help themselves, gushing women voters acknowledged Monday the overwhelming and uncontrollable attraction they feel toward the sexist Republican party. Smitten female voters across the nation told reporters that despite the way it treats them, they still find everything about the GOP—from its reckless, devil-may-care neglect of women's health issues to its devastatingly bold misogyny—completely irresistible.

"They openly insult me, undermine my intelligence, and  as if I lack the basic responsibility to take care of myself, but every time I hear them talking about why I shouldn't be able to choose what I do with my own body, I get a little turned on," registered voter Jennifer Wilson said. "My friends keep telling me I'll get Burned like I Always do when I elect guys who think their authority extends to my uterus, but there's just something unbelievably sexy about politicians who see something they want and then go out and take it."

"Sure, I could probably find a party that would respect me and be sympathetic toward my desire to make my own personal health care decisions," Wilson continued. "But what can I say? That's not what drives me wild."&lt;/blockquote&gt;http://www.theonion.com/articles/women-voters-cant-help-fawning-over-sexist-gop,27748/</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/676pki</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/uf5</id></website><link>http://www.eschatonblog.com/2012/03/period-police.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:31:31+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:47:29+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwvggf</id><link>http://www.eschatonblog.com/2012/03/period-police.html#comment-481123357</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5k4w8</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>