<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwl7iy/update/2012-03-30T12:58:18/4580993ab0c15da39180bd2fd359fd2c8f6d7275627f9501c14466c093c63595</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>"Third, hospital customer care is abysmal. Recent studies reveal that the average wait time in American hospital emergency rooms is approximately 4 hours. Name one other business where Americans would tolerate this low level of value and service."  
I have a problem with this statement. I used to work in the Emergency Department for years. The wait time issue, is in part due to the population of patients that come to the E.D. I found that quite often, patients use the E.D. as a form of urgent care and/or general care management, instead of using the E.D. for what is it designed: emergencies. Many of our patients in the E.D. 1.) are seeking pain control for a chronic ailment, as opposed to emergent care for severe acute pain; 2.) have ignored symptoms for some time and now are not able to cope (the disease or disorder is not emergent, nor appropriate for the E.D. care/intervention, but require full medical work up and long term care plans); 3.) are seeking care for Cold, Flu, or some other winter viral culprit; 4.) only require simple intervention for minor injuries, such as extremity x-rays, sutures, irrigation, or brace/cast (and the facility does not have a MIIC.) The main trouble with all of these described situations is that while these folks are seeking care in the E.D. for their symptoms, the E.D. is often simultaneously bombarded with incoming ambulances transporting emergent patients in life threatening crises (i.e. MI, CVA, sexual assault/domestic violence, MVA, trauma, DKA, child abuse, GSW, Burns, acute respiratory distress, drownings, etc.) With the ambulance bay constant traffic flow, and the fact that patients are seen by acuity and not by "first come, first served" protocol, the sickest are treated first while the less acute are forced to wait. I've Always thought the public should be educated on "how to effectively use the E.D." as well as what is the goal and purpose of the E.D. Knowing how the E.D. functions helps the public seek care appropriately as well as provide folks with realistic expectations, reinforced with truthful explanations and knowledge. This would diffuse quite a lot.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6cwsya</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/qj7o</id></website><link>http://www.kevinmd.com/blog/2012/03/onethird-hospitals-close-2020.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-14T23:02:01+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:58:18+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwl7iy</id><link>http://www.kevinmd.com/blog/2012/03/onethird-hospitals-close-2020.html#comment-480950577</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7gjs</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-14</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>