<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mknd7a/update/2012-03-26T03:57:34/42a6048d9fea4144d1fd7d3d7a64eab1fcd8a740cac85ffa157048e842678dca</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkqfdq</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yt8qv</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> I have been spayed 3 times with pepper spray and a couple times have had the opportunity to experience CS gas. I was born with severe asthma. My best advice, don't panic. A rescue inhaler will definitely help you after the incident. Do you like hot peppers? I do. The more experience you have with habaneros, and serranos and cooking with hot peepers and roasting hot peppers, the less of an impact the pepper spray will have on you. You will know what to expect. Pepper spray for the most part is the initial unpleasantness and subsequent shock and you can learn to know what to expect through exposure. And no kidding, having a like for hot spicy foods and cooking them. Most likely if you are not on a steroidal inhaler now, you probably would be put on one after an exposure incident for at least a month. If you are ever pepper sprayed, don't rub your skin or eyes. Get lots of water and milk for rinsing. And cry as much as you can to flush your eyes. If you are good at holding your breath that's the best bet if you know you are about to get sprayed. As for bears, I had an awesome experience in Glacier National Park a few years back. I was within 15 yards of a grizzly. It was one of the most memorable experiences of my life. Put quite a few things in perspective. I did not have bear spray and was a good 8 miles from any road or people. I had hiked to Grinnell Glacier and was coming back down the trail, and startled the bear. Fortunately the bear ran uphill in a sprint I could never compete with. The winds were right and the bear could not figure out exactly what I was and stood on it's Hind legs sniffing the air. As for the probability of anything bad happening, you are at more risk, even as an adult catching whooping Cough in Idaho and then succumbing to pneumonia then getting attacked by a bear, or any other wild animal for that matter. As for Grinnell Glacier, I understand it's all but gone now. It was pretty spectacular 12 years ago. Sadly, Global Warming will probably pose a more significant risk in our life times than hungry bears.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rq7ir</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnm5</id></website><link>http://www.idahostatesman.com/2012/03/25/2050458/study-bear-spray-tops-guns-in.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-25T22:35:46+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T07:57:34+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mknd7a</id><link>http://www.idahostatesman.com/2012/03/25/2050458/study-bear-spray-tops-guns-in.html#comment-476275357</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lx725</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>