<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwbvka/update/2012-03-30T21:45:05/ea85ec2885b20eab4ea04b6cfd64f48403112c721992498bcea102d0404fd327</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Let's face it. The press knows Obama is a fraud. I won’t say that all of them have Always known, but a substantial percentage did. They had to. Even those who didn’t before, do now, but it still doesn’t matter. They’re in too deep to back out, even if they wanted to. Which, of course they don’t.
Think about it.
Back when everything was all new and shiny, Obama feel good stories were worth their weight in gold. Every girl he smiled at on campus, every buddy he ever drank a beer with, every professor who had Spotted him as a prodigy, would have been gushing for the news hounds, etc. etc….
But somehow, nothing ever made the news. Weird.
Hasn’t anyone ever wondered why?
Well, now we know. 
Those intrepid news sleuths who managed to get a peek under the lid, 
slammed it shut immediately and then went looking for hammer and nails.
 Those that didn’t take the first hint, were silenced by their own organizations as they went into full damage control mode.

One story that came out the day of Sheriff Joe's news conference, laughably billed as straight news, had the gall to state, “Theories that the president’s COLB is fake have been widely discredited.”
Discredited? No. Discounted? Absolutely.
They discount anything that detracts from the official Obama narrative.
 Of course, they do it the same way a five-year-old does 
when he doesn’t want to see or hear something.
 Eyes clenched shut, fingers in ears, “LALALALA I CAN’T HEAR YOU!!!”


Going back to hisCOLB, has anyone, anywhere, seen any analysis done by a competent expert that says the Obama released PDF is legitimate? I sure haven’t, and I've been looking.

 You’d be thinking that Liberal computer experts would be all over this. 
But, nope. As near as I can tell, asmuch as they may love the Bamster,
 there is no way they are going to trash their own professional reputations by supporting something that is so obviously a fake.

...kudos to Sheriff Joe for moving the ball, but don’t expect this to be a game changer. 
There is a lot good stuff here, but nothing that will force the media to change their narrative. Yet....
Sooner or later something is going to pop up that will be too big for them to ignore.
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67dtg1</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6bwl</id></website><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/politics/2012/03/30/democrats-disarray</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:39:59+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T01:45:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwbvka</id><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/politics/2012/03/30/democrats-disarray#comment-481418461</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8z770</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>