<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/esvnqv/update/2012-01-21T04:29:37/3bfe33b314148a2f9920e05773f300f629c1a8b1a14c60b2f419c1922ef5babd</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/esrrlr</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>When I wrote Roth Leaps` "crusade" and hard work has paid , I was merely pointing out that a) Kudos to not missing a chance to tear into the Red Rocker, but also that b) It`s also time to calm down, because the rightful balance of the universe has been restored.  I admire Leaps` commitment to taking every chance to slam Hagar, I really do, but I know that he probably hasn`t changed many people`s minds. ..maybe some. 
I happen to agree with him on most points and find him funny.  And Dave IS so much better :)  Eddie had an affair with Sam, but he and Dave are back together.  Sam feels used, but he`s done bloody well out of the settlement.  The way things are right now, there`s nothing left to complain about (apart from Hagar lyrics, when we want to feel depressed).
I`m never sure that you legitimise your argument if you feel "Well, uh...Hello!" has a place in your reply, but seriously, it`s all good.  No one is stopping you enjoying your Hagar music.  
But I`m sure Leaps will not rest until you have not only Burnt your Hagar records, and Sammy refunds the money, but the deeds to the Cabo Wabo cantina have been handed to Dave and Tequila is Banned.
Which is fine by me, especially the last bit - had a really rough night once on that stuff!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yaxagd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/fbtm</id></website><link>http://www.vhnd.com/2012/01/20/exclusive-video-david-lee-roth-explains-tattoo-lyrics/</link><postedTime>2012-01-20T17:56:51+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-01-21T09:29:37+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/esvnqv</id><link>http://www.vhnd.com/2012/01/20/exclusive-video-david-lee-roth-explains-tattoo-lyrics/#comment-417317884</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-01-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>