<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tkxb/post/2012-03-29T10:22:08</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m37jd3</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a3m6m</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Swiffiness - why won't YOU address the issues I raise? Snarky and extremely ineffective attempts at diverting the truth, with lame-o-zois insults,  about the 100% consistent pattern of Negro violence, and dysfunction, as well as their Racial average 80 IQ - well it just doesn't work anymore. The New Black Panther (Gosh - I adore felines, and the name of that moronic racist group of Negro sociopaths is such an insult to genuine black panthers! Well -what don't they ruin?) strategem, of threatening to Burn Detroit to the ground, (which would be a substantial improvement at this point) in order to prevent "White Man's Law (aka functional civilization) from takng control of the Mogadishu in the MidWest, is illustrative of my thesis. When Da White Manz takes over control of Detroit, the Bruthas and Sistuhs will be assured of smooth flowing Welfare benefits. The EBT swipes on!  Under Black Rulz - they can't keep the lights on, maintain basic infrastructure (the Ruins of DEE-troy are world reknown, for the corrosive effects of the Black Undertow), or even police their own, in order to prevent their own from killing their own. Da White Manz brings CARGO to them . The bitterly funny element of this entire DEE-troy scenario is that the 24/7 Black City staff don't even blame Whitey for their woes, anymore. 
Should the enchanting Diverse Panterian Social Activists Act on their threats, and Burn DEEtroy to the ground - where will the denizens find refuge? Where do you live? Would you be willing to bring the Burnt-out bruthas to your hood?
Well would you?
FYI - I find slavery to be an absolute abomination. The American slave trade was run out of Rhode Island by Jews. Do research the DeWolf family, some time, will you? Jews have been slavers for ever. There are loads of accounts of this traditonal occupation, going back to the Roman Empire. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lun96</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/eyjq</id></website><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2012/03/the-worst-racial-demagogues-of-the-decade/255070/</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T14:31:20+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:22:08+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tkxb</id><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2012/03/the-worst-racial-demagogues-of-the-decade/255070/#comment-479524666</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/m5lhm</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>