<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwuzp1/post/2012-03-30T22:51:51</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I've been watching Keith since 2005/2006. He helped keep me sane and engaged through the Bush years. He has introduced me to so many great bloggers, jounros and thinkers over the years, I couldn't begin the list them. And yeah. I know about the Nation because of Keith too. I've seen the positive, strengthening and invigorating influence he has had on left, politically and media-wise, and at a time that American liberalism really could use a few, no-compromise champions and haven't really found them yet, unless you count Keith. While Beck was selling gold and O'Reilly hocking his books and coffee mugs, Olbermann did things like help raise money for free health care clinics and helped keep the pressure on when some ordinary person was getting screwed over by Walmart. He talked about what Bush was doing to Habeus Corpus while too much of the left media were just whining about how much Bush sucked. He took on the Tiller murder with more guts than anyone on TV save maybe Rachel Maddow (whom he also introduced me too through her guest host Spots on Countdown). And I had been continually impressed with his show on Current, especially on his coverage and guests on OWS, the assaults on Planned Parenthood and the Trayvon Martin case. I do think the Current show was every bit the quality show he said it has been in his statement today. 

A few times Keith has royally pissed me . He's no saint--and he's no panderer. I don't doubt for a second that being his boss is a bitch of a gig. But I don't think you get away with having so much impact without pissing Off a few people--or a lot, judging by my FOX News-watching family's Schadenfreude tonight over dinner. I don't presume to know what really happened (granted I was more than a little surprised at the unprofessional tone of Current's statement) and honestly, I don't get a flip about Keith's "history"--I know far too many bosses are bullies and parasites, and too often employees just put up and shut up. I kind of get the impression Keith just can't be one of those employees. If so, then good for him. And of course, I'm sure this isn't the last we're see of him.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6770ur</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q2aj</id></website><link>http://www.thenation.com/blog/167144/olbermann-axed-current-tv-promises-lawsuit</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T22:46:53+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T02:51:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwuzp1</id><link>http://www.thenation.com/blog/167144/olbermann-axed-current-tv-promises-lawsuit#comment-481462476</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yuoi2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>