<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3t8qf/update/2012-03-29T09:27:19/bf3bd75dac8e99cd405ea90d25caed1e294b2086482a27caacf9d1ade6e80fdc</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3v9sn</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/81yqm</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Grew up on it.  Although he decided not to pursue music for a living and became an civil engineer (  said it was more secure to raise a family) my dad was a great player and played at various times with several big Acts and some session work and knew many of them.  He had music in all genres at the house from bluegrass to classical all the time.  I heard and knew of Django and others as small child.  Mom was big into the big bands.  Had the old phonograph going more than TV most of the time.  

I could kick myself in the butt knowing what I know now as I had a drum barrel full of 78's growing up given to me by my grandpa, who was a traveling and on radio fiddle player,  Had every kind of music.,  One cut I would love to have back is an original in the sleeve of "Homer and Jethro with June Carter, before anyone had ever heard of her doing "Baby its Cold Outside."  Have no idea of what happened to all of them, but probably back then they got put in the closet with the advent of 8 track, and eventually tossed not realizing the value they would come to have.  Still have a lot of 33's in the original sleeves that are mint.  I still listen to them picking out the guitar parts to learn a solo version of a song

As great as Chet was and other great players are or were, they didn't quit learning other genres or couldn't be  influenced.  He played with Mark Knopfler to Lenny Breau and others and incorporated their styles into his.  He felt once can't learn and be influenced by great artist it is time to make a wall hanging of the guitar.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hptwu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/eid</id></website><link>http://www.mediabistro.com/tvnewser/the-scoreboard-tuesday-march-27-2_b118695</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T20:29:53+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:27:19+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3t8qf</id><link>http://www.mediabistro.com/tvnewser/the-scoreboard-tuesday-march-27-2_b118695#comment-479487013</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/9emg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>