<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwwvj9/post/2012-03-31T12:37:49</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Making the assumption that all of this is being orchestrated by the obama re-election committee, it makes one wonder if they know that they can control this enough to be able to shut the emotions down, or they can't control it enough and are willing to take the risk of letting it spin out of control and Burning a few cities.  And, if a few cities Burned, how would they handle that?  It would seem to me that there is no way obama could spin this if a few cities Burned, a few hundred people killed.  So, it must be that they are confident that they can turn the bla cks on and Off like water out of a faucet.  And, that is why Sharpton and Jackson have their jobs.  They are essentially the handle on the faucet.  But all of this is just getting the liberal factions energized.  The re-election committee is going step-by-step through each of their radical interest groups, creating an incident to get their people up for the election.  They have been through feminists and bla cks. Next will probably be a homosexual incident.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67pla2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yjmx</id></website><link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2012/03/31/trayvon-martin-funeral-director-no-signs-fight/</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T13:01:01+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T16:37:49+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwwvj9</id><link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2012/03/31/trayvon-martin-funeral-director-no-signs-fight/#comment-481978214</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h1ijg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>