<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3py48/post/2012-03-29T20:11:43</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3frp6</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lqpgm</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> I agree with everything you said but I have to correct your statements about the fans reactions to Rock at WM 17.

I just watched Stone Cold vs The Rock at Wrestlemania 17 and Wrestlemania 19 literally today.

You are absolutely correct that most of the fans were pro Austin at Wrestlemania 17, the Rock still had significant amounts of  everytime he made a comeback. Everytime he kicked out near the end there was a big pop. Now I have to admit that the  for Rock do sound a little high pitched which makes me think that perhaps the women and kids (lol Cena fanbase) was the majority of his fans at X-Seven whereas Austin had most of the males and lots of females/kids too. None the less, the Rock was not "booed out of the building" at X-Seven like he was at X-8. The crowd was just more Pro Austin and near the end the Cheers for Rock were quite strong with more males it seems because they seemed to deeper voices.

Also at WrestleMania XIX - The Rock was the heel and got a pretty good pop during his entrance and also got a nice pop when he won the match.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z4pf5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cq26</id></website><link>http://www.wrestlezone.com/news/252207-jerry-lawler-reveals-his-favorite-wm-match-to-call</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:24:00+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:11:43+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3py48</id><link>http://www.wrestlezone.com/news/252207-jerry-lawler-reveals-his-favorite-wm-match-to-call#comment-480055898</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzbe2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>