<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw41nc/post/2012-03-30T17:52:11</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Stand Your Ground Self Defense Law does not really apply in the Martin case. The law allows you to defend yourself. It doesn't say anything about you following a suspicious person around a neighborhood. Also, it doesn't allow you to ignore a 911 operator's instructions. Stand Your Ground Laws do work! Just ask the 21 year old widowed mother(her husband had recently died of cancer) of an infant son in Oklahoma. The woman was home alone and two men attempted to break into her trailer despite repeated warnings. The woman called 911 and yelled at the men to leave. They proceeded to enter. She fired and killed the one man. The other man took . She was backed by the 911 operator who told her  "That police were on the way but they that she should do what was necessary to protect herself and her child."I realize that this may be a troublesome outcome with some of the NDP fans out there whose hearts Always Bleed for the criminals. Worse, some of the NDPers might be upset that being a white woman from Oklahoma(an "evil Republican") she survived the encounter. My God, the Republican lives how awful! 
These laws have now been on the books for several years and have proven their effectiveness. This is why they  also have proven very popular in the U.S. where the population supports them by a 68%-23% margin(according to Angus Reid). Whites and hispanics strongly support the law. Even blacks support the law by 52%-38%. Under 35's support it 69%-19%. Over 55year olds, have the most opposition but still support it 66%-27%.Just because its an American policy doesn't make it a bad idea!
The NDP violent crime policy is outdated. Their answer to every crime policy is a social program. The NDP doesn't really believe in your right to self-defense. They follow Sarkozy of France's  belief that the public has no right to self defense because they have the police to protect them. Cute but not everyone lives in downtown Montreal, Toronto, or Vancouver.The NDP golden rule in the event of a break in is don't resist. Instead, they hope that you hide under the bed and hope for the best(P.S. Don't pray for help. Its way too Christian and anti-PC).</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67muo5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/r11g</id></website><link>http://www2.macleans.ca/2012/03/30/guns-for-everyone/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:01:30+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:52:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw41nc</id><link>http://www2.macleans.ca/2012/03/30/guns-for-everyone/#comment-481241811</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>