<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miyg4v/update/2012-03-22T20:07:38/eb4824006c8f259da9f7c96892d4e7c8aeb569981b7cd2ca0fc4cc25de2bc4eb</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Secularist Stupidity &amp; Religious 
Wars


By Patrick J. Buchanan2-9-6


 








"What hypocrisy. When it comes to what Germans 
are most sensitive about, Hitler and the Holocaust, they are ruthless censors. 
British historian David Irving has spent three months in a Viennese prison 
awaiting trial on Feb. 20 for speeches he made 15 years ago in Austria. Skeptics 
and deniers of the Holocaust are prosecuted, fined and imprisoned in Europe with 
the enthusiastic endorsement of the European press." 
  
  
That demagogues and agitators are exploiting 
those cartoons of Mohammed to advance a war of civilizations and expel Europeans 
from the Middle East seems undeniable. 
  
But that does not excuse the paralyzing 
stupidity of that Danish paper in running those cartoons ­ or the arrogant 
irresponsibility of European newspapers in plastering those cartoons all over 
their front pages. 
  
The storm first broke last September, when 
Jyllands-Posten published 12 caricatures of Mohammed, including a lampoon of the 
Prophet with a terrorist bomb as a turban. In the Islamic faith, any depiction 
of the face of Mohammed is forbidden. 
  
The Danish paper knew this. It published the 
cartoons to protest "the rejection of modern, secular society" by Muslims. The 
cartoons were thus a defiant provocation. And they succeeded. 
  
The Middle East responded with a boycott of 
Danish foods and goods. But when, in the name of press solidarity, Le Soir and 
Le Monde in Paris, El Pais in Madrid and Die Welt in Berlin republished the 
cartoons on page one, Islam exploded. For this was an in-your-face declaration 
by the secularist media of the European Union that it will exercise its right to 
insult any God, any Prophet, any faith, whenever it so chooses. 
  
"Enough lessons from these reactionary bigots," 
said Serge Faubert, editor of Le Soir. "Just because the Quran  images of 
Mohammed doesn't mean non-Muslims have to submit to this." 
  
Faubert, however, is not a Danish soldier in the 
Shi'ite sector of Iraq. Innocents will pay the price of his heroism. 
  
The U.S. State Department seemed to empathize 
with Muslim rage, stating that "inciting religious or ethnic hatred in this 
manner is unacceptable." But, within hours, State had retreated to neutral 
ground: "While we share the offense that Muslims have taken at these images, we 
at the same time vigorously defend the right of individuals to express points of 
view." 
  
As of today the Danish consulate in Beirut has 
been Burned, Danish embassies have been stormed, and Danes are fleeing the 
Middle East. Europeans are getting out of the West Bank, Gaza and Beirut, where 
mobs are attacking embassies and Christian churches. 
  
Islamic countries have recalled ambassadors from 
Copenhagen. People have been injured and property destroyed in mob assaults as 
far away as Indonesia. Relations between the West and the Islamic world have 
been dealt another rupturing blow. 
  
And for what? What was the purpose of this 
juvenile idiocy by the Europress? Is this what freedom of the press is all about 
­ the freedom to insult the faith of a billion people and start a religious 
war? 
  
Can Europeans be that ignorant of the power of 
the press to inflame when Bismarck's editing of just a few words in the Ems 
telegram ignited the Franco-Prussian war? Did Europeans learn nothing from the 
Salman Rushdie episode? Or the firestorm that gripped the Islamic world when 
Christian ministers in the United States called Mohammed a "terrorist"? 
  
European governments are wringing their hands 
over the rage and violence unleashed, but they seem paralyzed. What is the 
matter? Why cannot they denounce press irresponsibility while defending press 
freedom? Even friends of the West like Hamid Karzai in Afghanistan, President 
Hosni Mubarak in Egypt and Tayyip Erdogan in Turkey have denounced these 
cartoons as insults to Islamic values and deeply damaging to Western 
interests. 
  
British Foreign Minister Jack Straw deplored 
republication of the cartoons as "insensitive ... disrespectful ... wrong." But 
German Interior Minister Wolfgang Shauble haughtily dissented, "Here, in Europe, 
governments have nothing to say about which publisher publishes what." 
  
What hypocrisy. When it comes to what Germans 
are most sensitive about, Hitler and the Holocaust, they are ruthless censors. 
British historian David Irving has spent three months in a Viennese prison 
awaiting trial on Feb. 20 for speeches he made 15 years ago in Austria. Skeptics 
and deniers of the Holocaust are prosecuted, fined and imprisoned in Europe with 
the enthusiastic endorsement of the European press. 
  
Nor are we all that different. Sen. Trent Lott 
was Ousted as majority leader for a birthday-party compliment to 100-year-old 
Strom Thurmond. Atlanta Braves pitcher John Rocker was almost lynched for saying 
he considers New York a social pigsty. There were demands that Rocker undergo 
psychiatric counseling. 
  
We have "speech codes" in colleges and "hate 
crimes" laws to protect minorities from abusive remarks. But newspapers that 
hail these codes throw a blanket of "artistic freedom" over scatological art 
that degrades religious symbols ­ from putting a figure of Christ in a jar of 
urine to a "painting" of the Virgin Mary surrounded by female genitalia and 
elephant dung that hung in a Brooklyn museum. 
  
What has happened in Europe is that the secular 
press, which loves to mock the beliefs and symbols of religious faith, has now 
insulted a deadly serious religion that answers insults with action. 
  
  
Patrick J. Buchanan is co-founder and editor of 
The American Conservative. He is also the author of seven books, including Where 
the Right Went Wrong, and A Republic Not An 
Empire.


 </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y8s0d</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry2d</id></website><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50373</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T22:07:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T00:07:38+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miyg4v</id><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50373#comment-474078760</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zd1dw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>