<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms7r2d/update/2012-03-27T16:07:31/5bc9fd4677061e0b1291a09c801a00b20fd0cb8e7610db0b5b8449eca858de0c</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>For Mr. Nunez who wants a more "objective" analysis try this.  Most neighborhood watch groups are very clear that their members never carry weapons. Zimmerman did. The police dispatcher told Zimmerman not to follow Martin.  Zimmerman refused to follow the police'e directive.  In his second call to the police he is told that a squad car is on the way and he was asked "where are you now?" He refused to give his location to the police.  Instead he tells the dispatcher that he will "call you later and let you know."

The unmistakable inference to be drawn from this taped evidence of Zimmerman conduct is that he intended to intercept Martin before the police arrived.  He may have planned to make a citizens arrest-we don'y know. He may have planned worse.  

The only problem is that Martin had not committed any crime and there was no probable cause to make an arrest, either by a civilian or by the police. But Zimmerman would now have us believe that after this determined effort at stalking Martin, even when the police told him specifically to stand down, and that they would take over that when he finally confronted Martin that he simply got back in his car and walked away?

After all this determined effort and willful intent to avoid and deceive the police, he simply stopped and walked away, only to be accosted by a slightly built boy who weighed 80 pounds less than him?

This scenario was without a doubt cause to arrest Zimmerman on the Spot.  Self defense may be offered at the time arrest, but police typically make the arrest, seal Off the crime scene, conduct a forensic investigation and after the evidence is gathered they let the prosecutor decide whether the evidence supports a claim of self defense.

From what we know now Zimmerman was released at the crime scene with little evidence other than his version of what happened having been analyzed by the police.  One report claims that because Zimmerman claimed that Martin "must have been on drugs or something" that a drug unit detective, not a homicide specialist was assigned to the case.  If forensic evidence is available none was ever turned over to the Martin family's attorney.  Are there crime scene photos? We don't know.  Could Zimmerman's alleged injuries have been self inflicted?  We don't know.  

What we do know is that if a black man had done what Zimmerman did there is no way that he would be released from police custody on the flimsy story that Zimmerman offered.  This case shows emphatically that constitution or no constitution that it is only white people that begin their encounters with police with a presumption of innocence.  If you are black, the prevailing presumption is that you must have done something wrong, or were about to do something wrong and so you will be arrested and then you can prove your innocence.  

The idea that Florida's "stand your ground law" was the reason Zimmerman was never charged is ludicrous.  The police wanted to believe Zimmerman's story and did so without supporting proof or evidence.  Whether the truth will come eventually come out is doubtful.  Usually if a forensic investigation is not commenced immediately evidence gets corrupted or lost and we may be left with Zimmerman's version of white skin privilege on a rainy night.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lue3d</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dhzf</id></website><link>http://colorlines.com/archives/2012/03/you_got_a_problem_well_now_you_do.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T14:13:27+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-27T20:07:31+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms7r2d</id><link>http://colorlines.com/archives/2012/03/you_got_a_problem_well_now_you_do.html#comment-477725048</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/xak3</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>