<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwddjz/post/2012-03-30T09:46:08</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>"This woman was following advice from Govt Minister 
  Francis Maude &amp; ends up with 40% Burns"

Francis Maude did not advise her to decant petrol next to a flaming gas cooker.  He also did not advise her to take petrol into the house.
He only said people should fill up and get some spare fuel, not knowing that a jerry can is big rather than the small 5 litre container.

Petrol cans are usually stored in cars or garages; jerry cans in garages unless in the vehicle on long journeys with little chance of a refill - say like crossing the Sahara.

Quite apart from the danger of naked flames in the kitchen, even without naked flames she should not have brought the petrol indoors where it was in a confined space and there is a risk of petrol fumes.

The place to pour petrol is outside in a well ventilated area. When finished, it may be necessary to hose the area with water in case of spillages. If there's a hosepipe Ban, it's best not to pour.

Hope she recovers soon and when she recovers and is back home again, she should get rid of her gas cooker and get an electric one instead - especially if she intends to do such stupid petrol decanting stunts again.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z3wyz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/earth/energy/fuel/9175292/Fuel-strike-petrol-delivery-backlog-reaches-two-to-three-days-warns-motor-trade-union.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T07:39:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:46:08+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwddjz</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/earth/energy/fuel/9175292/Fuel-strike-petrol-delivery-backlog-reaches-two-to-three-days-warns-motor-trade-union.html#comment-480754778</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8g5qu</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>