<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miej4v/update/2012-03-22T17:19:27/ffa17a946bd81d5074a7ae685d97dad1a429fc6765dc66cdb63badeec3f738cd</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>GLOBALIST TRAITOR PUPPET!  Liberal Deemocrat Hawaii Governor Abercrombie searched the Hawaii Secretary of State records and told reporters "there is no such birth certificate in Hawaii."  Emperor ObaMarxist Keenyatta's grandma and grandpa in Kenya testified that they were present when he was born in that country.  The Government of Kenya stated that ObaMarxist Keenyatta's birth certificate is not available BECAUSE IT WAS CRIMINALLY REMOVED!!!  Michelle calls Kenya ObaMarxist's' "home country"!?  Sheriff Joe's FORENSIC CRIME EXPERTS say the birth certificate is a FORGERY.  They say his selective service card is a FORGERY!  His Connecticut social security number is FAKE!  His Indonesian foreign student records at Occidental and grad schools are "."  His medical records, demanded by the liberal mainlining media like howling rabid dogs from Republican candidates are "," as are files relating to the murder of his homosexual lover.  When the forged birth certificate was claimed by ObaMarxist to be real, his White House attorney RESIGNED over the fraud, trying not to become another Vince Foster.  A postman for the communist Ayers family in a Chicago suburb said he often talked to ObaMarxist, then a grad school student, who told him that he was a foreign student from Indonesia living with the Ayers family, and that ONE DAY HE WOULD BE PRESIDENT!  Sheriff Joe says TONS MORE EVIDENCE is coming!  Much more at the World Net Daily website, which has followed the evidence for over four years, evidence that the other globalist sellout puppet, the most useful of useful idiot RINO's, Johnny "Build the Dang FEMA Concentration Camp Fences" McAmnesty (McCain), knew about and IGNORED!?

The big question is WHY this totally flawed creature?  His Mom and her Mom were CIA OPERATIVES, and there has to be federal agency involvement to carry Off the coverup, so my guess is the CIA as the agency that recruited him.  But why ObaMarxist, with so much to hide?  Blackmail-ability doesn't seem to justify the risk. But since 1988 the One World Government Illuminati have bragged that since they control both puppet candidates for president from the Deemocrat and Republican't crime families, "you can vote for anyone, but you will be voting for us"!  THUS, THE FOUR HORSEMEN OF OUR APOCALYPSE:  Bilderberg "Neeeeeeew World Order" Bush, PESTILENCE to destroy nationalism and subsitute globalism; Parsin' Billy Jeff "BJ" Clinton, FAMINE, who starved the morality from America with his complete lack of moral fiber and belief in right and wrong; W(AR) Bush, involving us in endless neo-con chickenhawk wars to feed the military-industrial complex and Bleed us dry while leaving our borders open to invasion in violation of the Constitution; and now the Emperor ObaMarxist Keenyatta, a globalist traitor United Nations puppet imposter, here to bring about the DEATH of America and its Constitution. 

Now we are told that the Illuminati "choice" this time must be Keenyatta "or" the eiptome of a puppet for the globalist bankster TRAITORS, Willard "I Love to Fire People" RomneyRino!?!?  ARMAGEDDON, AMERICA, UNLESS WE STOP THEM NOW!  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yb8pc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6bwl</id></website><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/president-obama/2012/03/22/obama-asks-woman-do-you-have-your-birth-certificate</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T16:18:08+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T21:19:27+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miej4v</id><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/president-obama/2012/03/22/obama-asks-woman-do-you-have-your-birth-certificate#comment-473967304</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zdn5o</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>