<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msjt4d/update/2012-03-28T08:04:12/1e89fc40b1a32d31cd78ab15d855031e720d79254f452c635c24b22dd39d28f3</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Tawana Brawley.  Duke Lacross players.  And now Zimmerman.
What do these all have in common.  Racism.  Coincidence? I think not.
The sad story of Mr Martin who died at the hands of Zimmerman was reported in the press last week.  At first Blush it looked like some kind of heinous crime, and in all candor it was.  It is sad when anyone looses their life, especially a young man.
But, there was a rush to judgement of Zimmerman and a woeful holding back of other facts.
The pictures of Zimmerman made him look like a thug but Martin's picture looked like it was taken at his Communion.  What was not in the press were the large tattoos sported and the gold grille he sported.
Also not reported was Martin's twitter name which, part of which was the "N" word.  
Also not reported were all the his "brushes" with the law and school officials.
Also not reported is the eyewitness account of Zimmerman getting his butt kicked by Martin.
(Do not misunderestimate me,  I do not think Zimmerman is an angel but the press was far to quick to make him the demon and Martin the angel when neither are probably the truth,)
Also not reported is the $10,000 Bounty put on Zimmerman by the New Black Panther Party and a call for 10,000 black men to descend on Sanford Fla,
Also not reported was Spike Lee tweeting the home address of Zimmerman.
Racism?  You bet! But it is the other way around.  After all, if this was fair, would not the AG be looking into the death threats on Zimmerman  by the New Black Panthers?
Or, is that not being reported as well?
Why did it take 3 weeks for this story to hit the national news?  Why all of a sudden?  Why not when it first happened?  
Why are not stories opposite also being reported?
This thing stinks to high heaven and me thinks the source of this discontent comes from someone who hopes to capitalize from this tragedy.
God Rest your soul, Mr. Martin and God Protect you, Mr. Zimmerman.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6heqdu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/hmgk</id></website><link>http://www.newsday.com/news/nation/supporters-of-fla-shooter-fearful-of-speaking-out-1.3627273</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T07:29:46+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T12:04:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msjt4d</id><link>http://www.newsday.com/news/nation/supporters-of-fla-shooter-fearful-of-speaking-out-1.3627273#comment-478293344</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6ocfn</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>