<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4bta/post/2012-03-30T17:49:12</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I work for a doctor and I spend most of my working day dealing with the massive Headache that is Medicare and Medicaid.   Many doctors in our area have cut Off Medicare only patients and those on the Medicaid roles.  We still see them, but there are days I wish we didn't.  I have never seen such a group of entitlement babies as what walks through my doors each day. Patient's show up when they feel like it, not just a few minutes late for scheduled appointments, but days late, and expect to be seen.  One person in the family has the appointment, but Mama drags all 5 in and expects them all to be seen, which further clogs the schedule and puts our doctor behind.  Then people are coming up to the window complaining about how long they have been waiting.  Well, get used to it!  Government insurance dictates what, when and how often we can see you, how much they are going to pay for that office visit and what prescription drugs they will cover.  Stop blaming the doctors.  Standing there yelling at me about how far you have to travel to come to my office and how you don't want to come back for a follow up is not my choice.  The Government insurance mandates when and how often you can be seen and how many procedures they will pay for in one routine office visit.  It wasn't our choice, and we're not running a free clinic. I don't care which of your friends told you to get samples instead of prescriptions. Trust me, the drug reps are in the same boat as we are.  We don't have the sample that you are asking for because the pharmaceutical companies have scaled way back.  Many of the most basic drugs that we have prescribed for years are simply no longer available, production has ceased.  When a pharmacist calls me to say your insurance will not cover the medication prescribed, I save myself a lot of trouble by just asking him to tell me what they will cover and does he have enough of it on hand? The government has never solved a problem or stuck their nose in a situation that they didn't make 10 times worse. If the Supreme Court allows Obamacare to stand, I pity all of us.   </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67cz5e</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yjmx</id></website><link>http://www.foxnews.com/opinion/2012/03/30/what-doctor-knows-about-obamacare/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T12:43:07+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:49:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4bta</id><link>http://www.foxnews.com/opinion/2012/03/30/what-doctor-knows-about-obamacare/#comment-481239109</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8zblk</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>