<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/cnpvju/update/2011-06-02T05:06:06/7e5ab250faaf3d5385ae810d8e278a546494dc401826aca353c14b10d5584b8b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/cnprpu</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8zx0u</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>There has to be two parties or we would REALLY be in trouble.  I think we have an autocrat in the Oval office as it is.  

Two parties are essential, don't you think?  Because neither one can be trusted.  But the Democrats seem to want to destroy the Republican party and the Constitution and that means they are loaded down with dangerous factions.  

What President prior to this arrogant, dismissive, and divisive President would EVER have been allowed to bring a communist (the dangerous, ex-convict Van Jones) into the White House as a 'Czar'?  No matter how 'nice' people think this President we have is, or 'likeable', HE DID THAT!!!!  And that woman in the White House?  We've all heard her anti-American rant.  And then there are those Czars.  What are they up to?  We know what Mark Lloyd is up to. And then there is Valerie Jarret, also in our WHITE HOUSE,  who appears to be  a communist sympathizer and who 'admires' Van Jones and the 'work' he did in Oakland (Ca.).  We are in trouble!

Whomever said that the Democratic party is no longer the party of your grandfather was Spot on.  The belt line isn't even really a part of the United States or the 'people'.  There are completely disconnected from us other that for using the electorate as 'cash cows'.  

The trouble is, the Democratic Party seems to have morphed into something that has, number one, no regard for the 'people',  nor for the Constitution.  The Republicans are not Off the hook either, on any of this, including corruption.  But ACORN Obama represents total evil.  Wiener is one of the party's uber liberal  water carriers....a desk pounder and shouter.  Watching Wiener 'talk over' an opposer is frightening.  Watching the evolution of the Democratic party is  like the second coming of H i t ler, 

I would like to the the power of the President drastically curtailed.   Why are over 350,000,000 people so beholding to this one person?  The Brits have a better idea. 

I would like to see the States rights returned to them.  Their sovereignty needs to be restored.  And the sovereignty of America as well.  We need to stop selling ourselves to China.  We need to protect our nation from ideologues and radical's within our own shores.

I would like TERM LIMITS all around and even in the SCOTUS (which is now 'loaded' up with two very troubling (new) women whom I suspect are 'Brides of Obama'. 

Last, Obama simply must go.  It would be a blessing if they'd fire him right now.

In truth, has America ever seen anyone who loves America more than Sarah Palin?  I'm serious.  This woman is a true patriot.  And the communist, Marxist, socialist, liberal progressives that make up the new infested Democratic party, ripped her to pieces and destroyed her career.  They own the media, they own the courts and they are just as much of a horror as any dictatorship you can name.  What they've done to Palin (who wont be stopped or shut up)....that is the power of real, unbridled evil.  Thank God for people like Sarah Palin, Michelle Bachmann and the concept of the Tea Party.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/g6z6es</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6bwl</id></website><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/politics/2011/06/01/rep-weiner-his-attitude</link><postedTime>2011-06-01T20:28:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-06-02T09:06:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/cnpvju</id><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/politics/2011/06/01/rep-weiner-his-attitude#comment-216365603</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8nldh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-06-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>