<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m37bh6/update/2012-03-29T07:22:53/d7150ee71937681dad8a953490cdf4c2f1738b780a0e3f1b51cf2ea1a88c8d23</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m36c0f</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rk8dk</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>You know the great thing about all of this? You pretty much said that you don't like the guy for being himself. You know, in a world where no one is themselves. Or at the very least, it's very hard to be. I've never once called him "A wrestling god" However, I am a fan of his. Are there people out there that can out-wrestle him? Yes. But you know what else? There's people that can out-wrestle those people, too. And so on and so forth. There's an old expression that goes a little something like: "There is  going to be someone fatser than you,  stronger than you..." etc. etc. etc. No matter what YOU can do. There IS going to be someone better. Do you know why? Because even if it isn't true. Something as simple as an opinion can make it true. And yes, there are guys that will never be heard of that made the business stick around for these other guys. That's just common knowledge. Without (insert name here) there would be no Hogan, Bret Hart, Roddy Piper, Hacksaw Jim Duggan, Rock, Stone Cold, HHH, HBK... Etc. Everybody could make a list out of the "Without who, this person wouldn't have been around" So to single out CM Punk in that is just ridiculous in my opinion. Also: While I'm at it... You're a huge fan of Hogan. But all the things you listed as reasons for not liking Punk? That's Hogan to a "T" Always talking $hit. But that's okay. I'm sure that there is a logical reason to dislike Punk for the same attributes you mentioned.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h3urh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cq26</id></website><link>http://www.wrestlezone.com/editorials/252179-cena-rock-the-final-countdown-ric-flair-interview</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T23:53:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T11:22:53+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m37bh6</id><link>http://www.wrestlezone.com/editorials/252179-cena-rock-the-final-countdown-ric-flair-interview#comment-479419390</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/reocz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>