<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/171065/post/127912773/comment/328705201</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I&amp;#039;m not sure I loved the book as much as you did, but it was certainly thought-provoking! I loved the same characters you did - with Alec being, by far my favorite, with Taylor a close second. And wasn&amp;#039;t Mrs. Pettigrew just the most horrid person?  
 
I did enjoy the humor and the writing, but it wasn&amp;#039;t a &amp;quot;wow&amp;quot; read for me. Dame Lettie&amp;#039;s end was a huge shock! For such a humorous, little book - that was dark and unexpected. 
 
1.  That was the most interesting thing to me - and I think you&amp;#039;re right that the author was showing how each character thought of death in their own way. I found it interesting that only two of the characters (Mortimer and Taylor) were willing to pursue the thought that the voice was death itself - and they both seemed to have come to a healthy understanding of their own impending demise. 
 
2. Olive was an odd character. I thought it was hilarious how, at Godfrey&amp;#039;s age, simply a glimpse of stocking and garter was enough to get him going. :) I think in some ways, she represented the youth they were all trying to hold onto - especially for the older man she married. 
 
3. I also have a complicated relationship with thoughts of my own death. On the one hand, as a Christian, I don&amp;#039;t worry about what will happen to ME after death. But as a wife and a mother, the thought of dying young and leaving my husband and children behind is terrifying to me - to the point that I have often struggled with real panic and Anxiety any time I have a health issue. I also think that in the church grief is often belittled or minimized. It is too easy to murmur platitudes like, &amp;quot;She&amp;#039;s in a better place,&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;You will see him again&amp;quot; and then forget that the person is suffering from very real, heart-breaking, often debilitating grief over their loss right NOW. 
 
Thanks for hosting, Amy - while I didn&amp;#039;t love the book, I am definitely Glad for having read it, and look forward to our next discussion.  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:171065:127912773</id><idPostId>127912773</idPostId><idBlogId>171065</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:171065</id><idBlogId>171065</idBlogId><link>http://www.myfriendamysblog.com</link><displayName>My Friend Amy</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.myfriendamysblog.com/2012/03/faith-and-fiction-round-table.html</link><displayName>Faith and Fiction Round Table Discussion of Memento Mori by Muriel Spark</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T19:06:54.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:171065:127912773:328705201</id><link>http://www.myfriendamysblog.com/2012/03/faith-and-fiction-round-table.html#IDComment328705201</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T19:06:54.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Faith and Fiction Round Table Discussion of Memento Mori by Muriel Spark by booksandmoviescarriek</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://intensedebate.com/profiles/booksandmoviescarriek</link><idEmailMd5>07d5cfe05230f458757c2c12a91c408f</idEmailMd5><displayName>booksandmoviescarriek</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://intensedebate.com/profiles/booksandmoviescarriek"&gt;booksandmoviescarriek&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.myfriendamysblog.com/2012/03/faith-and-fiction-round-table.html"&gt;Faith and Fiction Round Table Discussion of Memento Mori by Muriel Spark&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>