<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw3okr/post/2012-03-31T12:02:15</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>BHO will go down as one of the worst presidents in history.  Though not entirely his fault we as a nation are no longer respected.  He is known as weak,  peace is Gained through strength as witnessed through the Cold war.  (Thanks to our military and SAC)  In his and liberal Utopian view there is no need for the military much less wars.  That is not a reality.  Even Penetta, his man, states the proposed cuts to the military put us at risk.  A recent poll showed most Americans do not want our nuclear stock pile reduced at this time.  Give me a little time and after the election I can be more flexible.  Where is the media on this?  Is he going to give the entire country away?  The Christian Science Monitor now reports somebody at an upper level in his administration has leaked vital security information about Israel.  Hello media, do your job and expose this treasonous person.  Could it be be BHO doesn't want Israel to protect itself and just before the election he will send our depleted military in for political reasons?  

As for drilling, actions speak louder than words,  the rig count in the Gulf is down, only 4 deep water permits have been issued.  Production and permits on federal lands is down.  Yes  I follow oil production.  BHO tells lies, I am for all of the above....Wrong.  The denial of the Keystone pipeline proves it.  Then when he could not stop the southern leg he was all for it.  'I need to study it', liar, 2 govt studies were done, one by his EPA and found it to be safe.  'We have 3% of reserves.'  Another lie, we have more oil and gas that is technically recoverable than Saudi Arabia.  We have trillions of cubic feet of clean Burning natural gas so why isn't he getting out of the way?  NG requires no refining. If he had put half the effort into that as he did green we would be well on our way to energy independence.  So you people out there come Nov remember the lies and also remember how he is destroying our HC  system.  Do you still have your same provider?  Did the rates go down as promised?   </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67f0p4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnm1</id></website><link>http://www.mercedsunstar.com/2012/03/31/2290875/barbara-ovalle-change-is-needed.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T09:21:35+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T16:02:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw3okr</id><link>http://www.mercedsunstar.com/2012/03/31/2290875/barbara-ovalle-change-is-needed.html#comment-481947239</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/83k4d</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>