<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mbv1y7/update/2012-03-09T18:28:12/a2b1354a9d3a5ab3947267a5aa01053ba7bf04e31871142285ea5ccd9a0ae909</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This is a bad law, remember the federal government's law is above state law, so any "legalization" of MJ is really still illegal and can be ignored by federal law enforcement, however the part of this law that will stick and the feds won't get in the way of is the DUI clause. That would still be left up to the state. So this bill just has too many risks, also MJ stays in the system for a lot longer then other substances specifically alcohol, where if you blow a .12 you can't really say you haven't been drinking for a while, where as if I eat a Cannabis Cookie yesterday and get pulled over today I can still get a DUI. So despite being a patient and totally for legalization, this bill actually does nothing but add another gross and unfair punishment for MJ users

Also 30 seconds on one leg? What kind of BS is that? Plus I don't trust police to be a good judge of if someone is stoned, it might smell like weed in the car and then they tell me to do the alphabet backwards on one leg in less then 15 seconds and all the sudden I have a DUI.

I used to bartend and I'd get  at 2am, prime time for police to pull people over for things like suspicion of not wearing a seatbelt, plate lights out, checking for a trash bag etc. With the sole suspicion that the person driving had just left a bar. So one night after working I was driving home and got pulled over because of a Burnt out license plate light, but I know what the officer wanted to nail me with, and he came in and said I smelled like alcohol, which I did because I had bartending for 10 hours that day, however I had the option of taking the breathalyzer and then passed, he still wrote me a ticket for "equipment malfunction" but at least you have the instant chance to prove yourself. There is no option to prove your not stoned, cause most likely one does smoke and that can stay in your system for up to a month in a UA. 

First Off I want to see the study that suggests that driving while high actually impairs your ability to be a safe driver. I have seen one study that says the traffic accidents and infractions have decreased in if not all states that legalized cannabis for medical use. The last thing we should do is pass laws that punish people for something that might not actually be a threat to public safety at all. Just a threat to class consciousness.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/y3231c</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/r3sw</id></website><link>http://www.seattleweekly.com/2012-03-07/news/the-high-road//</link><postedTime>2012-03-05T18:11:42+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-09T23:28:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mbv1y7</id><link>http://www.seattleweekly.com/2012-03-07/news/the-high-road//#comment-460992723</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-05</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>