<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kwzx/post/2012-03-29T23:01:28</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>My wife called the ambulance for me on 02Jan2012 because I was throwing up and passing out.  I have had a history of angina, Chest pains, and other cardiac-related problems.  She thought I might be experiencing a stroke and called the ambulance.  They came and took me to Huntsville Hospital (Alabama).  Fortunately, I was only having a severe migraine - that was the official diagnosis - and they sent me home.  

The bill came for the ambulance...just under $700.00 because they sent an Advanced Life Support (ALS) team - reasonable under the circumstances.  My insurance (Tricare Prime...I am a retired Navy Chief Petty Officer) is refusing to pay the charge because they say I didn't need ALS for a migraine Headache.  I am guessing that my wife should have known I wasn't having a stroke???  I certainly couldn't tell her because I was Vomiting and passing out.  

Now the ambulance company (HEMSI) is ready to send it to collections; I have been on the phone to tricare and the ambulance company several times.  I cannot get either side to budge or to help me get this Resolved.

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zotaf</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t33k</id></website><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/have-you-had-any-medical-bill-nightmares/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:45:56+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T03:01:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kwzx</id><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/have-you-had-any-medical-bill-nightmares/#comment-480181485</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>