<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwj6rn/update/2012-03-31T04:09:34/8426494079eef9cf870dd14ac194ab78e7fcfdcf4089cd5d3767c9b1c80e4650</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>put all the the chimps on a boat and send them to their own island, and see how long that lasts. they are animals and should be treated as such. when i go in a store and see a black (not african american, another Bleeding hearts description of animals) with a hoodie on i don't take my eyes  him, reason being, they are usually the ones committing the crimes. stop Acting and dressing like thugs and maybe you'll be treated with respect. long and short of it is that we build prisons in this country to house blacks, you no why?  shockingly enough, but there who is committing the crimes. the problem here is too many band wagon jumpers, and not enough people to think independently to figure that it is mostly BLACKS who are the criminals. you want a cause to jump on go help some deserving poor kid. but that won't get you on t.v. so why bother. you can't walk into a black neighborhood without the fear of being robbed or worse killed for no reason, but they can stroll through yours. go figure. you don't see the WHITE entertainment channel, but you do see the BLACK entertainment channel. they the BLACKS separate themselves from american society and then cry prejudice go away you pieces of poop. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/672mjn</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/oud0</id></website><link>http://www.delcotimes.com/articles/2012/03/30/opinion/doc4f751ea9028c6110903743.txt</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T09:46:40+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T08:09:34+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwj6rn</id><link>http://www.delcotimes.com/articles/2012/03/30/opinion/doc4f751ea9028c6110903743.txt#comment-481643264</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7bi5</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>