<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwq7pr/post/2012-03-30T18:35:00</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwtiae</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h4dds</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Yes, of course. There is nothing wrong with Islam or the Arabs, or Islam as seen by Arabs. The lack of a single functioning democracy in the Arab world is all the fault of Jews, Zionists and foreign imperialists. Right? Or perhaps there could be something wrong with Islam as practiced by Arabs that does have a negative impact on democratic progress?
As to which Asian countries the Arabs should be emulating.. Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, Singapore and even Malaysia (a majority Muslim country) and Indonesia (another Muslim country).Lebanon is not really a democracy, not a Muslim country in definition or composition (unless you have decided to exclude all the Christians and Druze from politics) and I doubt anyone wants other Arab states to emulate Lebanese history, though clearly some are intent on doing just that. Turkey is having some major issues in dealing with the seeming contradictions between Islam and democracy. One could easily point to the number of journalists in prison to justify that argument. As for the Turkish economy, one can also argue that it is in the process of hitting some rough Spots. Indonesia does seem like a stable democracy. Perhaps it has something to do with a more moderate version of Islam that has yet to take root in the Arab world?It is funny how you have decided to deprive the people of any of Arab countries of any power of actually making positive changes to their societies and governments and instead decided that all power derives from the great powers. It is especially amazing that you could do that given that the  of Western colonialism ended more than 60 years ago. Even more amazing that you can continue this argument when presented with obvious cases where states and peoples have actually managed to build for themselves flourishing democratic states out of impoverished hellholes. People living in this Era have no right to your opinion - one that deprives the vast majority of the world of agency over their own futures by blaming some invisible conspiracy that is determined to prevent their advancement. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67mzua</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/h8a5</id></website><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2012/03/201232710543250236.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:49:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T22:35:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwq7pr</id><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2012/03/201232710543250236.html#comment-481277135</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/d11ak</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>