<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3y6lu/update/2012-03-29T01:35:25/ed28e1c61d879c29b8c49dc7f57caf5cf6e388dd336b870c8d0167ee5df1249e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>

“Research affirms that there is in fact a kind of hole in
the addict’s soul”


No, clearly research has never affirmed anything about a
soul, nor about God, nor Satan, nor Unicorns. This absurdity seems to set the
tone for the remainder of this piece. 


 


“ . . . attendance at ritualized 12-step
meetings offers communion with like-minded folk and a safe haven from Anxiety
and loneliness.” 


That sounds like a wonderful thing that would
appeal to almost anyone. Who wouldn’t want to stop being anxious and lonely?  And for free, without having to pay for
treatment of any kind!  But how to
explain, then, that almost everyone who tries the meetings stops coming?


 


“ . . . relieving 12-steppers’ of their narcissism and other
personality flaws.”


Wow, who knew that the 12 steps could be effective in treating
personality disorders, the most refractory of mental health disorders? The
referrals are going to start streaming in. Seriously, though, could you cite
just one study to support that claim? Otherwise, I fear that some readers may
begin to suspect that you are fabricating. 


 


“The 12-step approach to spirituality long
ago proved its benefits . . .”


No, as a matter of fact, there is no
scientific evidence to establish that the 12-Step approach to anything has
benefits for addictive or other problem behaviors. 


 


“What’s new is that science is backing spirituality as a
recovery tool—and not just the 12-step version . . .” 


Could you cite just one randomized, controlled study that supports the claim that “the
12-Step version” is effective compared to control groups as a recovery tool in
treating addiction or any other problem?


 


“Florida State University research by
Nathanial Lambert and Frank Fincham recently found that people in recovery who
pray more drink less—even if they’re not praying in order to stop drinking . .
. “


Depending on how the study was designed, that
could mean absolutely nothing, or just about anything: for example that
individuals highly motivated to stop drinking are also motivated to engage in
practices (like prayer) suggested to them to help with sobriety; that
individuals who attend church (and pray) are more likely to be affluent, have
resources and stability that reduce stress; that individuals who are more
involved in organized religion are more likely to dishonestly report levels of
alcohol use, etc., etc. 


 


“Surrendering to a Higher Power (HP) is, in the 12-step
model, essential to recovery. And there is growing scientific support for this
belief: Ken Pargament at Ohio’s Bowling Green State University showed that
chanting mantras like “God is great” (or “Mother Earth is great” for the
humanists) lets people keep their hands in ice water for twice as long as
mantras like “Life is good” or “I am happy.”


It proves the opposite – that by the self-determined behavioral
choice of focusing on chanting, an individual can consciously distract from
discomfort, affirming his or her powerfulness, not powerlessness. A more
interesting test of the 12-Step model would have been to have subjects chant, “I
am powerless” or “Only God can help me”. 


 


“But psychologists and psychiatrists are more
relaxed about what qualifies as spiritual, whether in the minds of addicts or
others. They say it can range from conventionally religious activities to art
appreciation, long outdoor walks, cooking, rewarding time with family and
friends or even simple peace and quiet. The ability to soothe oneself comes in
almost as many names as forms: call it a holding environment, emotional
R&amp;R, mental hygiene, self-care.”


That’s right, none of which has anything to
do with the odd and countertherapeutic precepts of the 12 Steps. 


 “Lambert and Fincham,
in Florida, were surprised to learn that their praying subjects’ private
murmurings, while directed at loved ones, made them drink less . . .”


No reason for surprise. As Marlatt’s research supports,
meditative activities, which are physiologically calming, enhance positive
thoughts and connections to a social world, and improve mood, would be expected
to have recovery value. 


 


Bottom line – there has long been support for the ideas that
positive connections to others in thought or deeds  and relaxation techniques such as meditation
have positive effects in recovery. If those positive factors had any
relationship to the odd religious beliefs and practices embodied in the 12
Steps, then we would expect different results than 90 to 95% failure rates. 


</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hio7g</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/74jr</id></website><link>http://www.thefix.com/node/2440</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T21:26:31+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T05:35:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3y6lu</id><link>http://www.thefix.com/node/2440#comment-479123879</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>