<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34u0e/post/2012-03-29T11:08:34</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>What does critical race theory have to do with it?

I will show you:

Young black male is shot and killed.  There is NO overt evidence of race being THE reason he was shot.  Marches, protests, robbing Walgreens, Jesse and Al, Bobby Rush wearing a hoodie in Congress, Miami Heat wearing hoodies, Multiple Black Congresswomen blowing their "i hate whitey' whistles, Spike Lee tweeting the WRONG address so the shooter can be accosted, Black Panthers issuing Bounty,  President Obama posthumously adopting the black victim....etc......

Young white male beaten and set on fire in front of his home by two black males.  Young white male told he deserved it BECAUSE HE WAS WHITE.

Crickets from Congress.  Crickets from the media.  Crickets from the racist President.

There you have it.

CRT in practice for the world to see.

So, go ahead Black America.  Keep beating your 'I hate whitey drums'.  Pretend that Trayvon Martin being shot is the reason 75% of Black males don't stick around to raise their kids.  Pretend that Trayvon Martin being shot is why all those kids that are born to poor single mothers prevent escape from generational poverty.

Keep pretending that robbing a Walgreen's or supporting the Black Panthers will lead to young black adults making good decisions about having children and getting an education.

And we will keep pretending that as the Latino population and Asian population explode in America anyone will care at all about Blacks in 25 years.   

The Black Community within America will become a mirror of N. Korea within the global community.

The rest of us will just throw you some scraps in return for keeping your failed ideology and convoluted values away from the rest of us.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zzrti</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ju4p</id></website><link>http://www.breitbart.com/Big-Government/2012/03/29/Critical-Race-Theory-and-the-Trayvon-Martin-Case</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:03:56+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:08:34+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34u0e</id><link>http://www.breitbart.com/Big-Government/2012/03/29/Critical-Race-Theory-and-the-Trayvon-Martin-Case#comment-479561442</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hpw3w</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>