<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwgyrr/update/2012-03-30T06:55:55/dcdc1312008e886713bd96326122d50456b11e6c335d6dd9e42eecc77f5d9256</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>To Rivens, I know you are a Heat fan, and I am also rooting for them to win since I am a Great Lebron fan but I think they will have a hard time beating Oklahoma. Lebron, Bosh and Wade do not complement each other very well and in fact negates one another's effectiveness. I think Bosh should be a part of the second team so should be coming  the bench since Lebron and Wade nullifies his effectiveness by being such high volume shooters. 

Oklahoma on the other hand, is the opposite, they complement one another relatively better with Westbrook and Durant scoring 30+ on a frequent basis. Besides Haden the third leading scorer,comes Off the bench and is a great component of the second team. Ubaka, the center, leads the team in blocks so there is more division of labor compared to the Heat. Anyways I can't wait to see the finals. Home court advantage will certainly come handy if they meet in the finals. Meanwhile the Heat should find a way of getting Bosh more integrated into the team because he certainly is bring under utilized.  

Sorry guys, there isn't much going on football wise so had to comment on basketball</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ziuve</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dd6r</id></website><link>http://brazil.worldcupblog.org/world-cup-2010/the-greatest-brazil-goal-of-all-time.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T04:55:56+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T10:55:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwgyrr</id><link>http://brazil.worldcupblog.org/world-cup-2010/the-greatest-brazil-goal-of-all-time.html#comment-480615527</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cztn8</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>