<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/323728/post/127795657/comment/327533737</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Interesting writeup, though in the time that I&amp;#039;ve been watching Red Eye (about 4 years or so now) I&amp;#039;ve drifted from the right to more of the center (and maybe a bit left of it). In any case, I wouldn&amp;#039;t attribute that to the show, and I&amp;#039;d be wary of anyone being swayed politically by a show that airs at 3am.&#13; 
&#13; 
The main issue I have with the show now is its guests.  Some guests (Marc Lamont Hill, Nick Gillespie, SE Cupp, among others) are informative and entertaining. Others, such as Coulter, Angela McGlowan, and half the people in the leg chair are almost insufferable to watch. I understand and accept that the show will lean right, but at least get some competent panelists (I exclude comedians, because they&amp;#039;re primarily there to tell jokes, not offer insightful commentary).&#13; 
&#13; 
Also, I&amp;#039;m a bit disappointed that it seems like Jim Norton and Kevin Godlington no longer appear on the show.&#13; 
&#13; 
Anyhow, it&amp;#039;s usually an enjoyable show, with a dull episode here or there. Gutfeld&amp;#039;s Gregalogues can sometimes be ridiculous, but if you accept that he&amp;#039;s putting on a bit of an Act, they&amp;#039;re much better. Andy is the best part of the show (it sometimes seems like he&amp;#039;s wondering why he&amp;#039;s even on the show), and pairs well with Gutfeld. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:323728:127795657</id><idPostId>127795657</idPostId><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:323728</id><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><link>http://www.chrisisright.net</link><displayName>Chris Is RIGHT</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/02/03/an-open-letter-to-fox-news-regarding-red-eye/</link><displayName>An Open Letter to Fox News Regarding \"Red Eye\"</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-02-03T17:27:17.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:323728:127795657:327533737</id><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/02/03/an-open-letter-to-fox-news-regarding-red-eye/#IDComment327533737</link><postedTime>2011-02-03T17:27:17.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on An Open Letter to Fox News Regarding \"Red Eye\" by Chris</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>a741eee041b79ca321dd0c05c1efd29a</idEmailMd5><displayName>Chris</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>Chris commented on &lt;a href="http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/02/03/an-open-letter-to-fox-news-regarding-red-eye/"&gt;An Open Letter to Fox News Regarding \"Red Eye\"&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2011-02-03</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>