<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwhe15/post/2012-03-30T13:32:09</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3vr2u</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>You're young and that's good.  I think you will heal quickly.  It's hard for me to comment on whether or not being on your feet all day with your job will be hard over time.  It will be initially but I tend to think you'll heal quicker than I did.  I'm lucky as I'm a software engineer who slouches in a chair all day.  In your position you're forced to move in all different directions so you'll put extra emphasis on those minor muscle groups in the lower back.  Those will hurt initially but become stronger.

My experience is this.  Before surgery I had "trained" myself to bend in VERY weird ways that would alleviate any pain when doing various things.  For example, to pick up something Off the ground I used to stretch my right leg out and then bend sideways outside my left knee.  The humpty dance.  I never realized I made all these weird motions until post surgery after I've healed.  I can now bend straight down and pick something up like a normal movement.  This was very hard at first because those "normal" movements involved muscle groups I was never really using.  It took me a while to build those back up.  That healing was normal muscle pain and fatigue.  NOT unmanageable Nerve pain.

So back to your situation.  I think if you focus on posture, don't move at a super fast pace, be conscious of your movements... you'll be just find in your career.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/geenj7</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/m4ub</id></website><link>http://insanum.com/blog/spinal-fusion.html</link><postedTime>2011-05-24T18:30:53+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:32:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwhe15</id><link>http://insanum.com/blog/spinal-fusion.html#comment-480985348</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/afhbf</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-05-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>