<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5n6qw2/update/2011-08-03T05:36:08/3c8210150d6e62e8fd884dc8e05623bbc5f2d70d71580a8cdedc297d0f6b9ac6</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>No, ladies, it's not 'natural' or 'inevitable' for women to tear one another to pieces.

It's a type of behaviour that is *taught* to girls and women by boys and men, who are intimidated by us - one woman is scary enough but the idea that we might form bonds that don't include *them* sends a Cold Shiver up many men's spines ("If women get together, theyll eventually take over and castrate us"). 

Women must therefore be made to compete with one another, with male attention as the 'prize.' Sadly many straight women - I'm looking at you, utera - buy into the game, thinking it makes them 'special' if they win. Little do they realize that the men whose attention they Gain probably despise *them* as much as the 'sluts' they themselves denigrate.

I was called a 'slut' at school because I'm a lesbian (yes, we get called sluts too). I also had my head pushed down a full toilet - I'm 175 cm tall and very fit, so it took a bunch of girls to do this. 

I am a femme who dresses 'sexy' but I do it because *I* feel good, not to attract any brick-with-dangly-bits. I refuse to *compete* with my sisters and will happily disabuse any woman who thinks I am doing so.

And 'communism has never worked'? i could debate you on that - but it's an argument for another forum, perhaps.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/gpcga8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/twef</id></website><link>http://www.thefrisky.com/post/246-girl-talk-why-do-girls-slut-shame-each-other/</link><postedTime>2011-07-06T16:01:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-08-03T09:36:08+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5n6qw2</id><link>http://www.thefrisky.com/post/246-girl-talk-why-do-girls-slut-shame-each-other/#comment-275949432</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g2edi</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-07-06</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>