<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw14mi/post/2012-03-31T00:05:43</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>You had an early exposure to sexuality, I guess. As you know, sex is a 
natural craving for us to have and it comes from God's design. I hope 
you still have your girlfriend to look to for help. Don't ever threaten 
her or be so self-centered as to threaten suicide. 



You need to cool . I suggest that you have all porn blocked on every 
computer and device you have access to, and have your girlfriend receive
 reports on your internet activity. Try to learn to masturbate less 
often, and do it without porn or sexual imagery; if you do, your brain will make the 
disconnect with porn. Yes, it takes some discipline and self-denial, but
 you can do it. Whatever you are viewing during orgasm is what your 
brain is programmed to seek out on its next attempt to have sexual 
satisfaction. By giving your mind and eyes little to no sexual stimuli 
during orgasm, it will stop calling for porn and will be less interested in masturbation. Furthermore, by not using porn, you won't be pouring gasoline on your sex drive, which perpetuates the problem.



If you are 18, you are old enough to be married and further  your
 frustration, but you need to get back to being submitted to God, first and lose the anger. You can't let how others Act keep your from serving God. Seek God about marriage and healing from the Anxiety disorder. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zoz9g</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/eriu</id></website><link>http://www.xxxchurch.com/men/confessions/burned-out.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:42:09+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:05:43+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw14mi</id><link>http://www.xxxchurch.com/men/confessions/burned-out.html#comment-481513530</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>