<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m311fx/update/2012-03-29T16:15:07/1e60cdf5e96f3a8ecb03a60d25b713aa2701a12b4b2abb737d3b4bb78f1b9bba</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I see professional soccer players get bloody noses all the time.  The team doctors stop as much blood as they can, shove cotton up their noses so they can go back on the pitch to play.  You can still see the blood being sopped up by the cotton.  In some cases it seeps through the cotton and they have to go back  the pitch until the Bleeding is under control.  And their shirts  have to be changed because there's blood on them.  And their noses are RARELY broken.

I have broken my nose twice, once on the bridge of my nose.  Both times it Bleed a lot.

I'd love to hear what medical experts have to say on the matter.

In any event, whether it's the nose or the fact that Martin was allegedly on top of him when he was shot, there should be a LOT of blood stains on Zimmerman.  I sure don't see any signs of that in the video.  I sure hope the police took pictures at the scene before they "cleaned him up" that will either refute or support his claim.

Either way, I still don't understand how Zimmerman can claim he was justified in using deadly force, when he was the one who was the aggressor in the first place.  Also, doesn't Martin have that same right to use deadly force if he feels his life was in danger? (rhetorical)

It will be very interesting to see how this plays out in the courts.  At this point, Zimmerman would probably be better Off if he's arrested.  It sure doesn't sound like he's safe on the outside.  Regardless the people making death threats or suggesting violence, are no better than Zimmerman.  At this point, in my mind, the police are the ones they should be plssed at since they STILL  haven't arrested him.
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zcxr4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T06:16:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:15:07+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m311fx</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html#comment-479842329</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dfvm1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>