<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3f2gx/update/2012-03-29T16:29:20/9396a7416529d5080aa71f4693795ba3f02745d7a9b642ae2282196561722218</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ugun</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h92bv</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Have you seen the Cold Case Posse's evidence that Obama's birth certificate, the one he showed the world and proclaimed was his, is a forgery? The earler BC has been shown to be a forgery, too. They're the only documents, Obama himself, has presented to prove his citizenship. Unless he can provide legitmate evidence, there's no evidence he was born in Hawaii. Hillary's campaign had brought up this issue before the S.Res 511. Why wasn't Obama's eligiblity Resolved then? Was it because he was Black? Why didn't McCain and the Republicans demand equal treatment? Because they knew the truth, and were ok with it? Did they run McCain because they knew he couldn't win, because they too wanted Obama to be President? Because the powers that be in the Republican Party want the same things the Socialists that have taken over the Democratic Party want?

Rubio's parents were born in Cuba, they weren't naturalized until after Marco was born in 71, in 75. Neither one of Marco's parents were citizens at the time of his birth, even skeptics of the definition of natural born citizen allow that at least one of the parents has to be a citizen at the time of birth. By the way, Santorum has ignored requests that he provide documentation of his father's naturalization. Santorum's father was not born here, either, and no one has been able to find documentation he was ever naturalized. Santorum may be ignoring those requests, because they don't exist, which means he's not eligible to be President either. Too bad, I was going to vote for him.

 When you put Obama's ineligibilty, together with Rubio's and Santorum's, you have evidence of collusion, of a conspiracy, between both parties, to ignore Art II, Sec 1 of the Constitution, so that they can both run ineligible candidates for the Office of the President, and the media, including Fox News, are playing along.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h0f17</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f7e3</id></website><link>http://mobile.wnd.com/2012/03/mccain-kyl-back-obama-pick-seen-as-slap-at-arpaio/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T02:12:47+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:29:20+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3f2gx</id><link>http://mobile.wnd.com/2012/03/mccain-kyl-back-obama-pick-seen-as-slap-at-arpaio/#comment-479857161</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gj7e</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>