<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw9qts/update/2012-03-31T03:04:41/9011e18419f40aae31d8814f2403c8d6506ff2526ba6f2428993782793655263</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwfphh</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/d8z3</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>"supposedly" - like from what SOURCE, Chuckles? What's the friggin' LINK?

See, the amazing thing about this massive zombie winger problem that's screwed up this country so bad it's operating worse than a banana republic with extra stupid sauce (see below) is this really isn't about US, it's about you rubes &amp; the grifters who run &amp; lead your political party &amp; organizations. You're taking the rest of us down with you, apparently operating under the delusion that's like a 'good thing', but the problem isn't between the wingosphere &amp; the rest, it's between  your lemmings &amp; the grifters leading you by the pipe. They play you, constantly, then you expect the adults to come in &amp; fix the mess, so we shut down the crooked carnival &amp; organize a clean up the best we're able with you fat farts whining &amp; moaning about making sure to keep our - OUR - grubby hands  your friggin' somehow non-government-run Medicare &amp; Social Assistance, &amp; your magical roadways &amp; bridges &amp; airports that God apparently arranges for intermittently, plus your free cops &amp; perfect teachers to fix up the appalling destruction you've done to the minds of your own kids, &amp; if the crooked carny with the whizbang somehow perfectly safe while being completely unregulated thrill rides &amp; the very. same. grifters. operating out of the exact. same. booths enticing you in with kewpie dolls you never win, aren't there for you &amp; your fat retarded Jebus-blitzed kiddies the very next week, it's all SOCIALISM &amp; a COMMIE PLOT.  

Don't you get it? The grifters don't feed Off the rest of us, they don't con the rest of us, they don't fleece the rest of us - they just con, Bleed &amp; skin YOU, with YOUR consent, YOUR votes, YOUR support. 

All for kewpie dolls you never win.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67nmnr</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tz1k</id></website><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/bill-maher-on-george-zimmerman-tape-is-there-any-doubt-that-he-is-a-big-fcking-liar/</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T03:06:28+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T07:04:41+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw9qts</id><link>http://www.mediaite.com/tv/bill-maher-on-george-zimmerman-tape-is-there-any-doubt-that-he-is-a-big-fcking-liar/#comment-481608500</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7zl7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>