<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/276915/post/114545964/comment/329777096</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>the world more than a good man. Mr. Zhao, a good man in order to be able to find help, these two days is not posted on the Internet, is called the station, after the good man to know to contact him, he is a good token of. Because the good people to send him to high Fever children to the hospital, in order to race against time, Lianchuang five or six red light. Express Reporter Zhu Junjun &amp;#9633; to save the children, well-intentioned drivers with running red lights Mr. Zhao, who lives in Silver Dragon Garden three. At around 9:30 on the evening of 28 December 2011, Mr. Zhao\'s 21 month-old child Fever suddenly to close to 40 &amp;#176; C, and occurrence of syncope. Small husband and wife is scared, and hurried to call 120 for help. However, the 120 operator advised them to, because the child is too small, you should direct a taxi to the hospital or ambulance shuttle back and forth would delay the time. Mr. Zhao and his wife picked up the child to the Blocking of the cell door, but waited a few minutes but not a taxi. Saw the child\'s breathing has become increasingly weak. Mr. Zhao anxious covered in sweat, he saw a car after his hand on the bar, good-hearted people can take them. However, Mr. Zhao series stopped three vehicles, drivers see children so are shook his head and left. At this time,dr dre beats, the fourth car passing by, this is a black car, the driver heard the reason, and immediately let them get on the train, and then went straight to the Children\'s Hospital. the car after the child\'s pulse is very weak, the wife of Mr. Zhao\'s side  the name of the child\'s side to do artificial respiration. Mr. Zhao is at the edge to help attend to speak with the driver, but he could feel the driver to open soon, is also playing a double jump from Young Road, Stone, Guanghua Road, Muxu Yuan Street, Ruijin Road, Jiefang Road Zhujiang Road all the way Off, the Lianchuang at least five or six red lights, less than 20 minutes to the hospital. contact because he got into so much red light, can not let him stick the money, Mr. Zhao took down the license plate number - Su A257T8. Authority to pay for the marketing exposure After treatment, the afternoon of December 30, 2011, the child was discharged. Mr. Zhao is to find the good drivers become a priority. He first called to the traffic station, and then posted online, want to be able to owners, I just want a man to have a certain responsibility and sense of justice! Yesterday morning he took the initiative to call Mr. Zhao, not to return, but told Mr. Zhao Do a big way, so look for him, are things they do, not worthy of praise. this well-intentioned driver called Yan Huai-Dong. Yesterday morning, when the reporter contacted Yan Huai-Dong, he is very surprised, Yan Huai-Dong the Mengcheng people to do the transportation business in Nanjing, also lived in the Silver Dragon Garden. The evening, Yan Huai-dong finish business, home, saw the anxious look of Mr. Zhao, you know needs help, without thinking send them to go to the hospital who do not have a hurry to say, I do such a thing more than once through a few red light, but he refused to say anything to Mr. Zhao money. This makes Mr. Zhao was embarrassed, good people do good things, but also a disadvantage, how do we go? Yesterday, Express reporter Yan Huai-Dong to help reflect the Authority to pay to Nanjing to pay the HKMA leadership made it clear that, not good-hearted people suffer. Mr. Zhao, as long as the good with the day of the child\'s medical history, Yan Huai-Dong to be a certificate, will be able to put a few exposure eliminate. To work after the Express correspondent to the Authority to pay with Zhao and Yan Huai-Dong settle the matter. share: Welcome to the comment I want to comment microblogging Recommend | hot microblogging today (edit: SN017) </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:276915:114545964</id><idPostId>114545964</idPostId><idBlogId>276915</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:276915</id><idBlogId>276915</idBlogId><link>http://www.cinefamily.org</link><displayName>The Cinefamily</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.cinefamily.org/blog/the-last-year-at-marienbad-of-odd-tv-commercials/</link><displayName>The "Last Year At Marienbad" of Strange TV Commercials!</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T06:42:30.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:276915:114545964:329777096</id><link>http://www.cinefamily.org/blog/the-last-year-at-marienbad-of-odd-tv-commercials/#IDComment329777096</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T06:42:30.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The "Last Year At Marienbad" of Strange TV Commercials! by li8386612</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://cheap-beats-drdre.com</link><idEmailMd5>2c54c7ce04af6f3cc627ac355a5f2a88</idEmailMd5><displayName>li8386612</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://cheap-beats-drdre.com"&gt;li8386612&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.cinefamily.org/blog/the-last-year-at-marienbad-of-odd-tv-commercials/"&gt;The "Last Year At Marienbad" of Strange TV Commercials!&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>