<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/206085/post/127585820/comment/328169676</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The video is an obvious attack on a combination of the Asians&amp;rsquo; unfamiliarity with American culture, like football, and their discomfort with speaking the English language. It was funny to hear their accents and stuff, but the inappropriateness probably outweighed the humor. I&amp;rsquo;m sure the Asians did not enjoy being asked multiple questions about a topic that they have no idea on, while having a camera in their face. The intention of the video seemed like it was to put the Asian students in an uncomfortable Spot, and that is why it could be considered offensive. Now would the video be as offensive if the Asian students were replaced with white Russian students? I think the video would be about the same humor to offensiveness ratio. If the Russians were unsure about the topic of football and struggle through answers with an accent, viewers might give the same reaction they gave the Asians&amp;mdash;whether it was a laugh or gasp or whatever. It would be somewhat funny at first, but then the interviewer pushes the limit by leaving the students confused and uncomfortable. I think skin color doesn&amp;rsquo;t play a factor in developing this humor, but rather the unfamiliarity of culture and language. Now if I were in that type of situation where I was in an Asian country and they were interviewing me and attacking my lack of knowledge in culture and language, I don&amp;rsquo;t think I would be offended. I think I would find humor in that. That would almost be like having to answer a culture question in a Spanish class and being clueless. I know I personally struggled through speaking Spanish and had the worst accent, and found myself just laughing at myself when I was trying to get out what I wanted to say. Being interviewed like that would definitely be uncomfortable but there&amp;rsquo;s no reason to be offended. I would find comedy in it. I feel like I would have no idea what was going on, but I would try my best. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s just me, but I don&amp;rsquo;t really get offended by anything. Yes an interview like that while I&amp;rsquo;m in another country would make me look dumb, but getting a couple laughs out of it is worth it. But listen, I would understand why someone would get offended over a video like this, but I think we have to lighten up. No one is harmed at all. The people getting interviewed are maybe a little embarrassed, but everyone goes their own way and moves on. Living in a foreign country is obviously tough at times, so I say just laugh it Off. Finding humor in everyday things will make life easy and more fun. That&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;m about&amp;hellip;just having fun with life. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:206085:127585820</id><idPostId>127585820</idPostId><idBlogId>206085</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:206085</id><idBlogId>206085</idBlogId><link>http://www.worldinconversation.org</link><displayName>World In Conversation</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.worldinconversation.org/2012/03/27/voices-from-the-classroom-135/</link><displayName>Voices From The Classroom</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T01:06:38.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:206085:127585820:328169676</id><link>http://www.worldinconversation.org/2012/03/27/voices-from-the-classroom-135/#IDComment328169676</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T01:06:38.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Voices From The Classroom by littlethings4</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://intensedebate.com/people/littlethings4</link><idEmailMd5>5028f761898877d6e029af488f6dc314</idEmailMd5><displayName>littlethings4</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://intensedebate.com/people/littlethings4"&gt;littlethings4&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.worldinconversation.org/2012/03/27/voices-from-the-classroom-135/"&gt;Voices From The Classroom&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>