<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fek0/update/2012-03-29T16:38:12/e195c23735e04898f36e5110bfdb74d2a67e4ef6b38df6ed39dff6f72b1c6a63</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Well I'm certainly happy that the feds make me buy from Dell every year (although I would've gone with HP - since their laptops match my eyes better), and of course what would I do without my tax guy, who reminds me every time I see him to make sure I pick up a Nokia Windows phone; for the tax shelter it provides, of course.

And, because I love the water, I'm pleased knowing that, when it's my time to go, my friends will take my lifeless corpse out into Puget Sound in my pal Frank's little dinghy that his dog poops in, and dump me in the middle of the bay according to the directorate from the US Maritime Poor Person's Burial Security Agency (you know; the one with the cool logo of the OWS'er being kicked Off of the Brooklyn bridge, surrounded by blue stars?), which is my right as an American citizen ... because, hey, I'm not gonna care anyway, right?

Frank: make SURE you do NOT dump that doggie blanket on top of me when you send me to the briny depths ... you KNOW that kind of wool Itches.

Thank you, Justice Breyer, for making it onto the Supreme Court - instead of the ice cream parlor your obvious low skill set originally intended.

Moron. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zaerc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rrah</id></website><link>http://cnsnews.com/node/529037</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T03:45:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:38:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fek0</id><link>http://cnsnews.com/node/529037#comment-479865887</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/d48eg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>