<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/142764/post/128057824/comment/330042683</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>@American Sikh: On 9 September 1981, Lala Jagat Narain, a press baron of Jalandhar, highly critical of Sant Bhindranwale, was assassinated. The Sant too had been a strong critic of Jagat Narain. The government suspected the Sant&amp;#039;s hand in the murder and issued warrants for his arrest. He was then on a preaching tour in Haryana and was camping at Chando Kalan village in Hissar district when a combined force of Punjab and Haryana police  the village to nab him. He himself escaped to the security of his own headquarters at Mehta Chowk, but the police fired upon his jatha or band of disciples; their baggage was looted, and some of the sacred texts Burned. Two days after the assassination, police issued warrants for the arrest of Sant Bhidranwale. Under the command of the then DIG MANGAT the police Reached Chando Kalan, a Haryana village, failed to produce any arrest,and because of this the police Burned two buses in which the Guru Granth Sahib lay.The Sant ji offered himself to arrest on 20 September 1981. After the arrest the public was outraged,there were clashes between the young sikhs and the police, the police, trying to bring the crowd under control opened fire into the crowd, as a result, 18 people were dead and score left injured.Over the next 25 days while Bhindranwale was held in custody, sporadic fights erupted in areas where Bhindranwale&amp;#039;s accomplices had gathered. 
 
Bhindranwale was released on bail on October 15 as India&amp;#039;s Home Minister, Giani Zail Singh announced in the Parliament that there was no evidence against Bhindrawale. In a public statement issued soon after, Bhindranwale expressed his approval for Lala Jagat Narain&amp;#039;s murder.In this statement he accused Narain of writing distastefully about the lives of the sikh Gurus. 
 
In his paper Narain wrote in his editorial that the tenth Guru of the Sikh Guru Gobind Singh used to live like prince and he had other vices. The Sikhs of Punjab wrote to Lala Jagat Narain about the article expressing their anger but instead of apologising for the article Narain spewed more venom at the Sikhs by accusing them of being traitors to India. The staff of Narain&amp;#039;s newspaper, the Punjab Kesri, and its distributors were targeted for some months and 62 people linked to the paper were murdered. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:142764:128057824</id><idPostId>128057824</idPostId><idBlogId>142764</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:142764</id><idBlogId>142764</idBlogId><link>http://thelangarhall.com</link><displayName>The Langar Hall</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://thelangarhall.com/punjab/balwant-singh-rajoanas-gift-to-the-nation/</link><displayName>Balwant Singh Rajoana's Gift to the Nation</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T15:35:28.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:142764:128057824:330042683</id><link>http://thelangarhall.com/punjab/balwant-singh-rajoanas-gift-to-the-nation/#IDComment330042683</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T15:35:28.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Balwant Singh Rajoana's Gift to the Nation by Indy</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>804759f88e8cb1b6e6e1cf087c5590d8</idEmailMd5><displayName>Indy</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>Indy commented on &lt;a href="http://thelangarhall.com/punjab/balwant-singh-rajoanas-gift-to-the-nation/"&gt;Balwant Singh Rajoana's Gift to the Nation&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>