<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3t04z/post/2012-03-29T10:29:09</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Even King Nebuchadnezzar allowed Daniel not to be defiled in Babylon. What does this say about our corrupt government? Why are things blurred right from wrong? 

We know history repeats so this does not surprise me. 

1 Kings 14:24
King James Version (KJV)
 24And there were also sodomites in the land: and they did according to all the abominations of the nations which the LORD cast out before the children of Israel.

You can not serve two masters. I see Christrians being deceived here for the sake of "love" while their freedoms are being attacked just as these poor deceived gay men and women have been deceived. God does not like it when His children are deceived and Satan has already been judged. He doesn't get the victory either. When rights are given responsibilities go out the window. We need responsible leaders who say they will not stand for frivolous behaviors. Throw this out of our media, it's trash.

I am sure as the furnace of this world Heats up theres Always our God in the fire with us. Pray for repentance to all judgmental Christians as well as Gay organizations. HOO is doing Kingdom work with standing by their principles, if they lose money so what? Christians know where the storehouse is.  It won't be long til the writing is on the wall. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h0cyo</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/mx4f</id></website><link>http://www.kentucky.com/2012/03/28/2130257/public-schools-place-hold-on-purchases.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T01:32:01+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:29:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3t04z</id><link>http://www.kentucky.com/2012/03/28/2130257/public-schools-place-hold-on-purchases.html#comment-479529734</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cqjn9</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>