<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkf323/update/2012-03-26T13:01:46/bd72b685294390a6f7806cf310258a0b403acca0695b73dad6e2c3499ef188c0</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkurcs</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Quite a thought provoking issue and discussion.  It is undoubtedly more difficult for the reflective (and ethical) observer to determine which are the voices most to listen to - or interview - during a time of political crisis and transition such as this.  Having lived - though not been a journalist/commentator - in such a situation, I do not presume
to be an expert, but I tentatively put forward my thoughts on the subject.

I can understand the feelings and views of (many) Greeks wanting to ignore the voices of all representatives (and prime beneficiaries) of the previous political and economic system, and see it as part of an
inevitable struggle over what constitutes political legitimacy in the emerging order.  However I think an observer should *Always* be
wary of following participants attempts to exclude/ignore and ask why and whose interests that serves. They should not try second guess which voices are, or will become, legitimate (and powerful) and concentrate on those – this would only confirm their own biases and/or those of powerful forces in the society.

It certainly sounds as if Greece is in the early stages of an interregnum in which the old political system and order is decomposing and it is unclear what will emerge from the debris.  Comparisons with the Velvet Revolutions may be useful, although of course Greece differs significantly in that its current system is already a multi-party democracy. New and changed political parties and individuals - and other institutional and individual voices - will undoubtedly emerge in this situation to represent different interests and articulate different and emergent visions of the future. 

There is a danger in this situation, as ever, that the voices of the powerful - or those quick to Spot an opportunity to pursue a sectional interest (often in conjunction with powerful foreign interests) - will drown out those with less power and little or no voice.  I believe that an ethical observer should therefore also actively seek out the voices and concerns of those who are the most deprived and marginalised,
not just concentrate on those of the loudest and those seeking to grab power.  In this regard I found the discussion about the importance of the extended family, low social capital, and various signs of social breakdown in Greek society sociologically interesting.

I think, difficult as it is, the ideal observer - or set of observers - have a responsibility to try portray the whole range of the situation i.e. ‘the state of the nation’ - how the dominant sections of the old order are trying to defend their interests, how various voices are trying to articulate and create a new order, and the experience of those who both the old and various new voices ignore and often seek to marginalise.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66sl6b</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ref4</id></website><link>http://www.opendemocracy.net/node/65021</link><postedTime>2012-03-24T17:44:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:01:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkf323</id><link>http://www.opendemocracy.net/node/65021#comment-476540529</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/65ah4</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>