<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/28381/post/127761776/comment/327462034</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Send me a credible link, so could read more about your inferences made on c).  
 
a). he intended to kill the teenager in Cold blood and why?  
 
Nobody is inferring that  Zimmerman intended to kill anyone as the impetus intent to his involvement with Trayvon, instead why didn&amp;#039;t he not listen to the police and went on his own accord? Zimmerman killed a human being, got to go home, no charges and no investigation. Something is wrong with that....  
 
Zimmerman may have got scared and shot the black boy. That&amp;#039;s reasonable or logical, but the fighting nonsense is not. Just the fact, he&amp;#039;s using it that defense is immoral and destroys any credibility to his story. Zimmerman made a poor decision by voluntarily risking his life and  senseless Cold blood murder of a defenseless boy. 
 
Zimmerman is liable.  Stupidity is not a excuse! 
 
b). he followed Trayvon onto private property and confronted him, resulting in him shooting him. 
 
Zimmerman followed the boy on his own accord, nobody ordered or told him do that, not law enforcement. Gated community or private property is Martin father&amp;#039;s fiance&amp;#039;s home too. 
 
c) c). he followed Trayvon while on the phone to the police and did not confront him and Trayvon confronted him while &amp;quot;walking back to his truck&amp;quot; as some have said. What happened next has still so many rabbit trails that may determine if Zimmerman committed manslaughter or if he was &amp;quot;defending&amp;quot; himself despite the fact that he put himself into the situation.  
 
Zimmerman&amp;#039;s claims are rubbish. Martin&amp;#039;s hands had no indications of a such fight ever occurred. Zimmerman is lying about the fight.. 
 
  &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trayvon_Martin" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trayvon_Martin&lt;/a&gt; 
 
Zimmerman&amp;#039;s account of events 
Zimmerman told police that he followed Martin, but lost track of him. Zimmerman claims he was returning to his car when Martin confronted him and asked &amp;quot;Do you have a problem?&amp;quot; He says he replied &amp;quot;No&amp;quot;, and Reached for his cell phone. Zimmerman says Martin then punched him in the face, knocking him down, and began beating his head against the ground. Zimmerman claims he called out for help while being beaten, before shooting Martin in self-defense.[80][81] 
Zimmerman&amp;#039;s account of the event was called into question when ABC News obtained a video of Zimmerman being escorted into the Sanford police station after the shooting, apparently lacking the reported injuries to his face and back of his head. His face and head are cleanly shaven, so there was no hair to impede the view of any bruises if such bruises had actually existed.[61] The Daily Caller disputed this claim, and posted a still from the ABC video which it said shows what may be an injury on the back of Zimmerman&amp;#039;s head.[82] 
 
Once this is disproved and then Zimmerman will be spending his life in a jail cell.  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:28381:127761776</id><idPostId>127761776</idPostId><idBlogId>28381</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:28381</id><idBlogId>28381</idBlogId><link>http://www.komonews.com</link><displayName>KOMO - Seattle, WA</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.komonews.com/news/national/-Trayvon-Martins-parents-seize-on-video-of-shooter-144941875.html</link><displayName>Trayvon Martin\'s parents seize on video of shooter | National &amp; World News | Seattle News, Weather,</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:25:31.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:28381:127761776:327462034</id><inReplyTo><link>http://www.komonews.com/news/national/-Trayvon-Martins-parents-seize-on-video-of-shooter-144941875.html#IDComment327441894</link></inReplyTo><link>http://www.komonews.com/news/national/-Trayvon-Martins-parents-seize-on-video-of-shooter-144941875.html#IDComment327462034</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T00:25:31.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Trayvon Martin\'s parents seize on video of shooter | National &amp; World News | Seattle News, Weather, by SolomonUW</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://intensedebate.com/people/SolomonUW</link><idEmailMd5>38962eb8577a1312883144ec5e75cefb</idEmailMd5><displayName>SolomonUW</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://intensedebate.com/people/SolomonUW"&gt;SolomonUW&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.komonews.com/news/national/-Trayvon-Martins-parents-seize-on-video-of-shooter-144941875.html"&gt;Trayvon Martin\'s parents seize on video of shooter | National &amp; World News | Seattle News, Weather,&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>