<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrw0e/update/2012-03-30T12:36:50/c8a8388e6e242ff4505f05d1d2d1711289bf35cd55e99da6ad258540eef37a07</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The real problem is very ugly - it is that the Cold, hard realities surrounding the 17 black Americans who will be murdered today (and everyday ongoing) are extremely "inconvenient" as they contradict the standard liberal canards about race relations in America. 

If the media were to change, become honest, shed its ideological blinders and then do their job they would openly and honestly report on those murders and the disturbing fact that over 90% of those 17 murders are committed by other black Americans. 

The newly honest media would demonstrate its new integrity by practicing actual journalism as their for-bearers did to determine the *actual* root problems (instead of just parroting the (yawn) standard PC ideological excuses) that drive such an horrific homicide rate.

It would then be crystal clear that black people kill each other in frighteningly large numbers not because of white racism, but because of liberal government policies and political duplicity that they are told are "for their own good" but actually are coldly designed to  that they will remain vote-slaves to their limo-liberal betters. 

When enough black people and other good people of all races throw  the chains of the poisonous progressive-liberalism that keeps them as no more than government-dependent slaves, the times and  will change in their favor and we will be a more free, more prosperous nation for their efforts. 

As Jefferson said: "I am not a friend to a very energetic government. It is Always oppressive."</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67ervk</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/jpbk</id></website><link>http://theweek.com/article/index/226273/trayvon-martin-why-do-americans-often-ignore-black-shooting-victims</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:00:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:36:50+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrw0e</id><link>http://theweek.com/article/index/226273/trayvon-martin-why-do-americans-often-ignore-black-shooting-victims#comment-480928722</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/reu</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>