<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kleq/update/2012-03-29T22:20:39/b43fd1a90569febecb0c68803b751cde16d3ff8518ccfdfd22528218224fedb4</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kghw</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yzur</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I am only trying to point out that there is no evidence of a
crime. The shooter is not even required to explain his actions. He need offer no excuse or discuss the events at all. We have people who simply want to convict the shooter like there are teams involved. The simple explanation is likely the right explanation. The man is a community volunteer. He notified the cops and anticipated a squad car would arrive. That is not the action of someone looking to commit murder. The facts are that there was no arrest as there was no evidence of crime.
One of the worst riots in American history was in Brooklyn when
a  cop shot a 14 year old boy who came at him with a switch blade. The public somehow thinks that there will be no response because an offender is young. That is irrational. Another major riot broke out in either Detroit or Chicago back in the late 1960s. A black woman was shot by cops as she threw bottles at them as they walked down a Hall towards her apartment. The cops were there because she was disrupting the entire building and neighbors requested help. Apparently many people thought that cops should retreat or that flying whiskey bottles were not enough of a threat. So a neighborhood was badly Burned.
The point being that you need to use good sense and caution when
you confront others and consider what may happen if they feel that there is danger for them. It might save your life.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zh427</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ant8</id></website><link>http://www.alternet.org/newsandviews/article/873983/police_surveillance_video_shows_no_blood%2C_bruises_on_trayvon_martin%27s_shooter%2C_george_zimmerman/comments/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:28:28+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:20:39+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kleq</id><link>http://www.alternet.org/newsandviews/article/873983/police_surveillance_video_shows_no_blood%2C_bruises_on_trayvon_martin%27s_shooter%2C_george_zimmerman/comments/#comment-480152683</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z9e5</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>