<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw1sgt/post/2012-03-31T00:32:55</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I'd give all the trolls 5 bucks to stay Off the blog for a week.  The loons get 6 bucks.  The Donald would get 10 bucks if he could be on the show and not mention China.  I would give Obama a million to go back to Kenya.  I would offer to pay for Biden's brain surgery, Harry Reid's life time meds for his senility, and a new face lift for Pelosi.  I would throw Barney Frank a retirement party.  He could invite 3 friends over for a movie and pizza, and no teddy bear PJ's.  I would buy MO a membership in a fitness club.  I would add a statue of George Washington the the grounds by the monument, with him holding out a hand with two fingers pointing to the capitol,, and a plaque that says, "I'm watching you!" I would buy Media Matters and the Huff, and Burn them to the ground.  I would fly 1,000 Jews out of Russia to Israel, and send a million bucks to feed the starving Ethiopian Jews.  I would offer all the folks who don't like America a free ticket one way to wherever they want to go.  I would give Newt a contribution so he could run hard and beat Mitt at his own game. I would pay Geitner's taxes and throw him in jail, and hire a private investigater to get to the bottom of Fast and Furious, and thorw Holder in jail, too.  Then, a chrome muzzle for Al Sharpton and Jesse Jackson.  If I have any money left, I'm going to Israel for 6 months.  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67qnbs</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t33k</id></website><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/what-would-you-do-with-a-winning-lottery-ticket/</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T02:29:50+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:32:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw1sgt</id><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/what-would-you-do-with-a-winning-lottery-ticket/#comment-481531589</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/eyzhw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>