<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3jqzz/update/2012-03-29T18:34:51/d5791d0d6daa126edcd069538e261fdf48483d461bf23245b6913d748622c781</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>





I can appreciate your dilemma of having both feet in two camps
by addressing the considerations of two constituents. However, may I raise a different
perspective that is not being stated here? I, too, have served on selection panels
for candidates seeking positions and understand the Anxiety candidates can have
for operating in the dark; not knowing where they stand or unable to plan for
future engagements. 

 

What about the reputation of the  College or University seeking to fill the positions?
The perspective of applicants can be very fragile with many feeling that the institution
is merely going through the motions of appearing that the application process is
a front for a hidden agenda to select a preferred candidate already on campus. These
notions cannot be dismissed because I have personally experienced evidence of this
in my personal search for positions. Again, the reputation of the institution should
be considered to allow all candidates some understanding of the fairness the institution
want so exercise with its selection of the "best" candidate for the job.
Letting all candidates know the progress of the process, the effort being given
to select the best candidate, and to provide notification to candidates as soon
as possible when their candidacy is not being considered may be regretful but often
appreciate by applicants. A well written letter expressing empathy and appreciation
for the candidate taking the time to complete all administrative requirements for
the position will go a long way toward the reputation for an institution. Candidates
will maintain a favorable perspective for such schools as institutions they would
desire to Gain employment.   

</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ztq90</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/l7r5</id></website><link>http://chronicle.com/blogs/onhiring/whats-taking-them-so-long/30731</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:27:21+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:34:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3jqzz</id><link>http://chronicle.com/blogs/onhiring/whats-taking-them-so-long/30731#comment-479975414</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5ovn2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>