<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3trx2/post/2012-03-29T09:44:43</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The Daily Caller..web site..No..SHOWING AN ENLARGED PICTURE OF GEORGE ZIMMERMAN..BEING TAKEN IN..HANDCUFFED BY POLICE.

THE TOP OF HIS HEAD..HAS A WHOPPING BIG WOUND. THE BLOOD HAS BEEN CLEANED .......BUT SOMEONE OR SOME THING..WHACKED HIM GOOD ON HIS HEAD.
HE IS NOT FAT. TREYVON MARTIN WAS NOT SMALL. HE WAS 6'2" AND WEIGHTED 160..POUNDS..NOT 140 POUNDS. THAT IS THE SIZE OF A BIG H.S. FOOTBALL  PLAYER.
GEORGE ZIMMERMAN....IS 5'9 AND NO WAY DID HE WEIGHT 250 AS THE MYTHMAKERS ARE PUTTING OUT. HE DOES NOT LOOK LIKE HE WEIGHED 160 POUNDS.
GO SEE THE VIDEO..NOW..THE DAILY CALLER WEBSITE.

This morning Joe Scarbrough and his motley crew  of race baiters..This proves that Zimmerman is the baddie...Treyvon innocent. All of those people trying to demonize Treyvon are just racists. The  Sanford Police are racist and  have been. I mean he was on a rant.
HE WAS.......IS.......A CONSERVATIVE?

NONE OF THE RACE BAITERS HAVE EVER MENTIONED THE WHITE KID IN KANSAS CITY..WHO WAS CHASED TO HIS PORCH..WHILE WALKING HOME FROM SCHOOL..BY TWO BLACK TEENS. THEY THREW A CAN OF GASOLINE ON HIM...SET HIM ON FIRE..AND THEN DANCED AROUND AND CHANTED :GOT WHAT YOU DESERVE WHITE BOY"
THEY HAVE NEVER BEEN ARRESTED. THEY ARE FREE TODAY. THE MOTHER WHO WITNESSED THE BARBARIC HORRIBLE ACT..SAID HER SON'S FACE EXPLODED. HE HAS THIRD DEGREE BURNS.
CHARGED WITH A HATE CRIME? THEY ARE CHARGED WITH NOTHING BECASUE TO DO SO WOULD STIR UP RACE UNREST. THEY MAY CHARGE THEM..AS MANY WITNESSES SAW THE HORROR..BUT NO HATE CRIME.

AND JOE SCARBROUGH IS RAVING ABOUT IF TREVYON WAS A WHITE KID..THE POLICE WOULD BE ALL OVER HE.
HE MAKES ME WANT TO PUKE. THERE IS NOT ENOUGH MONEY IN THE WORLD TO MAKE ME SIT UP THERE WITH PEOPLE..WHO PAY NO ATTENTION TO BLACK ON BLACK CRIME..WHICH IS STUPENDOUS OR BLACK ON WHITE CRIME..WHICH IS MIND BOGGLING...BUT USE THIS INCIDENT FOR POLITICAL AND MONETARY REASONS.

JOE SCARBROGH..REALLY IS AL SHARPTON'S BROTHER. ENJOY.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hhjvh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f047</id></website><link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/218677-rep-waters-stiff-evidence-death-of-trayvon-martin-a-hate-crime-</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T13:38:02+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:44:43+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3trx2</id><link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/218677-rep-waters-stiff-evidence-death-of-trayvon-martin-a-hate-crime-#comment-479498724</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>