<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mqi5qn/update/2012-03-05T00:25:09/82c7f762aaeb0a8827a067d6849af00e2bf1ba806822291ab6f9dfb3a7a4c481</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>


One sided article
as usual... In India, you cannot look at the Hindu Muslim riots in isolation...
It has a long historical background with Muslims treating this land as
Dar-Ul-Harb and their supposed duty to convert the land of Kafirs to
Dar-Ul-Islam through either conversions or killings... Hindus have suffered a
great deal of ordeal at the hands of fanatic Muslim kings and their zealots
over centuries...



It was
thought that in independent India, there will be equality of sorts among all
the religions... but the subsequent congress governments have adopted the
policy of appeasement towards Muslims... The Muslim religious leaders and
politicians of India have  that the Muslim masses remain illiterate,
economically backward and in tight grip of the fanatic clergies, mullahs and
madarssas...



Muslims have
at every possible opportunity have incited separatism; have asked to themselves
to be carved out culturally from the people they live with... This is not
happening in India alone... This has happened every place where Muslims were
allowed to live in liberal state... be it US or UK, be it Serbia and Yugoslavia,
be it old Russia and recently in China...



It is so
hypocritical to think Hindus as intolerant whenever they have retaliated to the
Muslim aggravation in independent India... In fact, the intolerance of Hindus has
emboldened Muslims to keep doing the Acts of aggravations...



Why does no
body talk about the reason why the riots started in first place? Should that
Burning of Sabarmati coach had not happened, do you think these riots would
have started at all?



So when
Hindus retaliated that aggression it is religious hatred, intolerance and
genocide...



But when US
bombs Afghanistan because Muslim terrorists killed 3000 US citizens, it is a
ware for justice...!!



This is hypocrisy...
Unfortunately, with our people disunited, our leaders corrupt and opportunists
and our Muslim brother in the iron grip of Mullahs and Maulavis, it is
difficult to defend such nasty articles...


</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yoiphv</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/v052</id></website><link>http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2012-02-28/politician-rises-from-ashes-of-india-s-anti-muslim-violence-choudhury.html</link><postedTime>2012-02-28T20:19:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-05T05:25:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mqi5qn</id><link>http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2012-02-28/politician-rises-from-ashes-of-india-s-anti-muslim-violence-choudhury.html#comment-456581504</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hob1b</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>