<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mil51x/update/2012-03-23T00:53:49/6b36ffad6e955ebd3662370d2c1cbea7d4e3057246aeb83b8ce30f11d5e13e84</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>My mom was a hoarder, she just passed away Feb. 3 2012.  I have tried so hard through the years to help her, but to no avail. when she passed she left me with a physical and financial mess. I miss her, but at least she doesn't have to live like that anymore. I cleaned up after her for years, only to receive her anger at trash and junk being thrown out.  We helped her move 5 times total, cleaning up 3 different apartments to keep her from getting evicted or when she would finally get evicted. her last apartment, we filled up 2 u-haul trucks FULL of trash. when she passed she was living in a house, which is in forclosure due to non-payment. she was not good at managing money due to spending it on buying all her stuff. the house is full of trash, purchased items(some still in boxes or wrappings unopened), food items, etc. I will  have issues as far as the doorbell dread, cleaning my house and so on. no matter how much i clean, my house is never clean enough for me, and i Always have Anxiety about having people over, even family. i had even gone to counseling with my mom, hoping ot would help somehow, but i gave up after several sessions, as she was determined not to even attempt to make small positive changes. she lived with my family and i for about 8 months before getting her house(after getting evicted from her last apartment), and it was the worst time of my life. My doctor told me if she stayed with me much longer i was going to have a stroke or heart attack. my blood pressure was high, i was having Anxiety attacks up to the point of passing out in the floor several times. i was also giving her Anxiety attacks by threatening to clean her bedroom. hoarding affects the entire family, not just the hoarder. it has also affected my kids as the result of seeing her live the way she did. i believe if she was not a hoarder, she might possibly still be alive, as she died form bacterial and fungal pneumonia and had skin and sinus infections. she had autoimmune disease that affected her lungs, and they could no longer take the daily assault of the bacteria and fungus from her environment. i have read books, articles and watched tv programs about hoarding, but i will never fully understand. all i can do now is do the best i can to clean up the mess and try to remember the positive times.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/58ibl8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zi39</id></website><link>http://childrenofhoarders.com/wordpress/?page_id=547</link><postedTime>2011-03-06T07:41:52+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T04:53:49+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mil51x</id><link>http://childrenofhoarders.com/wordpress/?page_id=547#comment-474217653</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-03-06</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>