<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3mjvj/update/2012-03-28T23:29:15/1cdbd6b218d84dcc35f7bd2d876470305ddb5b7f2da8f4fb1ccc6ec172cb6a81</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I don't care if you call it GLOBAL WARMING, CLIMATE CHANGE, or Al Gore's Flatulence.  With the exception of Al Gore's Flatulence, it does not exist.  I am not a meteorologist, but I did serve five years of active duty in the weather field.  That does not qualify me as an expert, but it puts me years ahead of Al Gore.

I have heard many statements from Al (I invented the Internet) Gore and supporters, making some very interesting claims.  Man has been practicing metallurgy, controlled Burning and even Burning cities for close to 5000 years now.  Let's give them the benefit of the doubt and say that weapons were produced on a massive scale since the time that Jesus walked the Earth.  That's 2000 years, give, or take a few.  Some of the global warming estimates state that the average temperature has gone up one degree every ten years.  That doesn't sound like much until you think about it.

Let's see.... One degree every ten years for 2000 years.  2000 divided by ten.  There is is!  The average temperature has risen 200 degrees since Herod was King of the Jews.   At that rate, every drop of water would have boiled  the planet and our good planet Earth would look like Venus, surrounded by clouds.

How could that be?  Did we have some global cooling, too?  Of course we did.  Anyone that follows the path of the jet streams knows that fluctuations do occur, but that they are generally minor.  The article does mention that we have proof of this having occurred in the past.  We can, and have, taken 500 years of ice core samples in the Arctic and Antartica.  There are variations.  That's why we have averages and statistics.

There is one factor that man is responsible for.   Agenda 21 may solve that problem, though.   What is the problem?   It is human beings.   We have more of them on the earth than we have ever had before.  Human beings take in oxygen and emit carbon dioxide.   Not as much as Al Gore's house, or the airplanes headed for another Obama vacation, but the amount of carbon dioxide is significant and probably responsible for the less than one degree, Celsius, average temperature increase.  It will take men far better educated than I to prognosticate any permanent change beyond the fluctuations that I have already mentioned.

Until we can get a new resident of the White House and begin some serious economic recovery, we will just have to live with the CO2 that the older coal plants are responsible for.  We can compensate by removing the electricity to Al Gore's house (possibly the largest carbon footprint on the planet) and letting the Obama family vacation by bus, instead of by Air Force One.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lkphh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry2d</id></website><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50485</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T20:46:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T03:29:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3mjvj</id><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=50485#comment-479052747</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ycvzx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>