<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tt0r/post/2012-03-29T09:56:56</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>If the Supreme Court takes the individual mandate Off the table, we are not left with single payer as the only "solution," Ezra.  Expanding existing entitlements to everyone only bankrupts us faster.

The other alternative that no one is willing to talk about because it sounds Cold and heartless is that if you cannot afford health care, you should not receive health care.  If you are unable to pay for X, why should someone be compelled to provide X to you free of charge?  That may appear compassionate to the one receiving the service, but is it not simultaneously an injustice to the one providing the service?  And is it truly compassion?  Does it not foster dependence and irresponsibility on the recipient and disdain and callousness on the provider?  How is this compassion?  How is it charity?

Certainly America is a compassionate country.  All you have to do is look at our collective response to natural disasters.  People willingly and eagerly give of their time, strength, and money to help those that are in true need worldwide without one ounce of requirement from government.  But what Americans rightfully chafe at is forced compassion.  Compelling an individual to help another ceases being charity and becomes a form of slavery.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zrihy</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/egg0</id></website><link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2012/03/29/klein_if_mandate_is_struck_down_expand_medicare_medicaid_and_schip-comments.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:11:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:56:56+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tt0r</id><link>http://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2012/03/29/klein_if_mandate_is_struck_down_expand_medicare_medicaid_and_schip-comments.html#comment-479507015</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/egyrr</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>