<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkp1j9/post/2012-03-26T16:28:56</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Love the insight Steve!  I have to confess though, I haven't read the book and I probably won't see the movie for a while, but I can still relate to the things you've put in the post.  As a lot of fitness websites seem to play on the theme of success and pushing yourself, it's good to see a post that is all about taking control for yourself and others.  

I find that exact reason is why I won't quit lifting heavy things (like kettlebells and barabells), and it makes me walk through the door every night when I do Martial Arts.  If something happened to my wife or family that I could've changed, I'd be in a real Spot of bother.

Even though we aren't exactly hunters and gatherers, it is still survival of the fittest.  When something unexpected happens and we must Act, and it's the overweight couch potatoes who'll suffer - it's important for us to help them by educating them and pointing them in the right direction, chances are we won't be there!

Anyway, before I ramble on, awesome job man!  I've been really enjoying your outlook on fitness and lifestyle!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lc7jr</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5b4n</id></website><link>http://nerdfitness.com/blog/2012/03/26/the-hunger-games-guide-to-survival/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:59:06+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T20:28:56+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkp1j9</id><link>http://nerdfitness.com/blog/2012/03/26/the-hunger-games-guide-to-survival/#comment-476716454</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>