<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0a8nk/post/2012-03-31T14:59:00</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>                                              mr3tenn                           
                                                                

If the Darwinian theory is the best you atheists can come upwith as something to grasp onto, then it's no wonder you're soreadily misled in your faithlessness. One wonders if some of it is not trulydisbelief, but actual diabolical influence.


You seem to be under the delusion that you made a point. Asto delusions and hallucinations much of Darwin's Origin of theSpecies should be at the top of the unscientific list, but their is no reasonto Burn it. Biochemistry, genetics and the Law of Biogenesis long sinceindicated that Darwinian macro-evolution beyond the species level (genera,families etc.) and involving changes in morphological types as incompatiblewith the scientific method.
--------------------------------------
Evolution through natural selection is not something that atheists "came up with" - it is science. In fact, Evolution is the central pillar of the entire science of Biology.  

Biochemistry, genetics, and the law of Biogenesis in NO WAY invalidate evolution. Genetics in particular is one of the strongest proofs of evolution.  Why for example would man have broken Ape genes in our DNA if we were not related to them?

And I Always get a kick out of Creationists that like globbing on to the term "Marco evolution". Why?  Because they need to use that term to try to differentiate the very obvious, in-your-face proofs of evolution from the greater implications of evolution and how it falsifies their religious fairy tales ... </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/678u06</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6bwl</id></website><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/jesse-watters/2012/03/30/watters-penetrates-atheist-rally-are-you-afraid-youre-going-hell</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T12:05:49+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T18:59:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0a8nk</id><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/jesse-watters/2012/03/30/watters-penetrates-atheist-rally-are-you-afraid-youre-going-hell#comment-482099791</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rgste</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>