<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk1so3/update/2012-03-26T12:00:51/635d70eba1f68d0514421bfb4d32adc990f21d158638fdde3a63ddcc82ce639d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkb30d</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ma5iz</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Competition isn't  a good thing. Matter of fact in the case of schooling, Finland has absolutely no competition in schooling and has ranked in the top 3 for best education in the world for the last decade. The other two being South Korea and Singapore which are obviously nothing but competition/tradition.

Going after hospitals, or more specifically healthcare is a big no for me. The US model is obviously a huge failure, and the European model is much more abused (usually by foreigners) then our own. Given, the bureaucracy needs to take a slash but we need to keep away from private healthcare or we could very easily end up in an American style situation.

Capitalism as it is now is clearly very easy to abuse once you get in the right Spot. Majority of the media are bought , some if not all of the biggest political players are bought , and executives are working hand in hand to Ensure their profits over the masses seemingly blind sacrifice. Despite some potential in it, there has to be an even better system to replace it. If capitalism is the best we got, then we can expect to be locked in pointless wars, price gauging, fraud, and corruption till the day humanity goes extinct.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rn1zv</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7m2w</id></website><link>http://www.winnipegsun.com/2012/03/23/communism-door-closing</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T00:14:02+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T16:00:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk1so3</id><link>http://www.winnipegsun.com/2012/03/23/communism-door-closing#comment-476493585</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/88lgw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>