<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmfnn/update/2012-03-30T09:19:37/5ac3bc0e1474c5e77a3e8f274dce9c7f783ba013e55d3f19844d3d202ab7dcef</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw5b4f</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z5gk2</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Another non-story. Let me introduce you to a concept found in emergency rooms: Triage.

Triage means that if a woman is brought in, in a stretcher, Bleeding heavily and barely conscious, she is treated before a woman sitting in a chair saying she has a pain in the leg. Heck, my son came into a large emergency room with a slowly spreading MRSA and ended up sitting there for two hours because, believe it or not, there are things more imminent. His case was basically labeled "Serious, but not imminent".

"A pain in the leg" could mean anything. There are plenty of people who go to emergency rooms to get treated for a sprained ankle, for instance. "A pain in the leg" at that point means getting a doctor to basically feel it, tell her it's fine, and advise that she takes an aspirin if the pain gets bad and just let it heal. (There isn't a heck of a lot a hospital can do for a sprained ankle.)

I remember bringing my baby girl into the emergency room for a diaper that *looked* like it was black, which could mean internal Bleeding. They checked her vitals immediately, but then they turned us Off into a room and we were left there for well over an hour. Why? Because a motorcycle accident victim had just come in, and they were trying desperately to save his life. It turned out that what we thought was black was merely a very dark green, and our baby had reflux causing Diarrhea. It didn't even require a doctor's visit - of course, I didn't know that at the time - but there you have it.

However, since neither I nor my children are black, I suppose it doesn't matter how long we have to wait. Long Live Racism! Let's all turn Anne Brown into a rallying cry for more violence! Where was the church!? Isn't it their job to go into every hospital and play doctor for every woman who comes in with a pain in her leg, but only if her skin is dark enough?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zk0g9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yv37</id></website><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/2012/03/m-democrats_ignore_real_racism_while_exploiting_trayvon_for_obama_2012.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T06:13:32+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:19:37+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmfnn</id><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/2012/03/m-democrats_ignore_real_racism_while_exploiting_trayvon_for_obama_2012.html#comment-480729908</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zyiec</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>