<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m33pms/update/2012-03-30T01:06:34/73a3a9611b03e4ec0c8e81f502ef03b10c0933655e23af8bd9af0e926bce723a</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3sncr</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Where is the evidence that Carpenter threatened to cut him up. Pak admitted  that he came OUTSIDE the store, angry that Carpenter had banged his gas pump. Pak was not in imminent danger while inside his store. Carpenter says Pak came out, threw his money on the ground, tazered him,maced him and kicked him while another Korean beat him with a baton in broad daylight. The onlookers carried him to the church a block away. Pak called the police, and made allegations of a verbal threat of what Carpenter was GONNA do but no evidence that Pak had been assaulted and the police   Carpenter doesn't even know what hit him, only that he had a black eye and a concussion.
 I have a tape recording of the Korean who assaulted me telling his clerks after I called the police on him, to go home so that when the police arrived he would tell them I broke in the store, Willie Reeves signed a petition in support of Pak and offered to do a video for one of Pak's clerks. Pak later saw Reeves talking to the protesters when he was in fact was video taped telling the protesters that his disabled mother and the blacks in the area needed the store. Pak had him criminally trespassed and ultimately arrested while he was begging Pak to look at the video because he did not want nothing else on his record. Reeves spent 6 days in jail. Brother Jeffery says that Pak got confrontational with him. Two police officicers are witness to this. Pak says Jeffrey called him a racial slur, Pak's clerk who killed a wrongful thief testified that he chased the man across the street and that the man grabbed the gun ( I believe to save his life) and the gun accidently went . sounds like Pak and other oppressors feel empowered by people like Greg Howard who have Always thought a white man's ice was Colder. So I asked the DOJ office of civil rights office to investigate. They are taking calls for other incidents of mistreatment at this store. 
and hopefully they will be able to type our complaints up without typos. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h92kq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rp9i</id></website><link>http://www.dallasobserver.com/2012-03-29/news/showdown-at-the-shamrock//</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T17:56:15+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T05:06:34+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m33pms</id><link>http://www.dallasobserver.com/2012-03-29/news/showdown-at-the-shamrock//#comment-480268076</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>