<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi6fbp/post/2012-03-22T22:25:26</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Traveling Domestically is a Breeze compared to International Travel Jump.

Whether I was Based in LA, NY, San Diego, Tampa or Columbus, Ohio, I  found Domestic Travel a Breeze.  Except for those Cold Winter Frost Delays or Bad Weather Delays when you just wanted to get Home after a Tough Business Road Trip Even if it meant you weren't going get home until 2:30am.  You still wanted to get back home to sleep in your own bed...

Most of those Domestic Trips were 2 to 4 Days at a time, some back to back, some back to back to back.  Still you could work on the Plane, so going was easy.  And Coming Back you could kick back with a Glass of Bubbly or if that was not available due to a flight change and no seats up front and you were in Steerage, a nice couple of glasses of red wine or even a few brewski's  works just as well.

I flew a Lot to Hong Kong and Singapore Air was my Favorite Airline for that.
A Flight from SF Direct to Hong Kong Nonstop was 15 Hours...
I don't care who you are that is going to make you Stir Crazy...
The Flight was so long you had Breakfast, Lunch, Dinner, Breakfast and Lunch Before you landed...  The Service was Impeccable...  And the problem is once you got there you weren't tired and could not sleep due to the Huge Time Change so the Jet Lag took to Mind conditioning to Manage.   I Always found it better to set your watch to the Time of your Destination to condition your body and mind as you board the plane and by the time I landed  I timed my Naps to wear I was adjusted once I got there.

A Typical Trip for me would be win I was an Astronaut would be-
San Diego to Miami
Miami to Costa Rica
Costa Rica to Miami
Miami to Kingston Jamaica
Kingston to Miami
Miami to San Paulo, Brazil,
San Paulo, To Rio de Janiero,
Rio de Janiero to London,
London to in those Days Bombay, India (Today Mumbai)
Bombay to Columbo, Sri Lanka
Sri Lanka to Hong Kong
Hong Kong to Tokyo
Tokyo to to NYC
NYC to San Diego.

That is Around the World.
And I Year I did that 7 Times, Each Trip about 31 Days...

I loved it then, but I would Hate it Now...
But what an Experience in Seeing the World!
Some Great Memories and Lots of Friends made in all of those places...

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yf7kh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/9dd2</id></website><link>http://www.golfchannel.com/news/doug-ferguson/bay-hill-day-1-mid-round-wrap-tiger-three-back/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T19:02:40+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T02:25:26+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi6fbp</id><link>http://www.golfchannel.com/news/doug-ferguson/bay-hill-day-1-mid-round-wrap-tiger-three-back/#comment-474151493</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hanle</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>