<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwhzbq/update/2012-03-30T13:41:55/ac1369dfb9aa6b5dd66139eceb725f726302dc728cd4e60c53f1c7a40cd48cfb</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>We are all upset I almost got kicked out of the house a couple of times last year because of my yelling and screaming.  We have to face reality though Flynn was not the answer and we made the right choice here I think we will see that next season.  It was a present to all of us Dolfans that Fisher wanted no part of the Dolphins he is an egotistical Diva and a proven loser.  I know that the value we got wasn't equal for the player we lost but Marshall did need to go.  A real fan can see the bigger picture here he lost us at least 4 games last year.  He never took the blame he  layed it on the QB and his coaches.  He was a problem child on and  the field good riddance.  The things we should be upset with are the fact that the OL, WR and DL holes have not been addressed in free agency.  I think we should go for Tannehill in the 1st round he will not be there in the second.  Should he not be there we should get Weedon in the 2nd round.  I believe that both of these guys are going to be good QBs and are going to suprise alot of people in the next few years.  Lastly I am Glad the whole Peyton debacle is over.  You know I am sick of hearing about how John Elway was graded so good in 1984 draft.  What  about hearing about how good Dan Marino was and how Mel Kiper under graded him.  Dan did more with less than John ever did.  Put Danny Boy on those Denver teams and he would have won a couple of rings to.  I am not saying that Tannehill is ever going to be Marino but there is something Itching at me telling me that he is the guy we have been waiting so long for.  I still believe we will be better this year and will be in the race for the division crown. I really do think the coaching change is going to make a huge difference for us. I for one am a Phins fan for life win or lose I will still be true Aqua, White, Orange and Blue! Go Dolphins!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6raup1</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yzhx</id></website><link>http://www.miamiherald.com/2012/03/24/2712061/dear-miami-dolphins-we-cant-stand.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-24T23:39:26+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:41:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwhzbq</id><link>http://www.miamiherald.com/2012/03/24/2712061/dear-miami-dolphins-we-cant-stand.html#comment-480995659</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/59p6o</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>