<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/e2hz3c/update/2011-11-15T04:38:55/d495403b85c6bcab63422269f508d9a50e7ab5564589d4bc2422bcddd8b0402d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Since your post is so unbelievably uninteresting, I am going to pull a story out of it's arse, because I have nothing better to do right now.

Once upon a time, there was a lonely pineapple who wore a mask to hide her feelings from the cruel Universe. This pineapple was like an empty coconut, a square box with no pizza inside, an empty Poke-ball, a jar of Nutella with no Nutella in it, and not one person in the Universe cared.

That is, until OP found the pineapple sitting on a bench in a park, all alone, wearing a long-sleeved shirt. OP, being a lovely, caring, special person stared at the pineapple, then realized something: the pineapple was most likely wearing long sleeves because it had something to hide. But wait, the lonely fruit was also wearing a mask! Signs it was silently crying for help. OP ran to the lonely fruit, harshly hugged it, almost crushing it, and cried like there was no tomorrow for s/he felt so sorry for the thingy. Then the human violently ripped  the mask, only to cover his/her mouth with les hands in horror: the pineapple was wearing make-up.

"Oh, society, what have you done?! A pineapple who wears a mask, make-up, and long-sleeves just to hide from you, and please you?! I have lost faith in humanity." OP said, now moving his/her hands to cover the whole face to cry some more.

Enough. OP had enough of humanity. S/he magically pulled out make-up remover and sanitary pads out his/her arse, and harshly removed the evil from the fruit's face, then pulled a lighter out of his/her left nostril and set fire to the long-sleeved shirt, and finally sat on the ground, feeling satisfied.

But OP had one last thing to do: curse the cruel humanity some more, then tell the pineapple how special, unique, amazing, etc.etc.etcskip100compliments it was. After more hugging, more crying, and more cursing, OP finally left, but not before vowing s/he'd be back.

A few mins later, the pineapple started crying. It had been robbed of it's Halloween mask, it's Halloween make-up had been rubbed Off, and now it was Cold. What a miserable Halloween... all because of OP.


~~~

Bad story is bad and long, and probably doesn't make much sense, but I am tired and I was bored. P.S. I'm not making fun of you OP, I just needed an actor, and you were available.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/mpdrlj</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dypr</id></website><link>http://www.sixbillionsecrets.com/view/Love/1380148</link><postedTime>2011-11-15T09:03:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-11-15T09:38:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/e2hz3c</id><link>http://www.sixbillionsecrets.com/view/Love/1380148#comment-363422919</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rllgm</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-11-15</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>