<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3v9ud/update/2012-03-29T09:02:22/172389ebaca66aa8c94c6d1adfa3feb9037508bbc2b2c091784836310e2e925a</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>It's Always a pleasure to read quotes in an article from someone who knows her business.

I would just add a few points.
  
1. If Israel becomes a powerhouse in electricity generation via our natural gas resources, we should sell some of this energy to Europe via undersea HVDC cable (running also through Cyprus), rather than ship or pipe the gas in a raw or processed form. Selling a value-added product like electricity = more money.

2. There is no reason not to combine natural gas-fired power, with that other technology Israeli technologists have developed (and are implementing everywhere in the world now EXCEPT Israel): Concentrated Solar Thermal electricity generation. Both systems Heat water to make steam to drive turbines. Using them together means less use of gas = more savings.

3.  For desalination, the potential in using natural gas is far greater than presently thought. In the present  desalination system, electric-powered pumps force the salt-water through an RO membrane, clear water emerging the other side. The electricity needed is meanwhile generated (partly) by Heating the water with natural gas, which creates pressurized steam that is then sent through a power-turbine. If you cut out the electricity phase altogether, and use pressurized steam DIRECTLY to push the pumps, you can save about 30% in energy costs.(For piping steam, the natural-gas plants have to be built right next to the desalination plants.) Less energy = much lower cost for desalinated water.

This aspect of our future, at least, is pretty bright.
-MM</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hwwdq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/8cxx</id></website><link>http://www.jpost.com/Sci-Tech/Article.aspx?id=263886</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T01:22:25+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:02:22+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3v9ud</id><link>http://www.jpost.com/Sci-Tech/Article.aspx?id=263886#comment-479471588</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mdc81</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>