<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miesf2/post/2012-03-22T17:26:20</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miekzr</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6anl4</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Here are out top 10 Manchester United sex scandals:

10) Jonny Evans and the "piece of meat' partyManchester United's 2007 Christmas bash was the party to end all 
parties, largely because Sir Alex Ferguson has not allowed players to 
organise one since. The headlines focused on young Jonny Evans, who was 
falsely accused of rape, but the incidentals were Bacchanailal: An 
eight-hour booze-up followed by a party at Manchester's swanky Great 
John Street hotel, to which 100 hand-picked girls had been invited."It was horrible," said one of what transpired. "A player had been 
pestering me and my friends for ages trying to get us up to a bedroom. I
kept telling him 'no' but he just wouldn't take it.
"He was 
really drunk as were the rest of them. Then he just grabbed me and 
started to drag me away from the main area towards the toilets.
"I was in tears. The players were treating girls like pieces of meat."
The
night was also memorable for Wayne Rooney suggesting to one partygoer 
that she and her friend should join him in the toilets for a threesome. 
Alas, his roving eye had fallen on Daily Mirror undercover reporter 
Sarah Tetteh.


9) Kleberson and the teenage brideWhen midfielder Kleberson arrived at Old Trafford from Atletico 
Paranaense in 2003, two things became apparent: he wasn't as good as 
fellow new signing Cristiano Ronaldo and his wife was even younger than 
the preening Portuguese, then just 18.
It emerged that the 
Brazilian had started dating his missus, the former Daiane Williams E Silva, when he was 21 and she was just 14, turning down a move to Leeds in 2002 because, at 15, she was not old enough to leave the country without her parents.
The couple married on Daiane's 16th birthday,
which happened to be Valentine's Day, and a little over 10 months later she gave birth to their first child after the  of jumping up to 
celebrate her husband's goal against Blackburn sent her into labour.


8) The King of PornographyNo player has made a more impressive entrance to Manchester United than Dwight Yorke.
Having arrived from Aston Villa for £12.6million in August 1998, he managed to make both the back and front pages of a Sunday tabloid a month later  when it printed stills from a video found in the player's rubbish, which showed he and former Villa colleague Mark Bosnich involved in an orgy  with four women and a transvestite, the keeper being whipped by one leather-clad blonde while Yorke had sex with her friend. The footballers were later seen donning women's clothing.
It ushered in a golden age of Yorke shagging stories, of which his former landlady and friend  Sheila Dudley memorably said: "If some girl comes to his house with her knickers in her handbag, it's up to him, isn't it?"
Best among them was the conquest Yorke had convinced that he was a local postman named Brian. She said of their trip to a nightclub: "People were coming past and saying 'hello' to him and he said it was because he delivered 
their letters. I believed him. He seemed a lovely bloke." Later, 
he would invite then-girlfriend Katie 'Jordan' Price to Old Trafford, 
where Victoria Beckham would greet her in the WAGs' box with a cheery 
chorus of Who Let The Dogs Out?
In 2001, the pair would approach 
an undercover female Daily Mirror reporter in Monte Carlo, with Yorke asking, "Do you like black men? Do you fancy a threesome?" and Price pleading: "Come on. Please don't leave me on my own."
Hailed by the Old Trafford crowd with the song, "Dwight Yorke, wherever you may be, You are the king of pornography", the striker harumphed that the chant "set a bad example to kids", shortly before Sir Alex Ferguson sold him to Blackburn.

7) Fergie and the untouched kneeMarried to the former Cathy Holding for 45 years after first encountering her in a meeting to arrange a strike at the typewriter  factory where they both worked, Sir Alex Ferguson has one of the strongest marriages in football.
Which meant the press were immediately sceptical when, in October 2002, 21-year-old software technician Nadia Abrahams told South African police that Fergie had touched her knee and invited her back to his hotel after she offered him a lift when his car was involved in a 2am traffic accident near Cape Town's Waterfront district.
After all, Fergie's only previous brush with anything approaching a sex scandal had come when he was quoted as describing a former player's penis as "not just big, it's magnificent", mystifyingly annoying the recipient of the praise, Dion Dublin.

Sir Alex strongly denied any wrongdoing in South Africa 
and though Abrahams and boyfriend Brian Ebden managed to sell their story for £75,000, the case was dropped shortly after reports emerged claiming Abrahams had "flaunted herself at Sir Alex, dancing round and around him in circles" after Spotting him in the upmarket Mannenburg's jazz club while the United manager "was behaving like a total gentleman all night".


6) Ronaldo, Anderson and "no-holds-barred" spankingBefore September 2007, the public thought Cristiano Ronaldo's 
idea of fun was, in his memorable phrase, "putting a television high in a tree outside and kicking footballs at it".
Then came allegations that the Portuguese winger had organised an orgy at his Cheshire home, inviting two team-mates and five hookers.
Busy Brazilian prostitute Juliana Baltrusch claimed to have performed a sex  on Nani, dirty-danced with Ronaldo and later enjoyed a no-holds-barred spanking session with Rolph-from-the-Muppets lookalike Anderson. A year earlier, the Brazilian midfielder had been the subject of a  tabloid kiss-and-tell in which 20-year-old model Leah Houghton claimed Anderson had chatted her up with the words "f*** f*** f***", after whichshe had sex with him on a toilet.

5) Wayne Rooney, the Auld Slapper and the younger slappersNo wonder he lost his hair so quickly.
Having been a 
customer at Liverpool massage parlour Divas in his Everton days - 
sending one girl a note of thanks reading: "I shagged you on December 
26, loads of love, Wayne" and famously enjoying the services of 
52-year-old PVC-clad mum of seven Tricia 'Auld Slapper' Tierney - the 
spud-faced nipper was thought to have cleaned up his  after 
then-fiancee Coleen McLoughlin angrily threw her engagement ring into a 
squirrel sanctuary.
After his move to United, Rooney's penchant 
for grappling grandmas was immortalised in the Everton chant: "Auld 
Slapper is a prossie, She plays with dirty toys, And when she shags 
Wayne Rooney, She thinks of Davie Moyes".
Alas, September last 
year brought revelations that Rooney had been paying Manchester 
prostitute Jennifer Thompson £1,200 a time for sex, once allowing 
Thompson's like-minded chum Helen Wood to join them for a threesome and a
lesbian show.
Coleen forgave, as only she can, and the most 
shocking element of the whole farrago was thought by many to be the £200
Wayne paid a hotel employee to bring him a packet of cigarettes while 
sampling Juicy Jeni's dubious charms.
4) George Best, Miss World and the mink coatA swordsman of Beattyesque proportions in early 1970s Manchester,
Bestie wisely opened two private clubs - Slack Alice and Oscar's - 
where his roistering would go unreported.
Memorable incidents that
evaded the press included celebrity lawyer George Carman, who had 
helped clear his friend of slapping waitress Stevie Sloniecka and 
breaking her nose, marching up to him in Oscar's and declaring: "George 
Best, you blackguard. You've been f***ing my wife."
When Best was not in his Mancunian bubble, however, all bets were .
In
February 1974, he was photographed leaving London society club Tramp 
with reigning Miss World Marjorie Wallace, then engaged to Formula One 
racing driver Peter Revson.
The scandal deepened when Best 
returned to Manchester without her after a row, only to be arrested in 
Slack's at 3am and brought back to London's Wood Lane police station, 
where he was charged with burglary of her flat and the theft of a £2,000
mink coat, jewellery and spirits.
Wallace was stripped of her title and Best advised that he could go to prison.
But on March 22, five days before Best was due in court, Revson was killed in practice for the South African Grand Prix.
Wallace flew back to the States and the case collapsed.
3) Ryan Giggs becomes  Woods"I can’t believe it, he’s such a family man," said Giggs' agent 
Harry Swales when the jug-eared Quorn enthusiast was finally revealed as
having taken out an injunction to quash stories of a fling with topless
Big Brother mopsy Imogen Thomas.
The phrase could hardly have 
been more unfortunate given further claims of an eight-year affair with 
brother Rhodri's wife, Natasha.
Now, there's talk of a third woman
and the emergence of fascinating details from the past, including his 
dalliance with PR girl Caroline Stanbury during his courting of Stacey 
and the rumoured existence of a city centre pad, known as Giggsy's 
Corner, where conquests could be taken.
2) Martin Edwards blows the toilet doors offManchester United chairman Martin Edwards had long been regarded as a lucky man.
Having
failed to sell  a controlling stake in the Red Devils to 
ball-juggling UFO abductee Michael Knighton for £20m in 1989, the 
butcher's son then sat back and reaped the Premier League riches, even 
brushing  dalliances with prostitutes in Brazil and Switzerland, who 
gave him stinging reviews including "he was old and like a grandad" and 
"it took four hours to make love and it wasn't very good".
However,
that luck ran out in scandalous fashion late in 2002 when the 
dad-of-two received a police caution after allegedly being caught 
peering under a cubicle door in the ladies' loos at Cheshire's swanky 
Mottram  hotel.
More allegations followed and former United 
security chief Ned Kelly later claimed to have been briefed to follow 
Edwards at the club's post-1996 FA Cup final party as "his visits to the
ladies are becoming more frequent".
Wrote Kelly: "It had been a 
constant source of amusement to the players and ground staff, but it was
undeniably embarrassing. He just seemed to have a compulsion to invade 
the space of women in their most private moments."
Edwards left 
the United board shortly afterwards and by 2003 had sold  his stake 
in United for £80m, although he remains an honorary life president of 
the club and was part of their sparsely-attended and rain-sodden 19th 
title parade around Manchester.
1) Tommy Docherty and the physio's wifeIt's a 'What if...' double whammy which perplexes United fans andjournalists even today: Would Manchester United have broken Liverpool'slate 1970s and 1980s stranglehold on the title had Tommy Docherty not been sacked in July 1977?And how many acres of newsprint would beexpended on the story today had a contemporary Old Trafford boss left his wife and four children for the physio's missus on the eve of the FA Cup final?Despite offering to resign at the club's victorious banquet after beating Liverpool at Wembley, The Doc initially survived the furore and was holidaying in the Lake District, contemplating plans to sign Peter Shilton and the mercurial Tony Currie, when the Axe finally fell.Rumours claimed Docherty had been a victim of WAG power in the shape of letters to chairman Louis Edwards from players' wives demanding his dismissal - hardly surprising as the manager had made his share of dressing room and backroom enemies during five turbulent years in which he eased out Bobby Charlton, brutally dumped George Best and Denis Law and fell out with the likes of Alex Stepney and Gerry Daly.In came safe pair of hands Dave Sexton and Docherty's thrillingly cavalier side, starring midfield schemer Lou Macari, wingers Gordon Hill and Steve Coppell and barrel-chested strikerStuart 'Pancho' Pearson, was about to be broken up.The Doc himself started ultimately unsuccessful legal proceedings against Edwards for defamation and wrongful dismissal, announcing his decision while sporting a black eye given to him by cuckolded magic-sponge man Laurie Brown, to whose ex-wife Mary Docherty has now been married for nearly 30 years.United fans mourned their loss with this creativereworking of Knees Up Mother Brown: "Who's up Mary Brown? Who's up MaryBrown? Tommy, Tommy Docherty."</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yxkgu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t5xu</id></website><link>http://www.dagbladet.no/2012/03/22/sport/fotball/premier_league/wayne_rooney/20802329/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T16:07:55+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T21:26:20+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miesf2</id><link>http://www.dagbladet.no/2012/03/22/sport/fotball/premier_league/wayne_rooney/20802329/#comment-473974020</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lyk1f</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>