<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/206085/post/127451060/comment/328101312</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I would think that there are a lot of people out there that do say certain things in public to be politically correct but have other feelings they truly believe and/or only reveal to a small, trusted group of family or friends. However, I am not sure that is the case with the individuals who were mad, disappointed, angered and so on by Rue, Cinna, and Thresh being black in the movie the Hunger Games. If you are going to tweet something, it is possible it is going to be read by your followers and I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t consider my followers to be a trusted, close group. I think these people are just racist and can&amp;rsquo;t read. 
I saw the movie and it blows my mind that people would be so upset that Rue was black. She was so adorable and I became invested in her character and the character development was done very well so I was devastated when she did die in the movie. In fact I was mad during the movie because she DID die. Obviously I knew it was coming because of the whole premise of the movie. I hated the movie. I can appreciate that it was made very well and the  was also very good but the whole plot is sickening to me. Something is wrong with our society when the number one movie is about children killing each other. I get a lot of Heat for this opinion because I haven&amp;rsquo;t read the books and only saw the movie so apparently that has something to do with my opinion. But I saw the movie with my sister and she said she didn&amp;rsquo;t like it either and it made her nauseous. She believed that putting faces to the characters and then watching them kill each other and die made her not enjoy it. 
I just think that if someone is going to tweet something like that they aren&amp;rsquo;t worrying about being politically correct; they are not trying to hide their racism or their ignorance. However, it does say something that most of them started deleting their twitters once their tweets went public. I am sure they weren&amp;rsquo;t expecting it to Reach as many readers as it did. I think of being politically correct as being aware of what you say before you do it. Consciously calculating your sentence before you say it in order to be sure if is not offensive to anyone. I think there is a lot of politically correctness going on in society. I only recently found out you can be in more than one stage at once and I think that along with another stage, many people are also in stage two 
 </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:206085:127451060</id><idPostId>127451060</idPostId><idBlogId>206085</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:206085</id><idBlogId>206085</idBlogId><link>http://www.worldinconversation.org</link><displayName>World In Conversation</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.worldinconversation.org/2012/03/26/the-hunger-games-and-race-relations-in-2012/</link><displayName>The Hunger Games and race relations in 2012?</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T22:37:52.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:206085:127451060:328101312</id><link>http://www.worldinconversation.org/2012/03/26/the-hunger-games-and-race-relations-in-2012/#IDComment328101312</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T22:37:52.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The Hunger Games and race relations in 2012? by lrp1991</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://intensedebate.com/people/lrp1991</link><idEmailMd5>1edd306a45de695ef0c2279fed0a8a4c</idEmailMd5><displayName>lrp1991</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://intensedebate.com/people/lrp1991"&gt;lrp1991&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.worldinconversation.org/2012/03/26/the-hunger-games-and-race-relations-in-2012/"&gt;The Hunger Games and race relations in 2012?&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>