<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mslmik/update/2012-03-27T13:27:25/99dd88f5cfd10e3b8b3dd282f84c3c76dd1192e9fd67a8924184ede56015fc7e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Eating before drinking definitely helps.  With food in your stomach, you won't be able to drink as much as quickly.  Spreading out your consumption will help you not be as hard hit the next day.  For mild hangovers, I recommend lots of water followed by some exercise (a short run), followed by some food, a shower, and a nap.  You'll feel better when you wake up, and feel like you accomplished something more than just being miserable for a half day.  For severe hangovers, I recommend lots of water, mexican food, micheladas, and some serious time spent on the couch watching something mindless and napping.  

Avoid  (liver), asprin (upsets the stomach).  Stick with naproxin or ibuprophin.  If you are so sick that you can't hold anything down, including water, then stop consuming anything for 4-6 hours to let your stomach "reset".  You shouldn't die of Dehydration during this short span provided you are a healthy adult with no underlying medical conditions such as kindey problems or diabetes.  After 4-6 hours, start with very small sips of water, dilute , or Pedialyte, every 15 minutes.  By small sips, I mean 1/2 shot or less.  If you can hold this down after an hour or two, start drinking more. If not, then take a trip to the doctor, urgent care, or ER to get some anti-Nausea meds and IV fluids.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l1y82</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rp9l</id></website><link>http://blogs.houstonpress.com/eating/2012/03/the_hangover_guidebook.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T15:02:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-27T17:27:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mslmik</id><link>http://blogs.houstonpress.com/eating/2012/03/the_hangover_guidebook.php#comment-477580999</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/m38gn</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>