<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m02s06/post/2012-03-31T14:50:31</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>below rightie is wrong..left asked bush why we were attacking multiple countries for oil while not funding wars and STILL gas prices went to record highs...this time it is STILL radical right denialist warmongers causing high oil prices by threatening world war III with iran china russia....what is hard to understand???  

it is  warmongers i.e. 'speculators'. causing high oil prices and it is post peak oil and it is after gulf is destroyed by big oil and north sea is now destroyed etc....

so times change...except it is getting worse and worse because of big oil. we should find out how many more species are extinct because of big oil pollution directly and why all dolphins in gulf have cancer due to big oil and how many species are indirectly extinct due to massive Heat waves droughts floods etc due to fossil fuel pollution..these are all externalities. big oil HAS to start paying the TRUE cost of their damages they are causing or there can be no recovery..it will nonstop climate catastrophes plus world war with iran. it will be about as successful as any recent war for oil. which is NOT AT ALL SUCCESSFUL and we will be worse Off..which is end goal of GOP.  (and to defeat obama). nowhere ever does GOP ever once state an actual concrete policy objective of improving americans' future. it isn't their goal!!!!wake up!!!!! </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/y3pnxm</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/amtr</id></website><link>http://www.treehugger.com/fossil-fuels/fox-news-explains-why-presidents-cant-control-gas-prices-2008-video.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-06T23:01:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T18:50:31+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m02s06</id><link>http://www.treehugger.com/fossil-fuels/fox-news-explains-why-presidents-cant-control-gas-prices-2008-video.html#comment-482092534</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rfe4y</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-06</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>