<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3t0ya/update/2012-03-29T10:28:39/ed69f68f92477c2d6a9bb8cc966d48201c18239ac62c82ecb4a84f6b54324307</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Let me help you guys (Wise and mudstump) out with the medical stuff. I would think you would know some of this but maybe not. First of all EMS  responds to emergencies where there is physical injuries. They, with the police standing by, attend to the injuries on site. They write EVERYTHING down: where the injury is, what the injury is, how long even the gash is, whether it is Bleeding profusely, moderately, etc.. EVERY SINGLE THING is written down. A broken nose is simply a break in the bone of the nose which indicates a violent hit to the face but that is really not visible especially. He might develop bruising but the next day or later. He probably had a nose Bleed but the blood didn't necessarily have to get on his clothes. He did have a RED jacket on so you might not see blood in the GRAINY video there. EMS, attends to the injuries, stops Bleeding, puts on dressings if the Bleeding doesn't stop on its own. They clean blood  the face/head, etc.; or at the least allow the patient to clean it Off. There is no law against that --- everything has been written down and recorded. The gashes (there were two) may not have been severe enough to require stitches, or maybe so. If you look at the video again and watch at 0.50 you will see a police officer move to the back of George and gaze very intently at the back of his head. That police officer is checking the gashes to make sure they are still NOT Bleeding. Neither of you have any type of medical training whatsoever do you?.. --- didn't think so!

You poor misinformed kiddos now know a little bit more about how medical stuff works. YAY! And, there was an accompanying article written by a journalist who admits that you can't see the injuries from that grainy surveillance video . It would require a better photo to see that. Believe me --- they have the photos. Just because YOU do not have the photo does not mean the gashes and the broken nose did not occur. IT IS EVIDENCE, IT IS PROOF. You are just in denial and I feel sorry for you.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l5slc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnmb</id></website><link>http://www.kansascity.com/2012/03/26/3515056/white-isnt-color-its-privilege.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T20:04:57+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:28:39+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3t0ya</id><link>http://www.kansascity.com/2012/03/26/3515056/white-isnt-color-its-privilege.html#comment-479529397</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zh96t</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>