<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m02jj3/update/2012-03-31T14:42:32/7478d5f5c71bf286fb168401650c3e956731e5ad64542defd71f97d868d11ba8</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I have developed a Theory on the Reason for all the Tremor, which is just wild speculation, of course. I've Always thought it was curious that they called the Offshore area near the Cal/Or Border a TRIPLE JUNCTION because there doesn't appear to be 3 bodies of land involved...of course it is just because of the Plates underneath that there are 3 components involved with subduction processes. At the other end of this zone however, we CAN SEE 3 bodies of land involved with the Subduction...they are Vancouver Island, the Olympic Peninsula and the Puget Lowlands. I think there is a Triple Junction in Admiralty Strait which is the last remains of whatever comprised the Upper Farallon Plate. The Explorer Plate is the northernmost remnant of the Farallon Plate.from Wiki...http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Explorer_Plate......and who also say that The eastern boundary of the Explorer Plate is being slowly subducted under the North American Plate, to which it may eventually accrete owing to the slow rate of subduction.
If you look at the landform, Vancouver Island appears to be rotated and so could the Plate, forming a Triple Junction in Admiralty Inlet, which is broken into little pieces! The slow subduction has turned into accretion maybe as they say, thus pushing the pieces down the Puget Sound to form the Island County land masses!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l0mft</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/v0v0</id></website><link>http://cms.pnsn.org/cms/blog_posts/51</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T00:00:08+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T18:42:32+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m02jj3</id><link>http://cms.pnsn.org/cms/blog_posts/51#comment-482085789</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8c14v</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>