<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/323728/post/127799748/comment/327570217</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I can see both sides here.  I lean a bit more toward agreeing with Greg, Andy and Bill, just based on my recollection of the show and the Twitter feed. (With the caveat that it&amp;#039;s been a bizarre week for me, so my memory is sketchy - I&amp;#039;m not entirely sure that this wasn&amp;#039;t the show that I only saw for the first five minutes or so before an emergency pulled me away.) &#13; 
&#13; 
I don&amp;#039;t remember anything particularly rude coming from Kayliegh.  I may have missed the exchange, so I will watch it once it becomes available on Hulu. Personally, I enjoy Heated exchanges on the show.  I&amp;#039;d never denigrate a guest for being passionate.  I might take issue with their argument, but I&amp;#039;d avoid insulting them as a person.  Obviously, an out of control or rude guest (think Paul Provenza) wouldn&amp;#039;t get the same consideration.  &#13; 
&#13; 
I do specifically remember some comments in the #redeye Twitter feed striking me as mean-spirited and over the top. Whether I read them as they occurred or after the fact, I can&amp;#039;t remember.  Regardless, I remember one or two that were very insulting.  Not &amp;quot;I don&amp;#039;t agree with her,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;I hope she&amp;#039;s not booked again,&amp;quot; or something of that stripe, but angry personal attacks.  Unfortunately, I&amp;#039;m on my mobile at the moment and it won&amp;#039;t allow me to go back on the #redeye timeline far enough to retrieve them. &#13; 
&#13; 
While I think Bill&amp;#039;s statement that Kayliegh is probably brighter than all the people tweeting is hyperbole, he and Andy do have a valid point that most people probably wouldn&amp;#039;t make good guests. I have a fairly healthy regard for my own intelligence, but I know that put into a position where I had to discuss various topics, in a rapid-fire format, on national television, while coming Off as well informed and funny, I&amp;#039;d be a disaster. &#13; 
&#13; 
No, I don&amp;#039;t think the hosts or guests on Redeye should be immune from criticism, but I do agree that on a few occasions one or two people on Twitter have crossed a line of common courtesy. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:323728:127799748</id><idPostId>127799748</idPostId><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:323728</id><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><link>http://www.chrisisright.net</link><displayName>Chris Is RIGHT</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/06/24/red-eye-in-which-the-guy-combat-negativity-by-twitter-fans/</link><displayName>Red Eye: In Which the Guys Combat Negativity by Twitter Fans</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-06-24T21:02:59.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:323728:127799748:327570217</id><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/06/24/red-eye-in-which-the-guy-combat-negativity-by-twitter-fans/#IDComment327570217</link><postedTime>2011-06-24T21:02:59.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Red Eye: In Which the Guys Combat Negativity by Twitter Fans by Dave</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>27ae4e1976409aef061ff75c34214071</idEmailMd5><displayName>Dave</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>Dave commented on &lt;a href="http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/06/24/red-eye-in-which-the-guy-combat-negativity-by-twitter-fans/"&gt;Red Eye: In Which the Guys Combat Negativity by Twitter Fans&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2011-06-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>