<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7wyt/post/2012-03-30T15:38:33</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Nick the silence around here is deafening; I shouldn't have taken today Off, as it has given me too much time to think about what could go wrong.  The way I figure it, even three points out of the last five games here should do it.  Rangers have the tie-breaker, and I don't see Pittsburgh winning four of five.  I went on the Penguin blogs for a little while this morning, just for comic relief, and they have given up.  They think their team will now blow the home-ice advantage with the Flyers as well; shows you most fans' mind-set changes every 24 hours.  It's really sort of amusing, actually.  Yeah, it could turn around again, but I don't see it.  I'm content to let them worry about that; not our problem.

OK so where is everybody over the last day or two?  I'm sure Torts won't let the team take anything for granted, and would like to beat out St. Louis or Vancouver for the President's trophy.  Probably means some money for the players and coaches.  As long as they keep the pedal to the metal over the next three games, next Thursday might not even matter, and Hank can get some rest if he needs it.  Buffalo, Ottawa and Washington can wear themselves out stretching to get that last playoff Spot.  Sabres are playing the best right now, but I don't really care who finishes 8th.  Conventional wisdom will tell you the Rangers don't do well against the Senators, but generally, regular season records don't necessarily mean much in the playoffs.

Enjoy the game tonight.

-orange        </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67yoeq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/hv2h</id></website><link>http://www.rangerstribune.com/the-rangers-tribune/2012/03/pregame-rangers-host-habs-with-hopes-of-extending-lead-in-east.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:40:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:38:33+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7wyt</id><link>http://www.rangerstribune.com/the-rangers-tribune/2012/03/pregame-rangers-host-habs-with-hopes-of-extending-lead-in-east.html#comment-481114421</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hii6t</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>