<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9jh06/delete/2012-03-18T03:22:34</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Alright so there is this guy
whose name is Greg Miller. He eats poo for a living. He was reported as once
saying this quote “Human poo is the best food I have ever eaten. Aside from dog
feces, I also eat toothpaste wrapped in pee and poo. It is sooo delicious that
it makes me have diarreah. After this extreme amount of poo I also poop out
some poo and I stick that in my mouth. Some days I take a dump on other IGN
staff member desks to insult them. Then I proceed to make love to a PS3 box,
filled with poo of course. Then I start making love to my sandals cuz my feet
reek of dog poo.” GREG MILLER IS A VIOLENT SAVAGE WHO MUST BE REPORTED. People
of IGN, I am calling a public awareness campaign to stop this sick monster. It
is called MILLER 2012. On April 20, 2012, we will take posters of Greg Miller
eating feces and plaster them all over in order to create public awareness
about this monster. Greg Miller is one lucky son of a Greg. He eats so much poo
that on occasion IGN staff members such as Colin Moriarty have reported him as
eating so much that his own poop came out of his mouth when he was Vomiting.
Colin said that this somehow “turned him on”. Colin then decided to make eat
poop again. It was such a disgusting display that Colin left IGN. That is why no
one sees him on IGN anymore. He has been hospitalized for poo addiction. HELP
US STOP THIS MONSTER GREG MILLER.  


All in all, Greg Miller is a nice
guy. If you’re reading this Greg, GO DO YOURSELF ONE FAT FAVOR AND EAT A BIG
PILE OF OSTRICH FECES WRAPPED IN MOTHER POOP. 


 


Thanks guys, this has been an IGN
News coverage by Russ the mothamothamotha dog poop. GOOD NIGHT. You stupid pansies
why are you guys on IGN anyway. Worthless organisms.


 


 


This message has been brought to
you by sonichero007. Productions.


And Id like to make a Shout out
to my boy RJ, YOU ROCK BROTHA&gt; No you actually do stink at rapping though.  Except that one song. Call me, so I can come
and take a poo and Greg Miller for ya.


 


GOOD NIGHT IGN YOU”ve been a
horrible crowd. I hope you all live splendid lives and marry beautiful women
(Or men, if that’s you’re cup of tea Greg).</body><verb>delete</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6gvzui</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7d9s</id></website><link>http://games.ign.com/articles/122/1220979p1.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-17T00:17:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-18T07:22:34+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9jh06</id><link>http://games.ign.com/articles/122/1220979p1.html#comment-468211078</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z5dcm</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>killed</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-17</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>