<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mws79v/post/2012-03-31T10:44:46</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>It won't help what happened here, but everyone should know these basics...

Three Rules of Preparation:
 -  notify responsible people of EXACTLY where you're going and EXACTLY when they should expect you back. This provides much better chances of rescue if you become lost, stuck or injured.
 -  have a map and compass, and know the area you're headed into. This can avoid a potential survival situation altogether. 
 -  check weather forecasts, and be prepared for the worst weather you might face.

Rule of Three's for Survival Priorities:
 - You can die in THREE MINUTES from lack of air or profuse Bleeding - Keep a first aid kit!
 - You can die in THREE HOURS of exposure - Prepare for the WORST weather you might face!
 - You can die in THREE DAYS from Dehydration - Always store extra drinking water, or the means to procure it!
 - You can die in THREE WEEKS from starvation - Food is typically your LAST concern in a survival situation.

In this situation, even the most basic preparedness (water, a compass and some oars kept in the boat) would have prevented this tragedy. Several hours... a day at most... paddling East would have taken them back to shore. Instead, something as simple as motor failure left them adrift.

PS - Even if they were properly prepared, a 10 foot boat has no business being more than a couple miles from land. Chalk this up to the unfortunate ignorance and inexperience of youth.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hcxfx</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/thpf</id></website><link>http://www.outdoorhub.com/news/18-year-old-fisherman-survived-adrift-for-28-days-on-raw-fish-and-rainwater/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T04:42:35+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T14:44:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mws79v</id><link>http://www.outdoorhub.com/news/18-year-old-fisherman-survived-adrift-for-28-days-on-raw-fish-and-rainwater/#comment-481883560</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cqg8i</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>