<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mqg9wb/update/2012-03-03T12:29:36/f14dc5a05925321ff5f16cf565b077e17e97203de6177ace1c054b5f20ed7e02</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Ms Ahn makes the classic mistake of assuming that sanctions hurt the common people of NK while harming the leadership not at all.  On the face of it, this is true.  But a deeper analysis is required to understand the implications of not imposing sanctions.  North Korea, with it's tiny hobbled economy is nonetheless a threat to it's neighbours, Japan and South Korea in particular.  With economic sanctions removed, their economy absolutely would grow, and the common citizens in the street would, in theory, benefit.

Or would they?

Chances are the only purpose that the North Korea regime would put increased economic activity toward would be the building of additional military capacity, including nuclear capacity.  The only North Korean citizens who would be any better Off would be those that are usefull in building the military capacity to threaten, bully, and even make war on North Korea's neighbours.  The vast majority of the North Korean populace would see little or no benefit and the potential for truly disastrous military misadventures by the regime would increase.

It is unfortunate that there are few means to hobble the North Korean regime that do not have negative impact upon the common citizens.  But that is the Cold harsh reality, just as is the reality that being nicer to them will do no more good than did being nice to Hitler, Kruschev, Stalin, Hussein, Milosovic, bin Laden, Atilla or Genghis or Pol Pot.  

For every life lost due to sanctions on the regime, dozens are spared by preventing that self same regime from building the capability to do more harm still.  Those that wring their hands in abject sorrow over the plight of North Korea's poor who suffer the brunt of the sanctions, if they truly want to see that suffering end with a minimum of human suffering from all involved, should instead be advocating for a military intervention to remove the head of the snake.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yir4xs</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/01/opinion/ahn-north-korea/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-01T18:19:49+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-03T17:29:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mqg9wb</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/01/opinion/ahn-north-korea/index.html#comment-455444158</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hjqnb</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>