<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mspq8t/update/2012-03-28T10:09:49/89d73de6987499d127d615f0a395c84130669ee03c4e4c77b553f0cec055e4b4</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msr543</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8zhwn</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Let's deconstruct your sad efforts. 1. It looks like you just copied and pasted from web sites. 2. The New BPP is not a liberal group, liberals - The Southern Poverty Law Center - have denounced them as a hate group just like the KKK. So, your construction is that if a group is Black, then it is somehow liberal and liberal whites must support any black group. Not very bright.  3. Fact: whether Martin was an idyllic teen or not, in the moment, he was walking home. Period. Want to use the not an angelic teen argument then we'd go kill 90% of the teens in the country.  4. Fact: Zimmerman did chase Martin, so if "stand your ground" laws were equally enacted, Martin would have had the right to shoot Zimmerman.  5. Fact: The police let Zimmerman go with no investigation, no alcohol or drug test. Why? Just one more dead black kid. Corollary awareness: Had it been a black kid standing over Zimmerman, the police would have shot him on the Spot, no question. 6 Martin laid in the morgue for three days with no effort to find family. All his parents knew was he had gone to the store and not come back. 7. Zimmerman, on clarified recordings says to the dispatcher the "f%$#* coons" Always get away. That is racial motivation, by definition. 8. Sharpton and Jackson have not declared the whole white race guilty, what a hyperbolic, stupid comment. I'm white. Finally, your argument is of the type , "but mom, they did it first!" Not exactly an adult approach. Come back when you actually have a rational, adult comment to make. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lf13x</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ydw9</id></website><link>http://motherjones.com/node/169246</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T16:07:59+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T14:09:49+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mspq8t</id><link>http://motherjones.com/node/169246#comment-478388681</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a3csz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>