<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3dzq8/update/2012-03-29T00:18:07/f5e405dd61cf49fc2d7633a768b353c7c7d599924a292f4373db136a87c1474c</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I hear there will be a march in Ft. Worth tomorrow in support of justice for the family of Trayvon Martin. Here's yet another chance for the George Zimmerman cheerleading squad to come from behind the safety of their computers and PUBLICLY show some solidarity for their idol, their prince, their hero. The only hispanic in the history of the S-T message board who has not been called an illegal immigrant by the white people and the first hispanic who has ever garnered this much support from the white is  right crowd. Funny though, the only reason the white folks love him so much is because he killed an unarmed innocent black teenager in Cold blood for no reason, he did what the white people wanted to do but don't have the stones to do. The white is  right crowd calls Trayvon Martin a thug, but their hero is the one with a criminal record. Assaulting an officer, beating on his woman, and pretty soon, murder. The Sanford police tried their best to cover this up. This story came out 2 weeks after it actually happened. The Sanford police department has a history of cover ups when black victims are involved.  In 2006, 2 security guards, 1 the son of a Sanford police officer, approach a black man, do not identify themselves as security guards, and shoot the man in the back. No questions asked, no charges filed. In 2010, another Sanford police officer's son, Justin Collison, coldcocks a black homeless, kinda like how Zimmerman says Trayvon Martin did him. The cops get there and let the cop's son go home. But someone filmed it, put it on YouTube, it goes viral and then they finally come back and charge him. Anyone from the Zimmerman cheerleading squad care to explain why Trayvon Martin lay in that morgue for 2 days before his parents were allowed to see him? Care to explain why Martin's corpse was tested for drugs &amp; alcohol but Zimmerman's fat ice wasn't? All of you Zimmerman cheerleaders keep saying let the police handle it, well when Sanford police lead homicide investigator Chris Serino tried to handle it &amp; recommended after his crime scene investigation that George Michael Zimmerman be arrested for manslaughter in the murder of Trayvon Benjamin Martin, the state attorney said no. Is it just me, or is it a coincidence that Zimmerman's parents work for the court system in and around Seminole &amp; Volusia Counties and may be getting a little home cooking. I mean he had the assaulting a police officer charge expunged from his record. Most hispanics can't pull that Off without a little help from the inside. Black folk will keep marching until the 4 part plan for George Zimmerman is complete. Arrest, trial, conviction &amp; incarceration. Like Trayvon Martin's father said, we don't want an eye for an eye, we want justice. No need to get in the gutter with George Zimmerman and his loyal fans, his cowardly fans, his racist fans, his inhumane fans. This kid has been dead for 32 days and his killer has not seen anything in the way of accountability for his actions from the city of Sanford, the county of Seminole or the state of Florida, and these crazy white folks are saying let the cops do their jobs. You wouldn't be saying that if this were your child or a white child. I'll bet it all on that.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hezi6</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnmw</id></website><link>http://www.star-telegram.com/2012/03/28/3840756/supporters-of-fla-shooter-fearful.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T07:23:09+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T04:18:07+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3dzq8</id><link>http://www.star-telegram.com/2012/03/28/3840756/supporters-of-fla-shooter-fearful.html#comment-479082638</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/81gxv</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>