<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tibj/post/2012-03-29T10:20:26</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Another good column (that's two in two weeks...what gives, Mary?).

How many times have stories of racist attacks/threats turned out to be completely fabricated hoaxes? Many, many times. And from all sides - black, brown, and white. Remember the woman who claimed she was attacked by a black man and had the letter "B" (for Barack) scratched into her face because she was a McCain supporter?

Rational people ignore the over-Heated rhetoric. Those people  the loudest are spouting Off about what they want to be true, rather than accepting the fact that the actual truth may be uncomfortable. They prefer their own narrative -- even if it's a lie -- over honesty. Those people don't deserve to be taken seriously.

This case will be thoroughly investigated by multiple agencies, public and private. I only wish people were as concerned about the miscarriages of justice perpetrated by our government judicial system every day on those not fortunate enough to have various "activists" (translation - loudmouths) take up their cause. 

We have a judicial system dominated by prosecutors who are accountable to nobody, many of whose entire focus rests on their unbridled political ambitions. Every case for them is an opportunity to further those ambitions, rather than seek justice. And cops aren't any better, resisting every reasonable attempt at independent citizen oversight - even though we're the people they're supposed to be serving.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h0sm2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnmb</id></website><link>http://www.kansascity.com/2012/03/28/3521032/on-race-we-pick-our-own-truths.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T02:24:57+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:20:26+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tibj</id><link>http://www.kansascity.com/2012/03/28/3521032/on-race-we-pick-our-own-truths.html#comment-479523411</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c2e9z</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>