<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mgszav/update/2012-02-08T13:35:34/b48b9f55de7fab4687665df6bc3864cb7691c7fbe020d56e368df03fc2faa1d3</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Okay folks. Everybody's freaking out because of lack of information. For most, we want to help. We feel personal about this. Our intentions are 100% motivated by care and concern for this young woman's safety, and compassion for her family.
Our Alaskan community has a long tradition of Reaching out to others in times of need. Nothing wrong with that!

We don't know where to go to find out what's happening, what's been done, how to help, who to approach to offer something, how to volunteer for legitimate search parties, etc. So I've done some homework to sort through all the stuff out there.

&gt; There are multiple FaceBook sites. They are legit, but each one is not necessarily the way to communicate directly with questions.

1. &lt;b&gt;Help Find Samantha Koenig - Kidnapped in Anchorage, Alaska&lt;/b&gt;
https://www.facebook.com/help.find.samantha?sk=wall

This is a Facebook "Community" created by volunteer missing persons organization, "Seeking TheLost". It appears that their main function is to serve as an easy accessible clearinghouse for flyers: Seeking TheLost makes flyers and pages for missing persons.
Description: &lt;i&gt;"This page is set up to notify Facebook users of new missing person pages made by the administrators of Seeking TheLost and to provide breaking news updates concerning missing person cases of interest."&lt;/i&gt;

It's monitored by the organization and can't really answer questions about activities and updates happening IN Anchorage.


2. &lt;b&gt;Please Help Find Samantha Koenig.&lt;/b&gt;
https://www.facebook.com/pages/Please-Help-Find-Samantha-Koenig/328733013838027 

This is a Facebook page owned by Mr. Koenig. Seems to be locally monitored.This has had more information about activities, volunteering, etc. Posts about where you can go to pick up flyers.
Description: &lt;i&gt;"If anyone has any idea, any tips, if you have seen anything strange or had a gut feeling that something wasn't right please let someone know. Please post and tips or updates or anything that you think could help. Even if its the smallest thing. With the outreach of support we will bring her home."&lt;/i&gt; 

Flyers - 
Anchorage: Wade's Printing, can't find an address, telephone: 388-6997.
Wasilla: The Ink Spot, 189 E Nelson Ave, 373-9966

T-shirt and ribbon sales for reward fund - don't know.

Reward fund account -  Denali Alaskan Federal Credit Union, #135006, or just use the name "Koenig".
Outside of Alaska: To find Shared Branching in your area, go to www.cuswirl.com

Organized search party on Wednesday, 8 pm. Meet at Common Grounds.

Candlelight vigil: Saturday, Feb 11, 6:30 pm, Delany Park Strip (downtown Anchorage)

Skiers - They request that cross-country skiers and trail users search area trails.

Crimestoppers: &lt;b&gt;Anonymous reports&lt;/b&gt;. You can report without revealing your identity and still get reward money. Telephone: 907-561-STOP
http://www.anchoragecrimestoppers.com/howitworks.aspx 


3. &lt;b&gt;Please find samantha Koenig &lt;3&lt;/b&gt;
https://www.facebook.com/events/102832079843848/

This is a "Public Event" page created by a family friend. This is where they've directed the public to go to find posted events and activities.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yz713r</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dneq</id></website><link>http://www.adn.com/2012/02/07/2305513/fbi-assists-search-for-abducted.html</link><postedTime>2012-02-08T06:14:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-08T18:35:34+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mgszav</id><link>http://www.adn.com/2012/02/07/2305513/fbi-assists-search-for-abducted.html#comment-433172500</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zdumw</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-08</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>