<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/312236/post/127908722/comment/328346129</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Megan, 
I am assuming that you are talking about a Camp Dutch oven with leg gs and a flat lid. If that is indeed what you have you can use them on gas stoves, electric stoves do not put out enough Heat to cook above the element. You can also use them in your oven in the house, just rotate the Dutch oven so that the legs fit through the baking rack in the oven. If you have a flat bottomed Dutch oven without legs then it can be used on the stove or in the oven quite easily. I have written 2 cook books on Dutch oven cooking and they are both geared towards outdoor cooking like the rest of the rest of the Dutch oven cook books out there. I put the degrees necessary to cook foods in the Dutch oven as well as  other info needed to cook outdoors as well as indoors.  You can email me if you\'d like more info about the books or any other questions. I teach Dutch oven cooking all over California, Nevada, and Oregon. There are many other people who teach all over the U.S.  Good Luck to you. BTW, use your Betty Crocker cook book and use the Dutch oven to cook your food. Just cover the Dutch oven with the lid and set the oven to the desired temperature you need.  Good Luck! </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:312236:127908722</id><idPostId>127908722</idPostId><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:312236</id><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><link>http://www.denpdf.com</link><displayName>denpdf.com</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.denpdf.com/dutch-oven-recipes-can-you-use-a-cast-iron-dutch-oven-on-the-stove-or-in-the-oven-i-am-only-finding-recipes-for-outdoor-cooking/</link><displayName>dutch oven recipes- can you use a cast iron dutch oven on the stove or in the oven? I am only findin</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T12:04:33.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:312236:127908722:328346129</id><link>http://www.denpdf.com/dutch-oven-recipes-can-you-use-a-cast-iron-dutch-oven-on-the-stove-or-in-the-oven-i-am-only-finding-recipes-for-outdoor-cooking/#IDComment328346129</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T12:04:33.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on dutch oven recipes- can you use a cast iron dutch oven on the stove or in the oven? I am only findin by David H</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>7a4013f464398cc71a9e9cc9a8e793bf</idEmailMd5><displayName>David H</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>David H commented on &lt;a href="http://www.denpdf.com/dutch-oven-recipes-can-you-use-a-cast-iron-dutch-oven-on-the-stove-or-in-the-oven-i-am-only-finding-recipes-for-outdoor-cooking/"&gt;dutch oven recipes- can you use a cast iron dutch oven on the stove or in the oven? I am only findin&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>