<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrk7r/post/2012-03-30T12:32:12</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw5z7f</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/59byr</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Hi Cole,

So then, it seems that your comment to me on the "Parable of the Lost Sheep: Calvinist Version" article, where you said:

"Religion was given birth out of the fear of death. There is no evidence for your loving God. He does not express His love to us. We see this when children get their faces Burned  by the universe that He supposedly designed. The universe breaks babies arms, cripples them, pops their eyeballs out of their sockets, peels the skin Off their bodies. If God wanted to bring these children up to heaven why not go about it in a more humane and gentleman-like way? Maybe send down some chariots from heaven and escort the children there since He loves them so much."

... is just your attempt to get me to "grow up" and stop letting God manage my life for me? Don't get me wrong, I really appreciate your desire to save me from what you see as my delusions about God... really, I do appreciate it. And I do completely understand the road you have traveled through this whole mess of God, religion, personal accountability, self-confidence, etc., etc. I have walked it - am walking it - on a continual basis.

But please, rather than try to point out that I have somehow missed the atrocities in the world as proof that God does NOT exist, why not assume that I am at least *almost* as smart, and as self-reflecting, and self-examining, and aware of what is going on around me, as you are; and that I am as perfectly able to come to my own conclusions as you are. I do not need you to enlighten me with graphic images of Burning children. I do appreciate your concern, but I'm a big boy Cole.

And please do not respond to my heartfelt response to your comment to me on that other blog. And do not think for a moment that I don't have a pretty good understanding of your mindset, its development and conclusions, and the need you feel to save me from mine. I forgive you for your sincere, yet misguided attempts at saving me from myself, just as I hope you will forgive me for my sincere, yet misguided attempts at giving you some hope that there might actually be a God. 

Now, in the words of Mother Theresa, "Go home and love your family." That's God enough for all of us.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/672hs0</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/m7z5</id></website><link>http://experimentaltheology.blogspot.com/2012/03/new-apologetics.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T09:56:14+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:32:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrk7r</id><link>http://experimentaltheology.blogspot.com/2012/03/new-apologetics.html#comment-480924119</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>