<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m09kkb/update/2012-04-02T01:47:22/a8efd59d8c2926082cb32ee648c599ed6320a6a0062dad2a6b5696853bed8936</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The Philippine Chamber of  Commerce and  Industries (PCCI) said it had 
been warning about a looming power crisis in Mindanao since 2008, “and 
as late as 2011,” well into Mr. Aquino’s first two years.

"Rome Burned while Nero fiddled away".
Like Nero, Mr. Aquino lazed around and ignored the Mindanao problem even if there were numerous indicators of a catastrophe in the making.
There lies no clearer proof of the administration's policy of "Noynoying" than how this situation was mismanaged and has developed into the national emergency it now is.
Despite their glaring shortcomings, this administration still has the gall to avoid legitimate criticism and instead, play its usual finger-pointing game against the previous administrations.
After two years in power, can the administration still not accept the responsibility and urgency to manage this country and its people effectively? 
I would have extended some sympathy if they had admitted to their faults and Resolved to bring immediate redress to the situation. However, by their childish and boorish behavior, this spoiled brat mentality only adds to the disgust the country has for Mr. Aquino and his nursery school administration.
I shall continue to point out how low this country will have fallen after four more years of this misery.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6vbfwf</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/l33l</id></website><link>http://opinion.inquirer.net/26077/power-crisis-no-time-for-noynoying</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T17:19:15+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T05:47:22+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m09kkb</id><link>http://opinion.inquirer.net/26077/power-crisis-no-time-for-noynoying#comment-483304162</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/llql2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>