<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0pybh/post/2012-04-02T06:48:23</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m090eb</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> In fairness to Mano,  Diego just came on the scene a short few months ago after being  for so long.  The last time he was this good was when he was with Werder Breman.  Otherwise he has been on and .  It cxould be bad club choice or whatever but he had disappeared.

I watched the game yesterday and he seems to be in pretty good form.  I think he should just keep doing what he is doing consistently to the point when it ll be hard to ignore him.

As harsh as we are on Mano,  he definitely has a selection Headache,  especially for the # 10 Spot.  Choosing players today with 2014 in mind is a tricky business.  Some are in good form but there is question as to where they will be in 2014.  Kaka is a good example of that because of his age.  Some are not necessarily in good form today  but may be promising for 2014.  Ganso is an example of that.  Mano seems to be intent on grooming Ganso and getting him ready for 2014.  As promising as that idea is,  Ganso is not a proven player as of yet.  The few games that are coming up will be the first serious of games for a fit Ganso (hope he ll stay fit and in form). 

Diego should keep up the form.  In the past he has been on and Off.  He cant afford to do that anymore.  Hopefully hell be picked up by a bigger club or may be life Atletico to a higher level.  Atletico plays in Europe so he should just keep doing what he doing.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ziuve</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dd6r</id></website><link>http://brazil.worldcupblog.org/world-cup-2010/the-greatest-brazil-goal-of-all-time.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T04:55:56+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T10:48:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0pybh</id><link>http://brazil.worldcupblog.org/world-cup-2010/the-greatest-brazil-goal-of-all-time.html#comment-483415285</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>