<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mj9f7d/update/2012-03-20T03:04:06/5faa17e9f689d390c5b19d820b7ac5d45d93674d49e69f519dca2ddfa357d30f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>"Congressman Paul’s weak Spots are his zealous supporters who can’t make reasonable arguments without insulting people."

I believe those kinds of supporters exist for every candidate; Paul's supporters tend to have the largest internet presence and therefore are the most offensive online.


"Paul is taking a back door approach and is trying to run a coup winning 
delegates in nonbinding caucus states where he didn’t even finish in the
 top two, let alone win."

This is the fault of the party, not Ron Paul. Any intelligent honest person would award delegates proportionally, so that the person who wins the most straw poll votes ends up with the most delegates. The GOP changed to the current system because they wanted more control over the nomination process, and it is that system (and not Paul) that is the problem.

If republicans are bothered that Ron Paul is successfully obtaining delegates, then they need to complain to the GOP to have the rules changed. It is my personal opinion that Ron Paul has purposefully chosen to campaign this way in order to bring to light just how easily the system can be abused.


"The Ron Paul campaign failed. Money is running out and your delegate strategy bombed big time …"

Actually, Ron Paul's campaign is nowhere near running out of money at $1.5 million in the bank with no debt (compare with Gingrich sitting below $70k after debt back at the end of January or Santorum at the same time sitting at $700k). Past super Tuesday he does not need to spend as rapidly, his appearance on Leno and upcoming money bomb will give him enough to ride to Tampa.


"Ron Paul will acquire, at most, 450 delegates …"

It will be interesting to see how the convention goes down. It's almost certain that Romney will have the most delegates of any candidate, but it's probable that he won't have enough to wrap it up at the start. 

As soon as delegates become unbound, Romney is in an even worse position. He will Bleed delegates to Paul, Gingrich, and Santorum, and right now I'm hesitant to believe that Paul or Santorum delegates will jump to Romney. At the same time, I don't see Romney delegates jumping elsewhere either, unless a new contender is brought in and believed to be superior to the current options.


"By keeping up with this they only hurt their cause. "

It only appears to really hurt the cause with folks who are pro-party, anti-democrat, and willing to compromise to Oust Obama. The team-players. Some people are like that; some are not. In the end however, I think the most interesting bits of information are the following:

- Statistics show that voters overwhelmingly vote the same way throughout their lives.
- If only people under 35 were voting, Ron Paul would win the presidency by quite a margin. 

So how long does the GOP have before it has to adjust or face extinction?
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6mx42v</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/68lr</id></website><link>http://caffeinatedthoughts.com/2012/03/ron-paul-is-he-running-a-campaign-or-a-coup/</link><postedTime>2012-03-20T05:38:51+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-20T07:04:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mj9f7d</id><link>http://caffeinatedthoughts.com/2012/03/ron-paul-is-he-running-a-campaign-or-a-coup/#comment-469858868</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h2wjd</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>