<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qvqg/post/2012-03-29T11:53:32</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>It could be argued all gameplay is a "grind" to get to the end of a game, or to the highest level of some statistic. It only stops being a grind when its a) fun, in and of itself, like combat or puzzles, or b) it presents a logical requirement in the games structure (of course you have to go back to where the boat/ship/jeep/helicopter dropped you ). And a third type c) reward, the requirement isn't fun but the pay  is worth it (if I kill 10 more gizzlewits I get the bakara sword!).

Type a) becomes a grind when you lose "challenge". Shooting enemies without any fear of failure or challenge or variation is only fun for a very short time. A puzzle isn't fun when you know how to solve it just by looking at it but it requires a lot of time to give the answer (moving many heavy blocks around is particularly annoying).

Keep varying the enemies, what weapons you have, the skills required. Make the puzzles more challenging and the gameplay remains fun and new each time it's attempted.

Type b) is usually the most obvious crime. When the required action seems to serve no purpose BUT to waste your time it's the worst. Having to find someones bow in a cave, to get a key, to open a door to get letter, which someone else needs, all to get to somewhere new, it's a form of punishment. A street layout with obvious barriers that force you through a linear maze. The valleys, Always with the bloody valleys that follow no known natural landscape just to hem you in.

I get the feeling many people just accept these limitations as normal videogame compromises but a bit of intelligence would go a long way to hiding these.

Backtracking is obvious but having it make sense makes all the difference. Call of Duty 2 has you assault Normandy right up to the guns. A mission elsewhere to vary the setting, then you return to back track almost the entire level. But playing this same environment twice is completely different. First attempt is pushing forward with brute, pig-headed determination to win. But the next time is backtracking in fearful, frantic retreat for pure survival. Same ground, different gameplay.

Type c) is pure Skinner box. Which means it should never be a chore if you test your game properly because you should find the sweet Spot of Effort Vs Reward. If killing 10 gizzlewits is tedious and the bakara sword not really very impressive then people will cry "GRIND!" Make it 5 Grizzlewits, or a better sword. The ideal of course is to make the sword awesome, and the gizzlewits a matching challenge for that awesomeness. Then the chore becomes a quest of epic proportions. 

Epic only turns to bloat when you fail at one of these 3 designs of gameplay. You fail to keep a challenge, you present illogical roadblocks, you misjudge effort vs reward.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rfpan</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7d9s</id></website><link>http://games.ign.com/articles/122/1221569p1.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T07:00:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:53:32+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qvqg</id><link>http://games.ign.com/articles/122/1221569p1.html#comment-479598449</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gkiob</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>