<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw040g/post/2012-03-31T13:34:59</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwsjfw</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6rxsb</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Thank you for the consideration, Rick, but no apology is needed.  You see, you are making my point for me.  It is these "theologians" who have made all of this about the Bible "confusing", when it's not confusing at all.

You put too much "faith" into what these theologians are teaching.

I need faith for the things I CAN'T see and prove.  According to Hebrews 11:6 Without faith, it is impossible to please God."  And without the attendant faith, one cannot see the wonders of God.

God is not the author of confusion.  It matters not to me if there was one person who wrote it all in one week, or if it took 10 million people to write it over 1,000 years.  It is all 100% factual or 100% BS.  And I I know it's not BS.

I have personally witnessed a leg grow 6" with my own eyes.  You can believe that or call me a liar.  A medical doctor was there and saw the same thing.  I watched an 8 year old girl who was born with club feet and could never walk like you and I- transform from club feet to perfectly normal feet and physically run around, where before she had to have the aid of crutches.  I have witnessed ears deaf from birth hear.  I have seen Fevers in my children go from 104 to normal in 30 seconds or less.  I have seen eyes blind from birth see.

What I have personally witnessed would keep you busy reading for hours, if all I was trying to do was impress you with my "evidence".  All of those incidences that I just described were the result of either my prayer individually, or a group of people praying collectively, in agreement.

You don't have to believe any of it.  But I have no Axe to grind and absolutely nothing to profit from it financially or otherwise.  I am merely sharing with you the evidence that I have eye witness testimony of.  I'm a businessman.  I'm not a preacher, nor do I intend to capitalize on my faith, financially, in any way.

And these "theologians" that you speak of have never seen any of this because of THEIR unbelief.

No, it's not nonsense for me to know that there is more evidence to believe in Jesus than Lincoln.  I have met Jesus.  Have you met Lincoln?

Besides, can you PROVE that your mother loves you?  It's a rhetorical question.  Obviously you can't.  What you can do is use behavior patterns to establish that she does, based on how we define "love".  And that's what I just did for you.  I gave you "proof" and "evidence" as you asked for.

Whether or not you choose to believe me is totally moot to me.  I couldn't care less.  But your unbelief will effect only you.  I will continue to see God's work being done.  I am simply inviting you to see it for yourself.

To me, what is totally nonsensical is for someone to think that all of this beauty that surrounds us every day was random selection- basically accidental.  That is tantamount to the princess kissing the frog and the frog turning into a handsome prince- plus a few million years.  

Utter nonsense.  A fairy tale on steroids.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67xu59</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnmw</id></website><link>http://www.star-telegram.com/2012/03/30/3849164/atheist-group-says-arlington-movie.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:23:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T17:34:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw040g</id><link>http://www.star-telegram.com/2012/03/30/3849164/atheist-group-says-arlington-movie.html#comment-482027729</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ld1y3</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>