<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/137788/post/127943192/comment/328973569</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The Merriam-Webster dictionary defines &amp;ldquo;treason&amp;rdquo; as: 
 
1: the betrayal of a trust; treachery  
2: the offense of attempting by overt  to overthrow the government of the state to which the offender owes allegiance 
 
According to our Constitution, Article III, Section 3: 
 
Treason against the United States, shall consist of levying War against them, or adhering to their Enemies, giving them aid and  (italics mine). 
 
To  in a manner that causes one&amp;rsquo;s country to become unable to defend itself from external attack, at a time when another country is making daily threats against us, and is about to become armed with nuclear weapons and already has the means to deliver them, could, by these definitions, easily be seen as treason. Indeed, a concerted attack by Iran, in partnership with their Russian pals and Venezuela, and possibly China, ever the opportunists, too, would likely cause the collapse of our economy, and thus our government, and the subsequent excuse to institute martial law. To knowingly make moves that bring about this outcome could not be seen as anything but treason. 
 
Obama-Soetoro has made it clear from the outset that he hates America and its constitution, capitalism, white people, and Christians 
Obama-Soetoro has made it clear from the outset that he hates America and its constitution, capitalism, white people, and Christians. He made a point of publicly insulting our long-time allies like Britain and Israel, and of bowing to the Muslim Saudi king and the Head Red of China. What has he done &amp;ndash; ever &amp;ndash; to contradict the notion that he believes America needs to be punished for her greatness, which he sees as having been achieved by criminal exploitation of &amp;ldquo;people of color&amp;rdquo;? 
 
Raised by Muslims and communists, on  young adulthood Obama-Soetoro, by his own self-aggrandizing admission, made conscious choices to closely associate himself with radical Marxists and black supremacists. These were, and are, people who ardently believe in the violent overthrow of our government and the destruction of America as a free, sovereign, capitalist nation. Are we now to believe that disarming America is not part of furthering this agenda? 
 
The Democrats seem to have the delusionary idea that having fewer nukes than China will persuade them to not attack us with theirs. This is not a notion that rational people share. It seems unlikely, too, that this is the &amp;ldquo;change&amp;rdquo; that many who voted for B. Hussein were hoping for. From what I have read, nukes don&amp;rsquo;t discern between the young and the old, the male and the female, the black and the white, the rich and the poor, the oppressor and the oppressed, the progressive and the conservative, the Muslim and the Infidel. Nukes kill &amp;lsquo;em all, and leave it to God to sort &amp;lsquo;em out. Not having enough nukes to  as a deterrent &amp;ndash; and the Cold War proved their effectiveness as a deterrent &amp;ndash; nor the apparent will to use them, is suicidal. 
 
Even a relatively small country like Iran, armed only with small nukes but run by religious zealots becomes a threat to every American, and every non-Muslim, world-wide. They have made clear that once they possess nukes, they intend to use them. A suitcase-size one, walked over the unclosed border from Mexico, could destroy a whole city and murder its entire population in a heartbeat, bringing the collapse noted above, and the imposition of martial law. With our military tied up in trying to defend/run our cities, our overseas interests, economic and political, disappear. Overnight, we become an isolated, poverty-stricken Third World has-been. 
 
Obama-Soetoro must not be allowed to get away with bringing down America. It&amp;rsquo;s bad enough that he appears to have almost no opposition to his policies that have already damaged us badly, looting the Treasury, and filling the pockets of his cronies/donors in the process. He must not be permitted to administer the coup de grace. 
 
The Tea Parties need to get active again, organizing some massive marches in Washington and elsewhere, like outside military bases, supporting, not denigrating our armed forces. We need to overwhelm the enemy with our numbers. And we need to send a loud, clear, unmistakable message to the political class that &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rsquo;re mad as hell, and we&amp;rsquo;re not going to take it anymore!&amp;rdquo; 
 
Michael Oberndorf, RPA  
Most recent columns 
 
 
The son of a German immigrant, I am an archaeologist by profession, with a BA from Metropolitan State College of Denver, and an MA from Leicester University, in England. I am also the Chairman of theFreedom21 Legislative Committee. Over the years, I have lived and worked all over the country, and traveled in Canada, Mexico, Central and South America, Europe, Australia, and Japan. I sincerely believe in the old saying, &amp;ldquo;America, love it or leave it.&amp;rdquo;  Michael can be Reached at:moberndorf@yahoo.com 
 
 
  &lt;a href="http://www.canadafreepress.com/index.php/article/44658?utm_source=CFP+Mailout&amp;amp;utm_campaign=4950d6e61f-Call_to_Champions&amp;amp;utm_medium=email" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.canadafreepress.com/index.php/article/...&lt;/a&gt; 
 </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:137788:127943192</id><idPostId>127943192</idPostId><idBlogId>137788</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:137788</id><idBlogId>137788</idBlogId><link>http://www.exposeobama.com</link><displayName>Expose Obama</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.exposeobama.com/2012/03/31/obama-the-russians-and-missile-defense-historical-parallels/</link><displayName>Obama, The Russians, And Missile Defense: Historical Parallels</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-01T04:25:29.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:137788:127943192:328973569</id><link>http://www.exposeobama.com/2012/03/31/obama-the-russians-and-missile-defense-historical-parallels/#IDComment328973569</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T04:25:29.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Obama, The Russians, And Missile Defense: Historical Parallels by Upaces</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>05570f2ac998782e460275ef5577af89</idEmailMd5><displayName>Upaces</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>Upaces commented on &lt;a href="http://www.exposeobama.com/2012/03/31/obama-the-russians-and-missile-defense-historical-parallels/"&gt;Obama, The Russians, And Missile Defense: Historical Parallels&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>