<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwfuy4/post/2012-03-31T01:32:13</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw17nn</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hi7dk</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I'm sorry, but I have yet to have a debate with a believer in evolution who didn't eventually begin insulting me, or try changing the subject. I'm not saying that they weren't willing to talk about the subject, they just never seem to stick to the subject, instead going Off on tangents about religion, or calling me too stupid to understand. It gets tiresome. Perhaps you will be the exception. 

If a person is going to join in a debate on any given subject they should educate themselves on that subject, or simply say that they lack the knowledge to explain it. I would respect that and accept it as reasonable and would not press them on it. I'm not trying to proclaim that evolution didn't happen, I just want someone to prove it to me. I am a born skeptic and I don't just take anyone's word on anything. Especially when they can't explain it rationally and without vitriol. Of course, proof is also desired. If the relationship between living creatures isn't known and the mechanism for evolution isn't known (in your words, the details are not known), then the science is not settled and no one can know that evolution is real. It's like saying that you know that people in ancient times enjoyed drinking coffee, but you can't prove that they had access to coffee beans, that they knew how to ground and brew the beans, much less how you know what they liked to drink coffee since there is no written record of them drinking coffee. All you have are some remnants of cups that look a lot like coffee mugs from which someone developed a theory. Believers in evolution want us to believe that science "knows" that evolution occurred when they can neither prove it, nor even fully understand how it's supposed to work themselves. That doesn't make sense. There are elements to the theory that I find quite plausible, such as beings that are maladapted to a certain environment are not likely to survive and thus will likely become extinct. However the idea that the incredible diversity of forms of life on Earth all have as a common ancestor, a lone single-celled organism, is something that someone is going to have to prove to me. Cold blooded, warm blooded, no blood, mammals, plants, fish and so on, all coming from that one little critter, and they can't even come up with a plausible explanation as to how it came into existence. I'm sorry, but I need convincing before I sign on as a believer. When I was in college I did try to engage several professors (biology professors, chemistry professors, a couple of anthropology professors, as well as some non-science professors) who all attested that evolution was real, in a discussion on the subject. Most refused to even try; one biology professor dismissed out of hand any argument that evolution was unproven. The other biology professors, as well as one of the anthropology professors tried belittling me on religious grounds, some even after I explained to them that I am an agnostic. They just proclaimed that it was real and that I should just accept that. They didn't want a discussion; they wanted students to roll over and agree with them. They were useless. Is it too much to ask that people who are educators actually educate a curious student? It's not enough to tell a student that something is so; a teacher should be willing and able to show how something is known. That is their job. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67hozm</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ju4p</id></website><link>http://www.breitbart.com/Big-Hollywood/2012/03/30/dukes-schneider-fired-for-questioning-evolution</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T20:55:23+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T05:32:13+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwfuy4</id><link>http://www.breitbart.com/Big-Hollywood/2012/03/30/dukes-schneider-fired-for-questioning-evolution#comment-481566726</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h3o50</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>