<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m02qyv/update/2012-03-31T14:29:30/f4fef80424a002658379ac829279e2bf038b36276413cba58f1f0b58080f2085</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m024o5</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lzh0g</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I'm trying to guess how old you are. I think most people would assume you are quite young
but I think there's more to it. No one develops the kind of bitterness and self
loathing you exhibit without going through considerable emotional pain. I can
only assume that you were abandoned, maybe by a parent or a loved one, maybe
you experienced some personal loss, maybe a bereavement, but something happened
to leave you so lonely and so insecure, desperately Reaching out for any sort
of reaction to validate your miserable existence... I think a lot of people
believe you're a repressed hom ose xual, I can understand their view, you
certainly exhibit signs of some deep social Anxiety... part of me hopes that is
the case because it would be tragic if you were simply an as sh ole. But I find
that unlikely. I suspect you are just lonely and isolated and bored. I hope
something goes right in your life and you find a way to move past this
unfortunate phase in your life. Things do get better. People can change. I hope
you find something that helps you develop a more fulfilling life.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67ud4e</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yjmx</id></website><link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2012/03/31/defense-secretary-panetta-blasts-defense-budget-cuts-in-visit-to-ship-off/</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T06:10:02+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T18:29:30+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m02qyv</id><link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2012/03/31/defense-secretary-panetta-blasts-defense-budget-cuts-in-visit-to-ship-off/#comment-482074756</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cf0xb</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>