<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw5o7f/update/2012-03-30T06:23:39/6b5e66b803ca9997b404b1589d9f09a37129c2a4971b3abf3a5c3f74bcce4ff5</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw5nrc</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h7owc</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> Man, that'd be so freaky...!

Once I knew I was in a state of sleep Paralysis, it does get easier, but since it feels like you're awake, the evil and presence feels so real.

Here is the other doodle--
http://thedailydoodles.tumblr.com/post/4490366785/sleep-Paralysis

I did it immediately after I had the more recent incident that I describe above.  It's an older one and maybe not as good.

I've heard of some people who have sleep Paralysis quite often, and even though they know what is happening the feeling of fear never really goes away.  

The worst part is how helpless you feel, since you can't move.  

The A-bomb dream was pretty peaceful, to be honest.  Now that I think about it, I believe it was my first experience with sleep Paralysis... I was just laying there, unable to move but awake, and then a bright light shined through my window and I assumed it was an a-bomb and we were all dead.  I just remember thinking to myself that it didn't seem so bad.

Haha, I actually woke up screaming HELP the other night, but it was a pretty pathetic dream compared to Red-eyes or old hag stories... I was on vacation in some resort (something I never do) and I had this keypass attached to a lanyard string thingy, and I was taking a shower and some lady Reached over and grabbed my lanyard and ran.

I couldn't chase her because I was naked in the dream, so I meekly yelled 'help' and then I bellowed 'HELP' and I woke up and knew I had said it out loud.  Hahaha... it felt lame.

I love your damn site!
--DMC</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z6q8j</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/jfh4</id></website><link>http://www.strangerdimensions.com/2012/03/29/old-hag-syndrome-movie-now-in-production/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T12:01:31+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T10:23:39+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw5o7f</id><link>http://www.strangerdimensions.com/2012/03/29/old-hag-syndrome-movie-now-in-production/#comment-480593653</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cygx5</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>