<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwv3n6/post/2012-03-30T16:25:05</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw72de</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/al2vy</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> Mr. Burns,

Really,  did you even read what I wrote.  Again it is not jealousy or desire for more privilege to look at someone like Bill Gates or Bernie Sanders and say you know what, if my husband will be paying  upwards of 25% of his income in taxes  then Mr Sanders should have to pay at least 25% of his income in taxes regardless of how he makes his income as that is a fair government tax system.  I am not talking about occupy though I will point out that their premise is similar to the question I just raised.  Now my husband works for salary and he works hard, there is no over time for his job and he goes in early and often stays late purposefully to take care of things because he cares deeply about his job.  The graduated tax system is actually not a bad idea and makes sense when you think about it, but it negates the entirety of your previous premise about oh goodness the rich paid the most in taxes because of course when 3.1 MILLION of the people make more than 40 million combined they are going to  be paying more  in taxes than others, they use the roads, they expect the protection of the military and help from the national guard when needed, they expect the government to protect their right to keep their business, and many other tax based services.  Because of this they pay in according to their income as all of us do.  It does not make people jealous to say HEY that guy over there who is paying a smaller percentage than I am makes over a million dollars that really isn't right.

Interestingly enough the other things Christ said about money was GIVE TO CESAR WHAT IS CESAR'S and GIVE TO GOD WHAT IS GOD'S  we have been requested to give taxes in fair amount to Our government and give our tithes as God has asked to him.

We must first raise taxes then cut spending, the cuts that either party wants to cut only take 1-10%  out of the deficit.  If we simply allowed the Bush  tax cuts to laps we would no longer be in deficit, perhaps then we could clearly see the way forward to start paying Off the debt for future generations.  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zl9z0</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/jgt5</id></website><link>http://www.honoracademy.com/2012/03/money-trillion-dollars/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:54:02+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T20:25:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwv3n6</id><link>http://www.honoracademy.com/2012/03/money-trillion-dollars/#comment-481160170</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cyjd7</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>