<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jpe6/post/2012-04-02T04:37:09</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>F*cking Helski!

Dave(call me Quisling)Cameron got where he is by lying, he is a compulsive liar. A political lie can only be sustained as long as the truth can be suppressed and that point in time has been , anything Mr Quisling says is now treated as a lie.

The road of the liar  has an ending, a point in time when lies no longer have the desired effect, when the people being lied to come to the conclusion that the liar is not capable of telling the truth about anything. The social democrat regime is a product of the new political corporate determination that lies can enable and empower and perpetuate a ruling elite.

So mired in lies and deception and falsehoods has Mr Quisling and his freak show become the fabricated reality they created is in tatters, they have nothing to offer us and now we know it. That ugly mental case Brown, a serial fantasist and liar came to the end of his road within three years and Cameron now mimics that fate.

The people of the UK trusted the rhetoric and the empty promises and the outright lies and the cynical deceptions, we are a trusting people but that trust has limits and that limit has been . The social democrat libdem dominated coalition is the child of the ruling classes, it is no more conservative or right wing than George Galloway.

A motley collection of rich wealthy arrogant spivs and traitors, political elites bound together in a common purpose to first destroy and then hand over the wreckage to the growing cancer of the EU superstate, as the UK Bleeds to death a tiny minority of profiteers get richer, a tiny minority of connected insiders and friends and families siphon Off our collective wealth.

David Cameron leads a minority regime that benefits a tiny minority, it is a true government of the minority, a tyranny of the minority where the majority are excluded and demonized and oppressed and ignored. He is a product of the modern professional ruling class that believes itself to hold a divine right to perpetual rule over us. We now find ourselves living in an autocracy and not a democracy.

Its time the people of the UK reminded this ruling class that it is we who hold the power in the land, that it is we who hold the ultimate veto and not them. This ruling class has come to believe in their own superiority, its time we gave them a wake up call isnt it?
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6v932u</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/politics/david-cameron/9179475/Tory-MPs-round-on-David-Cameron-and-George-Osborne.html</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T20:56:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T08:37:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jpe6</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/politics/david-cameron/9179475/Tory-MPs-round-on-David-Cameron-and-George-Osborne.html#comment-483347314</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8w0iq</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>