<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/evd9vj/update/2011-12-19T15:01:17/e603cd7a7cd0504efca25fd21b3a2fc2e5f9ceecf8bc05707d80c438b83fc43c</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>These are lunatics in power in china, and if they believe they can win a nuclear all out exchange with the US then they are really demented to say the least, but there red commies aren't they. you can sign all the treaties you want with these Yellow skin scumbags, all your going to get is lies on top of lies. my proposal to the US is , you better start mobilizing a greater force against these nuts or where going to lose much, but there going to lose far greater. there entire population,  we will blast the shit out of them from our space based weapons platforms before they even get a missle launched, watch out you Red Commies, you will lose everything, and when you come up from your stinking mole holes , we will wipe the rest of your shit ass army out. you eat your children anyway, and you murder your young for body parts to use on yourselves in your party and then you sell the rest. your a scumbag race of dirtbag evil people and when you finally get nuked by us, we will be rid of you for once and for all.   If you think russia is coming to your help, it won't and you can Depend upon that.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/dlr8lm</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q905</id></website><link>http://patdollard.com/2011/12/pentagon-report-china-military-build-up-in-preparation-for-war-over-taiwan/</link><postedTime>2011-12-14T17:06:50+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-12-19T20:01:17+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/evd9vj</id><link>http://patdollard.com/2011/12/pentagon-report-china-military-build-up-in-preparation-for-war-over-taiwan/#comment-390078459</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rz936</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-12-14</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>