<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjcqv/update/2012-03-26T14:12:04/a843150687427272ba28c4dfd1bc539e71c63f5fb1b52bfc7c6280e4c3a050b8</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk94a6</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zawm0</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>"Will all of Newser's Liberals now claim this side of the story to be false?"

 on the size of the carrot on the stick.  The girlfriend's account shortly before the altercation appears rather convincing at a first glance.  

"As usual, we see with Liberals that they have a lynch mob mentality.  They make decisions out of emotion and prejudice, rather than facts and objectivity."

It's people in general.  Some are more susceptible to it than others.  I distinctly remember how rabid conservatives became after the Shirley Sherrod story broke. 

"First, most people thought the shooter was White, because they WANTED it to be a White man."

I didn't see that at all.  Cite it, please.

"Most people assumed that the shooter was a Cold back stabbing killer who got   free, because they WANTED a White system to be responsible for the "injustice.""

Details incriminating Zimmerman were released long before anything indicating his innocence was released.  Not only that, the story broke largely because of Florida's inane "Stand Your Ground" law prevented any real arrest or action on this incident for weeks. 

"This entire drama just demonstrates that what the "Hoodie people" want is a race war, but they are just too cowardly to just launch one out of their own will....because their wills are weak."

I think you're over-analyzing the race aspect of this story and repeating the same kind of shit Geraldo has said.

"I must say, IF this side of the story is true, then I am Glad that Trayvon is dead, and justice was served."

That being the case, you would agree that every bar fight in America should end with someone's death.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l2zjw</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gblz</id></website><link>http://www.newser.com/story/comments/142713/zimmerman-trayvon-martin-pummeled-me.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T16:39:41+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:12:04+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjcqv</id><link>http://www.newser.com/story/comments/142713/zimmerman-trayvon-martin-pummeled-me.html#comment-476595628</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8wqot</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>