<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/50geuj/update/2011-09-01T23:25:02/5d05ce8267fadcf2750666187dc47cec3cee9878ece50b3fb297852100e5a647</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/5wwvf6</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ew0r4</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Conservatives: Bill Cosby has your philosophy- and even he received Heated criticism.  I mean when America's Favorite Father who was on the front lines to create MLK's dreams is uttering what you are saying and he is being bad-mouthed by blacks and whites alike then you know you are on the right track!

Many people get very upset anytime you shake the foundation - physical or philosophical.  We all agree that welfare systems are there as a safety net for those that really need them which  is why NO PRESIDENT OF EITHER PARTY has ever wanted to eradicate the programs.  It is not a Democrat or Republican agenda item.

However, there is real evidence that there is a lot of waste in the system where the freeloaders are the fraudulent users.  They have a job and somehow managed to get plugged into the welfare system and stay there.  This is a percentage that is being targeted because it is CRIMINAL.

Another group of people in the system who have been on it for generations and there is no dream/intent of there ever being something different.  They like getting their money in the mailbox.  Some also turn to street crime since that is tax-free money! They use it on themselves and neglect the children they produced.  They don't expect that their children will get a good education and make something better for themselves.  They may do BBBS but so that there children can be babysat, the kids can get more things from the Big Brother or Sister and buck back when educational materials come home rather than x-boxes, clothes, superficial materialistic things.  This unfortunately has been the experience of many Big Brothers and Big Sisters.

To see what is being done to correct this I think the movie The Interupters is very inspirational and challengers a lot of the mass opinion on the subject.  

In my 20's  I spent over a decade working in the projects: in their schools and in their homes. There were families trying to get out of the system, but for one reason or another The System failed them and they slid back into it.  Others were perfectly happy to not do anything, they had everthing provided for them so the money was used for clothes, hair, nails done on a weekly basis which was $150 a week!  Yet daughters needed new clothes, brother needed sketching pads and pencils and could have used art classes to help him explore his talents.These are the ones that need to be shaken up.  The Ohio model needs to be adopted that says we will be here for you to get  an education or a job and then you are on your own like EVERYONE ELSE.  No one is so special that generations are (I have met many 4-5 generation families on welfare and they weren't just black families either) on welfare without the government stepping in and saying, "Why are we still paying your way?"

In response to some poor have talents, BS EVERYONE has talents, but it is whether or not there is a parent, teacher, church member someone out there to help them see it and grow it.  In this increasing Me-centric society we have Neverland adults who blame and name versus shucking Off the victim suit and say "I live in America where even I can make a difference in my community, for my children, for myself."  Duh, that is why welfare is there - temporarily!!!  A chain is only as strong as its weakest link. America has many broken links that need to be replaced.  A reworked chaing can be worn with pride for it durability and pride.  Vivre America!!!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/eu6w8b</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zmtw</id></website><link>http://dev.front.moveon.org:12800/jon-stewart-f_ck-the-poor/</link><postedTime>2011-09-01T14:55:48+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-09-02T03:25:02+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/50geuj</id><link>http://dev.front.moveon.org:12800/jon-stewart-f_ck-the-poor/#comment-300893175</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/y9arq</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-09-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>