<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkp9gd/post/2012-03-26T16:31:03</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Lol, I think a lot of you guys are taking this the wrong way. The fact is, they left a lot of things open in the ending. We want more clossure, and have all ends, end. If you were really into mass effect (the whole series) you would understand where we're coming from. For example, here's a list of questions that a lot of people have to ask.

Why does shepard have an unlimited amount of bullets without him having to reload?

When Shepard went through the beam, he wasn't holding, or was shot in the stomach. It was only AFTER he shot Anderson, and after he died, that Shepard appears to be holding his hand over a stomach wound in the EXACT Spot.

If everyone (including team mates) were on the ground for the final push, why was your crew with Joker, and why did Joker leave through a mass relay? They wouldn't abandon Shepard, they wouldn't have time to because the explosion happened almost instantly.

What is up with Shepard waking up, after taking a gasping breath at the end?

If all things really happened, then what will happen the quarian , and ALL other races, that were bringing AID to earth in the final battle? All would starve to death sinse all massive relays were destroyed, and no food supply line would be able to be created.

Another question. This goes with the indoct. theory. Why was the catalyst being represented as the boy that died in the beginning?

If ME3 wants to end it the way they did, they should atleast had dialog that shepard died, maybe a couple of pictures of people starving to death on earth since all the races are stranded there, and say that it's all over, game over. I would be more saticfied with that ending, then the one they completely left open.

Btw, offending people, because a small percentage of you beleive the game is fine where it's at, doesn't help and will make you look like a complete idiot. There is a BIG difference between a debate, and people Acting like 15 year olds with insults.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ylrny</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/nihp</id></website><link>http://thebitfix.com/2012/03/mass-effect-3/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T07:23:42+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T20:31:03+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkp9gd</id><link>http://thebitfix.com/2012/03/mass-effect-3/#comment-476718236</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6ajqf</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>