<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6p21/update/2012-03-30T11:44:30/c3fa998162fd8d6112cbd109b0aaa6c1c73b4aca0793a9577d76362a32ae6a8a</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3dyhf</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zet8j</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>2 white 20 something year olds car jacked by 4 black men and 1 black woman in TN. held captive, both brutally raped by every one of their Cold sorry asses, then raped again with chair legs and broom sticks. They cut his penis Off in front her, while he was alive. Ten shot and Burned alive.. They werent done with her. They continuously raped her, made her drink cleanin supplies, poured it all on her open wounds and finally beat her to death.. 
You will have to google that one. 
2 black men, broke in white mans home in rankin co. Robbed him and beat him to death in his own home.. Na, that wouldn't be a hate crime would it? Of course not.. Blacks wouldnt target whites out of hatred would they! Only whites!!! 
That is what is bullshit!!!!!! Wake up and look around you!!! Those white kids were targeted bc they were white. They knew nothing more about them but they were white and they hate white. I am so sick of people like you, erIca basically saying the same old played out line---- " that us whites are trying to hold you back, keep you down, lock you up.. That is BULLSHit!!! I want criminals locked up! If people committing crimes, they need to be locked up.. I don't care what color they are.. 
 But satistics don't lie... They are the facts... Check up
On it.. And don't be mad at the white person but the blacks for committing the black on black crimes and the black on white crimes... That happens way to often... 

</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l84wo</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q0fi</id></website><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/26/former-naacp-leader-accuses-sharpton-and-jackson-of-exploiting-trayvon-martin/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:18:34+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T15:44:30+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6p21</id><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/26/former-naacp-leader-accuses-sharpton-and-jackson-of-exploiting-trayvon-martin/#comment-480874344</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>