<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3umgm/update/2012-03-29T15:08:10/abc92443d89a319f7c90fd85b592b2284749a07771556bf5e794e5b54282c08e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qtyt</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z5ekc</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Duck Hook - Spot on analysis.

Hope is not, repeat not, a business plan.

Her is a way to look at this.  This analogy mentions politics but don't take this as a political statement endorsing one candidate over the other.

You are the Republican party in the year 2012.  There have been several candidates in the primaries that supposedly "moved the needle." (Rick Perry anybody?)  However due the weakness and shortcomings of their performance in campaign they are, one by one, falling by the wayside.  The candidate that is winning the the process to become your party's nominee doesn't "move the needle" with the party faithful.  This may not be the preferred candidate of your party's hardcore element but you would rather not concede the election to the candidate from the other party.  What do you do.  Do you hope the candidate eats some bad chicken on the campaign trail and succumbs to food poisoning or some other unfortunate end?  Do you decide that your party faithful should just stay home?  Or do you come to a conclusion that the candidate you may not strongly care for would make a better President than the candidate from the other party, or worse, not having a President at all.  Or do you put your energies behind your party's nominee. 

Any writer can write a  piece on someone popular and generate hits.  Good writers and good marketers humanize a person or candidate, emphasize the positive and de-emphasize the negative.  Think about some of the people who have been elected in this country.  Going back four years or a hundred and fifty years, neither President from the state of Illinois with legal backgrounds had ideal features or attributes to be elected to our country's highest office but elect them we did.  

Yani Tseng is qualified to be the face of the LPGA tour.  She will qualify for the LPGA HOF before her 24th birthday and has twice as many Rolex Ranking of her nearest competitor.  She is an engaging interview.  She has the mental toughness to carry the expectations of the world number one player.  If the tour and media that present the tour for a more marketable dominating candidate to come along the tour will stagnate.  Let's see if these marketers and media are worth their money.  As a fan of the LPGA, I hope so.  If they think long-term, the tour will be stronger whenever and for whoever comes along to take over during the next Era in ladies golf. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hwff3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/9dd2</id></website><link>http://www.golfchannel.com/news/randall-mell/kraft-nabisco-so-much-at-stake-for-so-many/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T01:06:20+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:08:10+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3umgm</id><link>http://www.golfchannel.com/news/randall-mell/kraft-nabisco-so-much-at-stake-for-so-many/#comment-479772907</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h8qwu</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>