<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/8w49uc/update/2011-04-06T00:38:46/da0cfbfc94e91e4bfc0407e6c1f93e7d8cfcdbbab34c3d5504aaced029167d42</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/8wee0m</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Rlcp380 – I hope you can read all of this post, without asking for overtime.  The cars I have purchased and driven, since you brought it up, a  1976 Plymouth Duster, 1980 Pontiac Sunbird, 82 Ford Mustang GT Boss HO 302 V8, 87 Ford Thunderbird Turbo Coupe, 89 Jeep Comanche Pick Up Eliminator Straight 6, Chevy Lumina, Pontiac Grand Am, 97 Ford Explorer, 2001 Pontiac Montana, and  2010 Town &amp; Country.  So yes, I have supported your job with the cars I have purchased.  In case you are wondering, not one of the cars that I purchased was built in Japan and all paid for with my own money.  So I have supported this city and the American Auto Industry for many years, and will continue to do so.  I took my first job at the age of 12 and went to work in a Plastic Injection mold factory on Groesbeck at the age of 18 on the midnight shift, my first look at a union, oh that was fun.  This helped me decide to go to school.  My next job was as a laborer on a rough carpentry crew while going to school full time.  My next job was delivering to auto factories for one of the Auto Companies while completing my education.    My two best stories of Union workers; the guy I had to wake up to ask him to sign my paperwork every time I stepped on his dock and the guys at a transmission plant that completed their quota a couple hours after they punched in and spent the rest of their day in the parking lot with a BBQ and Cold beer playing cards.  So please, don’t pull your psycho babble on me, I have worked amongst you and while there are some great union workers out there, there are many more really bad ones.   I can speak first hand to the greed I have witnessed.  So again, is corporate greed bad and Union Greed ok?   No, I don’t believe everything I am told but, I do believe everything I see firsthand.   Your very elementary lesson left out some key facts.   Bob had to pay four union guys for every glass of juice produced.  One guy to squeeze the juice and two others to watch and make sure no seeds hit the floor, then a fourth to just be a Union Committee Man.  He didn’t do any work other than for the union but, Bob still had to pay him.    Because of all the unwarranted overtime they all worked and adding in the big taxes from the government, Bob’s juice now cost $20 a glass.  While most of us still purchased Bob’s juice to keep him in business, some people just couldn’t afford it any longer so Bob could not sustain his business, so people that didn’t get over inflated union wages were forced to buy from Bill to get their daily dose of Vitamin C.   While Bob went out of business, the union employees that worked for him still got 95% of their pay while they played cards in the back room of his shop, a room they lovingly called the Job Bank.  Then the Government stepped in and bought Bob’s juice and gave it to the Union guys and subsidized it for them.  With the subsidy, they were still able to play cards in the Job Bank and the rest of us still paid for the juice through our taxes, even though no more juice was ever produced.   Give me a break with your truly elementary economics lessons, you are very myopic.    Now, please wipe the Smug Smile Off your face.  I know my math very well and I also REALIZE that my NEIGHBORS are tired of YOU’RE union crap BECAUSE, now that Bob is out of business his building is the first to fall into disrepair and start the destruction of our fair city.  Look up the Broken Window Theory of Economics if you would like to learn more on this topic.   </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/55gu1t</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zwnv</id></website><link>http://blogs.denverpost.com/captured/2011/02/07/captured-the-ruins-of-detroit/2672/</link><postedTime>2011-03-08T22:49:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-04-06T04:38:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/8w49uc</id><link>http://blogs.denverpost.com/captured/2011/02/07/captured-the-ruins-of-detroit/2672/#comment-178913631</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-03-08</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>