<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkl3zs/update/2012-03-25T14:06:51/b430502f16389d8af81477fb81598aa3fdeda20d1097885682b21d55144cd050</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mk8yep</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zmnk8</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Hospitals can't magically fix all those things either. We planned our home birth keeping in mind that transport was a 5 minute drive down the street... and the reaction time of the hospital isn't much faster than that. In my birth, the things that were scary were caused by hospital interventions. They were necessary interventions in our circumstance, but they were NOT things that could have happened at home. 

My blood pressure could NOT have dropped to 50/20 in the middle of labor at home, because I would have been in tub, not getting an epidural. I needed pitocin for a variety of reasons, so we transported, but if I could have gone into labor at home, it would have been safer than the epidural was. The majority of problems the hospital handles better either are more likely to happen there in teh first place, give enough advanced warning in most cases that they can be handled with a transport from home, or are the kinds of things that can happen without labor, in which case they will happen at home even if a hospital birth is planned. 

The people I know who've abrupted did so unexpectedly, not in labor. Midwives carry pit and cytotec in my state, ONLY for dealing with PPH, and it buys enough time for a transport in the vast majority of cases, but a PPH is LESS likely to happen when there is not surgery, induction, etc. My sister had HELLP... and her midwife Spotted the early warning symptoms and transported her, so she could have a c-section. Umbilical cord compression is easily detected with intermittent monitoring, and is much less likely in a mobile, active mom who is changing positions often... and cord accidents happen sometimes no matter where a mom gives birth, sometimes before labor. We cannot fix everything, no matter how much we want to imagine that we could. Neonatal sepsis is much more likely in a hospital environment, due to the hospital environment. Dystocias can be problems anywhere, but midwives have good skills for dealing with them. The women I know who've had ruptured uteruses either ruptured during induced labor in the hospital, or before labor began at all, at home. It is POSSIBLE for a woman to rupture her uterus at home without induction during labor, but the likelihood is much lower when pitocin, cervical ripening agents and AROM are not used... and much lower still if a primary c-section is not performed. The lowest risk of c-section is in a home birth. 

Our local hospital was a tricky situation... if I'd tried to plan a hospital birth, the only one who would take me was the Perinatology clinic.  I was technically too high risk for the CNM practice, but my CPM was willing to work with me and consult with a perinatologist. When we did decide to transport, because I was using a CPM, they had us under the care of an OB who would not have covered my care if I'd come to her in pregnancy, but who was VERY willing to work with us to help me have the least traumatic birth possible. I couldn't have planned a hospital birth and had the outcome we did (despite pitocin and epidural, I was able to birth lying on my side, my midwife providing perineal support and my husband catching the baby) because the perinatology protocols are so different from the "stork doc" (homebirth transport receiving) protocols. And I'm fortunate to live in an area where midwives are licensed and therefor not afraid of prosecution, so they can consult as professionals with the OBs and transport without fear. I live in an area where the hospital wants to treat women and babies as well as they possibly can so that women will transport if they need to without being afraid. Lambasting people for choosing to birth at home is NOT the way to make birth safer. The way to make birth safer is to create a teamwork environment so that women who seek out the Comforts of home and midwife are not afraid to transport when needed. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6mig2j</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/eyjq</id></website><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2012/03/the-most-scientific-birth-is-often-the-least-technological-birth/254420/</link><postedTime>2012-03-20T12:11:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-25T18:06:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkl3zs</id><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2012/03/the-most-scientific-birth-is-often-the-least-technological-birth/254420/#comment-475934504</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gnmka</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>