<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mvsql6/update/2012-02-28T17:24:09/7d43c8459bb8dbc588b51fe4c5a29bd66370e76528f743a682a49255c618eddd</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Here is today's official John P number-crunching exercise.  If you want to follow along, you too can become a cult-buster using just an Internet connection and a calculator to expose the avalanche of lies and craziness from our favorite foundering bunch of whack jobs.  

All these numbers might sound boring, but remember that the accountants were the heroes who brought down Al Capone after the mighty FBI with all their guns and badges struck out for years.  

Let's dissect the e-mail offer from Galaxy Publications.  It starts  "Dear Educator/Librarian." So it sounds like they're sending this to a bunch of teachers and librarians. How many e-mails might they be sending out?  Well, the American Library Association web site claims 60,000 members.  And there are a lot more educators than librarians.  The National Education Association claims 3.2 million members.  But let's suppose, just to be conservative, that merely 500,000 (15%) of those are lucky enough to receive this Scientology spam bomb. 

Since this is a number-crunching exercise, we won't bother to critique the ad copy in the body of the letter.  So we won't be pointing out how the opening sentence is utter FAIL.  It asks me if I may have ever wondered what pulp fiction is all about.  There are one of two possible responses to the question -- either "no, I never have" (not too likely for librarians) or "yes, I have, but I stopped wondering a long time ago."  Then it simply tells me that I should listen to one of the free starter kits to find out.  

We also won't point out how this letter breaks every rule of direct mail -- you're supposed to make the product you're selling seem exciting and a must-have revolutionary offering.  There is nothing here to tell me what I'm missing by not being into the Next Big Thing in popular fiction.  The "selling proposition," the opening question, needs to be one that everyone can agree with.  You ask, "Do you worry about stale cooking odors," not "What are you going to do about the smell of tarragon-infused baked haddock in your house?"  

We won't laugh at how they don't tell the librarians that nostalgic interest in pulp fiction is exploding (with some bogus stats, of course, to show just how big this trend is).  We'll overlook how they miss an opportunity to tell me why L. Ron Hubbard is the definitive writer in the genre that should be represented in the collection ahead of just about anybody else.  

And we certainly won't talk about how, after this energizing prose hits the in-box, all the Scientology people have to do is sit back and hope.  Hope the reader doesn't ask why they should take up shelf space with a bunch of books from a single author, when an anthology of pulp stories from a bunch of different authors would be a much better way to cover the field. And hope that the librarian reading this lame sales pitch has no idea who L. Ron Hubbard was, so they would have no idea that this is a thinly disguised plot to expose unaware readers to Scientology (we'll ignore the amazing scam-within-a-scam where the &lt;i&gt;real&lt;/i&gt; scam is about getting rich Scientologists to buy the books).  

Nope, we'll focus only on the numbers.  First is the size of the mailing.  Taking the 560,000 potential recipients we've assumed above, how many &lt;i&gt;should&lt;/i&gt; to respond an offer for a free set of books?  Typical response rate for direct mail marketing is about 3%, and is often a bit higher for a no-risk free offer, where you get to keep the product no matter what. So let's assume that 4% of the 560,000 recipients would request a set of the books in an average direct mail piece.  You would expect to see 22,400 LRH pulp novel starter kits flying  the shelves in the weeks after a promo like this drops.  

How can we make an informed guess about whether that actually happened?  Let's look at the web statistics for the Galaxy Press web site.  We go to Alexa (dot) com, a free web metering site.  Type in galaxypress (dot) com, and you get a wealth of information.  First thing that pops up is the site ranking.  This major e-commerce hub is currently the 4,182,180th most popular site on the Web. That's an embarrassment, but it doesn't help us answer the question.  

What we want is to get the number of unique visitors hitting the site each month.  That's the "Reach" statistic.  Here, we get 0.000023% of the world comes to check out the LRH population. I'm using 250,000,000 million as a total wired Internet access population (the number of smart phones is much higher but those aren't likely to be people accessing the site).  So you're looking at about 5,700 monthly users (3-month average) hitting the site. 

Some of those are likely to be Scientologists looking in response to other direct mail pieces. So it seems reasonable to believe that only a percentage of those 5,700 users are the lucky librarian/educator recipients of the e-mail.  Let's say it's 1/4 of the total.  So the fact that the e-mail generated 1,400 instead of 22,400 hits means this direct mail campaign is already looking like serious fail.  

But let's try and figure out exactly how many LRH pulp fiction sets are going out the door.  The best way to do that is to look at the page views/user statistic.  Alexa says GalaxyPress (dot) com users visit an average of 3.1 pages daily (a reasonable proxy for per-visit).  Let's assume two different common use cases for a visitor to the site.  One use case is somebody who looks at the home page and perhaps at one title, then moves on to another site.  It takes three page views to from the home page to the "Golden Age" section and then to click on the page for the title so I can figure out just what the hell a "Chee-Chalker" is.  So we'll assume that half of the "tourist" visitors look at the home page before fleeing, and the other half look at three pages (home, category, and title).  So we'll assume 1.5 pages per non-purchasing visitor.  That's a conservative number, and if it's low, then the number of orders we derive below is going to be way too high.

The other case is somebody who actually orders something from the site.  Let's assume it takes about 10 page views to complete an e-commerce transaction to get the pulp fiction starter set on its way to a grateful recipient.  I'm not going to give Scientology my credit card number to count page views in their ordering system; I'm sure you can understand.  

Crunching the numbers, out of those 5,700 users, at an average 3.1 pages per visit, you can estimate that about 700 users will be ordering per month, and 5,000 will be "casual" visitors that look but don't touch.  So what we come up with is a site that books a total of about 700 orders per month.  

Remember, we assumed that perhaps 1/4 of the business came from Mr. or Ms. Librarian/Educator who was suddenly seized by the Burning need to learn more about the pulp fiction of L. Ron Hubbard.  So they get about 175 orders from this offer.  That's an actual response rate of 0.03125%.  That's about 1/100 of the standard direct mail response rate.  Massive fail.  

Let's do one last calculation before we leave this over-battered equine corpse.  Let's not forget that some percentage of teachers and educators are Scientologists.  What's the percentage of the US population who are involved in the cult?  Current Census Bureau population estimate is 313.1 million, and credible estimates of Scientology membership in the US is 25,000, which equals 0.0079% of the population.  That's a small number, but it's enough to be statistically significant in the response percentage we got above...  We would want to correct for any Scientologists who are librarians or educators sending in the coupon (assume all did on pain of death from OSA), so we arrive at the net number of orders from the "wog" community.  Subtract, and we get a net non-Scientologist response rate of 0.02327%, or about 130 orders from non-Scientologists eager to learn about LRH's pulp fiction days by getting a FREE set of books.  EPIC FAIL!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yonwnx</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rpyi</id></website><link>http://blogs.villagevoice.com/runninscared/2012/02/scientology_drives_librarians_nuts.php</link><postedTime>2012-02-28T13:04:49+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-28T22:24:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mvsql6</id><link>http://blogs.villagevoice.com/runninscared/2012/02/scientology_drives_librarians_nuts.php#comment-451655146</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lxzrl</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>