<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/212653/post/93788979/comment/327852559</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>For more than five years now, San Jose Mayor Chuck Reed has had one of the toughest jobs anywhere. He\'s presided over pay cuts, layoffs and bitter union negotiations. He\'s had to say no far more than yes. It\'s turned him much grayer.Reed offered folks a glimpse of optimism in his State of the City speech Thursday night. But it came within 24 hours of a damaging KNTV report that highlighted the mayor\'s Achilles\' heel: his sometimes-errant political instinct.In a piece titled \"San Jose\'s Fuzzy Pension Math,\" KNTV investigative reporter Jenna Susko focused on a number: The piece asserted that the mayor used the number of $650 million for pensions,burberry borse, when the real annual cost was projected at $400 million.That report surfaced just as the unions filed an 11-page complaint with the city\'s elections commission, alleging that Reed \"knowingly misled\" the City Council and public about pension costs. The timing was no coincidence. In truth,borse Burberry, the KNTV report was thin gruel. True,Burberry Donne, the mayor had used the $650 million as a worst-case scenario for the fiscal year 2015-16. The Mercury News picked it up two or three times. But in his pension reform ballot proposal and union negotiations,P.F. Changs China Bistro - Sunnyvale, CA - San Jose Mercury News, he had relied on $400 million.And it\'s worth saying that even with a $400 million number -- or $300 million, the latest -- the city has a huge problem. It cannot afford to keep giving cops and firefighters 90 percent pensions. Almost everyone understands the system is not sustainable.Bad interviewBut Reed botched the KNTV interview -- and so, to a lesser extent, did city Retirement Services Director Russell Crosby, who first threw out the $650 million as a rough estimate and then,By Jim Harrington, twitter/jimthecritic, according to the KNTV report, tried to reel it back.When reporter Susko pressed Reed whether he should have sat down with Crosby and asked him where he got the $650 million number, the mayor responded, \"No.\"\"No?\" asked Susko.\"No,A+E Interactive Archive for John Orr,\" said Reed, who explained that he  understood it to be a rough estimate.The problem with that response, and a couple of others, is that it left behind the Faint aroma of Marie Antoinette (\"Let them eat cake\"). The mayor has premised his administration on reforming pensions. At best,louis vuitton borse, he looked careless with his facts. Worse,Nike Mercurial Vapor Elite, he looked like he didn\'t have much empathy for the people bearing the brunt of reform. And that\'s more damaging than a debate about numbers that are abstruse to most folks.I know the Scrooge image is misleading: Reed is a devoted, hardworking guy who is trying to reform a system that makes it all but impossible for the city to deliver basic services. Flip sideThe mayor\'s faults are the flip side of his virtues. He is straightforward, well-informed and extraordinarily honest for an elected official. But he doesn\'t have the patter that helps lubricate a tough answer.Given that, he probably should have insisted the interview take place in the hallway rather than his office. And he should have clung to a spiel that lifted him above the fray, no matter the question:\"Look, we  made clear that the $650 million number was a worst-case scenario. I may have used it longer than I should have. But whatever the number, we can\'t afford to delay reform. I know all this is hard on city employees. They work hard and serve us well. But we have a huge credit card bill. We have to pay it down, not quibble. The repo men are at the door.\"Contact Scott Herhold at or 408-275-0917. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:212653:93788979</id><idPostId>93788979</idPostId><idBlogId>212653</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:212653</id><idBlogId>212653</idBlogId><link>http://www.ourartcriticism.com</link><displayName>Our Art Criticism</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.ourartcriticism.com/interview/catherine-forster-talks-about-her-duel-creative-roles-as-an-artist-and-curator/</link><displayName>Catherine Forster talks about her duel creative roles as an artist and curator.</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T14:22:53.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:212653:93788979:327852559</id><link>http://www.ourartcriticism.com/interview/catherine-forster-talks-about-her-duel-creative-roles-as-an-artist-and-curator/#IDComment327852559</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T14:22:53.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Catherine Forster talks about her duel creative roles as an artist and curator. by wetgjjk1082h</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://besttlisseurghdfr1.com/</link><idEmailMd5>a00ee0649d933977c5dca1f4f6b4384f</idEmailMd5><displayName>wetgjjk1082h</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://besttlisseurghdfr1.com/"&gt;wetgjjk1082h&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.ourartcriticism.com/interview/catherine-forster-talks-about-her-duel-creative-roles-as-an-artist-and-curator/"&gt;Catherine Forster talks about her duel creative roles as an artist and curator.&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>