<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m32ztf/update/2012-03-28T15:56:11/e81a4db2116ac485fc536fc6d27f7d363df12a3b741d970e7c128b5cb420cdaf</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jlhk3TRp6BI

Whenever I listen to this song, I think about how great it would fit in Majora's Mask.  It's actually unfortunate that the Stone Tower Temple music is so good--because otherwise, I'd have to trade it out for the song I posted above.  And that, coupled with this topic, has got me thinking.

A lot of people seem to be on one of two sides.  One side seems to want to turn Zelda into Skyrim, with total free-roaming, loads of sidequests, tons of optional dungeons, complex upgrading systems, vast worlds, etc.  The other side seems to want to turn Zelda into a movie, with complex plots, morals, cinematic battles, giving Link a personality, voice , etc.  I feel like both of these visions for Zelda don't fit the series at all, and I'm a little WORRIED that Retro is working on Zelda, because I'm concerned that a Western studio would (incorrectly) choose one of those directions.

I think Nintendo knows how much free-roaming AND how much story to put into their games, and I think they do that fine.  Look at Wind Waker--it had a strong story AND strong free-roaming/extras/etc.  And if you want a stronger story, or you want Skyrim, or you want something realistic, go play something else (I'll never understand why people think Skyrim is a good direction for Zelda to go).  Very clearly, Nintendo treats the Zelda series as art, and the ideal Zelda game, in my opinion, is a work of art.  The best three Zelda games after you take nostalgia out of the mix are Majora's Mask, Wind Waker, and Skyward Sword, and all of these took different artistic directions that really made them stand out.

I don't think Nintendo needs to make a game with thousands of dungeons.  I think in the ideal Zelda games, dungeons would just need to have a "wow" factor.  That's something Skyward Sword nailed.  Its dungeons, particularly the Lanayru Mining Facility and the Ancient Cistern, gave me Shivers.  Think of the Stone Tower Temple from Majora's Mask.  Didn't that wow you?  Majora's Mask only had four (arguably six if you count Ikana Castle and the Pirate Fortress) dungeons, but it was just fine.

For me, the ideal Zelda game would be like the song I linked to: quirky, weird, dark, but also whimsical and vivid.  We've seen Hyrule thousands of times, and for all you die-hard TP fans who keep demanding a full HD, realistic Zelda, I hate to break it to you, but Hyrule won't be all that different from what we saw in TP already.  More-detailed graphics won't be that much of an improvement, and I think Nintendo has to keep that in consideration as they make the next Zelda game.  I'd like a Zelda game ON A CONSOLE that takes place outside of Hyrule.  I'd love to see Holodrum or Labyrinna in 3D splendor, but somewhere new is okay as well.  I'd just want it to be surreal, like Link's Awakening or the official artwork of Majora's Mask (have you guys SEEN its concept art?  Wow!).

I think another Hyrule game, especially in better graphics, would be overdone.  Think about it, it would just be like if they kept making Super Mario 64 over and over again and just improved the graphics each time.

A dark Zelda game would be great.  But not an in-your-face dark like in Twilight Princess; I mean something like Majora's Mask or Link's Awakening, something where the darkness is lurking in the shadows, subtle, implicit.  I love the feeling of traveling a bright, cheerful world, knowing in the back of my head that there's an eerily dark touch to everything.  And speaking of Majora, that is one villain that desperately needs to be brought back.  There's only one timeline where she's done away with; what happens to her in some of the other timelines?

I think the graphics should be very bizarre, but not overly so.  It would be really cool to see something like the official artwork for Majora's Mask, or the concept art.  Tie that in with strange world or electronic music, and you'll have a very unique and memorable Zelda title.

Story-wise, Skyward Sword's take on romance was great (especially because it wasn't explicit), and it would be nice to see another emotional drive to saving the world.  I don't think it needs to be "mature," though; otherwise, kids won't understand anything that's going on.

And actually, going back to the location, now that I think of it it would be great to be able to go to more than one kingdom in the ideal Zelda game.  I Always was curious as to how Holodrum, Labyrinna, and Hyrule fit together (is Holodrum southeast of Hyrule?  Note the location of the Lost Woods...).  Or, to tie into the surreal aspect, there could be a sort of dream world, or alternate universe, or something like that, and we could switch between there and Hyrule.

I'm kind of going on and on, so I'll stop. :P</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l01d1</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/z5xv</id></website><link>http://www.zeldainformer.com/2012/03/forum-topic-of-the-day-describe-your-ideal-zelda-game.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T00:32:27+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T19:56:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m32ztf</id><link>http://www.zeldainformer.com/2012/03/forum-topic-of-the-day-describe-your-ideal-zelda-game.html#comment-478709341</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>