<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3v0np/post/2012-03-29T09:21:22</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkpw7s</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hoktw</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Hi Ashley,

Yes, you can broil the non-stick skillet. We've tested this recipe thoroughly. Because the the eggs are filling the pan, and the pan is in the oven for just 3 minutes, broiling the non-stick pan is safe. Additionally, non-stick pans will only start emitting fumes if the surface  temperatures in excess of 600 degrees, and the only way to get a pan that hot is to Heat it over a stovetop and forget about it. Here's some additional information on the safety of non-stick skillets. 

Best, 

Miriam
----------------
There’s been a fair amount of news and concern about the safety of nonstick cookware, which now account for more than half of all cookware sales in the U.S. What are the issues?
First, the production of nonstick surfaces can pollute the local ground water. This issue directly impacts anyone living near a manufacturing facility where nonstick surfaces are made.
Second, the ingestion of nonstick surfaces (once the coating starts to peel and ) probably isn’t good for you. Maybe the coating just passes through your system, maybe not. In any case, the coating is no longer working if it has started to  ; throw out the pan and buy another one.

Third, nonstick pans can emit fumes if the surface  temperatures in excess of 600 degrees. Manufacturers admit that these fumes can kill small birds and advise against keeping pet birds in the kitchen. These fumes can cause a Flu-like illness in humans.
So how much of a concern is this? We conducted several kitchen tests in which we exposed both cheap and good-quality nonstick pans to high Heat on the stovetop and under the broiler. We wanted to see how hot the cookware would get when used in recipes that call for high Heat like cooking a stir-fry. Using an infrared thermometer gun, we tracked temperatures and found only one way to get the temperature in the pan to 600 degrees: Heat an empty pan over a hot burner and forget about it.

Our recommendation: Never Heat any pan, nonstick or otherwise, without first putting some oil in the pan. The oil will smoke at 400 degrees—well before the surface of a nonstick pan will emit dangerous fumes. You will notice the smoking oil and can pull the pan Off the Heat. This is a good idea when using conventional pans too.

We continue to use nonstick cookware in the test kitchen, but for anyone who is looking for an alternative, we've found cast iron to be the most effective. Over time, cast-iron pans develop nonstick properties as the oils and fats used in cooking polymerize (the molecules change shape and link up) and essentially fuse with the surface of the pan. How much time? Clearly, the older and more seasoned the pan, the more "nonstick" it will become—as anyone who has been lucky enough to inherit their grandparents' cast-iron skillet will tell you. For the rest of us, it's never too late to start.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dwlod</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/1cvk</id></website><link>http://www.testkitchenschool.com/school/courses/essential-eggs/discussions</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T18:25:03+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:21:22+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3v0np</id><link>http://www.testkitchenschool.com/school/courses/essential-eggs/discussions#comment-479483165</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/r6omo</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>