<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwddcn/update/2012-03-30T09:45:12/54fed7f9622e5a6fb263d5fd56ad4a5da6bc0a3a31786a204b47f0b1742dda15</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>What about this Melenchon character running as an out and out communist in France and polling about 14%, with a bullet (Billboard-Hot100-metaphorically-speaking)?

I don't know even a bit about him but he seemingly pulls no punches, attacks the far right, the near right and the "socialists" all with equal gusto with the sarcasm of a  blogger and he seems to be striking a minour,  if not yet a major, chord.

Where is the British Melenchon? The Greek? The Spanish?

This space to the "left of Labour" sorely needs opening and that opening has to begin in Europe.

For here in the US, I'm afraid, we all realise that a US Melenchon will be lynched, high tech or otherwise, if she Reaches anything near 10% in the polls. This is why we've had to suffer the drip drip drip of third party fakes like Ralph Nader, whose "outsider" status no one can seriously rally around. The wan impotence of third party pinkos who nonetheless stir delusional dreaming among progressives every four years has been nothing short of a disaster for US leftism. If we are going to die of useless old age, at least lets go out choking on some red meat instead of the phony foie gras of middle class reformism.

The US left is terrified of its shadow since the 1960s.....and we're too scared to Bleed.
Like the apostles, we need a populist left leader to build upon. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67czgu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rzls</id></website><link>http://leninology.blogspot.com/2012/03/galloway-wins.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T12:43:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:45:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwddcn</id><link>http://leninology.blogspot.com/2012/03/galloway-wins.html#comment-480753920</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>