<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkppm0/update/2012-03-26T16:35:36/0421f65a35842730a651764a38e62e35c05ac9f5d0c397c5b43fa4d0f1133cd5</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Stanley Tucci and Lenny Kravitz both took me by surprise, because I anticipated them both being around adequate and instead they were picture perfect!  And Effie was brilliant.  And Prim's face was so well cast that they didn't have to give her a single line because her face explained her entire role in motivating Katniss.  And J-Law's presence just held together every scene she was in.  It was hard to even look at the other characters while she was there.  Honorable mentions to Seneca, Rue, Thresh, and the set decorators.  No love for Peetah, Gale, and Cato (personal pout and flounce for me).

What I didn't like (and of course I like a lot more but I didn't want to write a novel of gushing):

!) I wish they had taken the time to explain Katniss's father's death, her mom's ensuing, debilitating depression, and the starvation it consequently brought the family into, a bit better.  I'm not sure how well it came across to non-book readers, but I think that backstory is the absolute key to Katniss's character and all the decisions she makes throughout the series.  Learning, at such a young age, that she can't Depend on loved ones to be there for her in the end.  Learning that people she loves die and suffer and there's little to nothing she can do to fix that reality no matter how hard she tries (and is a big part of the reason she adamantly never wants kids of her own).  Why she so desperately feels like Prim needs her.  Why she's so self-sufficient (she had to be or she would have starved).  It also gives much greater significance to Peetah throwing her the bread.  

I'm not sure how much of this was there to non-readers but it came across to me like her mom was glum for a few days and so Katniss yelled at her until she snapped out of it.  Oh, and it apparently happened earlier that year since she and Prim didn't look any younger (she was like ten years old, right?)

2)  I wish the movie was either a half hour longer or that more of the plot had been cut from it.  I just felt like a lot of the scenes couldn't breathe.  Physically, the stakes of the Games felt very low (aside from the rampant risk of murder, of course).  She needs water, she finds it in about 15 seconds.  Peetah's almost dead from Fever, he gets the life-saving medicine in five minutes.  No one in the arena seemed very hungry or thirsty, or tired or Cold, or in danger of contaminated water or anything else.  No one's health seemed in danger in any real way.  Taking this physical reality out of the equation made it, for me, more of just a gladiator movie.  And it made Katniss's ability to hunt out food and vegetation seemed like an extra credit perk rather than a very valuable personality trait.

3) I felt like they took away some of Katniss's smarts.  The tracker jacker nest was her strategy completely, not Rue's (she only pointed out it was there so Katniss wouldn't get stung).  Her and the berries...I mean, what they had there was okay, but I don't think they did it justice.  It was a brilliant epiphany to get out of an impossible situation, and Katniss's quick thinking, cynicism, big heart, desperation, and understanding the psychology of the gamemaker's understanding of their audience, all had to be there.  I just don't think any of that got across in any significant way.

4) Unpopular opinion, but I didn't like the District 11 riot (even though Rue's dad did a freaking amazing job with his 20 seconds of screentime).  It just didn't belong in the first movie, I felt.  Sharing the berries was supposed to be the pivotal moment in the trilogy, the action that sparks the rebellion in all the districts, the moment that shows the Capitol isn't all powerful.  Snow pontificated (in CF) for a few pages on how dangerous and significant that moment was.  By having a riot so much earlier, it makes Katniss's role in the revolution (the one she never meant or wanted to start) pretty irrelevant, to the point where it confuses the whole point of her being a Rosa Parks of the whole rebellion.

Oh Melissa, I'm so happy you started this thread.  I loved the Hunger Games!

ps- sorry I left a novel :(
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lc6kr</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ync</id></website><link>http://shakespearessister.blogspot.com/2012/03/hunger-games-thread.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:53:01+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T20:35:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkppm0</id><link>http://shakespearessister.blogspot.com/2012/03/hunger-games-thread.html#comment-476722223</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/chwlm</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>