<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mko5lk/update/2012-03-26T15:07:06/0367ebad3345d826905b79e4c8dfd2403f981150748ef11dd62c0de3672f0eb4</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Look we can't let this fall apart. Next they will be claiming that maybe he could have been possibly stoned and was Acting suspecious when Spotted by zimmerman. Already the media is questioning the date of the baby face little boy picture.. They must not ever ruin this and post recient pictures of a six foot three guy with a mouth of gold teeth and tat's all over (or burses) like he really looked on the night he alledgedly beat the living daylights out of zimmerman, broke his nose and had him on his back screaming like a baby..  Facebook if not already, must be expunged of any reference of "friends" wanting to know where he was because they want to buy "plants". Those plants were likely roses cause the fourteen year old boy in that picture was innocent of all and we should remember him not the near adult.
No it's all about an innocent kid buying skittles and ice tea. (which if you happen to be stoned might sound really good I am told) The main thing to remember is that the balck panthers have a ten grand price on zimmermans head and they will be around long after this shakes out.
That is what the people want imo. An excuse to hate.. Believe a spin story and dam who might end up hurt or worse before this tragety turned farce is over. Remember race baiting and hatred often have fatalities of innocent bystanders.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r0c13</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yzhx</id></website><link>http://www.miamiherald.com/2012/03/26/2714778/thousands-expected-at-trayvon.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T15:37:07+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T19:07:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mko5lk</id><link>http://www.miamiherald.com/2012/03/26/2714778/thousands-expected-at-trayvon.html#comment-476643343</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zgyvd</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>