<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/304747/post/127824533/comment/327935480</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Not surprised-he is a christian hater. 
 
April 2008 &amp;ndash; Obama speaks disrespectfully of Christians, saying they &amp;ldquo;cling to guns or religion&amp;rdquo; and have an &amp;ldquo;antipathy to people who aren&amp;rsquo;t like them.&amp;rdquo; 
February 2009 &amp;ndash; Obama announces plans to revoke conscience protection for health workers who refuse to participate in medical activities that go against their beliefs, and fully implements the plan in February 2011. 
April 2009 &amp;ndash; When speaking at Georgetown University, Obama orders that a monogram symbolizing Jesus&amp;rsquo; name be covered when he is making his speech. 
May 2009 &amp;ndash; Obama declines to host services for the National Prayer Day (a day established by federal law) at the White House. 
April 2009 &amp;ndash; In a deliberate  of disrespect, Obama nominated three pro-abortion ambassadors to the Vatican; of course, the pro-life Vatican rejected all three. 
October 19, 2010 &amp;ndash; Obama begins deliberately omitting the phrase about &amp;ldquo;the Creator&amp;rdquo; when quoting the Declaration of Independence &amp;ndash; an omission he has made on no less than seven occasions. 
November 2010 &amp;ndash; Obama misquotes the National Motto, saying it is &amp;ldquo;E pluribus unum&amp;rdquo; rather than &amp;ldquo;In God We Trust&amp;rdquo; as established by federal law. 
January 2011 &amp;ndash; After a federal law was passed to transfer a WWI Memorial in the Mojave Desert to private ownership, the U. S. Supreme Court ruled that the cross in the memorial could continue to stand, but the Obama administration refused to allow the land to be transferred as required by law, and refused to allow the cross to be re-erected as ordered by the Court. 
 
Acts of preferentialism for Islam: 
May 2009 &amp;ndash; While Obama does not host any National Day of Prayer event at the White House, he does host White House Iftar dinners in honor of Ramadan. 
April 2010 &amp;ndash; Christian leader Franklin Graham is disinvited from the Pentagon&amp;rsquo;s National Day of Prayer Event because of complaints from the Muslim community. 
April 2010 &amp;ndash; The Obama administration requires rewriting of government documents and a change in administration vocabulary to remove terms that are deemed offensive to Muslims, including jihad, jihadists, terrorists, radical Islamic, etc. 
August 2010 &amp;ndash; Obama speaks with great praise of Islam and condescendingly of Christianity. 
August 2010 &amp;ndash; Obama went to great lengths to speak out on multiple occasions on behalf of building an Islamic mosque at Ground Zero, while at the same time he was silent about a Christian church being denied permission to rebuild at that location. 
2010 &amp;ndash; While every White House traditionally issues hundreds of official proclamations and statements on numerous occasions, this White House avoids traditional Biblical holidays and events but regularly recognizes major Muslim holidays, as evidenced by its 2010 statements on Ramadan, Eid-ul-Fitr, Hajj, and Eid-ul-Adha. 
October 2011 &amp;ndash; Obama&amp;rsquo;s Muslim advisers block Middle Eastern Christians&amp;rsquo; access to the White House. 
February 2012 &amp;ndash; The Obama administration makes effulgent apologies for Korans being Burned by the U. S. military, 51 but when Bibles were Burned by the military, numerous reasons were offered why it was the right thing to do. 
Biblically hostile ... yet prefere </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:304747:127824533</id><idPostId>127824533</idPostId><idBlogId>304747</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:304747</id><idBlogId>304747</idBlogId><link>http://americanvisionnews.com</link><displayName>American Vision News</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://americanvisionnews.com/2635/obama-bypasses-congress-gives-1-5-billion-to-muslim-brotherhood</link><displayName>Obama bypasses Congress, gives $1.5 billion to Muslim Brotherhood</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:01:14.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:304747:127824533:327935480</id><link>http://americanvisionnews.com/2635/obama-bypasses-congress-gives-1-5-billion-to-muslim-brotherhood#IDComment327935480</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:01:14.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Obama bypasses Congress, gives $1.5 billion to Muslim Brotherhood by michaelle</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>d41d8cd98f00b204e9800998ecf8427e</idEmailMd5><displayName>michaelle</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>michaelle commented on &lt;a href="http://americanvisionnews.com/2635/obama-bypasses-congress-gives-1-5-billion-to-muslim-brotherhood"&gt;Obama bypasses Congress, gives $1.5 billion to Muslim Brotherhood&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>