<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m30agi/post/2012-03-30T02:37:19</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Liverpool have stagnated as a club in the past few years. 



On the positive side - the club finally have stable ownership and the owners have made the right sort of noises regarding their plans for the club; new kit and shirt sponsors have enhanced our ability to compete financially in  the transfer market; and the club have won their first trophy in almost six years this season. 



Less positive is my view of the everlasting stadium issue. Though the FSG have seemingly made the right sort of noises on the topic, I've come to believe that they are not very serious about it or at the very least lack a sense of real urgency. What else am I to believe when it has been almost 18 months since FSG took over and they are yet to even decide whether a new stadium is even required? What other conclusion can I derive from the game of brinkmanship the club and it's ownership indulged in with the Liverpool City Council regarding the Stanley Park land? 
My opinion may be controversial and unpopular but I am yet to be convinced that FSG have fully committed themselves to the long-run at Liverpool. FSG are in this for the profit and they know little about football - both things they've admitted. Deriving profits while challenging at the top end of the PL and CL is not an easy task as our financial reports down the years  have shown. I believe that last year was an a trial-run of sorts conducted by the FSG. Despite the significant transfer outlay our position in the league has not improved and frankly looks at risk of being worse than what it was last year. I fear that the results of this season may lead FSG to conclude that the club requires sustained long-term investment into it's playing squad to turn it's fortunes around. The Cold-hearted, pragmatic decision would then be to sell the club when such a sale would still get them profits than undertake a risky long-term investment than has little guarantee of success. FSG having no cultural or romantic attachment to Liverpool F.C. would imo not hesitate to take that decision. And this I truly believe is the real reason behind the lack of any visible progress on the stadium front. Why spend their money on a new stadium if they have no intent to stick around till the fruits of their investment are available for harvest? 
I may yet be proven wrong, and I pray that it be so, but that  largely on how well Dalglish and Comolli are able to convince the suits at FSG, not just JW Henry, that the club is on the right track and that we will be competing at the elite level next season. Hopefully they will succeed in this endeavor. 



Frankly negative issues include things that have happened/ are happening on and  the pitch. Nobody can deny that the racism saga and the way it was handled has been an unmitigated disaster. It has cast very poor light on our club and irrespective of whether Luis Suarez was guilty or not, has truly damaged our standing in the football world. The actual first team squad is an  embarrassment to the Liverpool F.C. shirt. Andy Carroll and Charlie Adam are not worthy of wearing the Liverpool shirt. Henderson and Downing have shown some flashes of quality
 but Adam and Carroll have been absolutely disastrous for our club. 
Suarez - highly lauded by us fans as he is- is a failure at what he was 
brought in to do i.e. score goals. Spearing is nothing more than a squad
 player. Enrique has been poor these past few weeks - yet Kenny Dalglish
 refuses to rest him.



Dalglish may try to justify his purchases all he wants but it has nonetheless made our club a laughing-stock. It has damaged our clubs prospects of landing good players in the future too- as the pathetic non-performance of these players has  yet another year without CL football for us. Besides which world-class player would wish to play alongside numpties like these? One could even suggest that our club is becoming progressively less attractive to world-class players. We don't offer CL football, the team is full of pedestrian quality players, and frankly our football at times this season has been abject. The romance of Liverpool F.C. can  as a draw for only so long in this day and age. 



Coming to a person about whom speaking negative is anathema to most fans
 - Kenny Dalglish. I'm a young Asian fan of Liverpool F.C. My memories of Liverpool F.C. begin in the PL Era. I know of the glorious histroy of our club and the part Kenny Dalglish had in that history. But to me that is exactly what it is - history. I view our club with pragmatic eyes; without lenses shrouded by adoration for Kenny Dalglish. Please excuse me for saying this but this reign of Kenny Dalglish as manager has been one unmitigated disaster after another. The poor signings, his abjectly poor handling of the Suarez- Evra saga, his poor and churlish attitude during interviews, his unwarranted attacks against any who dare question his claims of progress or his signings; do I need go on? It is fine to defends one's track record or one's players but to ask those who question his version of things to take an intelligence check?.... I will confess that Kenny Dalglish would have been much better for me as a memory of a great player, manager and man than this caricature of everything that fans of other clubs accuse anybody associated with Liverpool of being - deluded, churlish and detached from any sense of perspective . He and his handling of our club in this past 14 months have definitely been detrimental to the image of our club and has left many supporters like me squirming in our seats in face of uncomfortable taunts from others- taunts for which we have no reply as the target things about our club that we have no defense for.  

In the broad view of things the positives of the last year and a half have been matched or even over-shadowed by the negatives. Our club has not grown - it has stagnated. There is no progress - no definitive news regarding a new stadium, no great team that could stake a claim to be amongst the best in the world, no CL football.... The only positives have been in terms of finance.... 



Kenny Dalglish can argue all he want's that the club has progressed but the truth is that we've not improved one iota. We're standing at the same Spot that Benitez left us in. Hodgson could not do anything - he was poor but his tenure was an inevitable failure given that he had to deal with miserable no-good idiots as owners and having close to zero money to improve the team and the fans turned on him big-time when the initial few results were not good. The role of Dalglish in the fall of Hodgson and the shambles we degenerated into is a highly controversial one and it is not something I care to discuss. Suffice to  say that everyone will have his or her opinions and so do I. Dalglish's tenure too has not seen us improve. There was that bump-up in form when he was appointed caretaker manager but since then it has all been poor. Our football has been poor, we do not impose our style on games that we play, we lose to mid-table and relegation form teams with alarming regularity- we only seem to play well against high-profile opposition and that is something that make me question the managerial acumen of Kenny Dalglish once again - what good is he as a manager if cannot motivate his players to play well in all their games?



No. Dalglish may seek to make us believe that this season has seen 
our team progress; that we should forget our abjectly poor form in the 
league and call our Carling Cup victory and FA Cup semi as progress... 
The truth though is that our club has become stagnant. A stagnant pool 
of water leads to decay and disease and I sure hope that the owners will
 do what is needed to revive our club before the rot truly sets in. A 
new and experienced manager (not Rafa Benitez) and a decent tranfer 
kitty for him would be a good start..... </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6rihxh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dxs5</id></website><link>http://www.thisisanfield.com/2012/03/give-kenny-just-a-little-more-time/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T11:38:58+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T06:37:19+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m30agi</id><link>http://www.thisisanfield.com/2012/03/give-kenny-just-a-little-more-time/#comment-480325026</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>