<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fxvl/update/2012-03-29T16:56:59/4d53d51b304310fb16b3280a88a989db9f08a0c0f950e256085f54016bf9e69f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m31swk</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l0hfl</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>So what?? He had a mild case of dengue Fever...so they say, but lets say he did. People go to work and school with the Flu,  has played with Colds before and allergies at Augusta....anyone knows a bad case of allergies feels just like the Flu. However, a mild strain of the achilles (he didn't know what it was at the time...tightness, some pain, and swelling) of an area that helped keep you out for almost 3 months last year 2 - 3 weeks prior to the masters is a whole other story. Most people in the golf community - analysts, PGA tour XM guys who follow along on course said it was the smart thing to do.

 I'd hate to send you to the grocery store for fruit because you seem to have a problem with apples and oranges. During that time (in the fall and Dec.)  was just coming out of injury, then began working full time in practice with foley...and since then has progressed steadily upward. He's now first in total driving for 2012, first in ball striking. His last 2 full stroke play events he's 2nd and 1st...If you're going back to last season...lets continue on to 2009, 2008, 1997 and include the 4 green jackets and experience that goes with them. It all comes down to who's peaking now and who's striking the ball the best. Rory will not have played a competive round in 3 weeks we'll see how that goes. Go to espn and read Harig's article on 's progression and then another one with stats  by a Columbia professor on 's numbers irons and  the tee. Rory is about to get schooled. Tiger smoked him last year and he didn't even have the game he has now.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h0lho</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/9dd2</id></website><link>http://www.golfchannel.com/news/golftalkcentral/couples-offers-thoughts-on-augusta/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T01:48:49+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:56:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fxvl</id><link>http://www.golfchannel.com/news/golftalkcentral/couples-offers-thoughts-on-augusta/#comment-479884764</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lwquo</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>