<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tixr/post/2012-03-29T10:20:22</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m37w1x</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6hcqb</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I have more questions.
You may have answerd this with pointing out the fact that Zimmermans father is a judge but what do the police have to Gain by attempting to cover up so many concrete facts? ex; the video clearly showing Zimmerman had no injuries. The facts point to Cold blood murder race has nothing to do with that. Him profiling is the "race" question which only points to another fact leading to murder.
second where are all of Zimmermans "black friends" or anyone that can credibly give a justification of his actions? If he was such a stand up guy wouldnt there be
people vouching to that besides other sububan whites? just saying...
The facts clearly show this was no case of self defense. This is a case of a vigilante with a gun who shot an innocent kid in Cold blood, furthermore the neglegant work of the police dept allowing this man to walk free to do it again. There is nothing that will ever justify the manner this child died especially not self defense. 
FYI NO ONE ACTUALLY WITNESSED WHAT HAPPEND, thats why the evidence is so key. What will condem Zimmerman and that Police dept is the video that CLEARLY shows Zimmerman had no injuries sustained despite the reports he was Bleeding from the back of his head/neck and nose.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zy6x3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ao2w</id></website><link>http://www.wivb.com/dpp/news/crime/martins-death-sparks-dialogue-on-race</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T10:51:02+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:20:22+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3tixr</id><link>http://www.wivb.com/dpp/news/crime/martins-death-sparks-dialogue-on-race#comment-479523359</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6ggv2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>