<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/323728/post/127788357/comment/327472160</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>As a Christian - I believe that creationism doesn&amp;#039;t belong in the schools.   However, I also don&amp;#039;t believe that evolution does either.  I have not seen credible evidence that humans landed on this earth because bacteria evolved into something complex. 
 
Godless, by Ann Coulter, has a wonderful chapter on evolution and how there really isn&amp;#039;t any credible proof of it.  The fact that scientists are researching it and therefore it&amp;#039;s called &amp;quot;science&amp;quot; doesn&amp;#039;t impress me.  It&amp;#039;s just politically expedient to keep feeding the evolutionary monster to keep creationism OUT.  Liberals live in fear that if they lose a toe-hold in the education system that Christians will swoop in and fill it.  They will perpetuate lies and go to great lengths to make sure their agenda moves forward and stays on top.  It&amp;#039;s part of the doctrine of liberalism just as creationism (which also eludes rational scientific explanation) is a doctrine of Christianity. 
 
Humans and animals ADAPT to their environment but we haven&amp;#039;t seen any true evolution that I&amp;#039;m aware of.  A fish might adapt from being a Cold water fish to a warm water fish - but it&amp;#039;s still a fish.  I could move to AZ and nearly pass out from the Heat for the first year I live there and not be bothered by it after that.  But, I haven&amp;#039;t Gained any special evolutionary cooling mechanisms to do cope nor did I turn into a lizard - I just adapted to the Heat.  To me, that&amp;#039;s not evolution. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:323728:127788357</id><idPostId>127788357</idPostId><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:323728</id><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><link>http://www.chrisisright.net</link><displayName>Chris Is RIGHT</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/?p=156</link><displayName>Why Conservatives Are Often Wrong About Science</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2010-05-24T11:02:57.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:323728:127788357:327472160</id><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/?p=156#IDComment327472160</link><postedTime>2010-05-24T11:02:57.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Why Conservatives Are Often Wrong About Science by RedMomBlueState</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://www.redmombluestate.com</link><idEmailMd5>dbb265c51b26e36261c10166292740ff</idEmailMd5><displayName>RedMomBlueState</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://www.redmombluestate.com"&gt;RedMomBlueState&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.chrisisright.net/?p=156"&gt;Why Conservatives Are Often Wrong About Science&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2010-05-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>