<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkpzfa/update/2012-03-26T16:14:18/629be0064f46406c5c287754fb83ac376f3fef80ceec711afd65da081f2b24a8</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I can't believe I agreed with Pat Buchanan on this one. There is the question of "self defense". 

First issue (aside from where I agree with Buchanan) is the use of 
force continuum which states you are justified in using force 1 step 
above what your aggressor is using on you. This, of course, can be 
altered  on circumstance. 


1) Command presence
2) Verbal orders
3) Soft empty-hand
4) Hard empty-hand
5) Less lethal force
6) Lethal force.


There are many variants to this but they all hold to this general setup. 


In this case, it's fairly obvious that Zimmerman was attacked (wait 
for it... I'm not done on that subject). Trayvon Martin was armed with a
 bag of skittles and an iced tea. This would fall into the hard empty 
hand. Martin did some damage to Zimmerman judging by the reports of a 
nose Bleed and cut to the back of the head allegedly suffered by 
Zimmerman. 


Now, with a hard empty hand being used, Zimmerman would be allowed to
 use a level above that of which is used against him, in this case he 
would be allowed to use his fists or "environmental weapons" (a weapon 
found in his immediate area that is not likely to cause death). There 
are many things he could have done but chose to jump straight to lethal 
force. I find any number of things wrong with this fact alone.


Second issue is this. Why was a volunteer community patrolman arming 
himself? I was a member of the Guardian Angels for 
several years. None of us were ever armed and in fact most chapters 
don't even carry handcuffs. "Weapon" in this case does include pepper 
spray. In 30+ years how many people did the Guardian Angels kill? None. 
How many Angels killed? 5.


Third issue, (this is where Buchanan actually agreed with me) the 
"stand your ground" law is intended to be used in situations when you 
are clearly being assaulted. You do not have to back down to an 
aggressor. While he was on the phone with police the dispatcher asked 
Zimmerman if he was following Martin. Zimmerman answered "yes" and the 
dispatcher told him "you don't need to be doing that". There is no 
aggression at this point from Martin so the law doesn't apply. After 
this comment there is a confrontation between the 2 that gets physical. 
Zimmerman is injured and decides he's losing the fight and he is going 
to shoot. That is not in question. 


The reality is the "stand your ground" law does in fact apply. It 
applies to Trayvon Martin. This kid was walking home and had an unknown,
 armed, man following him around saying God knows what to him. Trayvon 
easily, and rightfully, could have felt threatened by this and Acted to 
defend himself. He got the better of Zimmerman and lost his life as a 
result.


The bottom line is this. Zimmerman created the situation. Period. End
 of story. His claim of self defense is no different than somebody 
robbing a liquor store and then claiming he was defending himself when 
the clerk shot first. It's a disgustingly ludicrous claim and there is 
no reason whatsoever for this man to not have been locked up that night 
on at least manslaughter charges if not murder.
 </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r0w00</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/26/justice/florida-teen-shooting-poll/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T16:18:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T20:14:18+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkpzfa</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/26/justice/florida-teen-shooting-poll/index.html#comment-476703397</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lvo49</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>