<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwj8vf/update/2012-03-31T03:51:00/f7887d789971ac08e4956dbd9b8c0662898152398f0a07458177887b28ab104e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I know what mr Cook is writing about .

I have been there and done that when I was young  ,fit but broke and no place to call home, just keep moving till you find a farm in season and if you were lucky it would have some basic accomodation but  walking and hoping not to come across those big mean dogs farmers like to keep ,nothing gets me out of a place faster than when I was halfway up a farmers driveway and you would see a couple big dog starting to run towards me.

People worked in the fields that were sprayed the night before but I have also been exposed by the overflow carried down by the wind by planes spraying in the next paddock during the day.
Shot guns fired right over our heads to scare the fruit eating birds away while we worked crouched over the ground and yeah it was often Too hot to go bare foot if you know what I mean.

The numba one rule for working outside in an extreme hot climate is not to rely on anyone else to supply you with drinking water , you simply must bring your own and carry it if needed.
If you cannot bring your own than better bring a cup rather than to drink from the same water can.

The money never was brilliant but in a way people can save money by not paying rent and eating whatever produce is available from the harvest , or even the throwbacks that wont make it to market.
Now I have skin cancer to show for my time spend under the hot desert sun.
But the comraderie was great and I will Always remember it.
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/671m6e</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ant8</id></website><link>http://www.alternet.org/food/154775/why_are_people_dying_to_bring_you_dinner_the_shocking_facts_about_our_food_system/comments/</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T07:18:35+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T07:51:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwj8vf</id><link>http://www.alternet.org/food/154775/why_are_people_dying_to_bring_you_dinner_the_shocking_facts_about_our_food_system/comments/#comment-481633081</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/55g7k</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>