<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzjgr/update/2012-03-30T14:43:05/940d748bc4ed1b3d72121596e95028d8a39189e39d88519f9fc2db5f880b3790</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The media has made a step forward. Pictures of a twelve-year-old Martin are being shown less frequently. Maybe there is hope for finding the truth in this case.
 
Thank you, George Zimmerman. You did a great job and, if you are reading this, you should realize that there is no need to be depressed over what you were forced to do. People support you and no flash mob racist is going to change that.

At his school, Trayvon Martin once had marijuana residue in a bag in his possession, a pipe for smoking it, and a screwdriver used by burglars. 

It was discovered that there were items of women's jewelry in his backpack, none of which he could justify as being his. The school police reported this to the Miami-Dade Police Department as a possible case of stolen merchandise.

In addition, he had painted obscene graffiti and was Spotted by school officials hiding and covering his face.

His Twitter account includes a comment by his cousin on February 21 that speaks of him "swinging at the bus driver."

His Facebook page includes pictures of him displaying obscene gestures, showing Off his gold teeth (like a typical black criminal), and standing with his pants sagging to his knees.

He was absent and late so many times that his school suspended him for ten days.

In total, he had been kicked out of the same school three times for these various offenses. We can only imagine what else baby Trayvon was involved in at his school (gang activity, bullying, etc.).

Multiple witnesses confirm Zimmerman's story, in one case having seen Martin on top of him (attacking him, of course).

In other words, he did not care about "making his family proud." He was a typical thuggish

S C U M B A G .

Instead of trying to profit from his death by trademarking phrases containing his name, his opportunistic mother should have actually raised him TO BE A MAN.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67g7ix</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/us/trayvon-martin-profile/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T14:20:51+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:43:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzjgr</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/30/us/trayvon-martin-profile/index.html#comment-481058543</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ldcxx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>