<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jaie/update/2012-04-02T02:17:39/02fbdada37a65dbcca8cf7a6ddee62c73428102d8fc1226da7aa65a7e57f5cdb</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This is unfortunate for the victims, Nation, law-enforcement and Justice. Seems like Justified/Subsidized, assassinations, and vigilante Mentality/morality.

It is becoming an Epidemic of proportions where the victim count is Piling up. These Individuals committing such  of Vigilante- morality- Justice are pathological by Nature. Spawning Dr.Jeckyl, Mr. Hyde personas. They can morph/mutate into transformers, terminators,Robo-cops, in the 21st Century Matrix (They have plenty of Time/mistakes to kill un-armed Citizens). One would think Officers would be better prepared/trained to handle every situation ( Even  the average LA driver knows they must be prepared to, expect, the UN-expected!) Why aren't they? (If they can't take the HEAT they should get out of the kitchen,obviously some Officers, Police- departments aren't ready/built to handle the JOB) Officers are trained to make mistakes, They have a false sense of Power,reality,security and preparation. Officers are trained to react to situations instead of logically assessing the facts( they Depend more on Weapons/Fear/ adrenalin, than on Common-sense and are excused/rewarded. A curse to the Public. 

 When a Police Officer/Department can shoot/pump lead into an Individual 20,30,40 times and Justify their Actions as Lawful,get a clue America. It becomes an epidemic of proportions..."shoot first ask questions later"  Zimmermann didn't need TRAINING, or badge just hatred and lack of control. They become Judge,Juror and executioner and then they came for YOU. It was just All a mistake and misunderstanding a little too late. ALEC and the NRA can care less.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/676bds</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ewhe</id></website><link>http://www.thegrio.com/news/kendrec-mcdade-case-man-considered-victim-turned-suspect-in-shooting.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:21:09+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T06:17:39+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jaie</id><link>http://www.thegrio.com/news/kendrec-mcdade-case-man-considered-victim-turned-suspect-in-shooting.php#comment-483311886</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/apzzq</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>