<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkuuxh/post/2012-03-26T10:36:06</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkzc82</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cvzxk</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> Yeah dude there's a thought. Let's turn ALL justice problems over to a people that hold down a 10 year old boy while a duece and a half runs over his arm for stealing an apple. Or how about stoning a girl and her mother (you know how that's done? Bury them until their heads are the only thing visible then let your 4 year old son start with the first rock) for letting her daughter touch a member of a different tribe/clan. Yeah dude, let's go there. Death to anyone that has the stupidity to question Islam, Death to anyone that converts to a more peacefull religion, death, death death. Death to a woman that wants education. Death to a woman that wants to go outside without a male relative. Death to a woman that wants to marry for love instead of marrying to keep the money in the family. Death to the woman that won't marry her nephew after she shamed her family by getting divorced by her husband.(3 stones thrown at her feet by said husband and he divorces her . She can, in some circles, touch a red hot spoon to her tongue and if it doesn't Burn her she is free) Yeah dude, turn him over. Throw out his service to let you speak this drivel and turn him over. Follow him there and Act as his counsel, see how far your good intentions will go in that land. Tell Daniel Pearle I said "Hi" you ignorant POS.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ryz7s</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnm3</id></website><link>http://www.sacbee.com/2012/03/25/4364823/afghans-us-paid-50000-per-shooting.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-25T11:17:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T14:36:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkuuxh</id><link>http://www.sacbee.com/2012/03/25/4364823/afghans-us-paid-50000-per-shooting.html#comment-476434993</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l73ha</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>