<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/eyywe9/update/2011-12-03T11:24:00/22a1ad5d9c7eea86af43804324fe110d569d7ece79665b47f85189276d834741</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Here's the thing: I use ViSalis. I am NOT a distributor, nor will I be. I don't care to be. I'm not in it for the money. I'm in it for the better nutrition and Weight loss.
So, from someone who isn't a sales person or anything like that, let me boil it down for you guys who keep arguing the same point back and forth: Find me any company, in the WORLD, that can offer nutrition like that for as cheap as that, without feeling hungry. It doesn't exist. You guys are all babbling from a marketing stand point. I'm a fat chick and interested in other end of it: what it does for me, health-wise.
I work 12 hour shifts, 99% of which I sit on my butt for, or run like crazy. I rarely take a break in that 12 hours, and often times, not at all. Nutritionally - that's really horrid. On days , I eat really well. When working, it's usually order out and eat on the fly.
ViSalis makes it supremely easy. What's easier than a shake that is not only nutritious, not packed with chemicals (have you seen some of the so-called health shakes out there? The ingredients are insane) and filling and only takes about 60 seconds to make?
Weight Watchers costs around the same as ViSalis for the same time period (plus 2 weeks), but you have to take the time to weigh, measure, and prepare your food. I can't do that on 12s very easily.
Or how about NutriSystem? One month is anywhere from $250 to nearly $400. 
Or Herbal Magic? I went there for their Free Consultation, which felt more like an interrogation followed by a brow-beaten sales pitch. Their quote to me? Just shy of $1200 to get started.
And that's just the tip of the barrel for some of the Weight loss things out there.

So, for ViSalis: It's simple. One or two shakes (I'm doing 2 a day for now, especially when on 12s), which are easy and rediculously convenient, along with a normal balanced meal and exercise.
They can keep the BMW. I'm an -road gal and wild horses can't take away my beloved Jeep! $239 price tag? I'll spend it in eating out or worse anyway. 
It's inexpensive, simple, and really awesome for someone who works the wild shifts that I do (and those 12 hour shifts are interspersed with a 2nd 9-5 type job that I work on as call-in consult), travels as much as I do, and needs the simplicity.
Stop talking the money and look at what it really is. If you make money Off it, great. If you want the car, great. I'll just use it for what I want, and it's working like a charm. Love this stuff.

....and it tastes awesome, which no one else out there can claim.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/eynqls</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/72ay</id></website><link>http://darrenlittle.com/visalus-review/</link><postedTime>2011-08-06T18:25:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-12-03T16:24:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/eyywe9</id><link>http://darrenlittle.com/visalus-review/#comment-378377810</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-08-06</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>