<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwdk13/update/2012-03-30T10:16:54/1667c5438cf095311c89fdce4f7b1efb24d0a410c3a387c61e6b83cf51a31bd2</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Interesting that you bring up Nazi Germany. Like the Germans, black Americans with the exception of a small shining percentage have gone insane and are completely driven by the emotions of envy and hatred. Many for money, some for blood. How else can the Cold hard math of actual race-based murder statistics be so willfully ignored?
Not far behind are the selfish white intellectuals &amp; media people who fear &amp; suppress the truth second by second on the web for their personal . A better job, a better apartment, famous friends. It truly is a web. 
Why else would there be no national coverage of the horrific, anti-white racist Burning of a white child by hate-spewing black children? Why no national coverage of a grandmother being raped &amp; beaten to death in her own home in Toledo by a black teenager? These were RECENT Acts like the Martin killing but they were obviously intentional &amp; not within the murky gray areas of Florida law. That many of us no longer have the ability to reason or the spine &amp; the integrity to defend rational thought, should tell us that we are choosing a swift, deep decline into hooded barbarism.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zk0g9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yv37</id></website><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/2012/03/m-democrats_ignore_real_racism_while_exploiting_trayvon_for_obama_2012.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T06:13:32+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T14:16:54+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwdk13</id><link>http://www.americanthinker.com/2012/03/m-democrats_ignore_real_racism_while_exploiting_trayvon_for_obama_2012.html#comment-480784497</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lveis</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>