<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw3ucl/post/2012-03-31T11:53:10</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>1.)  99% of the time people divorce, better yet when one's spouse walks out, one loses weight.  It's called stress.  I don't know anyone who divorced &amp; didn't lose weight (unless they are the one who desired divorce.)

2.)  When the primary caregiver of 5 small children leaves &amp; suddenly, circumstances force another person to now raise &amp; chase said children, Weight loss occurs.  Even as much as one is able to ignore the children, there are just certain things that need to be done, including babies that need to be removed from situations for safety, whether current caregiver wants to or not.  That alone makes one's body move, versus sitting idly in a chair at computer and/or cell phone.

3.)  I don't think she photoshops her photos near as much as a lot of you do.  There are lots of 'tricks' one can do to change the appearance of a photo without photoshopping it.

4.)  I totally agree she has no business spending ANY amount of money, other than dadgum necessities.  But.  Blowing &amp; going &amp; being frivolous &amp; careless &amp; laughing the entire way is how she makes her living, as odd as that sounds.

5.)  I think she has a very small number of followers, but many, many enablers.  Every one who pays her, for whatever reason, is supporting, encouraging &amp; approving of her irresponsible behavior. And we know what the Bible says about that.  Ironic she never mentions THAT verse(s).

6.)  I have absolutely no idea if she receives any type of government assistance, but she deserves to.  Because she deserves to have her wages garnished, as does Iz.  If all this internet crap would come to a halt, she'd probably have to at least attempt proper employment &amp; then finally, those they stole from (not just the IRS) might get some satisfaction, even if it's not monetary for some.  And I don't by the whole 'but childcare for 5 would cost more than her check' crap. Bologna.  The chick needs a regular job where she deserves to work her ass Off.  Building an alter by the side of the road sounds great to me.

7.)  She has screwed enough people - at some point, it's time for her to pay back.  Big time.  This stupid RV Trip is nothing more than a stinkin' joke.  The first thing halted was her marriage.  What will be #2?

These Saturday morning thoughts are just my opinion, of course.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67dfgx</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7fwk</id></website><link>http://mwopblog.com/2012/03/weekend-open-road/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:50:46+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T15:53:10+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw3ucl</id><link>http://mwopblog.com/2012/03/weekend-open-road/#comment-481939752</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hhz74</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>