<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwssrb/post/2012-03-31T11:11:28</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwko8r</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>That case didn't involve direct contributions to candidates from the monied interests.  It centered around the ability to air communications that mention a candidate by name (which you do all the time) within 60 days of an election.  Unions (sort of the political antithesis of corporations, if you will) are also allowed to air their Spots.  Of course McCain disagrees with the ruling, it overturned poorly crafted legislation.  While I do agree that money breeds corruption in politics ( has, Always probably will) your caricature of the Citizens United case needs to be a bit more honest.  You're all for those evil corporations not being able to pay for communications that mention candidates by name (which they must also disclose and issue caveats during the airing of).  So, my challenge to you, this campaign season from September 6th through November 6th, in the spirit of upholding McCain-Feingold is to not mention any candidates by name in your column.  Deal?  My reasoning:  You write for The Hill, The Hill is a corporation, therefore, your columns are corporate sponsored.  The money, power, and prominence of The Hill in political circles can wield great influence and gives it's contributors far more exposure than a blog that I may want to write, correct?.  Opinion pieces such as yours are not news, so, your columns should fall under McCain-Feingold if you mention a candidate by name in the specified time period.  Or, you could take advantage of the Citizens United ruling and continue writing your opinions.  Have a good weekend.  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hsbya</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f047</id></website><link>http://thehill.com/opinion/columnists/brent-budowsky/218893-supreme-court-scandals</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T22:52:06+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T15:11:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwssrb</id><link>http://thehill.com/opinion/columnists/brent-budowsky/218893-supreme-court-scandals#comment-481905058</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>