<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/312236/post/127908670/comment/328345239</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Improved Dutch Apple Crisp

4-6 servings   1½ hours 40 min prep 
Change to:  servings US Metric    
2 1/2  lbs granny smith apples (about 5)  
2  lbs macintosh apples (about 4 medium)  
1/4  cup sugar  
1/2  teaspoon ground cinnamon  
1/8  teaspoon salt  
2  tablespoons unsalted butter  
3/4  cup golden raisins  
1/2  cup heavy cream  
Streusel Topping 
1 (1 1/4  cup) all-purpose flour  
1/3  cup packed light brown sugar  
1  tablespoon cornmeal  
7  tablespoons unsalted butter, melted  

Peel, quarter, and core apples,  each quarter crosswise into pieces 1/4 inch thick. 
Toss apples, sugar, cinnamon, and salt in large bowl to combine. 
Heat butter in large Dutch oven over high Heat until foaming subsides; add apples and toss to coat. 
Reduce Heat to medium-high and cook, covered, stirring occasionally, until apples are softened, about 5 minutes. 
Stir in raisins; cook, covered, stirring occasionally, until Granny Smith apple  are tender and McIntosh apple  are softened and beginning to break down, about 5 minute longer. 
Set large colander over large bowl; transfer cooked apples to colander. 
Shake colander and toss apples to drain Off as much juice as possible. 
Bring drained juice and cream to boil in now-empty Dutch oven over high Heat; cook, stirring occasionally, until thickened and wooden spoon leaves trail in mixture, about 5 minutes. 
Pack cooked apples into 8-inch square baking dish and pour reduced juice mixture over. 
Smooth with rubber spatula. 
Streusel topping: Combine flour, sugars, and cornmeal in medium bowl; drizzle with melted butter and toss with fork until evenly moistened and mixture forms many large chunks with pea-sized pieces mixed throughout. 
Line rimmed baking sheet with parchment paper and spread streusel in even layer on baking sheet. 
Bake streusel until golden brown, about 5 minute. 
;cool baking sheet with streusel on wire rack until cool enough to handle, about 5 minutes. 
Sprinkle streusel evenly over pie filling. 
Set pie plate on now-empty baking sheet and bake untel streusel topping is deep golden brown, about 10 minutes. 
Cool on wire rack and serve.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:312236:127908670</id><idPostId>127908670</idPostId><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:312236</id><idBlogId>312236</idBlogId><link>http://www.denpdf.com</link><displayName>denpdf.com</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.denpdf.com/apple-crisp-recipe-what-is-a-good-apple-crisp-recipe/</link><displayName>apple crisp recipe- What is a Good Apple Crisp Recipe?</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T12:16:27.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:312236:127908670:328345239</id><link>http://www.denpdf.com/apple-crisp-recipe-what-is-a-good-apple-crisp-recipe/#IDComment328345239</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T12:16:27.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on apple crisp recipe- What is a Good Apple Crisp Recipe? by Teddy Bear</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>2ead35f986748cc19032b2cad13fcf96</idEmailMd5><displayName>Teddy Bear</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>Teddy Bear commented on &lt;a href="http://www.denpdf.com/apple-crisp-recipe-what-is-a-good-apple-crisp-recipe/"&gt;apple crisp recipe- What is a Good Apple Crisp Recipe?&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>