<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msjz5d/update/2012-03-28T07:57:45/dbb5f2307273fe8c10fedfd71d66f5db0925722ed62ada98c59b50f938bf4ea1</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Having had my family "Burned at the stake" by the Roman Catholic Church a few years ago.  Twilight Zone is all I can say about my total faith in our Church, to do right by it's people.  And I having served 25 years of as a Lector, 25 years as a Catechists and Religious Ed Board Member, 4 years as a Parish Council Member and even Parish Council President, cleaning the toilerts, serving in the kitchen, grooming the ladscape, etc, etc.; Betrayed because of sick Parish Priests in cahoots with the married w/four children Liturgical Minister who had the goods on their mis-deeds and let him have his way instead of seeking the truth.  They let him groom and abuse our eldest daughter from age 12.  She Always volunteered her God Given Talents at Church, playing piano, pipe organ, singing and cantoring at such a young age.  Making her easy prey!  We thought we were the only ones!  The problem was our imagination, etc!
Really?  You have a problem with Reiki which professes No Ego and open truth and means Holy Spirit; and yet you continue to belong to a NOT for non-profit, lying, hate filled church.  
I most prayerfully suggest you run for your life, save your family from the ignorance I too once professed, as you are at this moment.
Be Spirit Filled and not man made religious!  Know God!  Know Jesus?  Know Holy Spirit!  Encounter Mary Magdalene...</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l3jgi</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/h40m</id></website><link>http://www.patheos.com/Resources/Additional-Resources/Killing-Us-Softly-Lisa-Mladinich-03-28-2012.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T22:25:06+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T11:57:45+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msjz5d</id><link>http://www.patheos.com/Resources/Additional-Resources/Killing-Us-Softly-Lisa-Mladinich-03-28-2012.html#comment-478288952</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>