<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/144884/post/127835356/comment/329695038</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I really enjoy an intelligent exchange of facts and well thought out/informed opinions on defense issues, as I&amp;#039;ve tried to keep current over the last 20 years, but in the case of the F-35, I have never read such Heated and controversial  commentary than on the F-35. The vast majority of proponents for the F-35 have been defense/aerospace lobbyists on the defense blogs and web sites I regularly read. 
 
I&amp;#039;ve never felt so comfortable just coming out and accusing defense contractors of being a bunch of diabolical thieves as Lockheed Martin and it&amp;#039;s sub-contractors. I used to accept the fact that there was going to be a certain amount of fraud, but at the end of the day America was getting the best defense money could buy, generally speaking. That is not the case any more. I think more thought was put into making the F35 a cash cow in every aspect for LM et al. than in making a fighter that everyone was proud of in supporting and defending what America stands for in this world and for humanity. They know that they have a monopoly on the worlds only &amp;quot;5th generation&amp;quot; fighter and even when Russia and China field the PAK FA &amp;amp; J-20, LM will still have the only &amp;quot;5th generation&amp;quot; fighter available to counter Russia &amp;amp; China. (except India)  
 
I have long dismissed any left-wing talk about the &amp;quot;genocidal military industrial complex that needs to invade countries so it can build an oil pipeline, rape it&amp;#039;s resources, and enslave it&amp;#039;s workers, blah blah,&amp;quot; but the F-35 is an example that I think Dwight Eisenhower would have used as a case in point on his concerns about the defense industry. 
 
The F35 has now, itself, become a threat to my country because of the vast amount of money it will take to obtain, maintain, and operate, which will rob other parts of the military of much needed capability because funding going to the F35 in this time of austerity.  
 
I think a combination of 4++ generation aircraft with standoff weapons &amp;#039;AND&amp;#039; UCAV&amp;#039;s would do just fine until a cost-effective solution to the F35 was achieved. It would also send a message to defense contractors that they can&amp;#039;t get away with anything they want by simply relying on lobbyists and insincere patriotism to secure more money. 
 
I think the vast majority of people that read these blogs love America, as do I, but I&amp;#039;m PISSED OFF that my country is being taken advantage of by people who&amp;#039;s job is supposed to give our country and people of the free world the arsenal of democracy needed to keep the peace and further the spread freedom &amp;amp; democracy to the still oppressed and impoverished.  
 </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:144884:127835356</id><idPostId>127835356</idPostId><idBlogId>144884</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:144884</id><idBlogId>144884</idBlogId><link>http://www.dodbuzz.com</link><displayName>DoD Buzz</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.dodbuzz.com/2012/03/30/f-35-to-cost-1-45-trillion-over-next-50-years/</link><displayName>F-35 to cost $1.45 trillion over next 50-years</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T03:56:36.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:144884:127835356:329695038</id><link>http://www.dodbuzz.com/2012/03/30/f-35-to-cost-1-45-trillion-over-next-50-years/#IDComment329695038</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T03:56:36.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on F-35 to cost $1.45 trillion over next 50-years by JimBobJoe</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>e103779b1e34c326762f867d5848d86c</idEmailMd5><displayName>JimBobJoe</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>JimBobJoe commented on &lt;a href="http://www.dodbuzz.com/2012/03/30/f-35-to-cost-1-45-trillion-over-next-50-years/"&gt;F-35 to cost $1.45 trillion over next 50-years&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>