<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qm32/post/2012-03-29T11:40:02</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3miwi</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z8h5v</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I recorded that report and have gone over every aspect, repeatedly.  
If you could see wounds, or a bloody nose or any other indication of combat on that man -- you must have X-ray vision.
There were no marks that anyone I know who has seen that video can detect. 
Bloody nose --NO blood on his clothing.
He supposedly was flat on the ground,when the pulled his gun and shot the boy in the chest, with the 9 mm pistol's muzzle touching or within an inch or two of the boy's clothing and chest.
NO blood on his own shirt or other clothing from that explosive wound, a fact very clear in the pictures. 
The undertaker who has received the boy's body reported for the record -- There was only one entry bullet wound in the chest, no exit wound anywhere.
He reports there are absolutely no bruises, cuts, scratches, scrapes, skinned knuckles or any other marks anywhere on the boy's hands, elbow, knees or anywhere on his body -- other than the one bullet hole in his chest. 
Explain how this slender boy knocked a heavy-set, stocky man to the ground, pinned his arms to the ground with his knees, covered his mouth with one hand and beat him in the face repeatedly without skinning even one knuckle.
Doubt that consideration. I invite you to lie flat, let a friend about the boy's size and weight sit on your chest, pinning both arms, cover your mouth with one hand and hit you as as hard as possible with his other fist. 
Three to six hard blows - His knuckles will be swollen, cut, scraped and bruised. 
Your face will reveal serious bruising, swelling, cuts and Bleeding from a bloody nose -- After a half hour, under a camera -- the damage will be visible.
What happened to the SPD casual position that Zimmerman had been questioned at the scene and allowed to leave?
Chief Lee was covering for the fact that both he and the state's chief prosecutor were at the police station on a Sunday night and the prosecutor decided a former judge's son could not be prosecuted. 
That midnight Sunday decision was Reached, well before a thorough investigation would have turned up an amazing amount of testimony and evidence conflicting totally with Zimmerman's account.
Not even considering the lack of physical evidence supporting Zimmerman on the victim's body or his own person. 


</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hc8qn</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dnmo</id></website><link>http://www.newsobserver.com/2012/03/28/1963233/foster-thorbjornsen-break-in-get.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T04:10:48+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:40:02+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3qm32</id><link>http://www.newsobserver.com/2012/03/28/1963233/foster-thorbjornsen-break-in-get.html#comment-479587284</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/metr2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>