<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mws4wq/post/2012-03-31T10:50:09</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>While amazon's position in tablet market cannot in any way be called a "Sweet Spot" from a microscopic point of view, but overall amazon is in a pretty sweet Spot position.

Amazon is in 2 major businesses that I can think of  the top of my head:
1. Retail
2. Digital Media (E-books, softwares, games, apps)

Amazon has already the sweet Spot in retail area. As long as they continue doing the same, they're good.

For E-books, there's the kindle, which again has the sweet Spot. It is one of the few devices in the market which gives the user the most flawless experience when buying and reading books. In fact, the kindle app is so convenient, it can be used on pretty much any Tablet or PC you own. So, even if you don't own an amazon device, you can still buy and read ebooks from amazon which means profit for amazon.

Now Tablets, when amazon sells tablet they bear loss, but they make up for it in profits on content and service. In addition, someone with a Fire is likely to order stuff from Amazon retail store, because its so damn convenient and the app works so well.

Having heard lot of praise about the amazon apps on kindle fire, Clearly they're doing something better than google does with android. Many users prefer the Silk browser to the android stock browser. Which means they know how to please the users in the app space as well. They just need to create more apps like this, to make the device more useful to user.

If someone likes one of amazon's services or products, they're likely to try the others offered by amazon. Because of this, I think amazon is in a good Spot, they just need to recognize the fine points and continue working on improving where it can and maintain the same standard of service.

FYI: I don't own any tablet, but I think IPad is more my type than the fire.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67rgf8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zjs9</id></website><link>http://www.computerworld.com/s/article/9225707/Why_Amazon_can_t_win_a_tablet_price_war_against_Google</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:47:24+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T14:50:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mws4wq</id><link>http://www.computerworld.com/s/article/9225707/Why_Amazon_can_t_win_a_tablet_price_war_against_Google#comment-481887739</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ms265</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>