<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7njf/post/2012-03-30T15:21:18</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>So, it's judicial activism if courts rule against "your side", but justice if the courts rule in "your favor." Bob, yes Bob (because Mr. is for adults), this is the most juvenile, petulant, "Cry baby" piece of literature (??) I have read. I wondered why Al Gore failed in his attempts to become president. Now I know why - there is no way he could have won an election with your involvement. I feel dumber for having read your article. Your writing is like an IQ sinkhole.
The courageous thing for Obama to have done was to create a single payer system, for ALL (no waivers - true indication of inherent hypocrisy). A government run, tax based system, with no trampling of the Constitution.  If an individual then wanted "private boutique care", then they could feel free to find such a physician and pay cash, like in Europe. Isn't that what all you superiorly intelligent liberals point to as the enlightened, progressive path? Oh, right. That would then make it real obvious that liberals like Pelosi, Obama, Reid, and  would use the cash system because the government system is for the bourgeois. And the lawyers - no more baseless lawsuits. Just ask Joe Biden. The reason he moved to Delaware - no caps on medical lawsuits! Truth - one of the largest obstacles to the institution of a government run single payer system - American Trial Lawyers Association.
So Bob, stop with the belly-aching. The law is unconstitutional.  It is a windfall for the insurance companies (everyone has to buy it). Status quo for trial lawyers (No way Obama vexes them!) Judges have Always been politically active as YOU decribe it. (Oh, that's right. Sotomayor and Kagan agree with you, thus they are pure and without sin or reproach.) Do some good and fight for real healthcare reform, and stop being a teenage cheerleader rooting for the "cool kids."

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6751ak</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/jpbk</id></website><link>http://theweek.com/bullpen/column/226270/will-a-tea-party-supreme-court-guarantee-obama-a-second-term</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:45:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:21:18+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7njf</id><link>http://theweek.com/bullpen/column/226270/will-a-tea-party-supreme-court-guarantee-obama-a-second-term#comment-481096933</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>