<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi8uaf/update/2012-03-22T13:29:11/679322eef38ac97b76335c25ab8439bcdc9c3af335a9c40cff0e0622f5dccfe6</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The secular disposition-- to talk away The End of The World, burning with no Blush of shame. As if God is playing a meaningless practical joke on the pair of these narcissistic narcs, I like to think. I reckon it is the norm now in art: a regular with old-fashioned ideas about the propriety of getting a void in the afterlife, so to subject himself against the uproar of abuse and threats about some "harmless" oversight. And yet these degenerates dismiss us for seeking  in religion, though these same oafs had never truly doubted the truth of religion in which they had been brought up. Just think and hypothetized: Once the first remote sign of the End World, of course they will repeat "Oh, my God! My God!" but goddammit, neither the word GOD or MY had any meaning to them until at that moment. IT IS EXACLY LIKE THESE PEOPLE WHO COULD FIND NO HELP IN CHRIST-- SON OF GOD, AND GOD HIMSELF-- UNLESS THEY WERE PREPARED TO GIVE UP WHICH ALONE GAVE MEANING TO THEIR BLIGHTED LIVES: FEAR. 

YOU KNOW WHY I DON'T GIVE A GOOD GAWDDAMNED ABOUT THE END OF THE WORLD?: I am a proper Christian. I am moral. I am wise. And you people do not see what I have seen. And yet I am not self-satisfied like you people with your dismissive cynical grins. Gawddamned, that's all you secular ingrates ask "Have I not tried, tried with all my might, to find a purpose in my life? Have I not try my damnest to love my fellow human being?" Gawddammit, IT IS NOT ABOUT TRYING-- DID YOU LOVE THEM? DID YOU ACTUALLY LOVE THEM!?? You see misfortunes, by the time when I understood that I could no longer deceive myself that I am alive, and cannot be blamed because God made me so, that I want to live and love through and BEYOND the end of the world.

And yet you non-believers  snigger. With you already set out Lilliputian chest-of-drawers-- flaring imbecilities, chests all Puffed out, and yet still bounded to say "I will wipe Jerusalem as a man wipeth a dish, wiping it, and turning it upside down," as if small beads of drizzle like bird shot was to make a halo, for dress-up only, mind. Maybe, just maybe you imbecilities are just like me: First an Orthodox, but then in order to attend Mass simply and solely to escape American Protestant sing-song guitars, but then lagging emptiness and dilution of messages, the horrifying vacuity of senselessness, et al. But then experience-- maybe for you folks, let's hope-- has taught the race that if knowledge of God is the end, then these habits of life are not the means but the condition in which the means operate. But of course, You do not have to do these things-- unless you want to to God. Keep in mind that they work on YOU, not God.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y6r8d</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/444-last-day-on-earth,71289/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T05:05:43+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T17:29:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi8uaf</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/444-last-day-on-earth,71289/#comment-473774893</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rw97n</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>