<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3u5cx/post/2012-03-29T15:04:27</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpbonv</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Your story sounds so familar to mine. I have a nine year old son who was finally diaginosed with ADHD and also has violent tendenceys. His father has never been in his life. He watches my other kids go with their father and my son gets to stay home. I have lucked out in some ways in which I have moved to the same town as my parents who are involved daily in his life ( mainly my father he will listen to a guy in his eyes some how girls do not know nothing which really sucks when disaplining). My town has less then 250 people which can be good. His school may not have all of the perks as a well populated city school of which he started out in, but my childrens school is small and every teacher knows each and every child from prek to 12th and they know which children need more attention/help. My sons ADHD is being controled by meds to where he can set in a class room now but this school year we adults are at a loss because he is now hurting himself, (biting to point to Bleeding, punch himself or walls, gouching eyes and so on) to the point that he requires complete supervision until he is calm. He has been talking about hurting himself to the point he dies which scares me to death. And now he has started running away when he gets mad cause things do not go his way. I really do not know how much more medicine a 69 pound body can handle. The depression meds that he is now on can cause the same behaviors that we are trying to fix. As a single mother I do understand how upseting and frustrating it can be to have a special needs child. People think that because I am a correction officer that I should not have a bratty child these poeple will never understand unless they are put in our shoes. I do try and take the first step when it comes to his school. The more you show you are going to be hands on involved with his class/ teacher coming up with ideas together and your expectations/ concerns it really does rub Off on to the teacher. I will notify the teacher in the morning if my son leaves home in a mad mood or what ever the case may be, and she contacts me the same. I want an open dialog with the school constantly going it helps him know that we stand together and also lets him know that he can not get away with any little tricks. good luck to all parents and teachers
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/8dp648</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/deo8</id></website><link>http://www.additudemag.com/adhd/article/1973.html</link><postedTime>2010-08-31T12:43:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:04:27+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3u5cx</id><link>http://www.additudemag.com/adhd/article/1973.html#comment-479768961</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2010-08-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>