<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3v3j2/post/2012-03-29T09:17:35</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Marion beating Vika makes me seriously happy.  YOu asked in your last post who we preferred as #1, Caroline or Vika, and to that I answer Yogi Bear.
I'm also finding Aga's continued success against top players surprising, but I like her.
Watched the last set of Rafa/Jo online--where I can just barely make out the ball--so my concept of what took place is dodgy.  But it was exciting as all hell.  I was more concerned how Rafa didn't close on his serve 2nd set.
Don't know what to think about the knee.  But know what I think about his need to use the FHDTL way more.  Let me harp on it!  Saw this again against JO, it almost  works for him as a point-ender, and he doesn't do it enough.
I thought Jo was playing v well in the 3rd set, and when Jo's playing well, he's as good as anyone.  I'll take that as a propitious sign for Rafa in the \matches to come.
From what I saw of Murray, I think Rafa will handle him easily.  Of course maybe the stomach bug explains Murray's less-than-impressive showing.  I still don't get why anyone likes him, because aside from his charm-free personality, his tennis isn't even that interesting.
Is COld  a DH story?  I used to love SOns and Lovers.  One of my brothers left an unfinished \PHd on Lawrence, so I Always perk up when his name is mentioned.  The film Women in Love was one of the very first I saw that was sexually candid so I never forgot it, and of course how can one forget Glenda Jackson and Oliver Reed, or Reed and Bates wrestling nude in front of a fire ...but I digress.
Missed you in the chat last night.  Saw you were there earlier before I got on.  Oh well.  Maybe for Murray, or DJok, cuz that's where were headed.
Gulp.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z5911</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/buag</id></website><link>http://extremewesterngrip.blogspot.com/2012/03/she-saw-something-nasty-in-woodshed.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T07:21:33+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T13:17:35+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3v3j2</id><link>http://extremewesterngrip.blogspot.com/2012/03/she-saw-something-nasty-in-woodshed.html#comment-479480796</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>