<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4mrj/update/2012-03-30T17:27:28/f4a8d9a8f07e9bc2303a839b3951ae34a471cdb9d11e4f41dfaddedc475036bc</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwt1wf</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/w2wt</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>This is from a 2006 Jerusalem Post story, "Israel's Arabs mark Land Day":

&lt;blockquote&gt;"Six unarmed Arab citizens were killed and some 100 injured, when they protested the confiscation of thousands of dunams of their land by the government. [] &lt;u&gt;The government sent in the army and police with tanks and heavy artillery who shot and killed six unarmed citizens&lt;/u&gt;."&lt;/blockquote&gt; According to Wikipedia, two of the dead protesters were killed by police; four, by the IDF -- and as you know, Arabs have never been part of the IDF. Though I haven't found a more reliable source for the demarcation of casualties as caused by police vs. army, the Jerusalem Post story quoted above does notice that, along with the police, the army, too, had been sent in to suppress the protests, and that all of those killed were unarmed. How can police and military forces equipped with "tanks and heavy artillery" fear for their lives in face of unarmed Arabs?

Zionists will be Zionists, I guess: they'll Always try and rape the truth, so as to not recognize their rogue country may have ever wronged Palestinians and Israeli Arabs.

----------

Response to post below by @abdi Salim

A. All sources on Israeli demographics make a distinction between the Druze, the Bedouins and Israeli Arabs. The Druze and the Bedouin may be Arab in the sense that originally they're Arabic speakers, but they - at least the Druze - clearly have an ethnic identity of their own, one that is distinct of the majority populations of the country where they live, whether it is in Israel/Palestine, in Lebanon or in Syria. It's not my intention to discuss their ethnic background or culture and how it stands vis-à-vis Israeli and other Arabs. It just suffices to notice that in books, press articles, etc., the distinction between those three groups - Israeli Arabs, Israeli Druze and Bedouins - is seldom forgotten. The IDF itself seems to have that in mind when it compels the Druze to serve in the army at the same time it exempts Israeli Arabs from military duty.

B. I don't understand all that you're trying to say - your first sentence is confusing. But even in the part I do understand I don't see much logic. There were more than 100 wounded protesters that day, and hundreds of others were arrested. I don't think this is at all inconsistent with a scenario where the police and the army had a clear hardware advantage, specially if you consider that the presence of tanks and other heavy equipment may have prevented both the protesters and the security forces from getting too nervous - the officers, by assuring them of their power advantage; and the protesters, by intimidating them into not Heating up the situation. Be that as it may, all sources are saying that the people who died that day - again, I'm not talking about all of the protesters, but of those who were killed -  were unarmed. This information I first found on as unsuspicious a source as the pro-Likud Jerusalem Post. I don't have the obligation to explain to you how this came to be: I was not there (like most people, I have to relie on secondary sources like press articles), and  you're not presenting any evidence to cast doubts about the mainstream account of the facts. You don't want to admit this may be the truth because it will not reflect well on Israel.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67ymxe</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/h8a5</id></website><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/inpictures/2012/03/201233016368704474.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:14:41+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T21:27:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw4mrj</id><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/inpictures/2012/03/201233016368704474.html#comment-481219479</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h4dds</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>