<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpyc9g/update/2012-03-21T10:45:11/b7b5245526cb7bdf428068c41c9e17da2451c9f986c6a8b448e2d743f99a2374</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpgo1d</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>There is only 20% ot these people and 80% of us and we could easily get the upper hand on them, if the other people would get up Off their lazy cans and help us take back our country.  It sounds like everyone is too scared.  They can kill but they can't eat you.  I will stand up for what I believe and if they try to get rid of me then so be it.  I will be going to Heaven and they will be going to Hell and guess what that means.  They think it is bad here, wait until they Burn in Hell forever.  All those Muslim Terrorist that have killed the Amreican people are Burning in Hell for what they have done.  I am praying the Lord will bring his wrath down on these evil people before the war between Israel and Iran with no help from the US.  That is another reason they will Burn in Hell for not stand by God's chosen people.  We have got to stand up against these 20% immediately, no waiting for Obama to be able to go back to the WH.  

All of you that can go to Washington DC on March 27 need to go and support the American people that are against Obamacare.  All of you can ride a bus to get there and it only cost $10. to $15. to ride the bus.  We need everyone that can go to please go to make sure we aren't  messed on.  I can't go because I have a handicapped daughter and she needs me at home, but if I could I would go.  It will only be a one day trip, so if you can go please go to help the American people.  That Obamacare is not an insurance, it is a governement takeover.  That is to take over the American people and tell them what they can do and can't do.  They have alot of senior citizen stipulations in this 2,000 page document and one is to cut $500,000,000  dollars out of Medicare, throw us under the bus and that includes the disabled, no surgeries, just take meds go home and die.  They also have an article that will be getting every Illegal Immigrant citizenship and let them have every benefit that we should be getting and at least 5-7,Million people will not have any insurance  and they don't mean the Illegal Immigrants won't have the insurance.  It will be the American White people that won't get it.  So what does that tell everyone.  Get ready because it is coming.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dejn3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/opxh</id></website><link>http://cowboybyte.com/5532/obama-seizes-control-over-all-food-farms-livestock-farm-equipment-fertilizer-and-food-production-across-america/</link><postedTime>2012-03-20T21:34:27+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-21T14:45:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpyc9g</id><link>http://cowboybyte.com/5532/obama-seizes-control-over-all-food-farms-livestock-farm-equipment-fertilizer-and-food-production-across-america/#comment-472396829</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5v95u</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>