<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ffsv/post/2012-03-29T17:02:45</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m311mp</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zy7ws</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I would agree that it may sound arrogant and very condescending but it is the the Cold hard truth.  We are lied to a constant basis and we just take it.  I keep going back to this Martin vs. Zimmerman thing.  How many times were we told by the media that Zimmerman was never arrested, never taken in for questioning?  Yet here I am today watching the video of him in handcuffs at the police station.  It is only one example, but if one cared to look, we would find more and more.  No one will be held responsible for lying to the public, just like the weapons of mass destruction we never found in Iraq and no one is held accountable.  If we never learn from our past mistakes, how could anyone call us anything other than stupid?

I'm sorry I didn't meant to make it sound like Obama would get re-elected.  I was referring to his campaign in 2008.  He said he would repeal the Patriot  then.  If Romney can keep his hands out of the social issues cookie jar, I think he can beat Obama, after watching hacking democracy, I don't consider anything a sure thing.  I do disagree on one point, if we don't change as people in the sense of what we expect from our government, Romney will just be the man at the helm when we go over a cliff.  Between endless wars and entitlement spending, we need serious change and I don't think our politicians have the brains or the guts to lose their jobs if it means doing what is right for the people of this country.  I can only hope that enough people realize what is going on and in 2016 we will have real change.   

There is a very very slim chance that the Republicans will get my vote this go around. If Rubio is on the ticket, I'll go 3rd party for sure. To me these bills/laws shows a person true belief in the role of government.  Nothing worse than a man that says he's for small government while pushing big government on people (hmhmm like Santorum!)
If history is a good indicator, government hardly ever gives up power once they have it.  I'll be shocked if any of these bills are ever repealed.  I'll even be pleasantly surprised if the SCOTUS overturns Obamacare.  

I can only hope that Obama was elected because of white guilt and absolute rejection of Bush's policies.  If Obama was elected because people thought he would be a good president, it may already be too late.  Sure he talked a good game, but if anyone actually looked at his record or the things he was saying when the teleprompter was Off, they should have been very alarmed.

I can only hope that all my worries are for nothing and that you are 100% right.  Some how I believe we are both wrong and right at the same time.  I guess we'll see in a little over 4 years.
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zhjy3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q0fi</id></website><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/29/rubio-obamas-open-mic-gaffe-prompted-timing-of-romney-endorsement/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:39:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T21:02:45+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ffsv</id><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/29/rubio-obamas-open-mic-gaffe-prompted-timing-of-romney-endorsement/#comment-479890528</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yt49t</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>