<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwqkvh/update/2012-03-30T19:01:56/e9e0fe5f392233a79c422ee6e0b2b827f452767e2d21ff55cbb66746b450bbe8</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>If in 2003 Omar Khadr had been a member of a Toronto youth gang and had, in the course of a gun fight with another gang, killed someone (let's say a paramedic who happened to be at the scene), he would have been charged as a fifteen year old under Canada's Youth Criminal Justice . He would have received due process of law, a speedy court process and if convicted, would have been incarcerated, received rehabilitative treatment and been released back into the community with close monitoring and reintegrative support. This process would have happened in a relatively short span of perhaps five years, in a controlled, humane environment and would have resulted in better prospects for public safety going forward.  
 
Instead, Khadr has been imprisoned for twice as long as he would have been in Canada, has not received rehabilitative treatment, has been subjected to abuse that would not have been tolerated under Canadian law, and has probably made a false confession just to bring this kangaroo court show trial process to a conclusion. Khadr has experienced more than a full dose of retribution for what he may or may not have done.
 
Lest you get all self-righteous while casting stones at Omar Khadr, you might pause to remember those members of Canada's own Airborne Regiment who tortured to death a starving teenager in Somalia. 

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Somalia_Affair

Those Canadian soldiers received prompt legal process. They were never subjected to the kind of punishment and pain that Khadr has experienced.
 
There was never any doubt that at some point - based strictly on established international and Canadian law - Omar Khadr would come home to Canada. Even the Americans - the aggrieved party in this matter, having lost one of their own soldiers - had enough of this business a long time ago and would have happily sent Khadr back to Canada had we simply - and wisely - requested it.
 
For those of you whose Thirst for punishment has not yet been quenched, there is nothing more that can be done to satisfy you within the law. It is doubtful that even a lynching of Khadr would give you the sick satisfaction you crave. Is our community safe from Omar Khadr? The greater concern is whether our community is safe from you.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67an9f</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/4r1e</id></website><link>http://fullcomment.nationalpost.com/2012/03/30/chris-selley-omar-khadrs-coming-home-now-what/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T11:04:19+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T23:01:56+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwqkvh</id><link>http://fullcomment.nationalpost.com/2012/03/30/chris-selley-omar-khadrs-coming-home-now-what/#comment-481297405</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hjtvn</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>