<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3a8ba/delete/2012-03-28T16:29:18</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>WHAT THEY FAIL TO TELL YOU IS: TRICKERY IS TREASON! no LAW AGAINST IT! when the MILITARY (call WEST POINT) by it's TRUE NAME BENEDICT ARNOLD ACADAMY;  with it's MOTTO: "duty" being to do as MUCH HARM as you POSSIBLY CAN DO for all those "damn good men" who DARED to want to be FREED from the TYRANNY of the BRITISH! 
   TRICKERY IS TREASON; they told our forefathers; with a SYSTEM that worked by EXPLOITATION; targeting &amp; harming the PEOPLE within THIS nation just like they have been doing in GREAT BRITAIN for centuries; as STATED in WM Shakespears works: leaving HIS FOOTSTEPS for future generations TO KNOW and UNDERSTAND that "first, kill all the lawyers"; BECAUSE EVEN IN HIS TIME HE KNEW: that the "legislative" SUPPOSED was ALL FABRICATED FICTION! with the LAWS disappearing just as QUICKLY as they have been doing HERE! 
   ISN"T THAT AMAZING? 
"democracy' which meant of course, setting the TRUTH to the SIDE and PRESENTING a DIFFERENT IDEA instead; (in other words folks: DECEPTION) 
    BRITS of course, have been OPPRESSED for FAR LONGER than we have HERE in the "new world"; by the BANKSTERS who of course, worked with the GANGSTERS who made up a FICTICIOUS "legal" SYSTEM supposedly to be KNOWN as "law";  like ELIZABETH WARREN, LAW isn't THAT something? PROFESSOR, at it was YALE; now, it is HARVARD; might just as WELL BE OXFORD HUH? 
    RUNNING of course for "ELECTION" for the FICTICIOUS "law makers" writing the FICTICIOUS "laws" to go on and become "judges" DENYING of course JUSTICE to EVER EXIST here in the USA since 1832;  &amp; IN ALL NATIONS with their QUEST for "absolute power" and absolute corruption on STEROIDS for ALL PEOPLES on this planet! because they CHOSE to WORK WITH DARKNESS! 
     BECAUSE of course OPPRESSION of the PEOPLE forcing them  &amp; ever to have to PAY; and then to PAY MORE MORE MORE was SUCH a BETTER WAY to RUN THE WORLD than ANY OTHER as they have REPEATEDLY STATED thru their "politicians" who are GUESS WHAT? LAWYERS! 
      LAWS are to EXIST; FIRM, STABLE, FIXED! like the WORD OF GOD IS PEOPLE! for the PROTECTION of the PEOPLE, the animals &amp; the PLANET ITSELF!~ 
   YET: THIS CORRECT AND TRUE PATTERN has YET to EXIST on this PLANET! 
       COURTS are to EXIST to make SURE that JUSTICE EXISTS! 
DO NOT NEED TO HAVE A COLLEGE DEGREE NOR EVEN A LAW DEGREE ELIZABETH WARREN, to be KNOWING such things as these! 
    HER RESPONSE as CHAIRMAN of a COMMITTEE for the FICITICIOUS "economic" recovery of the USA: to the QUESTION: what of usury laws? was , why, they just DISAPPEARED! when ASKED HOW IS IT THAT LAWS JUST DISAPPEAR? her RESPONSE as a PROFESSOR of LAW: was THIS: oops! caught us THERE huh! ha ha ha! 
    "democracy" of course, meant you FORCE the PEOPLE  and ever to pay more more more; they call this "socialism" in ENGLAND; DEMOCRATIC DICTATORSHIP IN CHINA and in MANY OTHER NATIONS on this planet;  same THERE as is BEING DONE HERE! 
    FICTICIOUS MEDIA is the ONLY REASON that we have NOT KNOWN about it HERE! 
WHICH of course IS ILLEGAL &amp; A CRIME HERE! in the USA; along with EXPLOITATION; targeting &amp; HARMING THE PEOPLE for THEIR OWN PERSONAL PROFIT &amp; PERSONAL ! 
    NOT at ALL what you THOUGHT it was at all now was it? 
WHENEVER misrepresentation/deception is USED in CONTRACTS OF ANY KIND; it is NULL &amp; VOID: it is FRAUD; it is KICKED OUT!  SINCE THESE HERE in the USA have USED "elections" CLAIMING FALSELY that it "is will of the PEOPLE"; and since WILL OF THE PEOPLE IS UNIVERAL; NO ONE LIKES BEING OPPRESSED! DOES NOT MATTER the COLOR of your SKIN, the TEXTURE of your HAIR; the SHAPE OF YOUR EYES! they were THUSLY KICKED OUT LEGALLY &amp; LAWFULLY FROM OFF OF THIS PLANET! 
    AND WE DO NOT accept ANY of their SO CALLED "laws" ANY RULINGS whatsoever from ANY COURTS set up by them; city, county, state HERE are NOT recognzied NOR authorized as government;  however they SET IT UP within ALL OTHER NATIONS is HOW IT IS BEING REMOVED! 
      COST: of gasoline should be PERHAPS guess what? 25 cents a gallon! if you have PAID for electrical or gas Heat for 5 years, YOU have been OVERBILLED ENOUGH FOR AT LEAST 5 GENERATIONS if NOT MORE! 
    NO building codes are followed EVER anywhere; chemicals are saturating EVERYTHING to cause as much harm &amp; damage to EVERYONE for MORE $ for themselves;  the SUPER INFLATED COST of "medical" INCOMPETENCE of one of THEIRS is SEEN: when one billed $450 for an office visit; and despite of NUMEROUS requests of both the doctor &amp; their staff; they were SO INCREDIBLY INCOMPETENT they COULD NOT EVEN FAX a SIMPLE REQUEST to have meds by mail reinstated for my neighbor; in tears, she finally called the company she gets her meds from; THEY know all along what has been going on; got what they NEEDED from the INCOMPETENT and CORRUPT "doctors"; and got her MEDICATIONS to her! 
   THIS is THE INTELLIGENCE that has been "running " this planet! aye aye aye people! 
ALL american medical association is SHEER BABBLING NONSENSE! so is every so called "report" EVER given to the PEOPLE! in ALL nations! 
     SO the FICTION that any ELECTION means ANYTHING anywhere on THIS PLANET is simply DECEPTION! </body><verb>delete</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lpou2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tsjl</id></website><link>http://truth-out.org/news/item/8148-voter-suppression-in-2012-past-is-prologue</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T19:16:41+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T20:29:18+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3a8ba</id><link>http://truth-out.org/news/item/8148-voter-suppression-in-2012-past-is-prologue#comment-478740601</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>killed</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>