<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/136753/post/26710582/comment/327662472</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Many people do not like to climb the stairs to climb stairs, because too tired, could not walk a few layers to pant for breath. So, as long as there is convenient and fast in the elevator,Gucci Sunglasses, you just please do part-time jobs to make money online I don\'t take the stairs. However, many people only think of climbing the stairs to the solution of Yu Tairong\'s difficult hard head, in fact, so tired all because of you I Qi and blood deficiency causes. The physical deficiency is due to a gas shortage, to flavor weak, viscera to form low as the main feature of the physique. Qi gas, should be understood as a kind of energy, is a comprehensive concept of gas, is. The maintenance of human life activities of the basic material, is the body\'s energy and Qi deficiency, mainly in order to strength is weak. And pathological reaction may involve systemic aspects, such as Qi, Wei, weakness, muscle table is not fixed, but difficult to sweat; Qi, limbs muscular dystrophy, whole body fatigue; Yang Qing Qi is not l, clear orifices dystrophy and mental fatigue, Dizziness tinnitus; Qi is unable to rate blood pulse, is weak or ray  3025 glasses fine; Qi is a metabolic disorder of water, the water solution of distribution, barriers, gelatinous sputum into drinking, even water evil is numerous and edema; Qi deficiency can also be resulting in organsTo decline, subordinate rabbit in 2010  year haul and a series of organs weak phenomenon. How to identify the physical deficiency is it right?? if you\'re flabby, and others to get the same layer RayBan official website number floor, easy to pant for breath; usually voice low,  feel out of breath, not enough gas; easy to sweat, as long as the physical strength is easily tired; observation of tongue, pale tongue, tongue body fat,Burberry Watches, edge has the tooth trace; introverted personality, mood instability, timid don\'t like adventure; defense ability drops, usually easy to Cold, after the onset of difficult to heal difficult patients, visceral ptosis; intolerance of Cold pathogen, pathogenic wind, Heat evil. Physical deficiency and Qi are not the same. Qi in TCM a syndromes. May you this time because of illness or too tired, will appear deficiency symptoms, you sick or lifestyle adjustment, on the not empty. But physical deficiency is a temporary gas shortage form, as a result of a person for nothing and fun, feel very tired, say a few words on the breath. Always sweating, but does not feel hot, it should be caused by deficiency of Witkey money online part-time. And there are two reasons for this. The day after tomorrowDeficiency and postnatal malnutrition. Such as intense exercise, especially in sweat after exercise, and was to wind, easy to catch a Cold, Cold will be adjusted in the course of time, energy, strength also RayBan sunglasses price cost. In addition, the popular Weight loss, but the vitality with your weight down by dieters eat more. Small,Abercrombie And Fitch Outlet, curved connecting guide RayBan sunglasses price induced is acquired in the gas is reduced. Because the human activity was unchanged, to meet this activity, must use the body of stored energy mm vitality vitality is acquired. The gas, only a small, should nourish it. But a diet war, you lose not only meat and gas. (http: / / 72by: Guo Yuping) love watch TV, elevate the risk for dementia crisis? Love watch TV, elevate </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:136753:26710582</id><idPostId>26710582</idPostId><idBlogId>136753</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:136753</id><idBlogId>136753</idBlogId><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com</link><displayName>HOCKEYCENTRIC</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com/instant-analysis/instant-analysis-san-jose-sharks-are-wallin-and-able/</link><displayName>Instant Analysis: San Jose Sharks Are Wallin And Able</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T07:53:48.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:136753:26710582:327662472</id><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com/instant-analysis/instant-analysis-san-jose-sharks-are-wallin-and-able/#IDComment327662472</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T07:53:48.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Instant Analysis: San Jose Sharks Are Wallin And Able by yi1qxfa186</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://shopburberryonline.net</link><idEmailMd5>6a2afae47e73b15c172fe6128c0ac791</idEmailMd5><displayName>yi1qxfa186</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://shopburberryonline.net"&gt;yi1qxfa186&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.hockeycentric.com/instant-analysis/instant-analysis-san-jose-sharks-are-wallin-and-able/"&gt;Instant Analysis: San Jose Sharks Are Wallin And Able&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>