<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/51387w/update/2011-08-11T16:03:21/ed2c32b516d04a3b731910f7f543d9456c05740a052bd54c3ff5c69cacbc9acb</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Wow.  This is kind of a rude article...I shop at all of the health food Spots in Austin - MFF, Snap, &amp; Mel's, and I actually like MyFitFoods best.  Some dishes are more flavorful than others, but with the American population afraid of anything with a strong taste, I can see why they err on the bland side.  Come on though guys.  It's not so hard to  your spice cabinet if you want to kick things up a notch.  Personally, I love the oatmeal, enchiladas, chili, the new cobb salad.  Also, I'm  telling people about their salmon dishes, which I think are better than most restaurant quality salmon.  I've  had a great experience with their customer service as well.  They Always remember my name, ask my about my dogs and other personal things, and walk my food to my car.  Oh, and on a final note, every single person that I've met there has been in great shape.  I'm sure there are exceptions, just like how not everyone who staffs the gym is ripped and lean, but I think they're doing something very nice for the general populace who would actually like to start thinking about their health, yet still want something tasty and convenient. Go MFF and please ignore all of the haters out there who wouldn't recognize a meal if it wasn't 2,000 calories and covered in bacon and cheese.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/edxhb5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rpf1</id></website><link>http://blogs.dallasobserver.com/cityofate/2011/08/my_fit_foods_losing_weight_by.php</link><postedTime>2011-08-04T17:09:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-08-11T20:03:21+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/51387w</id><link>http://blogs.dallasobserver.com/cityofate/2011/08/my_fit_foods_losing_weight_by.php#comment-283718302</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-08-04</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>