<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwfuou/update/2012-03-31T01:33:28/da9e26b22c25da4f6ef347c41d110265f5b960f462b0123ad19dda6dad292c20</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3iv5k</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lhoki</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Just wanted to add a few more the things in there...
The slow pace of drama is what separates it from others. The drama is slow, and steady, unlike the other dramas which are fast paced with many things going at once, this drama focuses on the main plot about 90% of the time. Although the main plot is being shown for so long, it's still a slow moving drama. Even though it's slow, and not modernized (for right now) its still very entertaining.
The plot as of now is two best friends who have the same "3second" girl but only one of them gets to keep her. One of them, In Ha, knows that they have the same 3 second girl, the other is unaware of it. In Ha being the shy, nice guy he is allows his friend to be with her. Problem now is that the girl, Yoon Hee, likes In Ha, not his best friend. The two like each other, but they don't know it. And it only gets even more complicated so on.
The cinematography is incredible. Rather than being filmed like the typical Kdrama, this has a much more movie like and fresh feel. There's also a lot of symbolism. The rain, the colors, and objects, such as the yellow umbrella. Those all behold a special meaning behind each scene. If your gonna watch this drama, pay attention to detail. For example, the weather, colors of objects, and color in general. The PD did an amazing job of detail and if you catch it, Shivers run down through your spine.
I just thought I'd share this... 
although most of you will go "TL;DR", I just wanted to get this Off my chest.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zj2x4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lyjc</id></website><link>http://www.allkpop.com/2012/03/light-and-shadow-fashion-king-and-love-rain-compete-for-viewer-ratings</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:17:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T05:33:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwfuou</id><link>http://www.allkpop.com/2012/03/light-and-shadow-fashion-king-and-love-rain-compete-for-viewer-ratings#comment-481567415</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lhoki</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>