<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jv20/post/2012-04-02T03:29:34</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>in BAD BOY Seungri and TOP look the best to me....

then Daesung.
not really feeling GD's look in BAD BOY.

in FANTASTIC BABY...
OMFG!!! TOP's eyebrows!!! PINK!!! O.O

ONLY TOP could get away with that look!!! [maybe GD too.... ]
soooooo eccentric! but he pulled it  pretty well! i'm impressed!

i like how each member had a particular color...
so... ranked in order of looks....
for me: #1. GD! gorgeous! i loved the glitter eye make up... and that's my fave  outfit from the vid :]

 #2. Daesung! he  looks beautiful in a suit and that particular color really compliments his complexion &amp; his hair color! &lt;3

#3. Taeyang! [possibly a biased rank :P] i think after being exposed to so much of his skin &amp; arms lately...it's nice to see him COMPLETELY CLOTHED!  ROFL! XD [what kinda Taeyang stan am i??? XP]

#4. TOP! "watermelon fashion" as it is being so appropriately called :P 
just what the summer Heat needed &lt;3 he should actually rank higher, in the #2 Spot for DARING, &amp; ECCENTRICITY bcz i think that it was an incredibly crazy look that he pulled  smhow. but as i find it a lil weird for my conventional taste... he ranked low. but definitely earns my awe &amp; respect! &lt;3

#5. Seungri. i really adore Baby Ri &amp; his never-ending quest to  maturity :P so i like that he's experimenting. i like the all red. he looks great. my only prob was... the red leather pants were too tight, so they put me Off a bit. and in this particular vid, maknae was upstaged by his gorgeous hyungs! better luck next time Ri! you ranked #1 for me in this BAD BOY vid, so dnt be sad! :P</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6vzjko</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/g1xx</id></website><link>http://www.bigbangupdates.com/2012/04/bigbangs-inkigayo-performances-120401.html</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T10:06:55+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T07:29:34+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0jv20</id><link>http://www.bigbangupdates.com/2012/04/bigbangs-inkigayo-performances-120401.html#comment-483330275</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lj366</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>