<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3zrxf/update/2012-03-29T05:19:03/f04c4ff5ee1cabcfd051c6846b359bd1c4584fc0f491b4447f441bd02d3b7353</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3z2tg</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zdisa</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>It is not on the new fliers because the family was getting so many people that the first thing out of their mouths was about the reward money, how much, what do i have to do to get it, even a so called psychic called and her first question was how much was the reward and how much would she get paid to have a phycic reading to tell where sam was. it just got so crazy about the money that the family decided to try to get the focus back on Samantha rather than having so much go on and on about the money. You might be asking questions for the first time about it, but hundreds of people are asking about it every time they speak with a family member, instead of asking, how are you doing, how are you holding up, what can i do to help. It gets old, repeating the same story over and over when all you want to do is cry and say where is my loved one. Until you have been through something like this, you have no idea how cruel and insensitive people can be. If someone's house Burns down, people take up a donation, and no one is standing behind you asking every five minutes, how much have you got, and how are you spending it, following you around the store and questioning your every purchase. You donate money to a church, you dont run behind the pastor and question every little detail until the annual aduit. People are asking for an accounting before the thing is even done. That was taking the focus Off Samantha being found. Even you are more worried about the money than you are about where this poor  girl is. That is why the family decided to quit discussing the money and focus on samantha, the amount of the reward has not brought her home yet, everyone knows there is a big reward if they turn in the information that brings her home.. so what more needs to be said? There will be an accounting to the right people, no one is stealing, no one is taking advantage, and the family wants to talk about Samantha rather than money because that is where their heart is. Why can't you people respect that?
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h29dv</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/dneq</id></website><link>http://www.adn.com/2012/03/27/2394159/man-linked-to-missing-barista.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T01:46:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T09:19:03+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3zrxf</id><link>http://www.adn.com/2012/03/27/2394159/man-linked-to-missing-barista.html#comment-479358781</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zez6m</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>