<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3j4wz/update/2012-03-29T18:34:11/ad6f96a0c422250bbb5763c758d7f8cdaa158fca2534ba6de2132e0768e2aca0</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>

 


From an
evidentiary perspective, the facts in the Trayvon Martin tragedy would likely
be apparent to a dull 3rd grader, or even to their intellectual equivalents –
the NRA cretins, bribed lawmakers and Neanderthaloids who favor the Stand Your
Ground law (Kill at Will).  


Trayvon
Martin was killed because he crossed paths with George Zimmerman, an armed,
neighborhood watch leader. On the night in question, Zimmerman reportedly
Spotted Trayvon and called the police; 
he was told to disengage his pursuit and surveillance of this youth. He
disobeyed that directive. From that point forward, he forfeits his claim to
self-defense for killing this youth.  That
makes it manslaughter.


The author
of the Stand Your Ground, Senator Baxley, NRA and no less than Jeb Bush all
affirm Zimmerman  outside of, and without the protection provided, by SYG.
(The law has done nothing to reduce crime. It has simply spawned vigilantism,
and added to the number of justifiable homicides – murders essentially – by anyone
(including psychopaths) who simply want to kill with impunity.)


Ironically,
if Trayvon Martin had indeed attacked Zimmerman,  the youth could clearly have claimed he Acted
in self-defense: He was pursued and confronted, at night, by an adult civilian
wearing a handgun.  Zimmerman’s actions,
demeanor and pursuit would reasonably have been construed by Trayvon as
menacing at the least – and potentially life-threatening at worst.  


Let’s face
it, Zimmerman was not driving around playing sheriff just for fun. He quite
possibly had delusions of heroism, self-importance; we’ll never know. He DID
have a 9mm, and he was clearly “on
the hunt.”  But, if he is ever prosecuted, whoever issued that gun to him, along
with the authors and sponsors of the cretinous and retrograde SYG legislation
(ALEC, NRA, et al) should be tried as accessories to murder.


</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ztxr5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/us/florida-teen-shooting-sanford-divided/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:29:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:34:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3j4wz</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/us/florida-teen-shooting-sanford-divided/index.html#comment-479974838</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzq9u</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>