<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/atheoj/update/2010-10-24T11:09:08/f95e89ab6d9c2816f77e47cfcca8939ee06734a57cbf0e6531252f4b98377ee0</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Oh my God.  Iran is buying  the Afghan's, we're buying  the Pakistani's, everybody is buying  everybody.   China has bought us and is determining our foreign policy.  We're probably only in Afganistan because the Chinese don't want to be there. We have  a White House that wants to 'share our wealth' with every two-bit crooked regime in the world 'because its the right thing to do"?  BULL.  Afghanistan....why are we there?  Why is our 'treasure' being shot, maimed, duped and set up?   We have a White House that doens't even care about this war.  Of course, when our kids come home, where will they work? Best to keep them over there in that shooting gallery, I supose.  Our governments real war, it seems, is with us.  For 20 months it seems to me, our government and the criminal unions that make the calls have been on one endless campaign to dominate us through a quiet, horrible takeover of ideologies and social programs we DO NOT WANT.  Not a day goes by that Barack Obama isn't shilling on television.  Can anyone ever rememer a Presidnet who seemingly did nothing others than brow beat?  Why are out troops setting huge bonfires of pot you can see Burning from outerspace in Afghanistan?   To deny the Europeans of their 'high'?  They deserve to be stoned.  Look at the governments of Greece, England and France.  It seems all the peoples of this Earth are all the victims of their own mad men 'leaders' and egomaniacl politicians. Our troops need to come home and protect our borders from the invasion we see everyday on our television screens.  If we are even seeing half of it.  And we need to keep our noses out of the insanities taking place elsewhere.  Who decided that America is the keeper of the entire world?   Our healthcare system is corrupted from the crooks and fraudulent practices of a few.  We don't need a 'one world governance' as Obama would like.  We need fewer people like Obama.  Foreign governments have corrupted, looted and taken advantage of their own people long enough and it's beginning to turn on them.  There is a boot on all of our necks and its time to cast it Off.  The first thing we need to do is get those troops out of harms way, get rid of this awful White House and never again give unions the strangleholds they now have or to let one party dominate.  The best thing that has come out of the horror of the past 20  months is that we've seen the 'sausage being made'.  We've watched our Presidnet lie straight into the camera and so we've been warned.  We need to take control of our own lives again because something is very wrong.  This Afghan thing is just one more lunacy we need to extricate ourselves from.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/8usvpd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yjmx</id></website><link>http://www.foxnews.com/world/2010/10/24/report-iran-paying-afghan-presidents-chief-staff/</link><postedTime>2010-10-24T08:21:23+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2010-10-24T15:09:08+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/atheoj</id><link>http://www.foxnews.com/world/2010/10/24/report-iran-paying-afghan-presidents-chief-staff/#comment-89634987</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8nldh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2010-10-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>