<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/8gnre8/update/2011-01-17T20:16:22/8748065d9e0b5baa7eac3a079014eb8c51eae716fb89fb96a01c6b7e80734a7c</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I love Palin.  I'm besotted.  Especially when I see how terrified the left is of her.  It gives me a 'Tingle' in my leg.  Not the seismic legasm's that throw Chris Mathews to the floor, gasping for air, but a Tingle never the less.  She is an amazing woman, a great patriot and the moronic attacks sway me not one bit.  They only  to solidify my Resolve.  In fact, the left is so strident and loony where Palin is concerned, they are basically self destructing as their idiocy is continually in plain view.  The Democratic party, generally, is infested with liberals and is plainly in trouble.  Until they find a purifying element as the Republicans have with the Tea Party, they are lost.  And we NEED a two party system. With both party's functioning for the good of the country.  

A 14 billion dollar deficit is not promoting the 'good of the country'.  That is why I would love to see a stingy, fiscally responsible (with the Tea Party holding a ball bat over them) Republican White House.  

Immediately following the Arizona shootings, I did feel real trepidation for Sarah Palin's safety.  Especially after Linda Lopez's fantastic conclusion that Sarah Palin and the Tea Party were responsible for the shootings.  Linda Lopez is a Democratic Congresswoman from Arizona who with her hideous, careless remarks put Sarah Palin in harms way.  She (Lopez) should not only apologize publicly, but she should be impeached for her dangerous, rush to judgement remarks made just one hour after the event occurred.  There is no excuse for her reckless, feckless words.  Shame on those who voted this loon into office. 

After two years of horrifying, incompetent governing by an ideologue, I can't wait for the new Republican President, whomever it will be.  Finally, it must be exhausting for Mathew's staff to come up with his nightly drivel, week after week and there must be a whole separate staff that is in charge of the 'race' baloney.  Is Mathews an angry blak person trapped in a nearly albino body?  Does he know at the end of an evening of silliness that an entire nation looks upon his style and delivery as appalling?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ctuilu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6bwl</id></website><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/culture/2011/01/17/sarah-palin-tribute-sung-battle-hymn-republic</link><postedTime>2011-01-17T22:29:32+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-01-18T01:16:22+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/8gnre8</id><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/culture/2011/01/17/sarah-palin-tribute-sung-battle-hymn-republic#comment-130278026</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8nldh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-01-17</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>