<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3i4v7/post/2012-03-29T21:28:05</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3o71v</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c8yu3</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Very good.  I did not qualify my observation by suggesting it was rarely used so I'm wrong. 
There are many conflicting accounts.  I completely support the press looking at this from every direction including the assertion that Martin was in possession of burglary tools, even if that turns out to be irrelevant. The special prosecutor should not leave a stone unturned and the press should not allow it.  I have worked with law enforcement as a consultant and in another life, had a connection to Duchess County when Sharpton was involved in the Tawana Brawley hoax.  I believe him to be a race hustler and knowing nothing else of you, would assign 100 times the trust in you to fairly examine the evidence in this case than Al Sharpton. 
I don't disagree that killing someone without provocation is serious and that lying on a police report is a criminal offense.  But, unless there are more witnesses, we don't know what provocations preceded the shooting., and may never know.  I don't believe Z simply shot him in Cold blood and would probably ask anyone who so claims to come forward with some evidence.  For example, If M was shot in the back at 10 meters, then Z would have a tough time convincing me it wasn't murder.  If the shooting took place at point blank range, that suggests some kind of confrontation.  Now, if Z is correct, that he was on his back getting the s beat out of him, and Reached for his gun, the entry wound is going to support that but if the wound suggests they were facing each other, that is a different story.  There is at least one witness that claims to have seen, from a distance, M on top of Z and Z yelling for help.  I'd want to know what the witness was looking at when he heard the shot.  I'd remember if Z was on the ground.  That, to me, is the key question that gets to whether or not this was a case of self defense or murder.  If Z was on his feet and the fight was over, even if Z had badly lost the fight, his life was no longer in danger, and he can't claim self defense. 
Based upon your observations, including knowing the LEO acronym, you can't be serious in concluding that the ABC video showing Z getting out of the car proves anything.  Either Z had a bloody nose and some signs of injuries at the scene or he didn't.  There would have been multiple police officers on the scene along with crime tape gawkers.   That is the one small piece of evidence that should be easily settled.  He may not have had a broken nose, but if he'd been in a fight and had injuries,  the evidence of that will be that from the crime scene, not a video taken later. 
My only request here as that you join me in waiting for actual facts and presume that if you are reading it in a newspaper or hearing it on TV, it is probably wrong and I'd include Fox in that as well.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z5r9w</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6rx1</id></website><link>http://www.sltrib.com/sltrib/opinion/53808843-82/martin-trayvon-zimmerman-black.html.csp</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T07:02:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:28:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3i4v7</id><link>http://www.sltrib.com/sltrib/opinion/53808843-82/martin-trayvon-zimmerman-black.html.csp#comment-480114159</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c8czx</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>