<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjgpm/update/2012-03-26T14:15:51/17aed016f4674771ea23e2546b767f98c709d586cd5b9141f46ead6a940e7ac5</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkj5g3</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gz8j4</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Afraid not:

Section 13A-6-90. STALKING. 1992. 


"(a) A person who intentionally and repeatedly 
follows or harasses another person and who makes a credible threat, either 
express or implied, with the intent to place that person in reasonable fear of 
death or serious bodily harm is guilty of the crime of stalking.(b) The 
crime of stalking is a Class C felony." 


Section 13A-6-91. AGGRAVATED STALKING. 1992. 



"(a) A person who violates the provisions of Section 
13A-6-90(a) [Stalking] and whose conduct in doing so also violates any court 
order or injunction is guilty of the crime of aggravated stalking.


(b) The crime of aggravated stalking is a Class B 
felony." 


Section 13A-6-92. DEFINITIONS. 1992. 


"For purposes of this article [Article 5. Stalking 
and Aggravated Stalking] only: 


(a) COURSE OF CONDUCT. means a pattern of conduct 
composed of a series of Acts over a period of time which evidences a continuity 
of purpose. 


(b) CREDITABLE [credible] THREAT. means a threat, 
expressed or implied, made with the intent and the apparent ability to carry out 
the threat so as to cause the person who is the target of the threat to fear for 
his or her safety or the safety of a family member and to cause a reasonable 
mental Anxiety, anguish, or fear.


(c) HARASSES. means engages in an intentional course 
of conduct directed at a specified person which alarms or annoys that person, or 
interferes with the freedom of movement of that person, and which serves no 
legitimate purpose. the course of conduct must be such as would cause a 
reasonable person to suffer substantial emotional distress, and must actually 
cause substantial emotional distress. Constitutionally protected conduct is not 
included within the definition of this term." 


Section 13A-6-93. RELATIONSHIP TO OTHER CRIMINAL 
LAWS. 1992.


"This article [Article 5. Stalking and Aggravated 
Stalking] shall not be construed to repeal other criminal laws. Whenever conduct 
prescribed by any provision of this article is also prescribed by any other 
provision of law, the provision which carries the more serious penalty shall be 
applied."</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6laffg</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tz1k</id></website><link>http://www.mediaite.com/online/george-zimmermans-police-report-trayvon-martin-approached-him-from-behind-bashed-his-head-against-sidewalk/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:43:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:15:51+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjgpm</id><link>http://www.mediaite.com/online/george-zimmermans-police-report-trayvon-martin-approached-him-from-behind-bashed-his-head-against-sidewalk/#comment-476598571</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rypw4</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>flagged</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>