<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3zd1r/update/2012-03-29T05:12:54/47903c8f2f74b5bd84cae1217dfaeb3321eff5b86e410d872b61edb506a7e412</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>What a crazy species we are.  In the last 100 we have moved forward in so many areas. The telephone, the automoble. We can even send space craft to th edge of our solar system.

When it comes to getting along with our fellow human beings we have done exactly the sane thing for thousands of years.  As intelegent as we should be, instead of learning about the people we share our planet with we would rather just hate them because we don't understand them.

Nevermind our human neghbors from the otherside of the world for just a moment. Let talk Trayvon Martin for a moment, he was killed by mr zimmernam because mr zimmerman felt threatened eventhough the police told him to stay away from him.  Maybe, just maybe Mr Martin was standing his ground.  After all, he was minding his own
 business when this guy twice his size and almost twice his age comes up to him and demands to know what he was doing. Wtf, I know what I would have done.  I would have said something wise assed to this bully who came to harrass me.  Know I am Not saying this is what happened, I am just putting Trayvons shoes on my white feet.

I would have said something like 'whats it to you". "Mind your business" and maybe Depending on Zimmermans attitude, " f u you big queer (no offence to my gay friends). Get the f away from me you perv.  And what if zimmerman brandished his weapon. Should Trayvon tour and run?  Hell no! I would have gotten in his face (standing my ground") and saying a lot of not so polite things.  And I probably would have taunted him. (Remember, I am 16 or 17).  I would have not stopped until I got a reaction from him. When your that young the last thing you would expect from this azz clown would be for him to kill me in Cold blood.
Only God, zimmerman and trayvon know what happened that day.  Even if Trayvon "stood his ground" and did not run (which I believe the evidence shows).  Then why is Zimmerman not behind bars?  Right, I remember know. You see I grew up in florida in a middle class white family.  As a kid I used to drive all around the state just to see different places. Twice I witness something that made me sick to my stomach. The last time was around 1982, I was with my pretend girl friend Wendy.  It was just before midnight, there was a crowd of cars parkrd along side this deserted dirt road somewhere north of the palm beach county line.  Just as we passed the twenty or so cars we found are selves in the middle of a crowd of men. Some were in blue jeans, most wore white robes. As we realized what we had just done they lit two cross's.  That's one of those experiences you never forget.  I will never understand what kind of a man would find pride in that sort of non sense. I wanted to throw-up. It still makes the hair on the back of my neck stand-up.
In what judicial system says a whit guy can harrass a black kid and make it illegal for the young man to "stand his ground"? And why is it legal for the aggressor to murder this kid in Cold blood.  Pure and simple.  Someone forgot what decade it was and probably thought the kid was supposed to lick his boots after showing his freedom papers.

This is flat-out an injustice.  It is events like this that makes me embarased to be an American.  I guess I mis understood "the land of the free".  Its more like the "the land of the whites" and th home of the lynchmen".

May your God save your soul because I don't think mine will.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hzoon</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/bpum</id></website><link>http://ideas.time.com/2012/03/28/where-are-the-protests-against-the-killing-of-shaima-al-awadi/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T14:23:02+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T09:12:54+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3zd1r</id><link>http://ideas.time.com/2012/03/28/where-are-the-protests-against-the-killing-of-shaima-al-awadi/#comment-479354987</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/r6gwe</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>