<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/136753/post/26057847/comment/329402710</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>trial, Tsinghua University, submitted a statement on the deaths of Professor Jiang Mentioned in the text, Professor Jiang 7pm temperature suddenly rise,  38.5 degrees, and accompanied by Palpitations, precordial discomfort,louis vuitton luggage, hold your breath shortness of breath and sweating phenomenon. In the meantime, they had many times to find Lee, I hope she immediately disposed of, but until there is no perception of Professor Jiang, Lee came to the ward, Professor Jiang has no heartbeat. Tsinghua University, said the hospital has never been whether the medical controversy for medical malpractice been identified Lee in violation of the deal with legal, there is nothing wrong handler on the behavior of Lee\'s medical mistakes. In addition, a letter of apology at October 12, 2009, Lee wrote to family members of Professor Jiang also has this to say, oral account of communication, and under a doctor\'s advice, but there is no timely and personally to the bedside to see the patient, and I apologize for the patient\'s sudden death, I have not estimated to Tsinghua University,oakley sunglasses sale, also submitted the minutes said, October 12, 2009, 22, Qinghua University Hospital twice a meeting to discuss Professor Jiang regarding the handling. The final conclusion: Lee should take full responsibility of a doctor on duty, and 22 made the decision. The decision that the October 8, 2009, Lee on duty when the call for family members of Professor Jiang, failure to make timely inspections and families to participate in cardiopulmonary resuscitation, resulting in complaints from the families of patients brought to the hospital with serious adverse effects. By the House leadership, several rounds of consultations, the financial compensation of 50,000 yuan closed. (Now) 40 percent of the amount of compensation decided by the Lee personal,Cheap Oakley Sunglasses, and cancel the current and next year candidate for the backbone of job qualifications, net of the month Outstanding Service Award for 50 yuan. for such evidence, doctors, Lee refused recognition. She said that the record of the meeting without her signature, a letter of apology is Lee, Ultimately, the court held that, according to Lee submitted a letter of apology from Tsinghua University, Professor Jiang family submitted a statement on the deaths of Professor Jiang and Lee\'s statements can be identified when she was on duty, Professor Jiang family members call failed to inspect and families to participate in cardiopulmonary resuscitation, and mistakes led to the complaints of the patient\'s family. Tsinghua University, Lee\'s punishment there is nothing wrong, the judgment dismissed the prosecution of Lee. hospital doctors,Oakley Sunglasses, Tsinghua University, charged that in February 1996, she worked at Tsinghua University Hospital, engage in medical careers. October 8, 2009, running, Lee in the medical ward on night duty. Was 75 years old with acute leukemia, lung infection, atrial fibrillation,Puma Ferrari, Professor Jiang sudden death. Complaints, after family members of patients to the Tsinghua University hospital at October 22, 2009, the hospital identified the matter is a medical accident and asked her to compensation of 20,000 yuan, and canceled her competition for the qualification of the backbone positions. Lee believes that the hospital did not identify the qualifications of medical malpractice, the decision made by fact-finding errors,coach factory outlet, in violation of procedure, lack of legal basis, and the prosecution asked the court to withdraw treatment decisions. &amp;#30456;&amp;#20851;&amp;#30340;&amp;#20027;&amp;#39064;&amp;#25991;&amp;#31456;&amp;#65306; Clear Msn History and Delete Msn History Tools How to configure Smartphone inbox e-mail options Eating Seafood at An Anaheim Restaurant </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:136753:26057847</id><idPostId>26057847</idPostId><idBlogId>136753</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:136753</id><idBlogId>136753</idBlogId><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com</link><displayName>HOCKEYCENTRIC</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-canucks-are-more-than-one-line-and-luongo/</link><displayName>The Canucks Are More Than One Line And Luongo</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-01T18:29:34.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:136753:26057847:329402710</id><link>http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-canucks-are-more-than-one-line-and-luongo/#IDComment329402710</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T18:29:34.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on The Canucks Are More Than One Line And Luongo by biuyt3w0</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://www.louisvuitton-purses-outlet.biz/</link><idEmailMd5>bc0dfb139bf240282eccd434c60a0f83</idEmailMd5><displayName>biuyt3w0</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://www.louisvuitton-purses-outlet.biz/"&gt;biuyt3w0&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.hockeycentric.com/general/the-canucks-are-more-than-one-line-and-luongo/"&gt;The Canucks Are More Than One Line And Luongo&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>