<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39aqv/post/2012-03-29T17:17:55</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>For people that can't Spot the fakery, I guess that's OK since they don't know what they're watching. However, for people that do, it takes away from the movie "suspend disbelief" moment. I suspect that many people have good eyes to Spot fakers.
Like fake guitar playing, unrealistic fight scenes, bad/bogus language skills, bad golf/baseball etc. swings, bad soccer kicks, basketball dribbling, foreign accents etc. One doesn't need to be an expert to Spot poseurs ... just some intelligence and an eye for beauty/symmetry. Good form in most activities is also beautiful and natural. I'm no movie star, but if I'm one, I'll strive to make it real. Like DeNiro in Raging Bull, who lost weight and  weight, so realistic I thought they have a double. Ditto for Hanks in Cast Away. Like the stunt actors that don't fall straight down, but Bounces against railings with their backs etc. to make it seemed real.  The real actors make you want to watch them because they work on their craft, and it shows. They don't have to be experts in whatever they're playing, but it needs to be realistic enough for the audience to suspend disbelief. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/65rt4j</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lkc4</id></website><link>http://www.wired.com/geekdad/2012/03/avengers-hawkeye-archery/</link><postedTime>2012-03-15T11:07:34+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T21:17:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m39aqv</id><link>http://www.wired.com/geekdad/2012/03/avengers-hawkeye-archery/#comment-479905612</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-15</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>