<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34r25/post/2012-03-29T10:49:23</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Wow... All I have to say is that God is good and that Trayvon and his family will get the justice they deserve no matter how many lies are told or how much evidence is hidden. Even a blind person can see that Trayvon was hunted down like an animal and killed. Why did Zimmerman follow Trayvon was he was asked not to. why was he carrying a gun ? Remember Trayvon jus went to the store to pick up some sweets and a drink. He was walkin home. He wasn't causing any trouble on the road . He was only trying to get home. Wow. Poor child. The location that Zimmerman sed that Trayvon was at was so much further than his home . The location that Trayvon was killed at  was so much closer to Trayvons home. That young boy was trying to get to his house. His girlfriend said that he said that this man is following him and he looks creepy. Zimmerman claimed that they Always get away with it . Who Zimmerman? Who gets away with it? And wat zimmerman ? Do they get away with?  Zimmerman you followed Trayvon and you killed that poor boy in Cold blood. No one is sayin that Trayvon was innocent because all children have attitudes nowadays . No child is perfect or maybe not even close to it but that child did not deserve to die and you had no right to kill him. You are not getting arrested when your gun was not even licensed .wow lol but we know you killed that young boy because you are racist and he didn't do anything to you. He was wearing a hood .. Lol wow . Small minded . Now you claim that Trayvon said that you're gonna die tonight ..lol wow. Zimmerman you will get what's common to you and everyone else that's on this case letting you get away with what you have done . Hiding evidence and everything because guess what? The almighty ... The greatest is in charge . God is great so I'm jus goin to sit back relax and wait . Lol ;) </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zcxr4</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T06:16:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:49:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34r25</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/29/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html#comment-479544628</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zz574</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>