<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3x7l5/update/2012-03-29T13:47:15/d48b68b2425a0180d7f8e7ace6f07d0cd60b49a8a8b198f2285d1272b85231c3</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ma3s</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Have you forgotten why that is?  The government stepped in and said you cannot discipline your child.  Therefore, they do not understand the real meaning of "truth or consequences"!   Most of today's adults know that if we don't follow the rules of life there will be consequences, i.e. running red lights, not paying taxes, drunken driving, murder and mayhem, etc., so for the most part, we follow those rules.  Kids today have never had to suffer punishment for anything.  They think life is a video game that they can turn on and  and just start over when they feel like it.  Never having gotten a spanking or their little hands slapped for touching something they should not, or punished for talking back to their parents, or making demands and getting what they want, they are ill prepared for what real life has in store for them.  They don't even know what it means to lose a game, or a contest anymore.  These are the same kids who are going to be in charge of the government and us some day.  Are you ready for that?  Don't forget....the government leaders today are the same pot heads from the 60's.  Burn the flag, anti-establishment, Burn your bras, make love not war!  Oh yeah....I knew back then that we were going to be in trouble when they Reached the age to come into power and boy was I right!  As the Bible says...."you reap what you sow."...Heaven help us because we have been raising a very poor crop indeed!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6han6w</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rlyt</id></website><link>http://visiontoamerica.org/8931/state-confiscates-newborn-over-vaccinations/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T02:38:08+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:47:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3x7l5</id><link>http://visiontoamerica.org/8931/state-confiscates-newborn-over-vaccinations/#comment-479690212</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>