<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwjc8c/update/2012-03-31T03:52:19/28a6264c868891a04ee40251f67d77e9e03d5e12dc3b8cbfc18d9904cb498ae7</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Answering my own question from a page or so downthread -- what Cincinnati has to trade is mainly bench bats, which we don't need. But the whole back end of their BP is a complete shambles; and they've got a young pitcher named Aroldis Chapman who is, at the moment, listed as #6 in their rotation, though up to now he's played mostly out of the BP. He has 69 MLB appearances, with a 6-3 W-L, 3.27 , and 1.247 WHIP. Crucially for us, he's still got one option year remaining, and isn't up for arbitration until 2015. He has a fastball (I believe that's what you call it, isn't it, when it averages 98.4 mph and has been known to hit 105? A fastball?), a deceptive slider, and a -- no foolin', now -- 92mph changeup that's nothing special but good enough to get him through an occasional Spot start.

Hey dere, Ben Cherington! You on this? Maybe we dangle Melancon, perhaps Albers, and a Player to be Named Later (who cannot be named yet, until he comes Off the DL, but his initials bear a remarkable resemblance to those of Bobby Jenks) in front of Mr. Jocketty's nose and see if he snaps at 'em?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67v6dg</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lz6q</id></website><link>http://boston.redsox.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120330%26content_id=27768988%26vkey=news_bos%26c_id=bos</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T23:04:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T07:52:19+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwjc8c</id><link>http://boston.redsox.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120330%26content_id=27768988%26vkey=news_bos%26c_id=bos#comment-481633851</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/csz32</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>