<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3vq8j/update/2012-03-29T08:45:35/d4c554500269e38ba2db0f1f915f118fe9d2be63179a383d2370a4d8dc002a54</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Really disappointing to see what's happened over the last 6 games or so with so much on the line.  Over the course of the season, there have been some real bright Spots (emergence of Spencer Machacek, Zach Bogosian and Blake Wheeler and Pavelec's play night after night) but too many over all disappointments.  Antropov and Fehr were huge "busts" and should be cut loose.  Ladd's leadership???  No one leads better on this team than Stuart.  Sure he makes errors but he blocks shots,  hits and even fights when he has to. If he doesn't wear the "C" next year, something's wrong.

Enstrom is promising with his puck handling but he is so frustrating to watch on the power play.  I've never seen someone with so many great opportunities to shoot the puck, wait and pass .  When he does decide to shoot, it's  from a low percentage area on the ice.  This happens night after night after night. So frustrating!!!!! Not sure how we can all see it but the coaching staff appears to do nothing to get him shooting.  He's got to get better at this next year.

The power play needs to stop giving up short handed goals.  Nothing deflates a team more than when you are a man up and you get scored on.  Then when you have to kill a penalty, you're done as evidenced against the Rangers last night.

The 2 brightest Spots on the team were Wheeler and Pavelec.  Let's face it...this is Wheeler's team.  When he's "going", he elevates the whole teams play.  Pavelec gets his "jock" shot Off night after night and still gives us a chance to stay close.  He's been a work horse for the team and has faced the 3rd or 4th most shots of any goalie in the league.  But I think he has hit the "wall" as of late.  Seeing more frustration from him these last few games.

Many will say this has been a successful year and in many ways, it has been.  But the bottom line is winning. To put the year in perspective, the Leafs look like a joke and are embarrassing to watch. They went 4-15-2 over a 21 game stretch...just brutal.  Yet they are currently only 3 points behind us as of last nights game.

Like most fans, I think we were prepared to cut the team some "slack" this year.  However, there is too much "potential" on this team and they need realize that potentail and make significant improvements for next year.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h43jz</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7m2w</id></website><link>http://www.winnipegsun.com/2012/03/28/fans-deserve-big-game-vs-rangers-jets-say</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T16:37:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T12:45:35+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3vq8j</id><link>http://www.winnipegsun.com/2012/03/28/fans-deserve-big-game-vs-rangers-jets-say#comment-479461779</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rrkmr</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>