<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrwun/post/2012-03-30T12:36:25</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body> Calling this a "racial" shooting is RIDICULOUS!!!! 
A Ridiculous Lie, perpetrated by those who truly are RACISTS!!!

While it is true that the volunteer neighborhood patrol person in this case did first Spot the young man in the neighborhood, the volunteer stopped following him as was ordered by 911 dispatch and continued to simply patrol the area, that is his job.That is what neighborhood crime watch people do, patrol, to protect you and the neighborhood.
(Thanks to all the volunteers crime watchers who protect us!)
 This strong healthy young man walked up and confronted the neighborhood patrol volunteer and  knocked him to the ground quite quickly I might add, and  started pounding his face in. Pounding it in so severely he was breaking facial bones
Getting your face pounded in while your on the ground by a strong healthy young man, as he is  wailing away at your face with his fists and breaking bones in your face.. I would hardly call that "racial" motivation. Having this out of control strong healthy teenager go for your gun while he is beating your face in and breaking your facial bones while your still on the ground. PLEASE!! That shooting is called "self defense" against an aggressor and dangerous individual who was Reaching for a gun to kill.
It is very very sad that someone died here, it is very very sad that someone got badly beat up here...  but get the facts straight.. no one was just skipping home with some candy from the store and all of the sudden they were chased down and shot.  All the facts have come out, that is why the volunteer was NOT charged by the police. That is why  the TRUE RACISTS have  come out as they have here recently and tried to say this young man was shot because of his race and THAT IS A LIE!  
This incident happened because of an altercation, where someone was being badly beat to the point of fearing for his life while his facial bones were being broken, and his gun was being removed from his body by an aggressor trying to kill him.
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6lfd6w</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gr2q</id></website><link>http://www.carltonjordan.com/2012/03/27/new-orleans-cop-says-treyvon-martin-deserved-to-die-like-a-thug/</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T15:46:49+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:36:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwrwun</id><link>http://www.carltonjordan.com/2012/03/27/new-orleans-cop-says-treyvon-martin-deserved-to-die-like-a-thug/#comment-480928304</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>