<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjos1/post/2012-03-26T14:50:48</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>You must have assumed that many Gallery workers would comment on this.  I am completely offended by this article.  It is very unfortunate that you had a bad experience in the Gallery, but attacking the staff as a whole will not accomplish anything.  Most of us work very hard at our jobs, and personally I go out of my way to be as friendly as possible to others. In fact I have had people give me concerned faces as to why I'm  happy at work.  Regarding East Neighborhood dining, I also worked there and later transferred to The Gallery.  We have a much more friendly staff in The Gallery, who have Always made me feel welcome and happy.... whether I was working or a customer.  As for you putting your comments about us getting paid for our work where they don't belong, please Burn your arm on the steamer, carry heavy preparation trays, sweat in the dish room, make food for hundreds of people, clean tables, gut out chicken, tenderize meat, sweep floors, clean the entire back kitchen in a half hour...... and then come talk to us about how our service is unacceptable.  I hope your future waffles are nice and crispy.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yie14</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/9og2</id></website><link>http://statenews.com/index.php/article/2012/03/caf_workers_need_professionalism</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T23:02:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T18:50:48+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkjos1</id><link>http://statenews.com/index.php/article/2012/03/caf_workers_need_professionalism#comment-476628504</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>