<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi6twu/post/2012-03-22T22:06:08</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi6ymf</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/00h9</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Stepping out of the Bubble

First Off we have some common ground.  I also believe Trayvon's death was senseless.  My comments were directed towards the opinion expressed in the article.
  Now for your stats.  Thank you for pointing out that the majority race in America holds some of the top Spots for crime.  Shall we talk crime by race using  % curve for population.  Yeah, I don't think you want to go there.  I know it's not fair because there is more to it then skin color (economics, family dynamics...). But that is my point there is more to it then skin color and this article, and many people want to make it about skin color and not about a poor kid loosing his life because of someone's reckless actions.  Even when the person who took Trayvon's life is a Hispanic, non-Law Enforcement person, we still see whites and Law enforcement vilified in this article...just saying maybe the community would be better served if the activist started looking at the whole picture instead of the " go to boogeyman ".  Maybe then instead of just stirring the pot some real solutions could be found.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yi5dc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/22/opinion/ifill-trayvon-martin/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T22:57:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T02:06:08+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi6twu</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/22/opinion/ifill-trayvon-martin/index.html#comment-474141551</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/00h9</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>