<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ocdm/post/2012-03-29T19:04:56</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I sort of strayed from the rules of today's practice. My story below is not about a recent travel I had but it is still a travel.
Hope you all enjoy :)

***


I hear the boosters die down. The rocket is now descending purely on gravity holders alone. I look at Father seated beside me with my eyes pleading. He studies me for a minute then I see a smile appear behind his mahogany colored beard followed by a small nod. With all haste, I unbuckle my seatbelt and I rush to the nearest circular window. Outside, I see Silcarine for the first time.

Stretching out before me is a sea of red. The red soil of Silcarine is dotted with small hills here and there. The land was still barren and uncultivated but when I squint my eyes and I look beyond the horizon I can see the outline of the Colony—spires jutting out of the red hued ground of the planet Silcarine. From here, they were so small it looked like they were needles planted on the ground. I raise my hand and I hold the Colony between my thumb and index finger. I smile at our new home.

The gravity holders are turned . The rocket touches the rough surface of the planet and the ship violently shook. I lost my footing and the Colony slips from my fingers. Fortunately for me, strong hands grab hold of my shoulders. I look up and I see the bearded face of Father. Father helps me on my feet. I try to take another glimpse of Silcarine but the circular window was closed. But that’s all right, because it means that it’s time for us to get Off the ship and to this alien planet.

Father passes to me a helmet shaped like a fish bowl. I put it on and the visor automatically closes down as I lock the helmet to my suit. Inside the helmet I see gauges and meters and all sorts of stuff appear on my interface. There’s one for oxygen left in my tank, another one’s for the gravity of the place where I am currently in. The others I’m still unfamiliar with. In front of us, the locks of the door of the ship twist and turn and steam emanates from them as they slide open. Father takes hold of my small hand. The huge metallic door rises up and we see Silcarine up close for the first time.

The Shepherd tells us that Silcarine is a planet plagued with violent sandstorms once every Earth week. Aside from the sandstorms, Silcarine is a safe planet void of any other living things aside from the humans who came before us. Today, according to him, is a safe day for us and we should have no fear of sandstorms. By pair we step out of the claustrophobic rocket ship and onto the red soil of our alien home planet. 

I look above me and I see the sky bursting with stars. There are millions, probably billions, of them. I stretch my palm upwards and I try to gather them in my tiny hand. I remember Father telling me once about stars. He said that because of the great distance between the stars and us we could still see their light sometimes even though the star itself had already died. As I crane my neck up and my eyes drown with the million Burning stars, I know that one of them is the ghost of our Sun still haunting the people it once gave life to. I don’t know which one’s our Sun but I know it’s still there watching over us even though it had already passed away. I smile at the thought and I utter a silent thank you. Father grabs hold of my shoulder and together we make our way to a hovercar that’ll bring us to our new home.
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zhx3e</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/n4i5</id></website><link>http://thewritepractice.com/all-the-pretty-words-writing-in-the-style-of-cormac-mccarthy/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T14:33:08+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T23:04:56+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ocdm</id><link>http://thewritepractice.com/all-the-pretty-words-writing-in-the-style-of-cormac-mccarthy/#comment-480001111</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lngol</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>