<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3w17c/update/2012-03-30T02:11:13/34c126ede3563831f450bfc3b3c325342edb8572419f9839f4ab0e536c437697</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m37o4z</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dq27q</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>@avclub-4a51fda79bbd54b4e7327dd6559b6c4d:disqus  - Thank you for your contributions to the discussion...it's  nice to have someone willing to debate issues reasonably, even if I / we disagree.

As Adam Farrar said, the defense that the MPAA works better than anything before it is relative.  Anyone who's involved in the current method of doing things says that because they don't want to be replaced.  "We don't need labor unions, we can police ourselves."  "We don't need clean energy, coal Burning works great as is!"  "Marriage has Always been between a man and a woman, no reason to change that now!"

I totally believe that Weinstein is using this situation as free publicity.  I also don't see a problem with that, as even prior to this film I've felt that the MPAA's ratings system is flawed and needs reform.  The only way that will ever happen is if enough people speak out about it to get them to change.

The United States' morality is so fucked up now it's insane.  Plenty of others here have already commented on it, but seriously - why is sexual content or language given as much or more consideration than extreme violence?

Example: The Grand Theft Auto San Andreas "hot coffee" hack was found.  "So it's okay to shoot a woman in the face, but not to have sex with her?"</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z8v7e</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/bully,71587/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T05:04:56+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T06:11:13+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3w17c</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/bully,71587/#comment-480308511</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/doxrl</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>