<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkf132/post/2012-03-26T12:48:24</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>

United
Kingdom


Main article: National Health Service


The UK's National Health
Service (NHS) is a publicly funded healthcare system that
provides coverage to everyone normally resident in the UK. It is not strictly
an insurance system because (a) there are no premiums collected, (b) costs are
not charged at the patient level and (c) costs are not pre-paid from a pool.
However, it does achieve the main aim of insurance which is to spread financial
risk arising from ill-health. The costs of running the NHS (est. £104 billion
in 2007-8)[29]
are met directly from general taxation. The NHS provides the majority of health
care in the UK, including primary care, in-patient care,
long-term
health care, ophthalmology, and dentistry.


Private health care has continued
parallel to the NHS, paid for largely by private insurance, but it is used by
less than 8% of the population, and generally as a top-up to NHS services.
There are many treatments that the private sector does not provide. For
example, health insurance on pregnancy is generally not covered or covered with
restricting clauses. Typical exclusions for Bupa schemes (and many other
insurers) include:


ageing, menopause and puberty; A I
D S /H I V ; allergies or allergic disorders; birth control, conception, se xual
problems and se x changes; chronic conditions; complications from excluded or
restricted conditions/ treatment; convalescence, rehabilitation and general
nursing care ; cosmetic, reconstructive or Weight loss treatment; deafness;
dental/oral treatment (such as fillings, gum disease, jaw shrinkage, etc);
dialysis; drugs and dressings for out-patient or take-home use† ; experimental
drugs and treatment; eyesight; HRT and bone densitometry; learning
difficulties, behavioural and developmental problems; overseas treatment and
repatriation; physical aids and devices; pre-existing or special conditions;
pregnancy and childbirth; screening and preventive treatment; Sleep problems
and disorders; speech disorders; temporary relief of symptoms.[30]
(† = except in exceptional circumstances)


There are a number of other
companies in the United Kingdom which include, among others, AXA, Aviva, Bupa, Groupama Healthcare, WPA and PruHealth.
Similar exclusions apply, Depending on the policy which is purchased.


Recently (2009) the main
representative body of British Medical physicians, the British Medical
Association, adopted a policy statement expressing concerns about developments
in the health insurance market in the UK. In its Annual Representative Meeting
which had been agreed earlier by the Consultants Policy Group (i.e. Senior
physicians) stating that the BMA was "extremely concerned that the policies
of some private healthcare insurance companies are preventing or restricting
patients exercising choice about (i) the consultants who treat them; (ii) the
hospital at which they are treated; (iii) making top up payments to cover any
gap between the funding provided by their insurance company and the cost of
their chosen private treatment." It went in to "call on the BMA to
publicise these concerns so that patients are fully informed when making
choices about private healthcare insurance."[31]
The NHS offers patients a choice of hospitals and consultants and does not
charge for its services.


The private sector has been used
to increase NHS capacity despite a large proportion of the British public
opposing such involvement.[32]
According to the World Health Organization, government
funding covered 86% of overall health care expenditures in the UK as of 2004,
with private expenditures covering the remaining 14%.[19]


 


</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6r04nx</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6bwl</id></website><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/justice/2012/03/26/howard-dean-s-shocking-obamacare-prediction</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T15:56:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T16:48:24+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkf132</id><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/justice/2012/03/26/howard-dean-s-shocking-obamacare-prediction#comment-476530020</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6gmpo</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>