<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/51zpvb/update/2011-08-10T18:24:25/d67e4d15ba5e32212c6928d939874c038135e6953271184d59ab51610cfc8449</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>IF OUR YOUTH DID THE SAME, I, AND YOU, WOULDN'T BE WATCHING OUR CITY BEING DESTROYED ON TV.   I WOULD HELP THE POLICE AND WOULD GIVE UP MY LIFE TO SAVE IT! 

WHO HERE would let rioters light YOUR car on fire and Burn down YOUR home or business and putting YOUR family in danger? 

MORAL OF THE ANN'S STORY: U.S. CITIZENS HAVE GUNS AND BRITONS DON'T! "Speak softly but carry a big SHOTGUN!"

ANYBODY WITH ME? BULLIES  back away when confronted with over-whelming force!

These English thugs remind me of OBAMA'S CELEBRATED WISCONSIN'S DEMOCRAT UNION THUGS/ANARCHISTS/LEGISLATORS that held the Wisconsin State House hostage! Didn't these BULLIES/SORE LOSERS/CRY BABIES get the spanking they deserved last night? OBAMA this morning: "Wwwwwaaaaahhhh Wwwwaaaaahhhhhh!" 

Some of today's youth are just looking for an excuse to riot and they remind me of the KATRINA LOOTERS who stole everything in sight before the cops showed up and who were mostly WELFARE IDIOTS TOO! That includes their WELFARE parents who didn't see the numerous warnings due to watching Jerry Springer, Maury, "You are not the father" on the mother's tenth appearance, and watching Oprah, Obama's number one fan.  They also couldn't be civil enough to use DEMOCRATIC PRINCIPLES, INSTEAD OF ANARCHY, WHEN THEY STAYED IN THE METRODOME! Not one person, or group of persons, came out of there as LEADERS??? Then the GOVERNMENT gave them WELFARE credit cards with a couple of thousand dollars so they could move to another city to try to get back on their feet but they instead bought TV's, X-Box's, and cell phones! HOW DO YOU HELP STUPID?

OUR WELFARE ENABLERS, THE DEMOCRATS, will argue they are more for Social Justice than England's and EU Socialists and equal to Russian Communists and Chi-Com Maoists!   

MORAL OF THE STORY: Obama, and other oath takers like Hillary, want to take away our "right to bear arms," TO BE LIKE ENGLAND AND A U.N. PROGRAM that seeks a "small arms Ban," even though they took an oath to defend THE U.S. CONSTITUTION, and all of the U.S. CONSTITUTION AS CURRENTLY WRITTEN, AND NOT WHAT THEY THINK IT SHOULD BE IN THE FUTURE!  That alone is an impeachable offense!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/erou1u</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry2d</id></website><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=45446</link><postedTime>2011-08-10T22:10:24+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-08-10T22:24:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/51zpvb</id><link>http://www.humanevents.com/article.php?id=45446#comment-282866854</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ajkck</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-08-10</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>