<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkx5qh/update/2012-03-26T06:29:52/6e8c2398abbaa595d8f3cbb54bcff1d0b986c5280288aa69b1c5d565c30ae2f1</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkllg0</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c9th5</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Easy enough to explain. If they're over 75 they don't get an increased allowance if they have income of £29,230 or more and if they're between 65 and 74 they don't if they have an income of £28,930 (with less of an increased allowance if they have incomes between £24,000 and these limits). And the benefits of these increased allowances are worth a maximum of £523 or £493 a year dependent on age.

These aren't massive incomes to live on - and widows make up a lot of these claims - who get only one personal allowance and a decreased income when their husbands die and are living on a much lower income as a result. And taking into account the massive unavoidable costs of gas and electric (and if you have mobility problems you need this far more), fuel for cars to shop, council taxes and so on living on these sorts of incomes isn't a very grand lifestyle. At least when you're at work you're not paying for Heating and lighting. 

And given the terribly low interest rates on savings of the past few years many pensioners have been living on amounts far less than this. These aren't the people that got us into a financial mess either- as you say many have paid Off their mortgages - not defaulted on them and caused the financial crisis - many have waited to buy things rather than take out credit.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/660v2d</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/politics/georgeosborne/9164178/Budget-2012-A-Nimby-storm-wont-divert-the-Coalition-from-its-course.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-24T21:01:47+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T10:29:52+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkx5qh</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/politics/georgeosborne/9164178/Budget-2012-A-Nimby-storm-wont-divert-the-Coalition-from-its-course.html#comment-476316985</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8qn5k</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-24</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>