<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/580p9a/update/2011-07-09T18:17:15/50638461616fe7f5601dfeb4f2a130470aeeae6e076758c8eebf35f00d1531df</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/cs8hoi</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>This topic needs some real science explained simply.

WHY MICROWAVE OVENS AREN'T BAD FOR YOU
All forms of radiation are exactly the same. People just categorize them by wavelength.All levels are safe at certain doses.High-frequency radiation is harmful except in very very tiny doses.Low-frequency radiation is Always safe, except in extremely high doses.Microwave radiation has the 2nd lowest frequency of any type, making it very safe.Here are the types, from highest frequency to lowest (most dangerous to least dangerous)• Gamma• X-Ray• Ultraviolet• VISIBLE• Infrared• MICROWAVE• Radio
You read that right. Even visible light is inherently more harmful than microwaves. It all comes down to quantity.

Microwaving food and cooking food in the oven are both safe. Microwave ovens use microwave radiation. Convection ovens use infrared radiation (which is higher on the chart BTW). The food is directly exposed to radiation in both cases, but our bodies aren't.

Sticking your head in the microwave and sticking your head in a Heated convection oven are both bad ideas, as in both cases you would be directly exposed to high doses of low-frequency radiation.

Microwaves are safe. BTW worrying too much about this stuff is more likely to give you cancer than anything else.

Live Awesome,

Jeff

P.S. I have an old microwave for sale if anybody wants to buy one.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/gups33</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rcq8</id></website><link>http://www.bodyrock.tv/2011/06/25/delicious-healthy-pizza-recipe/</link><postedTime>2011-06-26T02:44:44+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-07-09T22:17:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/580p9a</id><link>http://www.bodyrock.tv/2011/06/25/delicious-healthy-pizza-recipe/#comment-246895417</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-06-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>