<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwqk75/post/2012-03-30T19:01:53</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>you know what I find fishy about obito's death, why did they leave his body their in the rubble? 
sure, it could be because its technically his grave, but dont you think the leaf village should be cautious about 
leaving an leaf member, with an kekkei genkai in enemy territory? they go drastic measures for BG, why not SG 
since its MORE dangerous, according to the kakashi gaiden, that battle at the bridge whatever made kakashi, 
minato and obito famous. meaning that enemies also new about the whereabouts or an general idea as to where obito's body is at. 
yes its possible they took his body from the cave rubbles, but why would they not show that in the episode? instead it never
bothers to mention at all that they buried him at the leaf area where asuma's body is at, why do I say this because according to 
kakashi in land of waves arc, ninja who died in the leaf village ( mainly anbu's ) take their bodies and destroy it completly so that 
their  would not go into enemies hands ( ex: inochi ) it nevered stated that it had to be only anbu's meaning its reasonable 
that maybe it falls in line with kekkei genkai users ( mainly eye users ), which is another topic I want to bring up, what did the leaf 
do with ALL the uchiha BODIES? do you think they burried their bodies at the grave section where shikamaru visits? noticed how 
kakashi visits the carved named area while shikamarru visits the actual grave site. is it possible that Depending on how strong the 
ninja is or how valuble the ninja, they will Burn or destroy their bodies completely and carve their names in the stone, while the actual
ninja's who body still remains get an actual grave. It also brings into attention that sasuke doesn't visit his clans grave/or stone. 
the village elders probley didn't allow the uchiha clans name to be carved since they thought they started the kyuubi attack
and figured they must Burn the uchihas so that no one can get their kekkei genkai power ( excluding the eyes ). now another 
problem that doens't make sense, if the leaf didnt destroy the previous kages bodies, what is the point of doing that to anbu's? 
is it because the idea of destroying the bodies didn't occur until danzo organized the anbu squad while the kages who were dead 
already were not effected by the law, or because they never thought anyone would have the balls to enter the leaf village and take it
meaning that they never expected anyone to know the edo tensei at the time, so its possible that maybe they destroyed the 3rd 
hokages body, just in case.. now the overall conclusion I am trying to make here, if the leaf was dumb enough to leave obito's 
body their, its possible that maybe tobi took his body and his sharingan ( meaning its not crushed by the boulder ) I say that 
because if the boulder smashed his faced enough to where half his face was smashed, then he would had died instantly but he 
didn't, I  think the boulder actually smashed his middle organs ( partically the chest area and lack of blood ). so what I'm saying 
is that the boulder that smashed his face in halfway, he shouldn't even be able to talk because the boulder is halfway,  but thats the 
problem, the boulder is round and for it to not cover the lips completly means that it only crushed his lower/mid while the head
was impacted but only to partial of the blow that was covered by his stomach/chest. so the theory I'm saying is that  tobi was able 
to retrieve the sharingan, otherwise why would tobi cover one of his eyes? ( besides to take advantage of opponent by suprised ) 
SIMPLE, because that particular eye that he uses is special, unlike the others he wont use izanagi on that one.  whoever that uchiha is that
 he MOST likely stole from was an special ninja like shisui, and since kakashi MS is very similar to tobi's its reasonable to say that. 
I bet anything to say that IF tobi was forced to get rid of his current sharingan or his rennigan, he would choose the RG simply the 
fact that SH is the main bases of his survival, transportation, victories etc. 
- rewatch the anime version of obito's death scene, noticed how how his head moves slightly upward when Coughing up blood. 
  also notice how the bould is mostly on top of his middle body while the edge is slightly round towards his head, meaning his 
head took only half or less of damage impacted by the boulder, also you see theirs an shadow on between his head and the boulder
which means that their is alittle bit of distance between the two, now I must state that his right side crushed and that he couldn't 
even feel it, but that doesn't neccessary mean his eye was crushed, it just means the impact was more than enough to kill him 
by crushing his body, but the lost of feeling is only because its numbed and lack of blood. thats all I have to say, obito is still 
dead ( most likely ) but his eye is still possible of surviving the impact.. I excluded the final cave in which covered the rest of his 
body, but that still doesn't confirm that his eye is destroyed, afterall that boulder is strong enough to not get oversmashed by 
other boulders, meaning the eye is untouched... alrighty I'm done, its not an theory, just an guess from watching th episode. 
afterall kishi probley only covered his head in the frames and scenes, so that no one doesn't think his eye was taken. but from 
observation of the episode and tobi resemblance to obito doesn't add up. it has to be an HINT, tobi connects to obito in some way. 
you know what would be CRAZY, if obito was somehow RELATED to shisui or even better tobi was related to shisui. 
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hldpv</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ysqo</id></website><link>http://www.inaruto.net/naruto/naruto-chapter-580/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T12:25:02+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T23:01:53+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwqk75</id><link>http://www.inaruto.net/naruto/naruto-chapter-580/#comment-481297360</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8wehk</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>