<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwh42o/post/2012-03-30T13:46:03</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwym7z</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rb15x</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> Jim and Tracy - I think it was a little deeper than that.  One of the key issues the the team faces is how ready our young pitchers are and, while they grow, who is going to take up innings because we can't put our bullpen through another year like last season.

In a worst case scenario, Arrieta isn't ready, Britton needs to go back down and Matusz needs a complete overhaul.  Bundy is 2 years away and who knows how good anyone else will be until they get here.

Someone pointed out yesterday - and I wish I could recall who so I could give him some props - that we had not signed Chen and Wada at the time and Guthrie was still a question mark because what he looked to get in arbitration was out of line for his production.

Eveland would be a place holder.  If the "kids" had to go back to Norfolk or were not ready to step up then Eveland would be a guy to hold their Spot in the order.  

While he does not inspire images of champagne showers and ticker tape parades down Pratt St, he averages 5 1/3 innings as a starter and would have been no worse than Millwood and far better than Reyes.  And we would not have had to rush any of the young pitchers.Eveland was a low risk option to buy the team time for our pitchers to develop.  When better options - Chen, Hammel, Wada - were added Eveland became disposable.If some of the moves do not pan out how is it any different from the Yankees bringing in Tatum, Cust, Branyan, Dickerson, Nix, Hall, Rapada, DelCarmen or Moina?</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67a0cb</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/z6fr</id></website><link>http://www.masnsports.com/school_of_roch/2012/03/jim-johnson-addresses-loaded-questions-about-the-radar-guns.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T11:27:21+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T17:46:03+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwh42o</id><link>http://www.masnsports.com/school_of_roch/2012/03/jim-johnson-addresses-loaded-questions-about-the-radar-guns.html#comment-481000060</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mqovl</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>