<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miks1j/update/2012-03-24T07:09:18/372e587f1d91e9dcba148e4f6b9b22e104697c28eb5c85fa6b4a655099348291</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Congress is useless, obama and democrat governors held their own meetings to bypass the congressional body.  Thats what we have in washington d.c..  sec of def  goes to Afghanistan and forgot to pack his . 
    We have a call to kill a US soldier that killed 17 Afghan people, but dont say crap about the Major who yelled Allah Akbar and killed and wounded over 37 soldiers.  Supposedly safe in their own nation.  Congress doesnt give us anything!!! We demand them to comply with the peoples wishes.  Its "WE the People" not the president and congress allowing the people freedoms.  If you dont want to carry a firearm so be it.  DONT.  But dont tell me its wrong. 
Florida passed a law that was long over due and now the people have a right to protect themselves.   obama says if he had a son it would have been Trayvon Martin, you cant bullsh*t the amount of crap that comes out of obamas mouth.   This was to incite lawlessness and have the seal of approval from obama.  obama desicively made and choose to take a side and endorse it.  obama endorses lawlessness and approves of this action.  
 In California, LA Burnt to the ground because of Rodney King.  He was quilty then and was arrested many times after for the same criminal Acts.   The REASON why there is no RIOTING and Burning and killing in Florida is because of this LAW.  People are tired of the lawlessness, riots, destruction from a people that will take the race card everytime and use it to conduct total CHAOS.  The police didnt do anything in LA, the national guard didnt do anything in LA.   BUT the Koreans, held their ground until forced out by "The Law" then everything they worked for Burnt down shortly after.  
Make up your own mind.  But youll know my house.  My house will have all the dead bodies around it.  Show up with ill intentions  find out for yourself.  
Mike in Afghaistan</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/66z91t</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/opxh</id></website><link>http://cowboybyte.com/5621/will-the-concealed-carry-reciprocity-bill-pass-in-senate/</link><postedTime>2012-03-23T20:07:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-24T11:09:18+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miks1j</id><link>http://cowboybyte.com/5621/will-the-concealed-carry-reciprocity-bill-pass-in-senate/#comment-475140411</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/en7t</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>