<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miyfbj/update/2012-03-22T20:55:58/c6424f4146daa86f21798390979246bdd5c70ecdf120f6544bd7cd7159c140f5</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I sure hope somebody investigates this Trayvon case throughly and without prejeduce.  If they do, I am sure this story is going to disappear over night, like it never happened.  I have read several articles about this case, some shortly after the incident, and the facts then and now don't add up or at least some serious questions have not been asked yet.  Witness testimonies mysteriously change after this case gets national attention and the facts ignored in current articles or media reports.  I can state several interesting things.  First, testimony from eye witnesses first stated that they heard two men arguing and wrestling on the ground with Zimmerman on his back and Trayvon on top.  In the police report Zimmerman was noted with grass stains on the back of his shirt in addition to a bloody eye and head.  But, for some reason, these witnesses recently changed their stories?  I don't know about anybody else but I would more likely believe a statement given within 30 minutes of an incident than believe an altered one after several days and mass media attention.  In addition, when the 911 tapes were played for the father, he first claimed the voice crying for help was not his son's. (The first witnesses' statements also confirmed it was Zimmerman crying for help.) Later, the father recanted.  Also, the many articles about this story make the impression that Trayvon was practically executed on his knees in Cold blood.  However, according to this girl's testimony who was on the phone with Trayvon claims she heard Trayvon say, ,"Why are you following me?"  That tells me Trayvon turned and confronted Zimmerman.  Now, place yourself in this young, naive, innocent man's shoes.  What would you do if you turned and saw a 9mm pointed at you?  So, how did they end up wrestling on the lawn?  Well, it would only make since if Zimmerman didn't have the 9mm out.  Several other questions need to be answered also but I can''t cover everything here in this post and all I am saying is that case is taking on a personality of its own by obscuring the facts and being driven by emotion, media manipulation, and soon by politics. That's a dangerous combination.  Let's give the "cop wanna be" the benefit of the doubt before working everybody into a frenzy.  Just one last thing.  If I'm right, a lot of the facts and evidence can be confirmed by science forensics like voice analysis, biologicals, and ballistics.  I know this is not a CSI episode but I don't think it will take much to investigate and confirm the facts.  And when they are, I am sure this case is going to Vanish.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yottt</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q0fi</id></website><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/22/cnn-reporter-uses-word-ngger-on-live-tv-video/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T21:24:08+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-23T00:55:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miyfbj</id><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/22/cnn-reporter-uses-word-ngger-on-live-tv-video/#comment-474104835</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>