<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msktdg/update/2012-03-28T11:52:09/d014a81dce6616715b16fcdf654efaf68d0c394f0db929ea0b1c4cf4f9302ced</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Unfortunately, Jonathan has not done his homework and has not bothered to go into the details of the matter. Balwant Singh Rajoana is involved in killing of Beant Singh. Beant Singh was elected the Punjab Chief Minister when only 10 percent of the electorate voted. The Sikh population had decided to boycott the elections. During Beant Singh's tenor, 50,000 by conservative figures, Sikh youth was killed by the Government machinery. Balwant Singh was an accomplice in getting this ruthless butcher killed to stop him. If someone were to kill Hitler, it would be unfair to not support him and that is what Sikhs world over are doing. Balwant Singh killed no innocent person. He loves people and has already Pledged his body parts to be used after his death. He loves his people so much that it became necessary to kill Beant Singh to prevent the killing of innocent people in Punjab.
Also, bear in mind that Balwant Singh Rajoana hits right on the nail when he says that he has no faith in Indian Judiciary as  this same judiciary failed to punish anyone for the ruthless broad day massacre of 10,000 Sikhs including little children and women in the broad day light in the National Capital of India, New Delhi.What might be more interesting is to read how judiciary runs in India differently for minorities and majority community. One person called Ravinder Pal ( Nationalist Hindu) Burnt alive a Christian missionary and his two young sons. His capital punishment was converted to life sentence on frivolous grounds. Please read the case here:http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dara_Singh_(Hindu_nationalist) 
Rajoana is a hero of the same league as Bhagat Singh and Udham Singh who took to the arms.  Udham Singh killed Michael Dyer who was involved in killing innocents in Jalianwala Bagh. Udham SIngh is an Indian National Hero and his pictures adore the parliament and his story taught in school books. Rajoana is a hero and there are all reasons for the humanity to support him.
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h7wrx</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/4r1e</id></website><link>http://fullcomment.nationalpost.com/2012/03/28/jonathan-kay-why-are-some-canadian-sikhs-expressing-solidarity-with-an-unrepentant-terrorist/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T15:12:31+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T15:52:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msktdg</id><link>http://fullcomment.nationalpost.com/2012/03/28/jonathan-kay-why-are-some-canadian-sikhs-expressing-solidarity-with-an-unrepentant-terrorist/#comment-478479605</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zhmfm</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>