<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ubw9/post/2012-03-29T15:28:09</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Years ago after about six and a half years of college, I decided to escape.  I found a couple of waterlogged "fixer" surfboards on the beach and bought a VW bus.  I walked away from a fully furnished apartment and a girlfriend who had just discovered cocaine and wanted to kill me.  I did odd jobs for the next ten years and lived in three vans, two trees and three boats before I decided to head back to a normal reality.  I thought I'd try the American dream.  I bought a 3bd/2ba house with the two car garage full of toys, i.e. bikes, boats, etc.  I put up a white picket fence around the property and landscaped the place.  Then I saw some bums passing a bottle and remembered how Carefree that life was.  I gave away everything I couldn't sell, and am back to everything I can fit in my sailboat.  I'm planning a trip to the Bahamas, and if that goes well I'll head down to the Caribbean.  I hadn't considered the idea of obtaining new identification.  When I was living on the street everyone went by their first names and some other identifier like, "Guitar Randy", "Arizona Bob", etc.  Given the fact that I've never married and have no children, it's pretty easy to just pick up and leave.  Although I do have a cousin that bought a boat and sailed  from Canada down to Central America with her husband and two children.  I did experience some fear and Anxiety while I was getting rid of most of my stuff, but now that it's gone I feel great.  I highly recommend it for anyone who is tired of the "rat race".                                                                                                                          </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ytpn9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lp2f</id></website><link>http://www.jamesaltucher.com/2012/03/how-to-disappear-completely-and-never-be-found/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T13:01:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:28:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ubw9</id><link>http://www.jamesaltucher.com/2012/03/how-to-disappear-completely-and-never-be-found/#comment-479793410</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>