<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwdz5j/post/2012-03-30T09:53:33</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The global warming conspiracy needs to be put in perspective to be properly understood. This far-left attack by government-paid drones started in the 1970′s with the global cooling scam: we should disarm our nuclear bombers and fill them with soot to be spread over the poles and so prevent those new glaciers from descending south and crushing the New York skyscrapers to dust. When that did not work the same fakers invented the global warming hoax in the 1990′s; we should nationalize all industries and organize a UN-sponsored world socialist government based on "social justice" with the fakers in charge. What with 12 years of substantial cooling the fakers switched to the climate change flimflam in the 2000′s; so whatever happens we should…see above under the global warming hoax. And now we are faced with the cap &amp; trade power grab – but the aim is the same as above. Our socialists, Marxists, communists, Hollywood stars, university professors in social and political "sciences", and environmentalists are all clamoring for action while spurring　President Obama ("Tomorrow the oceans will stop rising and the planet will start healing") and his 35 czars/commissars to undertake immediate measures to save the planet – with the same aims as described above. 
It is evident from the above quote that our President believes himself to be either Jesus come back to Earth, or at least the 12th Imam so ardently desired by that jihadist terrorist and Obama’s friend Ahmadinejad. Like to the Pinocchio in the fable, Obama’s nose grows longer with every lie he pronounces, while jumping up the steps to his teleprompter like a marionette.In the meantime our Main Stream Media are unanimous in spreading this criminal propaganda daily; the ABC, CBS, NBC, MSNBC, CNN, NPR, NY Times, Washington Post, Boston Globe, LA Times, Associated Press, Reuters, Time, Newsweek, drive this drivel constantly. What is totally ignored are the detailed descriptions of faked data, skewed computer programs, politically revised conclusions by the UN-sponsored far-left clique of biased non-scientists – all government-paid drones that no private enterprise would hire. Another thing ignored is the "Global Warming Petition" (see Internet) where 31,487 independent US scientists (including 9,029 of them with PhD degrees) dispute decisively the findings of the UN-sponsored panel; also ignored is the "Manhattan Declaration on Climate Change" (see also Internet) where a smaller number of competent world scientists, about 712, including 142 pure climatologists, state the same – i.e., that the man-caused catastrophic global warming is a farce. The books by Christopher Horner, Robert Carter, Patrick Michaels, Lawrence Solomon, John Berlau, Steven Milloy, Ian Murray, Christopher Booker, R. C. Balling, D. Avery, S. F. Singer, Brian Sussman, and AW Montford　describing the lies, fakes, phony data, opposite conclusions, redacting by UN political hacks, reverse graphs, etc.,　have exposed this far-left propaganda in painful detail. In the case of the above mentioned Petition, several "environmentalists" had submitted phony names with phony credentials in order to sabotage that effort. It took several years of painstaking and expensive effort (that effort cost us more private money, no oil money there) to clean up the list from those saboteurs and verify all academic and professional data of the signatories. To put this whole conspiracy in terms of numbers, let me say that the projected world-threatening increase of carbon dioxide of 100 ppm (parts per million) by the end of this century would increase thermal absorptivity of the atmosphere by one-eighth of one percent; that is the definition of something totally negligible. On the other hand the sun cycles of cooling and Heating are many thousands of times more powerful with regard to the carbon dioxide in the air; when the sun is in its Cold cycle the oceans absorb billions of tons of it; and when the sun Heats up the oceans release the carbon dioxide in quantities many thousands　of　times bigger than anything the mankind could produce. To illustrate this point in more accessible terms to somebody who is not a climatologist or a scientist or an engineer; the argument of catastrophic anthropogenic (human-caused) global warming issued by our panic driven socialist/marxist government-paid hacks is like saying that a burp of a lonely wolf in Alaska will transform Florida into a Sahara-like desert - tomorrow! Perhaps an even better example would be to argue that the Pissing Boy in Bruxelles will inundate the continents by the end of the week. As for that bloviating gasbag and "climatologist" Al Gore, Dr. James Hansen with his tirades designed to get him more taxpayers’ money and who started his career by the global cooling scam in the 1970’s, as well as for Dr. Mann who inverted cause and effect in his "studies", for Phil Jones who destroyed faked data, and for the corrupt Maurice Strong who started the whole affair - they should be brought to the International Court in The Hague on charges of crimes against humanity, and then promptly shot by a firing squad.Marc Jeric (MS, PhD, Engineering, UCLA)"
In the meantime our Main Stream Media are unanimous in spreading this criminal propaganda daily; the ABC, CBS, NBC, MSNBC, CNN, NPR, NY Times, Washington Post, Boston Globe, LA Times, Associated Press, Reuters, Time, Newsweek, drive this drivel constantly. What is totally ignored are the detailed descriptions of faked data, skewed computer programs, politically revised conclusions by the UN-sponsored far-left clique of biased non-scientists – all government-paid drones that no private enterprise would hire. Another thing ignored is the "Global Warming Petition" (see Internet) where 31,487 independent US scientists (including 9,029 of them with PhD degrees) dispute decisively the findings of the UN-sponsored panel; also ignored is the "Manhattan Declaration on Climate Change" (see also Internet) where a smaller number of competent world scientists, about 712, including 142 pure climatologists, state the same – i.e., that the man-caused catastrophic global warming is a farce. The books by Christopher Horner, Robert Carter, Patrick Michaels, Lawrence Solomon, John Berlau, Steven Milloy, Ian Murray, Christopher Booker, R. C. Balling, D. Avery, S. F. Singer, Brian Sussman, and AW Montford　describing the lies, fakes, phony data, opposite conclusions, redacting by UN political hacks, reverse graphs, etc.,　have exposed this far-left propaganda in painful detail. In the case of the above mentioned Petition, several "environmentalists" had submitted phony names with phony credentials in order to sabotage that effort. It took several years of painstaking and expensive effort (that effort cost us more private money, no oil money there) to clean up the list from those saboteurs and verify all academic and professional data of the signatories. 
To put this whole conspiracy in terms of numbers, let me say that the projected world-threatening increase of carbon dioxide of 100 ppm (parts per million) by the end of this century would increase thermal absorptivity of the atmosphere by one-eighth of one percent; that is the definition of something totally negligible. On the other hand the sun cycles of cooling and Heating are many thousands of times more powerful with regard to the carbon dioxide in the air; when the sun is in its Cold cycle the oceans absorb billions of tons of it; and when the sun Heats up the oceans release the carbon dioxide in quantities many thousands　of　times bigger than anything the mankind could produce. To illustrate this point in more accessible terms to somebody who is not a climatologist or a scientist or an engineer; the argument of catastrophic anthropogenic (human-caused) global warming issued by our panic driven socialist/marxist government-paid hacks is like saying that a burp of a lonely wolf in Alaska will transform Florida into a Sahara-like desert - tomorrow! Perhaps an even better example would be to argue that the Pissing Boy in Bruxelles will inundate the continents by the end of the week. As for that bloviating gasbag and "climatologist" Al Gore, Dr. James Hansen with his tirades designed to get him more taxpayers’ money and who started his career by the global cooling scam in the 1970’s, as well as for Dr. Mann who inverted cause and effect in his "studies", for Phil Jones who destroyed faked data, and for the corrupt Maurice Strong who started the whole affair - they should be brought to the International Court in The Hague on charges of crimes against humanity, and then promptly shot by a firing squad.
Marc Jeric (MS, PhD, Engineering, UCLA)"</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zxvxj</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/opxh</id></website><link>http://cowboybyte.com/5801/obama-promise-kept-coal-plants-to-go-bankrupt-with-new-epa-carbon-cap/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:17:48+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:53:33+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwdz5j</id><link>http://cowboybyte.com/5801/obama-promise-kept-coal-plants-to-go-bankrupt-with-new-epa-carbon-cap/#comment-480761739</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hzgqz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>