<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3f59a/update/2012-03-29T16:35:17/50e88d85e946013a5ba985a202a92d08ca419493d1ad2f9a8fc0225f2c2c1450</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body> One thing that's Always coming to my mind these days when people talk about souls is Bleach. For the non-anime fans, it's a show with a setting that features "soul reapers," powerful human souls who swordfight in the afterlife, help ghosts left in the world of the living pass on, hunt down soul-eating hollows, and such. When a soul reaper gets in a fight, they can Bleed and die (again), just like living humans. I got a chuckle out of a soul reaper named Kaien Shiba speculating on what happens to a person's 'heart' after their soul dies.

For me, it kind of puts perspective on the needless redundancy of souls when it comes to explaining consciousness. Right now, neurologists are continuously shedding new light on how we think and learn, which means reducing a person to a collection of different parts and processes that add up to complex behaviors. Why should I think adding a soul will answer any questions? Whether we're dealing with neurons made of atoms or made of reishi particles, consciousness is a complex phenomenon, and I would expect it to be made of many simpler parts interacting with each other. My computer's made of many small parts carrying out several interactions to produce complex results. Whenever I observe simple individual objects, they behave in simple ways. Why should I be so arrogant to assume that I'm an exception to that general observation? Souls don't answer the questions of consciousness, they only compound the problem.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6l5xdh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry26</id></website><link>http://debunkingchristianity.blogspot.com/2012/03/more-criticisms-from-dr-reppert-on-otf.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T19:51:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:35:17+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3f59a</id><link>http://debunkingchristianity.blogspot.com/2012/03/more-criticisms-from-dr-reppert-on-otf.html#comment-479863081</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gpkn0</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>