<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwo19l/update/2012-03-31T06:07:55/3b1bdbb38bcc4437ca7093eafb496d1ed608b1d0afedf36263289588b753049f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>War and violence impact individuals and families horribly. Those without ditto experience can't begin to fathom the degree of hurt and bereavement over generations. We can't forget - even if we tried - but we can move on knowing that holding descendants accountable for the sins of their fathers  is unhealthy for both sides of atrocities.

Nursing hurts would doom generations to unending feuds and vendettas in any nation or culture aggrieved. For instance, Osama bin Laden retained historical memories of crusader invasions/atrocities in the middle east - against Muslims, since the middle ages. 

In his mind, he was continuing/justifying holy wars against invading infidels - centuries hence. Atrocities beget atrocities : Russian troops in WW2 raped German women in revenge for Hitler's earlier atrocities against Russians on the Eastern Front. German prisoners of war were released only as late as the 1950s - after a majority had died in imprisonment.

In policing the world for democracy, US troops - as human as others - committed atrocities against unarmed/fleeing Korean refugees in No Gun Ri during the Korean War. Again, in My Lai, when some soldiers massacred unarmed villagers during the Vietnam War.

That Nazi troops had murdered captured US troops in Cold blood - during the Battle of the Bulge in WW2 - can't justify US atrocities, right? Atrocities continue. The latest being Panjwai in Afghanistan when a rogue Staff Sgt Bales - some claim not Acting alone - massacred unarmed/innocent women and children. 

It's not the scale of massacres that's evil - every atrocity IS, including Hiroshima and Nagasaki. No human is exempt from doing/suffering evil. It's the nature of our beast to be unjust - some of us, at times - whether killing innocents or whatever. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/677zz6</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/hnd5</id></website><link>http://www.straitstimes.com/STForum/Story/STIStory_783681.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T22:11:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T10:07:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwo19l</id><link>http://www.straitstimes.com/STForum/Story/STIStory_783681.html#comment-481708596</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yu934</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>