<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m356oq/update/2012-03-28T19:30:31/e4c0f3f9f08788f7b92ef3a0282572568406063b3164decd9950268fb601154c</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I don't know if having the gods answer questions straightforwardly would really be a good thing.  Roleplaying's not exactly evidence, but when we've tried this in roleplaying campaigns it's not been good for the humans involved.  The PC party leader of our current campaign has actually  use of _Commune_ except to answer questions of Cold mundane fact ("where did they put the body?") because she saw first-hand what having an answer from the gods did to her peoples' initiative and optimism.  (She is neither devout nor good, but on this point I can't fault her argument.)

Thinking about it further, one thing I'm pretty sure of is that the universe is bigger than will fit in my head, so any understanding of it I have will necessarily be incomplete, and if I want my world to make sense to me I will inevitably have some not-quite-true simplifications papering over the things I can't grasp.  I don't think it would be a kindness to destroy all of those, forcing me to live in a world I can't make sense of at all.  And (due to the finiteness of my head) there's no way a god could give me answers that were true, complete, and fully understandable to me on some of the big questions.  Particularly "Why--?"

I don't think I have ever seen a story which featured a god who was (a) benevolent, (b) omniscient, and (c) informative.  As a storyteller at heart I Always suspect that if you can't make a story out of it, it's not a state humans are meant to be in.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hay3s</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/z910</id></website><link>http://www.patheos.com/blogs/slacktivist/2012/03/27/smart-people-saying-smart-things-27/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T02:20:49+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-28T23:30:31+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m356oq</id><link>http://www.patheos.com/blogs/slacktivist/2012/03/27/smart-people-saying-smart-things-27/#comment-478891171</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>