<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0o23l/post/2012-04-02T04:50:12</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>
Syrian Revolution News Round-up                ملخص أحداث الثورة السورية
Day 384: Sunday, 1 Apr 2012                            اليوم ۳۸٤: الأحد، ١ أبريل/نيسان ٢٠١٢
 
Friends of Syria Conference II Recognizes the SNC
 

Demonstrations in the Capital, Damascus, intensify

Top Stories
The Syrian National Council was recognized by the Second Friends of Syria Conference in Istanbul as a legitimate representative of the Syrian opposition.
A massacre was discovered in the village of Gharya Gharbiya in Daraa as regime forces slaughtered 18 civilians who tried to escape the security assault.
Regime forces deployed heavily in the Damascus suburb of Harasta after yesterday’s attacks on the Political Intelligence quarters in the city.
 
Top Videos
Aleppo University: Assad’s forces  the university campus to crush a protest, fire tear gas bombs, and arrest and beat protesters, P2, P3, P4, P5
Daraa, Faculty of Economics: Mass student demonstration at the university campus chants for freedom and vows to defeat Assad, P2
Bayada, Homs: Lifeless bodies of fallen heroes Abdul-Rahman Shihan and his son amid appeals to the world to save the souls of the remaining civilians
 
Summary of Events
 
The Syrian National Council was recognized by the Second Friends of Syria Conference in Istanbul as a legitimate representative of the Syrian opposition. The conference called for the expansion of the SNC and its inclusion of other opposition bodies and the support of the Kofi Anan plan with a preset time line for its execution. The Free Syrian Army command inside Syria welcomed Anan’s plan and stressed on continuing armed resistance until regime forces stop shelling the cities.
 
Regime operations continued throughout the country as it shelled Homs, Idlib, and Hama. Regime forces invaded the towns of Sinjar in Idlib and Qabar Fedda in Hama and Burnt dozens of houses after heavy shelling that led to the displacement of many families. They also invaded the city of Quriya in Deir Azzour under heavy shelling, machinegun fire, arbitrary arrests, and air force planes flying low over the city.
 
Assad’s forces killed at least eight today, most fell in Daraa, including four defected soldiers who were shot in the village of Gharya Gharbiya while holding Off regime forces. A massacre was discovered in the same village, as regime forces slaughtered by knives at least 18 civilians who tried to escape the security assault on the village.
 
In the Capital, regime forces killed at least two while opening fire at demonstrators in the central neighbourhood of Kafarsouseh. At the same time, regime forces invaded the town of Ghezlaniya in the Damascus suburbs under random fire and set up several checkpoints. Regime forces also opened random heavy machinegun fire on the fields of Madaya after the defection of soldiers manning a checkpoint, and deployed heavy security forces in Harasta after revolutionaries attacked the Political Intelligence quarters in the city yesterday.

http://us2 .campaign-archive1. com/?u=556aeef60722f6e5811ea2519&amp;id=cd43852edc&amp;e=5c0b3d7513</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ylh931</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cjnq</id></website><link>http://blogs.aljazeera.com/middle-east/2012/02/05/fighting-back-against-assads-forces</link><postedTime>2012-02-05T09:27:20+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T08:50:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0o23l</id><link>http://blogs.aljazeera.com/middle-east/2012/02/05/fighting-back-against-assads-forces#comment-483357360</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zlwz2</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-05</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>