<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m025lx/update/2012-03-31T14:06:58/0b0c5bc5a6d1a8a9e733ff942ca6d26a2d7ae20cae2b27d8803e37e6cd7badce</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Check this out: http://www.wagist.com/2012/dan-linehan/new-videos-show-zimmermans-gashed-head-and-broken-face Even with the grainy still shot Zimmerman looks very much like he's sporting a broken nose.  Scroll down. Use your heads, people. Stop this crazy shit. You're being played. The media is the enemy. Never trust them. Truthfully, I have nothing but pity and sorrow in my heart for many blacks, hell, my 16-year-old nephew bears a striking resemblance to Trayvon, he was  a beautiful boy. I can understand the anger over what at the surface appears to be an 'injustice' for lack of arrest, but Zimmerman may very well have been eventually arrested and officially charged. There was absolutely NO need to turn this into a full-fledged national clusterfuck .

I swear, it really looks like these Far Left Progressive so-called "elites" who've jacked the media (mostly WHITE) just want to gin up the black community to Burn and destroy themselves and watch with glee from their distant Ivory towers, unscathed, licking their lips at the black smoke in the air. They're sick and twisted souls. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67uto8</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q0fi</id></website><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/31/public-opinion-shifts-on-trayvon-martin-case/</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T06:29:39+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T18:06:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m025lx</id><link>http://dailycaller.com/2012/03/31/public-opinion-shifts-on-trayvon-martin-case/#comment-482055429</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yapo8</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>