<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwl2j6/update/2012-03-30T12:39:05/9563e4c2600fa1b23bb8450e7e91650d55ea178f279d1da5260e38700c96927d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Global Warming Models are Wrong 
The fact that the 30 year temperature predictions of the IPCC’s  computer models don’t agree with over 30 years of actual satellite temperature measurements should alarm anyone that didn’t flunk their 8th grade Science class!  Obviously the Carbon Dioxide (C02) warming theory is wrong. Other theories such as cooling, instead warming due to increased low cloud-cover  when the solar winds ebb appears to be much more logical.  The recent CLOUD experiment at Switzerland’s CERN  laboratory verified  its physics.

Most of us know the 1930's were pretty tough;  farmer's lost their farms because of the "Dust Bowl" and  many places had “highest temperature ever".  No one understood why, but we knew our climate changed over time. Huge glaciers overtook our continent several times in the past, and giant mastodons once roamed in hot Alaskan jungles.
 
When some academic professor postulated that maybe C02 created by Burning  a lot of fossil fuels might cause  Global Warming, the Mainstream Media jumped on the possibility that we might have a planet catastrophe.  However C02 is just a trace gas that amounts to  less than 0.04% of the earth's atmosphere.  If C02 had a significant impact on our climate, the big increase in fossil fuel Burning in the 1940's would certainly have shown up in global temperatures.  The ships, tanks and planes  of WWII all Burned fossil fuels and dumped tons of C02 into the atmosphere.  Automobile  production in the late 40's added  millions more cars on the roads.  Air conditioning, which had been pretty much limited to Movie Theaters in the 30’s,  was installed in millions of buildings in the ‘40’s.  Air conditioning made Dixie and the western deserts inhabitable for 12 months a  year.  Any idiot would  agree that it should have caused an   increase in our global temperature, but it didn’t and we were surprised!  We found that we had no global warming from 1940 to 1978.
Now is the time to give up on the EPA  giving big government grants to professors with an Axe to grind  
Jim Hood
Santa Clara CA</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zfrxp</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zmzu</id></website><link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2012/mar/29/intemperate-global-warming-rules/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T23:33:15+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T16:39:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwl2j6</id><link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2012/mar/29/intemperate-global-warming-rules/#comment-480931030</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ecn0</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>