<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzjll/update/2012-03-30T14:43:19/a928ffe98fd8e7dc9d6321310b39e4d653ff2673226152e220464abb36be2a4e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwhdoh</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Hewhohaspaid?  Are you sure your username shouldn't be hewhomustbeobeyed?

You know it's this sort of ignorant and silly generalistic comment that makes me wonder if it's politics you are in already or should be working in?  Perhaps, you believe that those in less fortunate circumstances should pay regardless, well come on (you say), it's only one hundred euro. 

Let's face it, this is not about €100, it's about the astronomical incremental tax increases that are coming down the track after this.  My grandmother, a very wise woman once told me 'there but for the grace of God go I', while there may be people out there who live by your sort of sanctimonious preaching, I  wonder how many people like you are willing to walk in the shoes of those less fortunate than themselves!  The same individuals, who may or may not be able to afford €100, today, but most certainly will never be able to afford any figure above that in the future!
Sounds like you're one of Phil Hogan's cronys for Heaven's sake.

A few weeks volunteering in St. Vincent de Paul might sort out your warped thinking.... and before you get a nose Bleed climbing back up there on your pulpit, I have been in both situations, a great job at one time to not having enough food in my cupboard. I have volunteered for several charities, I know what it's like from both sides (i.e. the receiver and the donator).  

I am law abiding citizen, but I am getting too old for this sort of nonsense and there comes a time when you have to stand up for what you believe is right.  This tax is not right.  Its' preface, the calculation and application were formulated by monkeys.  Most politicians are good at one thing, and that's lining their own nest.
Please don't encourage them with these Off the cuff statements!  If they said that everyone had to take in unpaid guests tomorrow would you agree to that too just because they said it was THE new law?  This is how irrational this piece of legislation is.

You know my friends, there comes a time when people get tired of being trampled by the iron feet of oppression [Martin Luther King]</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/675n0v</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/qxal</id></website><link>http://www.independent.ie/national-news/just-under-600000-sign-up-for-household-charge-ahead-of-tomorrows-payment-deadline-3066924.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:41:07+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:43:19+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwzjll</id><link>http://www.independent.ie/national-news/just-under-600000-sign-up-for-household-charge-ahead-of-tomorrows-payment-deadline-3066924.html#comment-481058796</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>