<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xtg3/post/2012-03-29T13:50:06</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>And the African American community will invite stereotyping as criminals as long as a disproportionate percentage of African American youth are in prison, and the Italians will invite stereotyping as vacuous idiots as long as Jersey Shore continues showing, and Polish people will invite stereotyping as long as Polish Jokes are told.

Oh, I almost forgot!!!  The Jews will invite hatred as long as they don't repent from killing Jesus.  How silly of me!

The moral equivalency of terrorists and those who fight them, and the acceptance by the media/"intelligentsia"/Arab street of that equivalency, is mind boggling.  Mareh targeted children, shooting them in Cold blood, including two young boys who ran to their mortally wounded father (whom Mareh had just shot as well).  He shot soldiers in their own country, going about their daily business.  He and others can justify it all they want, but it is clearly premeditated murder.  Children regrettably killed in war, or in the incident of killing a terrorist or an enemy, are horrible, regrettable, and should be avoided - and this is known and Acted upon by the US and Israel, and most other countries (Syria a notable exception, and that is even assuming the opposition could be construed as enemies of Syria.  The point here is that Syria doesn't care about collateral death.).  But this point is clear to anyone who can think and make distinctions.

Those who buy into this moral equivalency only embolden the terrorists and are, if not willing supporters, useful idiots in the war the terrorists are waging against us.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hf5bp</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5rgv</id></website><link>http://www.nybooks.com/blogs/nyrblog/2012/mar/28/toulouse-middle-east-conflict-france/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T17:36:47+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:50:06+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xtg3</id><link>http://www.nybooks.com/blogs/nyrblog/2012/mar/28/toulouse-middle-east-conflict-france/#comment-479692581</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>