<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3jycu/post/2012-03-29T18:17:54</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The Massacre of the Afghan 17 &amp; the Obama Cover-Up
"After the Cold-blooded murder of the 17 
Afghan villagers in Kandahar Province the US military and the 
ever-complicit Obama regime constructed an elaborate cover-up, exposing 
the Administration up to charges of conspiracy to suppress the essential
 facts, falsify data and obstruct justice: All are grounds for criminal 
prosecution and impeachment..."

..."Obama’s contention that a ‘lone 
unbalanced gunman’ committed the crime is completely self-serving and 
exposes serious and deep structural problems with the war in 
Afghanistan. US combat troops in Afghanistan are demoralized and angry 
because their military commanders have marched them into a cul de sac – a
 dead end. They are engaged in a long, losing war where every dead US 
soldier is accompanied by scores who are maimed, blinded and mentally 
traumatized. In Obama’s war, the wounded are patched up and recycled 
back into the same meat grinder in an increasingly hostile environment, 
where rape, torture, maiming and murder become their only ‘recreation’. 
Sgt. Bales was coerced into multiple tours of duty in Iraq and then 
shipped Off to Afghanistan, contrary to his expectations of a promotion and an end to overseas combat assignments.There is a huge gap between the
 world of the political warlords in Washington and their accomplices 
among the warmongering ‘lobbies’ and that of the soldiers who risk their
 lives in imperial wars of occupation. These dispensable soldiers are 
repeatedly deployed to brutal colonial wars thousands of miles from 
their homes to confront an ‘enemy’ they cannot possibly understand. They
 end up brutalizing the families, friends, neighbors and compatriots of 
the elusive Afghan anti-colonial fighters – who are everywhere. Back in the Washington
 none of the political war-mongers ever experience the pain and 
suffering of a prolonged war, which for any soldier on the battlefield, 
is ever present, everywhere. Soldiers, like Sgt. Bales, operate in a 
very hostile environment where, a roadside bomb or a grenade thrown from
 a motorcycle, or even a ‘trusted’ Afghan ally, who might turn his gun 
on his US ‘mentors,’ are omnipresent threats to their ever returning 
home in one piece...."
Article by James Petras  http://www.boilingfrogspost.com/2012/03/28/the-massacre-of-the-afghan-17-the-obama-cover-up/#more-13372 </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/y46mx9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ms5w</id></website><link>http://my.telegraph.co.uk/clothcap/clothcap/16313809/down-the-tube-gate/</link><postedTime>2012-02-13T20:47:40+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T22:17:54+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3jycu</id><link>http://my.telegraph.co.uk/clothcap/clothcap/16313809/down-the-tube-gate/#comment-479962067</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6c6wz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-13</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>