<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0p7dp/post/2012-04-02T07:03:24</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Didn't mention Drew Storen (I hope he doesn't become another Chad Cordero). Desmond and Espinosa need to form a strong infield combo like Rollins and Utley. Zimmerman should shine and I am expecting more from Werth (aren't we all). I don't mind Morse on the DL as he seems to get a slow start. Weak positions are 1B and CF (at least until Harper appears). 

Pitching will carry us - I can't imagine Strasburg, Zimmermann, and Gonzales all having bad years (Jackson will eat innings, but I don't expect a lot). As I stated before, I think Lannan will thrive as a 4th or 5th starter - I am not Too hot on Wang (injuries). 

Phillies and Braves are on their way down (Mets have owner problems and will be bad). Miami could be really good or bad - too many variables. 

Overall, I expect a winning season (over .500), but playoffs will Depend on who else will have a better-than-expected season (e.g., Dodgers) - extra Wild Card helps. If not this year, Nats have a very bright future. 

The biggest thrill in baseball is following a team on the rise.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6vouvj</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lz6q</id></website><link>http://washington.nationals.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120401%26content_id=27823398%26vkey=news_was%26c_id=was</link><postedTime>2012-04-01T22:40:25+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T11:03:24+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0p7dp</id><link>http://washington.nationals.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120401%26content_id=27823398%26vkey=news_was%26c_id=was#comment-483422573</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h8gmb</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-01</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>