<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/8f3nzk/update/2011-03-11T17:20:40/3331a54e1e1138cb9de0afa9d89803559cfc79db9742d1f52a9910d37b2f5fd2</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/81k25e</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>"Second, WHY would ANYONE plea to something they did not do? I swear on my life that I would never plea to something where they had no DNA or any other type of evidence to prove that I did something wrong. I am literally tired of hearing these excuses. Sex offenders WILL re-offend. They are NOT rehabilitative. I am NOT saying that they don't try to stop and they don't try to live a "normal" life (normal meaning NOT raping children), but from all I have read and heard from sex offenders own mouths lead me to believe my opinions. "

I'll assume by your words you are a male and you have apparently NOT done your "own" research and likely a right wing conservative church goer. I apologize if that characterization is wrong.
1- Research how low the re offense rate actually is, not just the high profile media blasted horrendous cases of child molestation.
2 - Your ignorance of the "legal" system is clear when you say  " I swear on my life that I would never plea . . . "  Being arrested for any sex offense charge automatically puts you in a no win situation simply by the fact you DID get arrested and lodged. I guaranty YOU  will plea because you will have no other choice, you will lose anyway. The system is designed to  provide a conviction no matter what. Anyone naively disagreeing with that has never had any contact with an arresting agency. 
3 - It's interesting Nicole mainly responds to empathize with a female poster.

So here's my story since you say no one ever tells it blah blah blah:

   My wife unexpectedly walked out of our home 3 weeks after our sons 3rd birthday resulting in divorce 6 weeks later and 14 days short of 8 years. I kept custody out the 2 boys , 3 and 4 1/2. I admitted to physical abuse of the younger one at the age of 6 due to frustration of his continual soiling/incontinence of his clothes. Several months later they were removed from my custody, placed in separate foster care and never lived with each other again as children until recently they share an apartment at 21 &amp; 23.  I was charged with sex abuse in the first degree and served nearly 6 years, I've been out over 5 years. Why? The older boy was doing things and behaving in ways normally a child of that age shouldn't know but these things were kept  from me by the school and social services to build/ create a case. Incidentally, the young man is gay today. It was said he wouldn't know those things unless someone taught him and that person became me. His brother tells me he believes his brother was born gay. My younger son also tells me he agreed to say what he did about me back then was because he got tired of being asked about it so much. It true kids don't lie but they will answer a line of questioning written to get the responses needed. The accusations were encouraging oral sex and causing him to perform on me. He would also wake in the middle of the night and go to my bed- unknown to me until he turned in his sleep and woke me - which was at that time a king sized water bed that could Heat the room. That transformed into I  put him in my bed.Is that detailed enough for you?
For 8 months in county jail I repeated over and over what I was accused of DID NOT HAPPEN.One day my 2nd attorney came to me with another attorney to explain the futility of this. They described other cases to me and asked what I thought the sentences were. I was wrong in every one, they ALL got prison time. One got 6 years for having consensual sex with his 30+ year old wife in an isolated public park in the dark. My own father was happy I took the plea saying at least I didn't get the 14 years the DA wanted to throw at me. Again I repeat, it's all about the conviction, not the integrity of the so called system.People like you say a sex crime is a sex crime. Sex offender does not translate to child molester. That's like saying a collectors gun in a locked museum display is just as dangerous as an assault rifle. Wake up Mr. and Ms. perfect!! The media, the legal system and personal stories of abuse fuel the fear and paranoia. By the way, when I revealed at the age of 35 I was molested as a child it was decided I MUST HAVE  done it.
I found this blog because I was curious how difficult it would be for a 49 year old to find a relationship with my history. I am not shocked to learn popular feeling is caution is so extreme as to ostracize the the now high percentage of law abiding ex-offenders. Is it no wonder we keep our pasts close to us? Oh no, you say, that alone makes them untrustworthy. WE are everywhere; you pass us all the time and may know some of us; you trust us; you have no reason to fear us, until the day you learn of our past and suddenly we are less trustworthy then the shark out in the water you wont go in to. THAT is what happens when there is so much commercial driven media frenzy to make a monster out of an ant. I don't say that to minimize what some self serving people do, I say it to show things are not Always what they are reported to be. Of course any caring adult should have caution even if you are not a parent. 
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/tnbj3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/8hs6</id></website><link>http://healthbistro.lifescript.com/2009/08/13/would-you-date-a-sex-offender/</link><postedTime>2009-08-13T17:27:53+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-03-11T22:20:40+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/8f3nzk</id><link>http://healthbistro.lifescript.com/2009/08/13/would-you-date-a-sex-offender/#comment-164488855</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2009-08-13</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>