<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwv4ka/update/2012-03-30T16:05:32/050736df963f34b833998bc24f44d0200fd167dcf8e0a94d07d31c7a5c9fd641</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw6vvj</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> What is this 'West' that you speak about? Different countries have wildly different ways of providing medical care. The US is rated one of the worst in the world in terms of medical insurance, since you can't get treatment without insurance, which you'll lose if you're ever laid  from your job. Canadians have no such restriction and get excellent health care but have a long wait.
Scandinavian countries also offer full free social health care where everything from a common Cold to open heart surgery is borne by the state. And the NHS is in the UK, not the US. The US system is called Medicare. The experience varies across countries and yes, there are nightmarish anecdotes like you mention, but by far the majority of people in these countries DO have access to health care. 
Look at any govt. run hospital in India - overcrowded, overworked staff and as usual those who have connections get priority. The middle class have no recourse other than getting fleeced by the Apollos and other private hospital chains. Where's the poor people gonna go, when they can't even afford the 200 to 500 bucks consultation fees at these places? No wonder you find them in various states of sickness, crowded outside AIIMS and Safdarjung hospital in Delhi, as an example.
Bottom line as Lakshmi says, healthcare remains out of the Reach of a majority of our population.

For people like you, nobody is allowed to criticize anything about India because by doing so it automatically means that they approve of everything in 'the West'. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z0t7q</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/776o</id></website><link>http://www.firstpost.com/living/why-going-to-the-doctor-is-the-great-indian-nightmare-260977.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T09:05:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T20:05:32+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwv4ka</id><link>http://www.firstpost.com/living/why-going-to-the-doctor-is-the-great-indian-nightmare-260977.html#comment-481141117</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/nlbh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>