<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/198527/post/127851078/comment/328538124</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Shawn Michel - most of the time Kick never makes contact but opponent losses 
 
Triple H - opponent gets his hands down just before hitting ground 
 
Austin - stunner is the biggest seller in my opinion - look how opponent fly in air and lands 2 mtrs away 
 
Ziggler - Dolph gets more impact than his opponent but have agree that Ziggler is the best seller WWE has now.. Just look how he made Great Khali look good. 
 
Taker - Pile Driver - If done wrong opponents neck may get broken or hard hit on skull could permanently damage opponent even  worse Death 
 
Ric Flair - no idea how he got famous, dude can&amp;#039;t wrestle. His all matches have the same routine. 
 
 
Ortan RKO - again ortan gets more impact than his opponent. Technically Zero effect on the opponent 
Ortan Punt - Overrated/hardly makes a contact 
 
Sleeper Holds - worse finishes.... u can clearly see the gap between the arms and opponent&amp;#039;s neck. 
 
Michelle McCool - I think I saw that move by AJ Styles long before McCool.  
 
Christian - Most stupid move - technically you can&amp;#039;t lock arms the ways christian does. Opponent just has to take one step back and his out of Kill Switch 
 
Hogan - Leg Drop - the leg which makes contact on the ground take all impact 
(Best Leg Dropper - Yokozuna) 
 
Batista - I find his version of power slam is the weakest of all. Check out Taker&amp;#039;s version(Last Ride) 
 
CM Punk - good finish. once he broke ray mysterio&amp;#039;s nose with that move 
 
Jericho - getting more impact than opponent. Technically hold isn&amp;#039;t powerful, all opponent has to do is just stand. 
 
Tyler Reks &amp;ndash; Burning Hammer - Seriously - but have to admit, its definitely better than Angle Slam 
 
Sheamus &amp;ndash; Brogue Kick - never makes a contact 
 
Bret Hitman Hart &amp;ndash; Sharp Shooter - what can i say - He is best there is, the best there was and the best there ever will be. 
 
John Cena &amp;ndash; Attitude adjustment - thats just stupid - Cena reminds of RVD, who doesn&amp;#039;t hit his opponent but  wins 
 
The Peoples Elbow - the most electrifying move.. 
 
all this is fake and just for entertainment - kids should be told. You don&amp;#039;t want there hearts broken when they grow up.. 
I am one of those.. :( 
I remember when I was kid i used to argue with people that its real. Now I look like a idiot. 
 
I am Glad that found somthing real - MMA :D </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:198527:127851078</id><idPostId>127851078</idPostId><idBlogId>198527</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:198527</id><idBlogId>198527</idBlogId><link>http://thechive.wordpress.com</link><displayName>theCHIVE</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://thechive.com/2012/03/30/20-best-finishing-moves-of-wwe-20-photos</link><displayName>20 Best finishing moves of WWE (20 Photos)</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T14:11:28.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:198527:127851078:328538124</id><link>http://thechive.com/2012/03/30/20-best-finishing-moves-of-wwe-20-photos#IDComment328538124</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T14:11:28.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on 20 Best finishing moves of WWE (20 Photos) by Heart Broken Kid</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>77d84dcbf0f456960a91b5123bdc2b2d</idEmailMd5><displayName>Heart Broken Kid</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>Heart Broken Kid commented on &lt;a href="http://thechive.com/2012/03/30/20-best-finishing-moves-of-wwe-20-photos"&gt;20 Best finishing moves of WWE (20 Photos)&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>