<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mszjh4/update/2012-03-27T15:40:21/e2e7c3cc11755a1e98db99d113448da3221601bbf09ce2c242274864513ef4fc</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>'The reasoning is that the federal government clearly has the power to regulate the health insurance industry under that clause, as it spans every state in the nation.'

Indeed.  Health care that applies the advantages of modern medicine to everybody who needs it is far, far too great a task for local mom-and-pop insurers.  Those small-scale insurers will tend to go bankrupt.  Only large-scale insurers - or a single large-scale insurer - will Always have enough support to pay for everyone's health care without going bankrupt, provided that enough people pay this insurer adequately to do so.

But an insurer of this size, private or public, needs to be regulated.  An unregulated monopoly is a dangerous and above all an expensive thing.  We need to have laws that require it to operate in the public interest - to fund it adequately without overburdening any individual who pays into the system.

If we simply taxed people and diverted the proceeds to a public insurer, we would not have to be arguing over whether the health insurance industry is necessarily "interstate commerce."  It offends me that we even consider health insurance to be principally a commodity rather than a public good that serves a basic human need.  Zornick is right: This "Constitutionality" issue arises only within the structure of Romneycare and its assumption that health insurance is only another widget whose purpose is to make a profit for the seller.

I cannot be so sanguine about Zornick's claim that the failure of Romneycare would mean an increased chance of success for the single-payer idea.  The problem lies not in convincing people that the Romneycare glass is half-full rather than half-empty. The problem lies in convincing them that the solution is to fill the glass the rest of they way up, rather than to empty it.  Unfortunately, the 1% have a big advertising budget to Burn to persuade people to choose the latter option.  Our challenge is to show that the greatest justice, the best public health outcomes, and the greatest savings will only come when we fill up that glass.  This means screaming out the facts about well-functioning health care systems, for example in Western Europe, Canada, and Japan, and drowning out the propaganda and fear-mongering of the insurance profiteers, whose corrupting influence has held back health care reform here for so long.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6loiaw</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q2aj</id></website><link>http://www.thenation.com/blog/167071/if-mandate-fails-single-payer-awaits</link><postedTime>2012-03-27T18:33:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-27T19:40:21+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mszjh4</id><link>http://www.thenation.com/blog/167071/if-mandate-fails-single-payer-awaits#comment-477699606</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8mbfl</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-27</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>