<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0prtj/post/2012-04-02T06:53:25</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Definitely sign me up for WIMPS! I have  harboured a sneaking suspicion that the five core values are a touch of motherhood-and-apple-pie; who's going to disagree with them? There's barely a follower of Jesus on the planet who could not subscribe to them in one way or another.

The issue with values statements of any kind is how the values get earthed in congregational and denominational life. I like Stuart's suggestions.  So, here's a jumble of thoughts (intentionally provocatively expressed) on how the values and his pointers might find purchase in our communities. 

I agree that there has been a deal of Anxiety driving many of the contributions to our discussions - Anxiety about money, about the balance of power, about whether my particular take on baptist life gets heard. A worshipping community is focused on following the carpenter from Nazareth who had nowhere to park his bandwagon or lay his head and who in the darkness of Gethsemene expressed his trust in the one who was leading him to his death. How different might our conversation be if this value drove it in this way?

The peace church focus is crucial and blends with being a prophetic people. Prophecy to some is about having minor faults pointed to in hot and heavy sing-alongs; to others, it is about confronting real economic and political power in the name of the God of justice and equality. More than that, it is about modelling communities that point to a different way of living that isn't marked by exploitation, violence and injustice. Which version of prophetic is in our mind when we speak of being a prophetic people?

I think there needs to be a proper conversation about strategic partnership between BMS and BUGB and BUS and BUW. Is it sensible use of resources to duplicate so much admin and communications effort? Is it theologically tenable to maintain the distinction between home and overseas mission? The recent BBC 2 series on reverse mission has demonstrated how much we have to learn from Christians living in those places that vast numbers of 'our baptist family' (I too don't find that designation helpful) still refer to as 'the mission field'. Sweeping away this invidious distinction would help all of us re-imagine our call to mission as a movement of God's people.

I share the misgivings of some about large churches supporting smaller ones. But as the minister of a large church that has tried to support smaller ones, I think the power issue works both ways. Small and unimaginative churches, poorly led and lacking vision beyond maintaining what little they already have, exercise dubious amounts of power within our current system, levering in quantities of cash that could be used for mission elsewhere. I agree with Stuart that being a sacrificial people means asking the questions about buildings (and the amount we spend on them) in the context of the mission we are called to today and pondering answers that might involve the pooling of resources between churches to make possible the release of pioneering, missional movements in our localities that will be a genuinely worshipping and prophetic voice. Too many of us cling to what we have because we cannot see that losing our life is the only way to Gain it.

I'm grateful to Stuart for helping us to focus our conversation on values. Those values really need to fire honest, sacrificial dialogue at all levels in our movement.

</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6vwslv</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/1syc</id></website><link>http://www.beyond400.net/entry/29-in-search-of-our-values</link><postedTime>2012-04-02T06:29:29+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-04-02T10:53:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m0prtj</id><link>http://www.beyond400.net/entry/29-in-search-of-our-values#comment-483417711</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/heupd</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-04-02</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>