<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3i75e/post/2012-03-29T21:22:27</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>This is getting so pathetic. Iran should just be ignored. The U.S has wasted way too much money taking out the worlds trash. The world is Always going to have trash. The U.S is going to run itself into the ground chasing crazy people around the world. Seriously this is like the exact same situation with Iraq. Dictator Threatening wepons to look tough the U.S and Isreal convince the world they are going to all die if they don't start a war. This really just is an unnecessary move by the U.S to try to secure the region for the dwindling future oil supply. America is over 15 trillion in debt. America does not have the money for this. I love America but it seems like America is going roge by trying to achieve unnecessary dominance making mountains out of molehills. The people need to say enough is enough and focus on our own policies. America survived the Cold war this is the same situation except now it is Iran which is backed by russia and china. If you view it from a foreigners perspective the rest of the world is really tired of America racking up huge amounts of debt and then using the money to bully everyone around with. Russian generals on youtube say that if America starts a war with Iran it will be world War 3. We need to stop telling other people how to run their countries and start running our own</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hsw8t</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/28/us/iran-sanctions/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T23:11:40+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T01:22:27+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3i75e</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/28/us/iran-sanctions/index.html#comment-480109830</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/l0ups</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>