<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3so59/update/2012-03-29T23:54:50/a34765b93b2d5b3ebd475be37f401e7d731dea176b779b908c8365dbb896660a</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Having seen that video, I don't believe it is possible to say anything other than the account given by police of Zimmerman's condition, and certainly Zimmerman's account of events, is untrue.  Beyond the fact that there is not even a bruise on this guy let alone any sign of lacerations, he claimed to have had his head banged on the concrete.  You would surely have symptoms of concussion ( Dizziness, Nausea, Disorientation, unsteadiness ).  There is no sign of anything of the kind.  And, if he is telling the truth, there would have to be.  He practically jumps out of the police car, steady on his feet and apparently unconcerned.  He has just shot an unarmed 17 year-old to death by his account during a struggle for his own life and he looks about as concerned as if it were a traffic ticket. 
Having your unprotected brain slammed around in your skull is no small thing.  People have died from such occurrences.  Yet the police did not take him to the hospital.  At this point, this case reeks. 
I believe it was the boy, Martin, on the ground screaming for help.  Not Zimmerman.  As far as I'm concerned, even the police investigation is tainted at this point and this needs to be taken over by the Feds.  I think racial animus could be established by the facts of the investigation ( or lack thereof ) as known to this point and by the fact that his calls to 911 involving 'suspicious' people in the neighborhood Always, without exception, involved black youth.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zb883</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5xa</id></website><link>http://www.americablog.com/2012/03/guns-dont-kill-people-hoodies-kill.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:44:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T03:54:50+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3so59</id><link>http://www.americablog.com/2012/03/guns-dont-kill-people-hoodies-kill.html#comment-480220010</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>