<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpbapb/update/2012-03-21T21:15:11/d90b0e5b08ca6714b468cf67ed77d1b3464ba66845985d53f850abdcf893ef82</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp6b7g</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6aqus</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>With respect to Jose's comments, the real issue is politics and who has the most to Gain and who has the most to lose in this proposed exchange. In the US, outside of the greater metropolitan Miami area, little, if any, is known of the Cuban Five or Alan Gross for that matter. Anything that Obama does that reflects a positive or humanitarian gesture towards Cuba can only hurt him politically within the Cuban emigre community and potentially beyond to to undecided independent voter who still equates Cuba with the Cold War. On the other hand, in Cuba, the Cuban Five are national heroes and Alan Gross is almost as well-known throughout the island. Any positive gesture by Cuba only serves to reverse the largely negative international image Cuba maintains with regards to human rights. Chess, in Cuba, is a national pastime. The US sacrificed a pawn by giving Gonzales a two-week pass to visit his ailing brother. As Anya stated, he has to return to the US as directed. On the other hand, Cuba can conquer a bishop, if they were to magnanimously permit Gross to visit his mother and daughter. Their tactical mistake was allowing the US to move first with allowing Gonzalez to travel. Had they granted Gross' petition first, they would have conquered a king.  Still, a bishop ain't bad.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dp9co</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yoof</id></website><link>http://thehavananote.com/node/999</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T14:53:55+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T01:15:11+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpbapb</id><link>http://thehavananote.com/node/999#comment-473000890</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h96as</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>