<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kh8x/post/2012-03-29T22:22:19</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3oy2f</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zzni6</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Again, you seem to think old prejudices just die.  Would you not be concerned if you were a black man in the South with an all white jury? Just because Segregation did end 50 some years ago does not mean we can be suspect.  The same goes for Poles criticizing Jews - particularly when they use extreme and over broad rhetoric.


Second, I think your history is a bit biased.  


"In 1948 Israel displaced nearly a half of a million Palestinians, 
destroyed nearly 4/5ths of existing Palestinian villages, destroying 
thousands of homes"

-----In 1947 the Palestinians began choking  the Jewish villages with their war of the roads - killing and destroying all Jewish people and vehicles.  They began attacking Jewish kibbutzim.   They rejected the UN Partition Plan that would have given them a state of their own.  They called upon the standing armies of their Arab brothers to come fight the Jews with them.  The Palestinians were hardly innocent bystanders.  

"making refugees out of people who had lived 
peacefully on their land for generations. "

------Jews have had a continuous presence in Israel long before the Arab armies ever came out of Arabia in 637 AD.  And, the Palestinians were not "living peacefully" on their land for generations.  Even before the so called large scale immigration of Jews to Palestine, there were Arab pogroms against Jews.  The tiny Jewish communities in Safed, Tiberias and Jerusalem were subject to routine prejudice and persecution. The Pogrom in Safed was notoriously terrible.  This
 pogrom is known in Jewish history as ‘The great plunder of Safed’ and 
it lasted from the 15 of June 1834 to the 17 of July of that year. For
 33 days the lives of the Jews of Safed had practically no value, and 
anyone of them who showed his or her face in public was at risk of being 
beaten to death by the Arabs, sometimes by people they knew as neighbors or business 
associates.

 The 1920 Nabi Musa riots or 1920 Jerusalem riots took place in British Mandate of Palestine on April 4–7, 1920 in and around the Old City of Jerusalem.  [A] riot broke out, the people began to run about and stones were thrown
 at the Jews. The shops were closed and there were screams... I saw a 
Zionist soldier covered in dust and blood... Afterwards, I saw one 
Hebronite approach a Jewish shoeshine boy, who hid behind a sack in one 
of the wall's comers next to Jaffa Gate, and take his box and beat him 
over the head. He screamed and began to run, his head Bleeding and the 
Hebronite left him and returned to the procession... The riot  
its zenith. All , "Muhammad's
 religion was born with the sword"... I immediately walked to the 
municipal garden... my soul is nauseated and depressed by the madness of
 humankind."

In these Palestinian riots, 5 Jews were killed, 216 killed, and 300 had to be "evacuated" ie ethnically cleansed from the city of Jerusalem.  These were also the religious Jews, not affiliated with the Zionist movement at the time. 

The Hebron massacre refers to the killing of sixty-seven Jews on 23 and 24 August 1929 in Hebron, then part of the British Mandate of Palestine, by Arabs incited to violence by rumors that Jews were massacring Arabs[1] in Jerusalem and seizing control of Muslim holy places. This massacre, together with that of Safed, sent shock waves through Jewish communities in Palestine and across the world. During the massacre, 67 Jews were killed and Jewish homes and synagogues were ransacked. Several cases of rape, mutilation and torture were reported to have been committed by the Arabs.


"And the argument that 
justified these actions? God gave us this land 2000+ years ago.  Face 
facts, Israel is not treating Palestinians fairly and needs to revise 
its policies to eliminate the human rights abuses which are occuring 
daily in the region."

----Sorry, but prior to 1948, the Jews were purchasing their land from Arabs and Ottoman Turks.  There was no Palestinian state. There was only Ottoman territories and British Mandates.  

Israel not treating the Palestinians fairly?  I'm sorry, but how should Israelis treat a people that declared war on them in 1948, rejected the UN peace plan that would give them a state, and invited their "arab brothers" to loot and murder the Jews along with them (ie the armies of Egypt, Jordan, Iraq, Lebanon, and Syria).  Then in the 1950s, they used Fedayeen attacks on the Jews in the PRE-1967 borders, murdering thousands of innocent civilians.  In the 1960s and 1970s, they waged a war of international terrorism, murdering even Olympic athletes.  In the 1980s the Palestinians decided to launch rockets at Jewish civilian towns from Lebanon and stage terrorist Raids from South Lebanon.  In the 1990s, the Palestinians began their campagin of bus bombings, suicide bombings, molotov cocktails, sniper attacks, and stabbings,  which lasts up to now.  So don't complain about being treated "fairly."  




 </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z6cyd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/eyjq</id></website><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2012/03/why-the-arab-uprisings-will-force-the-us-to-rethink-israel-palestine/255194/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T11:37:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:22:19+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3kh8x</id><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2012/03/why-the-arab-uprisings-will-force-the-us-to-rethink-israel-palestine/255194/#comment-480153837</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zgx5y</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>