<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwohbx/post/2012-03-31T05:42:38</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>(1) Capital Punishment Crimes:


 


Kill People
Who Don't Listen to Priests


    Anyone arrogant enough to reject
the verdict of the judge or of the priest who represents the LORD your God must
be put to death.  Such evil must be purged from Israel.  (Deuteronomy 17:12 NLT)


 


Kill Witches


    You should not let a sorceress
live.  (Exodus 22:17
NAB)


 


Kill
Homosexuals
    "If a
man lies with a male as with a women, both of them shall be put to death for
their abominable deed; they have forfeited their lives." 
(Leviticus 20:13 NAB)


 


Kill
Fortunetellers


    A man or a woman who  as a
medium or fortuneteller shall be put to death by stoning; they have no one but
themselves to blame for their death.  (Leviticus 20:27 NAB)


 


Death for
Hitting Dad


    Whoever strikes his father or
mother shall be put to death.  (Exodus
21:15 NAB)


 


Death for Cursing Parents


    1) If one curses his father or mother,
his lamp will go out at the coming of darkness.  (Proverbs 20:20 NAB)


   
2) All who curse their father
or mother must be put to death.  They are guilty of a capital offense. 
(Leviticus 20:9 NLT)


 


Death for
Adultery


    If a man commits adultery with
another man's wife, both the man and the woman must be put to death. 
(Leviticus 20:10 NLT)


 


Death for
Fornication


    A priest's daughter who loses her
honor by committing fornication and thereby dishonors her father also, shall be
Burned to death.  (Leviticus 21:9 NAB)


 


Death to
Followers of Other Religions


    Whoever sacrifices to any
god, except the Lord alone, shall be doomed.  (Exodus 22:19 NAB)


 


Kill
Nonbelievers


    They entered into a covenant
to seek the Lord, the God of their fathers, with all their heart and soul; and
everyone who would not seek the Lord, the God of Israel, was to be put to
death, whether small or great, whether man or woman.  (2 Chronicles
15:12-13 NAB)


 


Kill False
Prophets


    If a man still prophesies,
his parents, father and mother, shall say to him, "You shall not live,
because you have spoken a lie in the name of the Lord."  When he
prophesies, his parents, father and mother, shall thrust him through.  (Zechariah 13:3 NAB)


 


Kill the Entire Town
if One Person Worships Another God


    Suppose you hear in one of the
towns the LORD your God is giving you that some worthless rabble among you have
led their fellow citizens astray by encouraging them to worship foreign
gods.  In such cases, you must examine the facts carefully.  If you
find it is true and can prove that such a detestable  has occurred among
you, you must attack that town and completely destroy all its inhabitants, as
well as all the livestock.  Then you must pile all the plunder in the
middle of the street and Burn it.  Put the entire town to the torch as a
Burnt offering to the LORD your God.  That town must remain a ruin
forever; it may never be rebuilt.  Keep none of the plunder that has been
set apart for destruction.  Then the LORD will turn from his fierce anger
and be merciful to you.  He will have compassion on you and make you a
great nation, just as he solemnly promised your ancestors.  "The LORD
your God will be merciful only if you obey him and keep all the commands I am
giving you today, doing what is pleasing to him."  (Deuteronomy
13:13-19 NLT)


 


Kill Women Who Are Not Virgins On Their Wedding Night


    But if this charge is true (that she wasn't a virgin on her
wedding night), and evidence of the girls virginity is not found, they shall
bring the girl to the entrance of her fathers house and there her townsman
shall stone her to death, because she committed a crime against Israel by her
unchasteness in her father's house.  Thus shall you purge the evil from
your midst.  (Deuteronomy  22:20-21 NAB)


 


Kill Followers
of Other Religions.


   
1) If your own
full brother, or your son or daughter, or your beloved wife, or you intimate
friend, entices you secretly to serve other gods, whom you and your fathers
have not known, gods of any other nations, near at hand or far away, from one
end of the earth to the other: do not yield to him or listen to him, nor look
with pity upon him, to spare or shield him, but kill him.  Your hand shall
be the first raised to slay him; the rest of the people shall join in with
you.  You shall stone him to death, because he sought to lead you astray
from the Lord, your God, who brought you out of the land of Egypt,
that place of slavery.  And all Israel, hearing of this, shall fear
and never do such evil as this in your midst.  (Deuteronomy 13:7-12 NAB)


 


   
2) Suppose a man or
woman among you, in one of your towns that the LORD your God is giving you, has
done evil in the sight of the LORD your God and has violated the covenant by
serving other gods or by worshiping the sun, the moon, or any of the forces of
heaven, which I have strictly forbidden.  When you hear about it,
investigate the matter thoroughly. If it is true that this detestable thing has
been done in Israel,
then that man or woman must be taken to the gates of the town and stoned to death.  (Deuteronomy 17:2-5 NLT)


 


Death for
Blasphemy


    One day a man who had an Israelite
mother and an Egyptian father got into a fight with one of the Israelite
men.  During the fight, this son of an Israelite woman blasphemed the
LORD's name.  So the man was brought to Moses for judgment.  His
mother's name was Shelomith. She was the daughter of Dibri of the tribe of
Dan.  They put the man in custody until the LORD's will in the matter
should become clear.  Then the LORD said to Moses, "Take the blasphemer
outside the camp, and tell all those who heard him to lay their hands on his
head.  Then let the entire community stone him to death.  Say to the
people of Israel:
Those who blaspheme God will suffer the consequences of their guilt and be
punished.  Anyone who blasphemes the LORD's name must be stoned to death
by the whole community of Israel.
 Any Israelite or foreigner among you who blasphemes the LORD's name will
surely die.  (Leviticus 24:10-16 NLT)


 


Kill False
Prophets


    1) Suppose
there are prophets among you, or those who have dreams about the future, and
they promise you signs or miracles,  and the predicted signs or miracles
take place.  If the prophets then say, 'Come, let us worship the gods of
foreign nations,' do not listen to them.  The LORD your God is testing you
to see if you love him with all your heart and soul.  Serve only the LORD
your God and fear him alone.  Obey his commands, listen to his voice, and
cling to him.  The false prophets or dreamers who try to lead you astray
must be put to death, for they encourage rebellion against the LORD your God,
who brought you out of slavery in the land of Egypt.
 Since they try to keep you from following the LORD your God, you must
execute them to remove the evil from among you.  (Deuteronomy 13:1-5 NLT)


 


   
2) But any prophet who
claims to give a message from another god or who falsely claims to speak for me
must die.'  You may wonder, 'How will we know whether the prophecy is from
the LORD or not?'  If the prophet predicts something in the LORD's name
and it does not happen, the LORD did not give the message.  That prophet
has spoken on his own and need not be feared.  (Deuteronomy 18:20-22 NLT)


 


Infidels and Gays Should Die


    So God let them go ahead and do
whatever shameful things their hearts desired.  As a result, they did vile
and degrading things with each other's bodies.  Instead of believing what
they knew was the truth about God, they deliberately chose to believe lies.
 So they worshiped the things God made but not the Creator himself, who is
to be praised forever.  Amen.  That is why God abandoned them to
their shameful desires.  Even the women turned against the natural way to
have sex and instead indulged in sex with each other.  And the men,
instead of having normal sexual relationships with women, Burned with lust for
each other.  Men did shameful things with other men and, as a result,
suffered within themselves the penalty they so richly deserved.  When they
refused to acknowledge God, he abandoned them to their evil minds and let them
do things that should never be done.  Their lives became full of every
kind of wickedness, sin, greed, hate, envy, murder, fighting, deception,
malicious behavior, and gossip.  They are backstabbers, haters of God,
insolent, proud, and boastful.  They are forever inventing new ways of
sinning and are disobedient to their parents.  They refuse to understand,
break their promises, and are heartless and unforgiving.  They are fully
aware of God's death penalty for those who do these things, yet they go right
ahead and do them anyway.  And, worse yet, they encourage others to do
them, too.  (Romans
1:24-32 NLT)


 


Kill Anyone
who Approaches the Tabernacle


    For the LORD had said to Moses,
'Exempt the tribe of Levi from the census; do not include them when you count
the rest of the Israelites.  You must put the Levites in charge of the
Tabernacle of the Covenant, along with its furnishings and equipment.
 They must carry the Tabernacle and its equipment as you travel, and they
must care for it and camp around it.  Whenever the Tabernacle is moved,
the Levites will take it down and set it up again.  Anyone else who goes
too near the Tabernacle will be executed.'  (Numbers 1:48-51 NLT)


 


Kill People for Working on the Sabbath


    The LORD then gave these further
instructions to Moses: 'Tell the people of Israel to keep my Sabbath day, for
the Sabbath is a sign of the covenant between me and you forever.  It
helps you to remember that I am the LORD, who makes you holy.  Yes, keep
the Sabbath day, for it is holy.  Anyone who desecrates it must die;
anyone who works on that day will be cut Off from the community.  Work six
days only, but the seventh day must be a day of total rest.  I repeat:
Because the LORD considers it a holy day, anyone who works on the Sabbath must
be put to death.'  (Exodus
31:12-15 NLT)</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y7ikc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/8cxx</id></website><link>http://www.jpost.com/International/Article.aspx?id=262965</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T11:07:21+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T09:42:38+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwohbx</id><link>http://www.jpost.com/International/Article.aspx?id=262965#comment-481694205</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/fhhe</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>