<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7lxw/post/2012-03-30T15:10:41</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Can I Burn trash on my private property? Can I grow marijuana for my own consumption? Can I refuse to have Social Security withdrawn from my paycheck, or am I "forced" to purchase it? Can I have multiple wives, as my religion states I should do? Can I refuse to offer blood transfusion coverage to my employee's health benefits since my religion states this is a sin? There are thousands of ways someone could twist a scenario to make it seem the big, bad Government is controlling me, taking away my "freedom." But, the courts have shown repeatedly, personal freedom doesn't trump societal needs, even if it is religious. And, that's not universally a "bad" thing. 

Ignoring this, let's assume the so-called Obamacare is negated by the Supreme Court. Will you jump up and down with Joy, or will you quickly realize we have simply been put back on the Titanic and now have to search for a different lifeboat? Because one this is certain: the health care delivery system prior to Obamacare cannot survive.  It is both too costly and will become irrelevant when medicare enrollees balloon to the point that your taxes can't keep up with Medicare expenditures (predicted to be in 10 years or so. Ten short, short years!) 

So, the real question goes beyond whether Obamacare is legal; the real question that is being ignored by near everyone is what do we do if it is not upheld? </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6znb26</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/b7s3</id></website><link>http://www.kearneyhub.com/news/opinion/article_3319d066-79c5-11e1-9078-0019bb2963f4.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T19:41:01+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T19:10:41+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw7lxw</id><link>http://www.kearneyhub.com/news/opinion/article_3319d066-79c5-11e1-9078-0019bb2963f4.html#comment-481086358</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8u8nz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>