<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwdrdh/post/2012-03-30T09:49:36</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The biggest thing this lineup can do to get to where they have to be is make more contact and get thier K's down from the horrible number of 1,193 Tampa had in 2011. Just putting the ball in play more often will get the line up from .244/.322/.402 of last year. Too many K's W/RISP just killed Tampa in 2011 and also contributed to thier .222 average W/RISP. They have find a way to fix that as it looks like they will again have trouble scoring runs. Even more so if they continue to strikeout at a high rate. This first month of the season is a big one with the Rays coming out against New York, Boston, Toronto, important wins against division foes, and other good division contending teams in Detroit, Los Angeles, and Texas with a series facing the Twins at the Trop sandwiched in. If Tampa can't get the runs they need this could be a tough month to get out of. Of course playing in the A.L. East Tampa will  have 72 games that are going to be tough, mostly offensive minded games. Carlos Pena and what he can bring to this lineup will be a big part of where this Rays team goes in 2012. If he can get around .250-.260 while keeping his OBP at .350 and hit 25+ home runs with 75+RBI he can give this offense a needed boost. But again much of that  on if he can at least show teams a willingness to go the other way. If he keeps doing what he has done then the shift will keep killing him. He's another one that has to get his K's down to a reasonable number. It's a bit scary that he didn't improve his average in Chicago in 2011 and even though he did hit 28 homers and 80RBI would hope that he could have gotten 35+ in the N.L.. He is back where he had his best years so we will see. Luke  is also a very big key to what this lineup can do this year. Tampa needs the Luke  of 2010 to emerge after his injury riddled 2011. This is a guy that's more than capable with career numbers of .264/.349/.494 with 112 homers, 341RBI, 146 doubles and surprisingly 17 triples. Maybe the biggest help to this Rays team is his ability to put the ball in play consistently. He's struckout 519 times in 2243 career at-bats. He would be a good fit to be behind Longoria, Zobrist, and Joyce but in front of Pena. The 6th Spot in the lineup would be ideal for Scott as of now. Keppinger has to have a good April in the second Spot as well with Upton out. If he does he could be the biggest offseason signing for Freidman for 2012.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zf7el</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lz6q</id></website><link>http://tampabay.rays.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120329%26content_id=27741432%26vkey=news_tb%26c_id=tb</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T23:39:26+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:49:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwdrdh</id><link>http://tampabay.rays.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120329%26content_id=27741432%26vkey=news_tb%26c_id=tb#comment-480757981</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cszkh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>