<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwsx30/update/2012-03-31T10:54:55/3383e5ef503723801f890e31f7c9f5fc7270902b2d938e3c7212a52cbd9fe421</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body> 

Prof. Peter Kagwanja resurfaced with an article,lemmi quote for u “As the
region sinks to a siege mentality, its political class has blamed its woes on
an evil trinity: Raila Odinga, ICC and Britain. But on the road to the
watershed election in March 2013, the region’s choices are stark: return to
enlightened politics of reason and nationhood or perish in the dynastic
ghetto.” Kagwanja is not a man we can take seriously, because he has traits of
a mercenary; he conspired with  Ocampo to
try and fix Ocampo 4. Kagwanja tried to get to Mr. Kigeugeu’s office to replace
Comrade Miguna Miguna, but another Kikuyu intellectual prostitute (read Paul
Mwangi)  there before him!Kagwanja must remember the following inspired
words uttered by former Israel Foreign Affairs Minister, the late Abba Ebban:
“Genocide is not synonymous with nationhood…national suicide is not an
international obligation!”


Let us now listen to lawyer Tharcisse Gatarama, who works for the Defence at
the International Criminal Court for the Rwanda (ICTR). Gatarama wrote an
interesting article on Prof. Makau Mutua  “As a practitioner of international criminal
law, I have been a keen follower of the ICC cases against the initially six and
now four prominent Kenyans… In recent weeks, I have seen strange happenings
around the ICC process in Kenya starting with the alleged leak of a British
Government conspiracy to indict President Kibaki when he retires, alleged
hacking of witnesses’ email accounts to the dramatic Internet posting of
material suggesting that an apparently critical witness in the case against Mr.
Francis Muthaura and Mr. Uhuru Kenyatta had as early as 2009 retracted his
allegations against the two. When I first saw this material on the Internet, I
equated it to and dismissed it as the normal social media gibberish until Prof.
Makau Mutua, the renowned Kenyan legal scholar and Sunday Nation columnist
waded into the unfolding saga and contended that James Maina Kabutu, the man
who, according to the material on the net, had retracted his evidence against
the Ocampo two, was indeed prosecution witness No. 4. In his first article on
the subject entitled “Did key Ocampo witness recant his testimony?”  Prof. Mutua did not question the identity of
the witness but rather his motives. He opined something similar to what I had
heard the defence teams say during the confirmation hearings: that witness No.
4 was a liar! Prof. Mutua made the perfectly correct legal conclusion that the
witness had either lied in his sworn deposition recanting his evidence or had
lied to the ICC. In his most recent article entitled “How they tampered with
Ocampo witness”  Prof. Mutua made a
complete turn-around… In startling revelations, he wrote that he “can
absolutely and without equivocation confirm that Mr. Kabutu was put under
unbearable pressure to recant his testimony” and accused David Matsanga (the
man who made the alleged recantation video public) of tampering with the
witness. Prof. Mutua further stated that Mr. Kabutu was forced to read an
“affidavit” on video by two officials with the Kenya National Commission on
Human Rights (KNCHR). Although the officials do not appear on the video, Prof.
Mutua suggests these two officials were present and that in fact were giving
cues Off camera to Mr. Kabutu as he read the affidavit retracting his earlier
evidence. Prof. Mutua went further to “confirm” that Kabutu was both bribed
with money and had his family threatened but did not blow the whistle or call
the FBI to arrest his tormentors because “he felt he had no choice but to do
what was ordered for the sake of his kith back home.”


· He (Prof. Mutua) continued that the whole saga was being orchestrated to
frustrate justice but that “the good news is that Mr. Kabutu is unshakable and
won’t be bowed.” He described Kabutu as a hero who had already “taken a bullet”
for Kenya.After reading the article, I asked myself many troubling questions:
How is it that Prof. Mutua is privy to such detailed and apparently
confidential information? On what authority does he so confidently confirm that
Mr. Kabutu is indeed prosecution witness No. 4?Who told Prof. Mutua that Mr.
Kabutu was bribed, threatened and subjected to other forms of coercion leading
to the retraction of his evidence? How does Prof. Mutua know that KNCHR
officials – the same body that provided evidence against the suspects for the
Waki Commission and the ICC – were involved in Mr. Kabutu’s recantation?Considering
that Prof. Mutua did not seem to have all of this information when he wrote his
first article on the same issue, it must have come to him afterwards.


 If we accept that Mr. Kabutu is
indeed prosecution witness No. 4, then the most logical deduction (given the
certainty and confidence with which Prof. Mutua makes his conclusions) would be
that he either obtained this information from the witness himself or from the
prosecution.This raises a number of issues. In what capacity would Prof. Mutua
be in contact with a protected prosecution witness? What role is he playing on
this matter that he would have access to such information? Why would the
prosecution provide such information to him?Should it ultimately be confirmed
that Prof. Mutua is indeed in touch with this apparently important witness, I
foresee a situation where he himself should be ready to answer hard question.
In what circumstances did Mr. Kabutu disclose the information to him? Could any
contacts he may have had with Mr. Kabutu also be construed as witness
tampering? Is Prof. Mutua an intermediary of the prosecution? Being an
established lawyer of international repute, Prof. Mutua would know of the unflattering
manner in which ICC judges sometimes view the use of intermediaries. For
instance, in the recent verdict against DRC’s Thomas Lubanga, the judges
evaluated the impact of the prosecution’s use of intermediaries and found that
in several instances, the testimony of some witnesses who had been in contact
with these intermediaries was untruthful. As I don’t have the full facts
surrounding Prof. Mutua’s allegations and conclusions, I cannot for sure say
that what happened in the Lubanga case regarding the use of intermediaries has
happened in respect of witness No. 4 in the Kenyan cases.However, Prof. Mutua’s
unexplained, apparent access to a protected witness on whose behalf he seems to
be talking could raise serious questions about the integrity of the ICC witness
protection regime and the reliability of the evidence of key witnesses.On the
other hand, by commenting on a matter that may very well be under investigation
and providing unsolicited “confirmations” and conclusions regarding how the
witness was bribed and threatened, Prof. Matua may have recklessly prejudiced
the outcome of any such investigation.” Well done, Tharcisse Gatarama: you are
Spot on!


</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/67pl18</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/z2gh</id></website><link>http://www.the-star.co.ke/national/national/69274-icc-trials-may-start-march-2013</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T13:02:06+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T14:54:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwsx30</id><link>http://www.the-star.co.ke/national/national/69274-icc-trials-may-start-march-2013#comment-481891607</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z7g91</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>