<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xqkv/post/2012-03-29T13:54:24</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3n1v9</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/669fc</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Since season 2.  And I later caught up on most of the season 1 moments.

We may like the show a little bit less now and feel the contestants aren't as special, but the reality is that some of the "great" performances from years back don't really hold up to the better ones from this season and last season.

(Totally random example:  I remember there was UPROAR when Sundance Head didn't get into the Top 12 on season 6.  Go back and watch the performance of "Jeremy" that supposedly guarantee him a Spot in the finals)

Take someone like Carrie Underwood, who is the most successful contestant to come  the show, and actually watch her Idol performances.  Save for the occasional "Alone," she was notoriously stiff and not all that special vocally.  She had a lot of duds (Love is a Battlefield) and never really had anything in the league of what someone like Jessica has been providing this year.

And Ruben is a joke compared to Joshua.

More importantly to the point, there have been VERY few shows, especially at this point in the annual competition, in which everybody was "on."

Let's look at a show like "Movie Night" in season three.  You had Fantasia's best-of-all-time "Summertime" performance.  LaToya's "Somewhere."  Jennifer Hudson's "I Have Nothing."

But wait.  You also had George Huff falling Off a cliff with "Against All Odds."  Diana DeGarmo's trainwreck karaoke rendition of "My Heart Will Go On."  JPL's embarrassing "Jailhouse Rock."

I'm not as into the show anymore, but I can be real and honest--I'm pretty sure we can count the number of "good from top to bottom" performance shows on one hand.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6za88l</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/9-finalists-compete,71163/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T03:38:30+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:54:24+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xqkv</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/9-finalists-compete,71163/#comment-479696092</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lcxac</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>