<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fu5z/post/2012-03-29T16:59:10</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>When the SUN ran with the headline "Suite deal in Regent Park" they clearly implied that McConnell and others received sweetheart deals on their units. The implication was that they paid far below market value something that would be not only unethical but potentially illegal in the case of McConnell as it could be seen as a kick-back

This was a very serious allegation by the Toronto SUN and it required that its writer - Sue-Ann Levy back up her allegations with PROOF of below market purchases. 

To date the SUN has failed to provide evidence that McConnell or others got preferential treatment - and Worthington concedes that he would be "be surprised if he finds anything that’s overtly illegal."  

If there is nothing illegal in McConnell's purchase why did the SUN defame her with a libelous headline "Suite deal in Regent Park".

Worthington says its all about "appearances". If McConnell had secretly purchased the condo and was renting it out I would agree that might look bad but the FACT is she was Always upfront about the purchase - clearing it with the then ethics commissioner and boasting about her purchase in newsletters. She didn't buy it as an investment, she is living in the Condo. Like wise the VP's at Daniels who bought units used the fact that they purchased units as part of their sales pitch to potential buyers. Lets not forget that not long ago the idea of investing in a condo in Regent Park was anything but a sure bet even in Toronto's Heated market. 

The SUN has lost a lot of credibility with Sue-Ann Levy's series of poorly researched and libelous articles. I don't know how they can keep her on the payroll after this. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zvuuh</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zsj8</id></website><link>http://www.torontosun.com/2012/03/29/when-it-comes-to-conflict-of-interest-appearances-matter</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T16:47:00+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:59:10+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3fu5z</id><link>http://www.torontosun.com/2012/03/29/when-it-comes-to-conflict-of-interest-appearances-matter#comment-479886926</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/aidxv</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>