<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwd3bu/post/2012-03-30T10:19:28</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>In fact, going to a pub does not entail breaking any of the "eat food" rules above. Most pubs sell actual food..and sometimes surprisingly good food. Leaving out the worry of hormone-injected meats and other details we can't really worry about when eating at a pub, a chicken wing is still part of a chicken, a burger is still meat from a cow, fries are from potatoes, and they have salads at pubs too. Many English/Irish pubs also have great tasting Indian curry dishes.

So going to a pub one, and on occasion twice a week (but maybe 3 times would be pushing it) is not the problem...it's what we do during the other days that makes the real difference. I take a system approach here...most of us like enjoying ourselves and going out and I personally like beer a lot...so taking the simplest guideline in this case, and expanding on Pollan's rule #5 - everything in moderation. After 2 beers usually, my body says that is enough...and once in a while I will go one or 2 more after that but not much more as I then feel the negative effects and the beer buzz isn't worth it anymore. I can also eat a lot...and I can sometimes even eat two burgers...but again my body will tell me when i've had too much...but the best is when I cut  before feeling bloated. But the days or after pub night, if I go to work, sit down all day, go home and sit down and watch TV all night, and then do this every day until the next pub night, THEN THAT'S A DIFFERENT STORY...

In terms of Weight loss and weight Gain, another simple guideline to maintain weight...CALORIES IN = CALORIES OUT. If I don't expend some of those excess calories I had at pub night the in the next few days, then they basically add to fat cells. So as part of the systems approach..in addition to watching what and how you eat, activity that Burns calories is needed...an active lifestyle combined with healthy eating habits...one without the other would not make sense.

With regards to fast lunches and breakfasts...same applies...whether eaten quickly or not, how will you use up the calories. I take about 30 mins. for lunch on weekdays...and I usually have to buy lunch, so I walk across the street to the mall...which allows me to get up and out of the office after sitting the morning (more on sitting and the importance of moving later).</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zqd9c</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/pcig</id></website><link>http://thegenghisblog.tumblr.com/post/20123925201</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T18:41:51+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T14:19:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwd3bu</id><link>http://thegenghisblog.tumblr.com/post/20123925201#comment-480787007</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>