<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3k352/update/2012-03-29T22:59:10/27759b78c1c66a7e1530ce058c8a7077a1e9a900fe9716f93eee624586e7a259</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>NL East Predictions:

Phillies 1st = 90+ wins
(if one of their big starters goes down for the year, they'll sink below 90)
Nationals 2nd = 85-88 wins 
Marlins a close 3rd = 85-88 wins 
(but only if Johnson is healthy and pitching like himself for the Fish)
Braves 4th = 85-87 wins
Mets 5th = ?????? (somewhere between 67 to 82 wins,  on Santana's health and a gazillion other factors)

I really, really, really want the Phillies to crash and Burn in the most terrible way.  However IMO, they'll need one of their big starters to go down for this to happen.  They are essentially the same team as last year (102 wins), but with a better closer.  Yes, they are old and the injuries are happening, but they've happened before.  For the past 2 seasons, the Phillies infield (Polanco/Rollins/Utley/Howard) has averaged roughly only 125 games played per player, and they won 97 games in 2010 and 102 games in 2011.  I'm not hoping for an injury to one of the big three, but that's probably what it will take for them to fall below 90 wins...for this year anyway.

Strasburg/Zimmerman/Gonzalez/Jackson is a d--n good top four, and their bullpen has been solid as well. 

I agree that the Marlins have the highest Beta.   

I'll say it again - the Braves were over-rated last year, and they have a lot of question marks this year.  Again, they were 7 games under .500 against winning teams in 2011.  The only team in the NL East that they had a winning record against was the Marlins (13-5 against them) - that ain't happening this year.  Their interleague schedule was soft last year, and this year, it's very difficult.  Hudson is old and hurt (out until May).  Jurrgens might be toast after his injury (they tried to trade him and couldn't).  Hanson is coming  injury, too.  I agree with Toby in that the young starters won't give them length this year, and I wouldn't expect them to be playoff caliber just yet.  Also, Viscaino is down for the year, and Teheran has shoulder stiffness right now.  Offensively, they were 22nd in the majors in runs scored, and 26th in OBP...they didn't have a good approach, which probably isn't going to change much.  They are relying on Chipper Jones in the middle of the lineup, and he's already having surgery.  They added Bourn, and Heyward should Bounce back a little...but they also added Pastornicki who looks questionable.  I don't see the offense improving greatly, and I think the pitching could be worse...and their schedule is more difficult.  Good luck.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zxi67</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/teqz</id></website><link>http://www.metsminorleagueblog.com/new-mostly-mets-podcast-2012-preview/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T20:34:20+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:59:10+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3k352</id><link>http://www.metsminorleagueblog.com/new-mostly-mets-podcast-2012-preview/#comment-480179808</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/g5fs0</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>