<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw3nu4/post/2012-03-31T11:49:27</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw3mx2</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Let's address those inefficiencies, Steve.

First oil.  The typical gasmobile wastes about 80% of the energy in a gallon of gas.  What to know where it goes?  Stick your hand on your engine block after you've driven for a while.  Hold you hand against the tail pipe.  (Don't really do that, but think about what would happen if you did.)

And that's just part of the waste.  A significant part of the barrel of oil extracted from wells is Burned to refine the crude into gas/diesel/etc.  Electricity is purchased, coal is Burned, natural gas is Burned - lots of energy gets used to turn oil into fuel.  More energy wasted.

And let's throw in the wasted energy used to drill/pump/transport/distribute oil.  

Overall, tremendous inefficiencies.  It could be that only 5% of the energy in a gallon of the stuff down in the ground is actually used.  

--

Now let's address the energy consumption needed to charge EVs and PHEVs.

There are losses if we Burn fossil fuels to create electricity.  But we're in the process of transitioning away from fossil fuels.  And coal/gas plants are more efficient than ICEVs.

Of course there's no fossil fuel energy loss if we're talking about electricity from renewable sources.

We loose a very small amount of electricity in transmission.  There's about a 10% loss in  charging.  EVs are very efficient, they waste only 10% or so of the energy in Batteries - 90% goes to moving the car forward.

The energy coming out of wind turbines and solar panels - we're wasting roughly 25%.

--

5% vs. 75% - There's no contest.  

Gasmobiles are the energy black holes of transportation.  We throw away an incredible amount of energy moving ourselves around with this outdated technology.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6hhb70</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/68bl</id></website><link>http://cleantechnica.com/2012/03/28/shocker-conservative-fox-news-guest-tears-up-conservative-lies-about-chevy-volt/</link><postedTime>2012-03-28T13:31:34+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T15:49:27+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mw3nu4</id><link>http://cleantechnica.com/2012/03/28/shocker-conservative-fox-news-guest-tears-up-conservative-lies-about-chevy-volt/#comment-481936590</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cctpv</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>