<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmlf7/update/2012-03-30T09:01:23/31b4c7c9c9dbad359b052bfca81b52f4899c73e2ed1bb48df3162e409c0d4643</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mweisq</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ma9h9</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>The three practical pump storage sites in the UK, have already been exploited.

The proposal to add more is just an expensive and counterproductive sticking plaster, over a gaping wound that is irrational thinking over energy.

LFTR, because it was designed as an aircraft engine, is throttleable, and can provide both base load power and peak load power.

Safely, cheaply, cleanly, efficiently, and into the distant future (where it can work alongside hot fusion, which can even make Thorium fuel for LFTR as a byproduct).

We can have a few new coal plants devoted to the Fischer–Tropsch process, which will help with liquid fuels until there are enough LFTR stations to synthesise liquid fuels (and fill the energy gap on their own), using fluid bed furnaces running on residual petro-Coke, which are clean Burning then extract Thorium from the ash. There'll be enough energy available for water desalination (evaporative from the high grade Heat with LFTR, as well as pumped through membranes as developed by the Israeli's), and waste Heat can be used for all manner of industrial uses, as well as commercial growers with large greenhouses.

There's all manner of relatively cheap solutions available, but there's too much incentive for some people to profiteer from fictional problems and scaremongering.

Those people have got to go, and they will go.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6z63l9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ms5i</id></website><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/jamesdelingpole/100148065/what-pastygate-tells-us-about-camerons-conservatives/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T12:22:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T13:01:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwmlf7</id><link>http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/news/jamesdelingpole/100148065/what-pastygate-tells-us-about-camerons-conservatives/#comment-480713235</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/a3n2l</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>