<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ys3u/update/2012-03-29T02:36:20/0a5360f5cd935fd0da1de2bec26b3e4074d980ab14e5a4b52d48b0e55277c2c8</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3e7nc</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/mh7qq</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>""This was not self defense," Cutcher said. "We heard no fighting, no wrestling, no punching. We heard a boy crying. As soon as the shot went , it stopped, which tells me it was the child crying. If it had been Zimmerman crying, it wouldn't have stopped. If you're hurting, you're hurting."

 She and her friend say they heard the sounds from a few steps away, where they were inside beside an open window. Seconds later, they dashed out to find a boy face down on the ground and a man standing over him, a foot on each side of the body on the ground, with his hands pinning the shooting victim down.

 "I asked him, 'What's happening here? What's going on?' said Cutcher's friend, who did not want her name published for fear for her safety. "The third time, I was indignant, and he said, 'Just call the police.' Then I saw him with his hands over his head in the universal sign of: 'Oh man, I messed up.' "

 The women, who were the first on the scene, said they saw Zimmerman pacing back and forth.

 "I know what I heard. I heard a cry and a shot," the second witness said. "If there was a fight, it did not happen here where the boy was shot. I would have heard it, as this all happened right outside my open window."

 The women think there may well have been a physical altercation between the two, but it must have taken place in a different Spot, where Zimmerman perhaps had a chance to compose himself and draw his weapon.

 Cutcher was one of eight or nine 911 callers that night but she said investigators dismissed her, and a detective failed to follow up with her. Both women said police seemed very blase."

And:

""I saw someone lying on the ground, and I heard screaming," said Austin, 13, whose mother asked that his last name not be published. "I don't know that it was the person on the (ground) who was screaming, but to me it sounded like a kid who was crying. It was a yell for help, and I think it was Trayvon."

 Austin wasn't sure if the person was in a fight or had slipped and gotten hurt. Austin's Boxer puppy got  the leash so the boy went chasing after the dog and lost sight of the scene for a moment. Then, he heard a gun go Off.

 He ran home and told his sister to call the police."

And:

"The witnesses say they are coming forward now, because they were shocked when no arrest was made.

 "To me what happened here is that a grown man got whooped by a 17-year-old, and he was not afraid, but angry," said the woman who heard from inside her house."

That's what the witnesses say.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6h08n3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/4847</id></website><link>http://www.therightscoop.com/abc-news-surveillance-video-shows-no-blood-or-bruises-on-george-zimmerman/</link><postedTime>2012-03-29T01:30:37+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T06:36:20+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ys3u</id><link>http://www.therightscoop.com/abc-news-surveillance-video-shows-no-blood-or-bruises-on-george-zimmerman/#comment-479153147</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cumjf</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-29</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>