<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkna9z/post/2012-03-26T03:25:54</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi3ywh</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ewmvj</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>

Hello Nic. 


1.      
The natural cooling of the water can be modelled
using Newton’s law. I took a different approach by making use of actual
measurements performed by Bosman, Grobler and Dalgleish at the North West
University. Through simple regression analysis they derived straight line equations
of losses versus water-to-ambient temperature difference. Their equations are
useful because data was gathered from many systems at different temperatures,
both with and without insulation. I could then set up a time series where I
assumed straight line cooling over each one minute interval. One minute
intervals are short enough to still capture the exponential nature of cooling
without introducing much error.


2.      
I made use of the specific Heat of water and the
power rating of the geyser throughout my calculations. These are not shown in
order to keep the complexity of the presentation within everyone’s Reach. 


All Kwikot geysers have power ratings matched
to the cylinder capacity, so that, as I have mentioned, water temperature will
rise by 17ºC per hour.
This is a rule of thumb for those that need to know how long before their water
is warm. This number was never used in any of the calculations, instead it was
derived from the calculations.


</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6mqtsp</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zzkq</id></website><link>http://www.moneyweb.co.za/mw/view/mw/en/page292681?oid=564803&amp;sn=2009+Detail&amp;pid=287226</link><postedTime>2012-03-20T03:45:19+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-26T07:25:54+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mkna9z</id><link>http://www.moneyweb.co.za/mw/view/mw/en/page292681?oid=564803&amp;sn=2009+Detail&amp;pid=287226#comment-476266694</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>