<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwvkfu/update/2012-03-30T16:22:36/7f7d1bc754a69c36ebbd9e21288dd1819b8e7a20b8322890961bcd3867515455</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwvlgf</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Unfortunately, their opinions do matter because they can make and break careers. If they don't come on board where he's concerned, then they will critically bury him for the rest of his career and write him  as a light weight pretty boy whose only audience is quivering females. That is harsh and insulting, but this is what the PERCEPTION of him will continue to be. This perception of him has blinded them to his other performances but now that perception is starting to change and it's got to because it's his ONLY way out of critical annilation. And if the perception doesn't change, it will alter the course of his career because he'll stop being considered for the best roles. I use that word 'perception' a lot because that's what human beings do...we 'perceive'. And unfortunately, 'truth' doesn't  have much of a say here because perception will beat the shit out of truth any day of the week. 

This reminds me of Jessica Lange. Back in the mid seventies, she was labeled as a wooden model trying to  with absolutely no ability. Her reviews were BRUTAL! But she hung in there for about five years. Then Jack Nicholson and Bob Rafelson took a chance on her and handed her the role of Cora in the remake of The Postman  Rings Twice and the critics woke up. The next year she gave the greatest performance of her career in Francis which unfortuately came out the same year Meryl Streep gave her greatest performance in Sophie's Choice. Meryl won the Oscar, but Jessica was nominated for Best Actress and they gave her one anyway for Best Supporting for Tootsie (cos they had to give her something) and that was IT! From then to now she was/is heraled as one of the greatest actresses of her generation. She was  good but the critics just didn't see it because she wasn't getting the roles that displayed her talent or working with the directors who could draw those performances out of her. But once she did, she was Off and running.

The critics despise Twilight and sneer at his performance of Edward Cullen, for the most part because they do not understand the character. But they don't care about 'book' Edward and what depth of character may be found in those pages. They only care about what they see up on the big screen. THIS is what they are judging. And what they saw, they pretty much unanimously, didn't like.  Hell, even some of it's ardent fans have a lot of problems with these movies because they weren't executed properly. And lets be honest, for many, our 'perceptions' about Edward, about Rob helped to sway our opinins when watching these films too. Not for all, as some just stumbled onto them Cold turkey not knowing anything before hand or even having a negative opinion of it all. But once they saw Rob and fell for him, feelings and 'perceptions' changed. 

As much as this grates (because they didn't see all along what we saw), he NEEDS this critical validation. We should stop thinking about our feelings here and try to imagine what his might be because of the early reception he's getting for this film. I would imagine he's feeling a little bit of relief because believe me, he's been scared that Twilight was going to bury him so deep that he'd never be taken seriously. And yeah, maybe he's feeling a different kind of fear right now that he won't be able to meet these newfound expectations. But better to fear that than to be dismissed as insignificant. All actors want respect for their talent and though he may have never shown it, he's been scared that respect was going to elude him. I know actors, their insecurities and how they think. Trust me on this one.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6761ae</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/djgv</id></website><link>http://www.robsessedpattinson.com/2012/03/positive-reactions-for-robert-pattinson.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T18:23:35+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T20:22:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwvkfu</id><link>http://www.robsessedpattinson.com/2012/03/positive-reactions-for-robert-pattinson.html#comment-481157771</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8yswf</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>