<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mcl5ld/update/2012-02-03T15:35:09/71ef4120991bb748829643d799047efd0f044b2d945a8a146f6a33447638d179</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The content of comedy isn't about what's right or wrong, it's about where it comes from. If you're making derogatory and negative remarks with intent to be malicious, then that's malicious. If you're saying or presenting something with good intent, to make people laugh, then it's not malicious. There are seven billion people in the world, everything is going to offend someone. Twilight saying 'egghead' is going to offend someone. Dash and AJ quarrelling is going to offend someone. The fact that the FiM doesn't conform to Christian ideologies offends some people, you can read about that here; http://www.cuttingedge.org/ce1021.html Do a Ctrl+F and search for My Little Pony.


If people didn't say things that offend at least one person, comedy wouldn't exist. Friendship is Magic wouldn't be around, Seinfeld wouldn't have been made, The Office wouldn't exist, Friends wouldn't have made it past one season.

From my perspective, this 'Derpy Hooves' debacle is dividing an already segregated community. The 'brony' movement came in and said 'My Little Pony? This is ours now', and all the collectors and fans of the show prior to 2010 were left behind, their hobby was taken from them. The 'brony' contingent is also dividing the new wave of fans between male and female fans. The definition of 'brony' changes based the argument. If someone says the term excludes women, it suddenly becomes a gender neutral idiom. If you ask them what it means, without the context of it being sexist, it defines a male fan of the show. The popular argument is 'well dude and man are gender specific!', I disagree. Over the decades 'dude' and 'man' have become interchangable exclamations. 'Come on, man!', or 'Come on, dude!', they're used for emphasis, not to dictate gender. When used contextually, they're exclamations, not gender denominators. 'Brony' is a term conjugated to define a male fan of the show, that's where it started, and Depending on your opinion of the word, that's what it is. 

Where does that leave female fans? If you don't have a Y chromosome, you don't have the key to the 'brony' side of the community. Unless you're saying that it is an excluding term, in which case it isn't. The community is divided, and this isn't helping. The 'bronies' will tell you that the movement is tearing down the walls of assumed gender roles. It's doing the opposite. If they wanted to tear down assumed gender roles, they'd have no problem saying 'I'm a guy, I like playing with doll hair', but you can't say that, that isn't cool, that's not socially acceptable. Affix the 'brony' label, and suddenly it's cool. They're saying 'we need a shield to protect ourselves from the fact that we like to buy and collect what are ostensibly dolls. Also, women aren't allowed'. That does nothing gender stereotyping or gender equality. It enforces the typical white male attitude of 'it's not valid until a white guy says it', and the stereotype that men take what they want, and Burn the ground behind them.

The worst thing about this 'Derpy' situation, and the 'brony' community is that they're wholly overlooking the best part of the show. Friendship is Magic is aimed at young girls, probably 6-12, and those are very, very formative years. I hope that somewhere out there, there's a young girl who's watching Friendship is Magic who's booksmart, shy, abrasive, into fashion, or thoroughly exuberant (in the case of Pinkie Pie), and it inspires them to think 'it's okay to be the way I am'. We live in a society that tells young girls 'you're princesses and homemakers', that's what's presented to the pre-adolescence female populace. Look at the toys, music, and programs offered to that age group, they do noting to tear own gender barriers, they reinforce them. Friendship is Magic turns that on it's head. All of the characters are unique and interesting for a variety of reasons. None of them fall into the 'pink and pretty' mold. Rarity could have, but rather than her being stuck up and doting on her appearance (which she admitted is and does), that's not her character. She's a successful business owner, and an artist. That's her character.

The community is screwed. It's not going to go back to normalcy until the Friendship is Magic fad dies down. My advise is to do your best to avoid it till then.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yr7gga</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/4la2</id></website><link>http://www.mylittleponynews.com/2012/02/derpy-hooves-controversy.html</link><postedTime>2012-02-03T20:00:24+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-02-03T20:35:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mcl5ld</id><link>http://www.mylittleponynews.com/2012/02/derpy-hooves-controversy.html#comment-428867576</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-03</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>