<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/midk1t/post/2012-03-22T19:44:59</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Oh god, so much of this was me. SO MUCH. I started smoking at twelve and fell in love instantly. By 13 I was a smoker and by 16 I was smoking about 15-20 a day. My mum was NOT cool with it until I turned 18, when she realised she couldn't stop me. I smoked at all times: drinking, in the car, after food, after, before and often during sex. I would be halfway through a ciggarette and I'd think about lighting another. One cigarette at a time was not enough for me. Having a conversation was another big instigator of my smoking. Or being on the phone. I loved to chainsmoke and talk.

I loved, loved, loved smoking. It was a part of me, you know. I was miss_dot and I smoked. A lot. Those were the two most true things about me. 

But... At the age of 26 I started getting Chest pains. Bad ones. I would get Puffed rolling over in bed. I couldn't exercise at all. I could see where it was taking me and if I kept at it, how it was going to kill me. I was 26 and I KNEW smoking was going to kill me.

So I started trying to quit then, and after a few disaterous attempts, I am now (about to be) 30 and I have  been free of that nasty shit for 7 months. In that time I have lost 14 kilos and become addicted to kickboxing. I replaced one addiction with another, but this one is a good one. Now, whenever I feel the slight creeping of a craving, I think, 'do I want to be a well-muscled Muay Thai machine, or do I want to smoke?' The answer is pretty easy for me.

I quit Cold turkey. It's the best way for me. I also read the quit smoking bible: Allen Carr's Easy Way to Quit Smoking. I credit that book with saving my life, really.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yxvp2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tdqu</id></website><link>http://www.xojane.com/healthy/my-love-affair-smoking-and-why-we-re-breaking</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T15:49:24+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T23:44:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/midk1t</id><link>http://www.xojane.com/healthy/my-love-affair-smoking-and-why-we-re-breaking#comment-474066017</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/gqly3</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>