<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/240793/post/72702815/comment/328268418</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>about July 31,michael kors, 15 ,chaussures louboutin, Morning News ,coach outlet stores, the angel river tourist attractions in Yuexi County dump heavy rain ,franklin marshal, thunder and lightning ,coach outlet store online, the scenic rubber dinghy drifting terminal side of a man ashore when ,mercurial vapor, struck by lightning ,lunettes de soleil chanel, was killed. Yuexi County the iris town a storage villager surnamed ,adidas f50, the lightning struck a body fat than young men . time of the incident ,michael kors handbags on sale, the villagers went to the river shore participated in the rescue,chaussure de foot, according to him,herve leger, a few villagers saw someone being struck by lightning ,lunettes de soleil ray , quickly ran over this man was carried to the stone . let the control out of the water in the stomach lying on the floor ,michael kors outlet, but the man had stopped breathing . It is understood that the incident of this river of Anhui angel river tourism has developed rubber dinghy drifting project areas ,franklin marshall pas cher, scenic areas belong to the state 2A level scenic Spots . At present ,coach outlet, the scenic area is still normal for business. After the incident,louboutin pas cher, Yuexi County Tourism Bureau sent field investigation found that the man was struck by lightning killed the the Chaohu membership tourists,herve leger dress, who just turned 20 years old this year . At present,mercurial vapor pas cher, the family of the deceased has been Reached with the travel company financial compensation agreement . Related articles&amp;#65306; the evening of June 1 and then decide when to stop this practice . he has been severe insomnia. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:240793:72702815</id><idPostId>72702815</idPostId><idBlogId>240793</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:240793</id><idBlogId>240793</idBlogId><link>http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com</link><displayName>Are You Healthy?  Are You Happy?</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com/2011/01/26/do-you-have-the-post-holiday-blues-happiness-how-to-get-it/</link><displayName>Do you have the Post Holiday Blues?  Happiness:  How to get it.</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:48:32.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:240793:72702815:328268418</id><inReplyTo><link>http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com/2011/01/26/do-you-have-the-post-holiday-blues-happiness-how-to-get-it/#IDComment125967655</link></inReplyTo><link>http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com/2011/01/26/do-you-have-the-post-holiday-blues-happiness-how-to-get-it/#IDComment328268418</link><postedTime>2012-03-31T04:48:32.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Do you have the Post Holiday Blues?  Happiness:  How to get it. by ia2z5m168q</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://coachoutlet-handbager.com</link><idEmailMd5>eb2ba209b589b8a8346ff03e880fa070</idEmailMd5><displayName>ia2z5m168q</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://coachoutlet-handbager.com"&gt;ia2z5m168q&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com/2011/01/26/do-you-have-the-post-holiday-blues-happiness-how-to-get-it/"&gt;Do you have the Post Holiday Blues?  Happiness:  How to get it.&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>