<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms73ls/delete/2012-03-27T16:40:19</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Some of you are killing me with your comments.  As I sit here at my desk at a river grain elevator.  Farmers pay property taxes in each county, which if you look goes towards our township's road work.  The DOT numbers go to the state, where that is for state road work.  Which is more then ever for overpasses, bridge work, and interstates.  The pot holes and chucks out of the road, are more from the Cold weather climate that rural central america is in.  Not from a tractor/combine/ or grain truck.  No I'm not saying that the farmer does no wrong.  Trust me, I know some that do.  But the majority of my farmer customers, are the nicest, helpful, caring people you will ever meet.  What this is... giving each farmer/tenant/landlord a required DOT number is just a way for the state to get more money, (which really, more then likely won't go towards the debt it has made for it's self)  

When a farmer comes into the elevator, he splits his load with a landlord, a old lady who has lived out in her house for 60 years, with her husband passing away 2 years ago, and that is her income.  To not let that farmer haul for that land owner under that land owner's name caused huge problems.  Then you say why don't the farmer and land owner get thier own DOT numbers and changed them out when in a different field.... well I'm sure that's a whole other can of worms I could open.

It comes down to this.... we can take america's heartland that supplies america and many other countries give them a set of rules, that makes it harder on not only the farmer but the old lady landlord, the grain elevator and thier paper work.... and on and on.... and maybe just MAYBE with that money the state will fix your pothole you drive over every year fixed.... or we can take away all farm vechiles and go back to horse plows.  

this makes me think of OSHA coming in and saying do this do that, they parent making the kid put on helmets and pads to ride the bike, for the government to say what you can and can not do.  When does it stop, when is there freedom.... to be a good hardworking american, that can go home with some pay Off?  Am I right or am I wrong? </body><verb>delete</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/eehz52</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q905</id></website><link>http://patdollard.com/2011/07/dot-to-mandate-all-farm-vehicles-require-cdl-licenses-could-bring-demise-to-farmers/</link><postedTime>2011-07-31T18:01:14+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-27T20:40:19+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/ms73ls</id><link>http://patdollard.com/2011/07/dot-to-mandate-all-farm-vehicles-require-cdl-licenses-could-bring-demise-to-farmers/#comment-477754016</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>killed</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-07-31</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>