<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xy95/post/2012-03-29T13:38:13</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>In his version of events, George Zimmerman had turned around and was walking back to his SUV when Trayvon approached him from behind, the two exchanged words then Trayvon punched him in the nose, sending him to the ground, and began beating him. Lie number 1! why would the 911 operator ask Zimmerman if he were following the so called suspect. He said "they" Always get away with everything" that was probable cause right there. 2nd If that was the case how come they were found buildings away from where his truck was????? On the phone with the operator before Zimmerman started to pursue him,  He told the operator that  the so called suspect was coming towards him, that he was coming to check him out. Nothing was recorded being said to Zimmerman by Martin or it would have been recorded. Just like his racist remark was at that time. All Trayvon Martin was doing was trying to get home. If Trayvon wanted to start a fight with Zimmerman, he would have started it in front of the clubhouse where he made the first call.  Zimmerman began to follow Martin and Martin tried to get away. When Trayvon Martin thought that he was home free,out pops Zimmerman mad that Martin ran. He took out his gun and shot this child in Cold blood. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6laffg</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/tz1k</id></website><link>http://www.mediaite.com/online/george-zimmermans-police-report-trayvon-martin-approached-him-from-behind-bashed-his-head-against-sidewalk/</link><postedTime>2012-03-26T17:43:05+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T17:38:13+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3xy95</id><link>http://www.mediaite.com/online/george-zimmermans-police-report-trayvon-martin-approached-him-from-behind-bashed-his-head-against-sidewalk/#comment-479682940</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zz6kc</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-26</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>