<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3srdm/post/2012-03-29T23:24:35</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Greta, how about you do a story on lawyers' bill nightmares? Worthless lawyers don't do anything productive in life and charge everyone hefty retainer fee and clients only get 50% chance of winning. 
Stomach ache is a hindsight diagnosis, which is 20/20. You do get this idea????? It was determined as a non-threating disease AFTER the necessary the tests. If all you sefl-rightous journalists/ lawyers/patients/bloggers can diagnose stomachache as a simple stoamache, not appendicitis, not enteritis, not bowel obstruction, without tests, then go ahead and open your own ER  and do everything by looking and touching, examining without any IV, radiology works, labs and bill patients cheaply. Let's see how many people you will KILL!!!! Doctors work their butts Off to save any Tom, Harry, Dick and after these ungrateful people get well, they complaint about their cost. Like after you get full and complaint that the foods are too expensive. Doctors should get smart and post their prices and have patients pay before they get treated!!!!. PATHETIC News piece. Last time I am watching your show. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6zotaf</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t33k</id></website><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/have-you-had-any-medical-bill-nightmares/</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T02:45:56+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T03:24:35+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3srdm</id><link>http://gretawire.foxnewsinsider.com/open-thread/have-you-had-any-medical-bill-nightmares/#comment-480198103</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>