<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34kz6/post/2012-03-29T11:20:21</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The first time I heard Fall Out Boy I was already into my 30's so neither "needed" their music as a form of escape or anything else quite so revelatory. I also wasn't particularly a fan of the music that they often got herded into (emo, indie, punk, etc) - I simply thought it was great music with some killer melodies, clever lyrics sung by a guy with a fantastic voice. Then again I went on to adore Infinity on High &amp; Folie a Deux so according the so-called music press I know nothing. That is where they are wrong however. I've been a huge Michael Jackson fan since a kid &amp; until he tragically passed away, found myself arguing with those-who-know-best telling me that the only decent thing he did was some early Motown stuff, Off the Wall &amp; Thriller. Now it's a different story, the world realised his talent but too late to "save him" - back before 2009 to say you were an MJJ fan was to label yourself a freak, post-2009 it appears that actually, just about everyone was a massive Michael Jackson fan after all - hmmm. I guess what I'm saying is that it's not about nostalgia to me, just like it was never about liking the flavour-of-the-month when they first hit it big, Fall Out Boy &amp; Patrick Stump simply made some bloody brilliant music.

One final thing however - they didn't perform Coffee's for Closer's or 20 Dollar Nose Bleed at the gig to support the final album &amp; I'm stilll not happy about it. I have unfinished business with Messrs Stump, Wentz, Trohman &amp; Hurley ...</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/you08x</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6hqk</id></website><link>http://www.underthegunreview.net/2012/02/28/editorial-the-cure-to-growing-older-a-musical-retrospective/</link><postedTime>2012-02-28T15:21:53+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T15:20:21+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m34kz6</id><link>http://www.underthegunreview.net/2012/02/28/editorial-the-cure-to-growing-older-a-musical-retrospective/#comment-479571058</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-28</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>