<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ohmx/post/2012-03-29T19:20:03</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/msa8bf</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zrhe7</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>&lt;b&gt;Dean Corso&lt;/b&gt;, from &lt;i&gt;The Ninth Gate&lt;/i&gt;. A morally conflicted collector of rare books, he underwent something of an encounter that changed him...some say it was with the Devil itself. All Dean ever says is "It was about a woman." Rumored to be immortal, he just looks a bit skeevy.  He's recently been employed by the mysterious and independently wealthy Adrian Veidt to seek out and assemble a colorful group of very fringe, very private figures with their own ambiguous ties to the supernatural world. Corso complains to himself "I don't know what Veidt wants me for. My only experience is with fictional characters."

&lt;b&gt;Hellboy&lt;/b&gt;, from &lt;i&gt;Hellboy&lt;/i&gt;. (the movie version). The League's not-so- weapon is the son of the Devil, an inhuman brawler with a dry sense of humor and a gentle soul.  His sense of right and wrong used to be clear, until his friends at BPRD were murdered and any mention of their existence erased. Now he can't help but wonder who this new group he's  himself with is actually working for.

&lt;b&gt;Hanna&lt;/b&gt; from &lt;i&gt;Hanna&lt;/i&gt;. a quiet, soulful 16 year old killing machine. She wanted to hide from civilization, but Veidt finds her everywhere she turns up. Raised in isolation by her father, she worries that she'll never really be able to understand the humans (and monsters) that make up the rest of the group. For their part, they worry that her violent instincts can't truly be controlled.

&lt;b&gt;Mike Newton and Jessica Stanley&lt;/b&gt;, from &lt;i&gt;Twilight&lt;/i&gt;. The only survivors of the Vampire/Werewolf wars that have ravaged the rural northwestern United States. They're ordinary humans, at times petty and prone to squabbling. But only they've seen first hand the real stakes of the supernatural divide. Humans are evolving into what may seem to outsiders to be monsters, but are in fact the next stages of a new race, one that can survive environmental disasters and even nuclear fallout. They've seen how powerful and seductive these new forms are, and yet they also strip us of our humanity, our decency. They are the keepers of the  choice that will soon face the whole Earth: To survive, to become, or to stand our ground and accept possible extinction in the name of preserving everything humans have accomplished.

&lt;b&gt;A revolving Spot&lt;/b&gt; for characters who are inevitably killed or quit within a mission or two. &lt;i&gt;Includes:&lt;/i&gt; &lt;b&gt;Britta Perry&lt;/b&gt; from &lt;i&gt;Community&lt;/i&gt;, who changed her mind after accidentally wrecking much of the training room during her first exercise (and it was a written exercise). &lt;b&gt;Dr. Paul Weston&lt;/b&gt; from &lt;i&gt;In Treatment&lt;/i&gt;, who after nine weeks of intently psychoanalysing the other members of the group, talked himself out of taking the job. Whether he helped anyone else is a matter of some debate. &lt;b&gt;CM Punk&lt;/b&gt; from &lt;i&gt;WWE Wrestling&lt;/i&gt;, who was found with an arrow through his chest after attempting to molest Hanna. &lt;b&gt;Gene Parmesean&lt;/b&gt;, from &lt;i&gt;Arrested Development&lt;/i&gt;. This master of disguise was far from the best P.I., but was just beginning to settle in when he disguised himself as a garbage can that was being used as a target for one of Veidt's missle tests. Spot ultimately to be filled by a good character from something by Dom Delillo, or maybe Terry Pratchett or Thomas Pynchon. I dunno, I need to read more.

&lt;b&gt;Henrietta the Giant Chicken&lt;/b&gt; from &lt;i&gt;The Hoboken Chicken Emergency&lt;/i&gt;. A well meaning but petulant 266 lb. chicken. Gets along well with Hanna, who keeps her as kind of a pet. But her relationship with Hellboy is somewhat more competitive.

--&lt;b&gt;Assorted Allies &amp; Enemies&lt;/b&gt;--

&lt;b&gt;Adrian Veidt&lt;/b&gt; from &lt;i&gt;Watchmen&lt;/i&gt;. The wealthy, prominent businessman is the creator and benefactor of this new League. He seems friendly and charming, but none of the group really trusts him. For one thing, he refuses to tell them what their endgame really is. Much less his past as superhero &lt;b&gt;Ozymandis&lt;/b&gt;, or how much of the world he really owns, or plans to own in his lifelong obsessive quest to save humanity from itself.

&lt;b&gt;Kalinda Sharma&lt;/b&gt; from &lt;i&gt;The Good Wife&lt;/i&gt;. The real best Private Investigator money can buy, Veidt employs her anytime he needs to find something out quickly and quietly. She co-exists with the League, although she treats them somewhat condescendingly. Publicly, she insists she doesn't believe in monsters. Privately, she may be playing a double game, searching for something even Veidt can't give her...eternal life.

&lt;b&gt;Olivia Dunham&lt;/b&gt; from &lt;i&gt;Fringe&lt;/i&gt; (Season 1, for the freckles and general cuteness). An FBI agent who's developed a singleminded fixation on supernatural activity. She Always seems one step behind The League, unable to prove for certain they exist. How long will it take her to piece together what's really happening to our world, and will it be too late?

&lt;b&gt;The Devil&lt;/b&gt; from &lt;i&gt;The potholes in my lawn, various&lt;/i&gt;. They say the greatest trick The Devil ever played was convincing the world he didn't exist. But maybe Adrian Veidt's greatest trick was convincing the world that he did.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ddu6z2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/t3dj</id></website><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/regional-holiday-music,66270/</link><postedTime>2011-12-09T01:30:33+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-29T23:20:03+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m3ohmx</id><link>http://www.avclub.com/articles/regional-holiday-music,66270/#comment-480014049</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dp232</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-12-09</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>