<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/323728/post/127796007/comment/327537063</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>So much to say on this post--what Burns my ass is that in VA there is the &amp;quot;DARE&amp;quot; program funded by local/state/federal govts &amp;amp; maintained by county Sheriffs Depts that goes into schools to educate students on the dangers of drug usage. Part of that is that they show the kids drugs, and encourage them to do projects where they draw anti-drug posters that are on display in the front Halls of the school. I&amp;#039;ve seen ones with plastic bags of powder, oregano or dried fall leaves, and other paraphernalia meant to resemble the real thing. Also present in VA schools is the PRIDE program, where students join &amp;amp; preach to other students &amp;amp; encourage them to remain drug free. Then they go to rock concerts and get high as hell. Fun little gem of info on that.&#13; 
&#13; 
One of the most bullshit laws on the books in most states &amp;amp; on the Federal level is the change of &amp;quot;intent to distribute&amp;quot; which is determined based on a measurement of drugs found upon the person or in the possession of the individual charged with the crime. I maintain that &amp;quot;intent&amp;quot; cannot be prosecuted, there is no way to try &amp;amp; convict people based on what YOU think THEY ARE THINKING. It&amp;#039;s ridiculous, but it&amp;#039;s been going on for years. Rather than toughen the penalties on possession, they use this one to amp up the jail time or the fine, and in some states the level of the penal code (misdemeanor usually, but in this state above a certain level puts you at a class one felony potentially)&#13; 
&#13; 
I&amp;#039;m rapidly leaning Libertarian on this issue. Much to my family&amp;#039;s chagrin, I&amp;#039;ve come to understand the the &amp;quot;War on drugs&amp;quot; is a crock. At this point, we&amp;#039;ve got a Fed govt that manufactures drugs and yet assumes the responsibility of punishing citizens for the same? Insanity that is currently reigning supreme. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:323728:127796007</id><idPostId>127796007</idPostId><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:323728</id><idBlogId>323728</idBlogId><link>http://www.chrisisright.net</link><displayName>Chris Is RIGHT</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/03/18/red-eye-schools-zero-tolerance-drug-policy-is-laughable-free-the-mrs-dash/</link><displayName>Red Eye: School\'s Zero Tolerance Drug Policy is Laughable: Free the Mrs. Dash!</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-03-22T16:55:26.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:323728:127796007:327537063</id><link>http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/03/18/red-eye-schools-zero-tolerance-drug-policy-is-laughable-free-the-mrs-dash/#IDComment327537063</link><postedTime>2011-03-22T16:55:26.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Red Eye: School\'s Zero Tolerance Drug Policy is Laughable: Free the Mrs. Dash! by The Eye</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>3b7d10ec84201f372ad5f4bd5e6e0640</idEmailMd5><displayName>The Eye</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>The Eye commented on &lt;a href="http://www.chrisisright.net/2011/03/18/red-eye-schools-zero-tolerance-drug-policy-is-laughable-free-the-mrs-dash/"&gt;Red Eye: School\'s Zero Tolerance Drug Policy is Laughable: Free the Mrs. Dash!&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2011-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>