<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwqcn7/update/2012-03-30T18:14:35/6a8c41b06100f405479915bb97f8ef957d69bd31a6fddce35e6715f6989505aa</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Shakers, I'm a bit shaken up tonight.

Today I had a conversation at work with someone I feel very uncomfortable with. He is not a safe person. I do my best to avoid him, which is usually pretty easy because he works in a department on the other side of the building (I also de-friended and blocked him on Facebook), but we happened to be on break at the same time today. I tried to avoid him but somehow he tracked me down and kind of cornered me into a conversation I didn't want to have. He said some derogatory things about a friend of mine that he used to be friends with. I feel bad for not defending my friend but all I could think about was how to get away from this guy. Fortunately a friend I hadn't seen in a while stopped to say hi and I was able to make up an excuse to leave. I'm so mad at myself for not doing a good enough job of avoiding this person and also for not defending my friend. All I could think about was how to get out of this situation with as little trouble as possible. On top of that, today was just an awful day at work. All I could think about today was having a Cold drink and taking a nap. I get three days Off in a row next week, which has never happened since I've been at that job. I hope I can make it until then.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/677d5k</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ync</id></website><link>http://shakespearessister.blogspot.com/2012/03/virtual-pub-is-open_30.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-30T22:01:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-30T22:14:35+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mwqcn7</id><link>http://shakespearessister.blogspot.com/2012/03/virtual-pub-is-open_30.html#comment-481261263</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dxr9</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-30</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>