<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi5z1o/post/2012-03-22T15:13:17</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp17lg</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lm4bg</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>With all do respect, I am being realistic. I am not sure how long it has been since you have been in high school, but with the image that girls feel they need to keep up, they do not want to get sweaty or wet and mess up their hair or makeup. And childhood obesity is not a stretch. Study Hall as an alternative is a joke. It's a free nap. Walking the stairs is actually a really healthy, lo impact alternative activity to swimming. If your kid chooses not to get in the pool, male or female, and they do not have a doctor's note then the very LEAST they can do is walk the bleachers. No one is asking them to run or be timed. I bring up the boys purely because this father says his daughter is singled out. Boys walk the bleachers too, they just have a higher participation rate in the pool (fact, not assumption). If a girl is really feeling that poorly because she has cramps, go lie down at the nurse. If not, a tampon will suffice for the 30-30 minutes that she is actually in the water. Also, blood in the pool is no comparison to the amount of chlorine in that pool (fact). When I pulled a diver out who was Bleeding from her head, I called my doctor and they said there was absolutely no risk of blood borne illness because of the chlorine content.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6mvpvq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/9tev</id></website><link>http://www.thereporteronline.com/article/20120319/NEWS01/120319648/father-of-nphs-student-says-gym-teacher-singles-out-girls&amp;pager=full_story</link><postedTime>2012-03-20T01:00:50+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T19:13:17+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi5z1o</id><link>http://www.thereporteronline.com/article/20120319/NEWS01/120319648/father-of-nphs-student-says-gym-teacher-singles-out-girls&amp;pager=full_story#comment-473857372</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zgq9q</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>