<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mic0yj/post/2012-03-22T14:46:28</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>While I don't believe that the D will be "there yet" in '12 ... I also anticipate that it will be better than Jon seems to suggest.

We had much the same cast running the D in '10 ... and that was with a D that contended with a good number of injuries in the back 7, particularly at LB.  All the same, that D was still statistically among the top Ds in the nation ... and that was even with the Big 10 featuring some truly impressive quarterbacks.

The above point being that while the D will different now that it's "officially" Phil's defense ... it's still the Iowa D.  The immediate implication being that Ferentz will not skimp when it comes to placing emphasis on the D-side of the ball.

If you look at the experience and the talent that Iowa has at LB, I think that we're going to observe continued improvement there.  I liked what I saw out of Alston and Collins last year ... and I heard good things about Fisher too.  When you add those guys to the projected starters ... that's a recipe for some great competition!  And contrary to what some fans seem to think ... Morris and Kirksey are BOTH pretty darn impressive players!  Hitchens has shown flashes, but I need to see better consistency out of him.  All the same, each of Iowa's projected starters at LB have seen a lot of action.

In the secondary, I think that Iowa has a great mix of experience, talent, and potential.  I really like Hyde and Lowery at CB ... and I think that we'll see Lomax and some of the young guys contribute.  I really like Miller and Law at S ... and I think that we'll see Lowdermilk and some of the young guys contribute.  As new guys go ... I really like what Lile and Gair bring to the table ... and it will be interesting to see how far Flemming is along with his rehab.  Regardless, Iowa has talent in the secondary and I don't think that Phil Parker will hesitate to use that talent.

And, of course, there is Iowa's DL.  What I think that many Iowa fans seem to fail to recognize is that many factors really contributed to undermining the Iowa DL in '11.  First , Coach K taught the guys how to play the right way ... however, given how his style of coaching contrasts with the other Iowa coaches, it doesn't take much to figure out why the DL had trouble finding that extra bit of motivation toward the end of the game.  Now Coach K is gone and the Iowa DL is going to benefit from an exceptional teacher who will help bring them together as a group ... and that will make it that much easier for them to find inspiration and motivation from each-other.  Also, the DL was hit hard be injuries even before the season began ... and that really seriously hurt them before they even had a chance to come together as a group.  Then, once the season started, the only regular starter who wasn't battling against injury was Binns.  Nardo missed games due to injury, Daniels wasn't as productive due to his injuries, Alvis had a season-ending injury, Daniel fought through a few injuries, and Davis was never really able to even get started due to his injury issues.  While injuries are certainly a part of the game, the degree to which they struck the DL, when coupled to Iowa's lack of depth at the Spot, goes a long way to explaining why Iowa's D had some of the issues that they had.

When you look to the '12 installment of the Iowa DL, there are definitely tons of questions that need to get answered.  However, provided that Alvis and Davis successfully return from injury ... I think that Bigach, Alvis, Davis, and Gaglione provide the Iowa DL with solid foundations.  Gaglione won't be a starter ... but I'm willing to bet that he'll be just as much of a contributor as Follet was in '05.  It's Always important when a veteran guy can come in and provide the group with quality reps.  Similarly, whether Carl Davis can elevate his game enough or stay healthy enough to be a starter remains to be seen ... he should also be able to provide the DL with a guy who can be a positive contributor.  Bigach and Alvis and definitely guys who are both likely starters, assuming that Alvis successfully rehabs.  Those guys may not necessarily be flashy ... but they're capable of being every-down starters for us.  Heck, given what has been said about Alvis ... should he remain healthy over the next two years ... he might just yet prove to be "flashy."  Lastly, I think that there's plenty to be excited about when you look at the promise/potential of guys like McMinn, Cooper, J. Johnson, and Ekakatie.

Given the combination of talent and experience of the guys that Iowa has on the DL, if the group can enjoy a little luck when it comes to injury ... I really don't see it being all that hard for the '12 DL to enjoy more productivity than the '11 DL.  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6diwt7</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7065</id></website><link>http://www.hawkeyenation.com/football/first-look-2012-football-season</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T15:48:23+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T18:46:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mic0yj</id><link>http://www.hawkeyenation.com/football/first-look-2012-football-season#comment-473837391</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>