<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpkzpn/update/2012-03-22T04:26:52/5cda86c2c0c885d99a3b14a1223f1d4fb3dd578a6b3e63dd7f91d61c2b93ef41</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>HEY "chauncey devega, Failed Polemicist"!

Why don't you write an article about THIS STORY??!!!?

Why are you "progressive journalists" TOTALLY IGNORING THIS HORRIBLE CRIME of MURDER and SEXUAL ASSAULT committed against ELDERLY PEOPLE, which is much more horrible and violent that the Trayvon story (tragic as it is)? 

WHY ARE YOU IGNORING THIS STORY, "chauncey devaga"?    Why don't you EVER write an article about the MUCH MORE COMMON BLACK-AGAINST-ELDERLY WHITE ATTACKS THAT TAKE PLACE MULTIPLE TIMES EVERY WEEK IN THE USA?

I guess it just doesn't fit in with your hate-whitey narrative.

Brutal Home-Invasion Ends 65-Year Romance
March 20, 2012


Couple met and married within a month and stayed together for 65 years... only to be parted after home invader beat wife to death


Nancy Strait, 85, was sexually assaulted and battered to death by 
burglarHer husband Bob, 90, suffered a broken jaw and broken ribs in 
attackPolice have arrested 20-year-old Tyrone Dale David Woodfork


An 85-year-old woman was sexually assaulted and battered to death by a
 home invader who also shot her  90-year-old husband in the face with a 
BB gun.


Nancy and Bob Strait, who had celebrated their 65th wedding 
anniversary in December, were discovered by their daughter at their home
 in Tulsa,  Oklahoma. Both the pensioners were rushed to hospital where 
Mrs Strait, who was nearly blind, died from her injuries.


Mr Strait, who served in the 101st  Division in World War II,
 suffered a broken jaw, broken ribs and severe Bleeding. He is in a 
serious condition in hospital.


Police have arrested 20-year-old Tyrone Dale David Woodfork in connection with the case. The
 Straits' distraught family today paid tribute to the pair, who grew up 
in poverty in rural Oklahoma during the Great Depression.


They met each other on a blind date on Thanksgiving 1946, married a 
month later and went on to have six children, 18 grandchildren and about
 50 great and great-great grandchildren. They hadrecently welcomed a 
great-great-great grandchild.


Their daughters Lanora and Andra told Tulsa World that the couple 
were loving and generous people who would do anything for anyone.


'Dad never talked, and Mama never quit talking,' Lanora said. 'Whatever
 she did, it came from the heart,' Andra added. The pair could be found 
sitting on their porch singing and playing the guitar during warmer 
summer evenings. Mr Strait, who had worked for the oil derrick 
supply company Lee C. Moore before retirement, enjoyed woodwork while 
his wife loved making quilts and baking. They had both been struggling 
with health problems before the attack. Mr Strait had been diagnosed 
with a terminal kidney illness but had outlived the doctor's prognosis.


'He was living because Mother was alive,' Andra told Tulsa World.


The couple had had food poisoning the week before the attack.


'There is no one else who has been through what he's been through who is stillalive,' Lanora said of her father.


'We pray he doesn't remember.'


Tulsa police believe burglars broke into the Straits' home either 
late Tuesday or early Wednesday last week. They were not found until the
 Wednesday evening. 


The home invaders made Off with their Dodge Neon, a television and $200. 


Woodfork was later found hiding in a nearby house after a witness Spotted the stolen vehicle being driven down the road.


He is being held at Tulsa Jail without bail accused of first-degree 
murder, burglary, assault with a dangerous weapon and two counts of 
armed robbery. 


'This investigation is far from over,' Officer Jason Willingham of 
the Tulsa police department told Tulsa World. 'We've still got a lot of 
questions that we still need answered.'


Mrs Strait's funeral will be on Friday. The family has set up a fund 
the Nancy Strait and Bob Strait Support Trust to help pay for the 
service and her husband's medical care.


http://www.dailymail*co*uk/news/article-2117695/Brutal-home-invasion-Oklahoma-couple-ends-65-year-romance-meeting-blind-date.html#ixzz1pggJW1LB</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y2fit</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/m28u</id></website><link>http://blogs.alternet.org/speakeasy/2012/03/21/george-zimmerman-the-murder-of-trayvon-martin-and-the-twenty-first-century-slave-patrol/</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T20:17:55+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T08:26:52+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpkzpn</id><link>http://blogs.alternet.org/speakeasy/2012/03/21/george-zimmerman-the-murder-of-trayvon-martin-and-the-twenty-first-century-slave-patrol/#comment-473437640</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zgh1c</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>