<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/micfpd/update/2012-03-22T14:30:23/64901b03eee305dc85cee2b40d2bb0de4beca8430f8c205afdcbee00955d0bae</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>A.B. - this is a "Not Exactly" column for you. Santorum did not derail because he was  message, he derailed because he was on message. Romney camp screwed up in CO by assuming they had CO in the bag - take out the CO win and Tricky Ricky is back to 2%. I live in CO - those that voted at the caucus were far from representative of the state in a General Election - activist that have nothing better to do than show u at a caucus on a Cold winter night and vote for thr far right candidate.

Rick lost PA for someof the same reasons he could never win the primary Far Right Social agenda and quite frankly a lot of BS - let's drive around Iowa in a borrowed pick up and  Buy America but go home to a 2 million dollar house with an Audi in the garage - Ron Paul was dead on with calling Santorum a fake - Tricky Ricky simply ran out of people to fool. Iowa BTW was quite bogus - first Romney wins, then Santorum is ahead - next teh committee states that there ar 9 precints than cannot be confirmed and they will not be able to certify the results -- next day after primary Santorum is confirmed winner - this is where teh difference between Romney and Santorum are at teh extreme - Romney could hav asked for a recount or complained he did not - however Tricky Ricky aka Ricky The Whiner complains about MI amd one extra delegate - Ricky is a loser and UNELECTABLE

His blunder in Puerto Rico, his gaffe about not caring about the unemployment, support of Specter, support of big labor - the bridge under the Allegheny River just to name a few - that bridge got him the support of the labor unions - pretty stinky del like asking Dems in MI to vote for him - he is sleazy.

Tricky Ricky got a boost into orbit because he had not been vetted just like Obama, actually they are polar opposites with much in common - far left vs far right,  center ideologies, masters at misrepresentation etc.

Romney did not run Ricks bus Off the road Rick was in the drivers seat and did it all by himself.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ycr4q</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f047</id></website><link>http://thehill.com/opinion/columnists/ab-stoddard/217429-santorums-lost-message</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T22:30:03+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T18:30:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/micfpd</id><link>http://thehill.com/opinion/columnists/ab-stoddard/217429-santorums-lost-message#comment-473825132</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zdrox</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>