<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/eb0a6q/update/2012-01-05T13:23:18/103c70f9a05983c3510592ece966a94dafb43e9d9fa8e00a51fdece8996a10a7</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The problem with the studies which purport to show long lasting hormone changes after significant Weight loss all involved severely calorie reduced diets, thus it's impossible to know if the Weight loss caused the hormone changes or if the starvation caused Weight loss. To the best of my knowledge it's starvation which results in these hormone changes not fat loss per se.  

Slow fat loss of less than 1%/week is considered optimal for avoiding sending one's body into starvation mode.  If you plateau, then eat more to let body know you're not starving.  This has been conventional thinking for most of the last decade; it's a damn shame that the NYTimes health writer has missed this important component of fat loss.

People who have a history of yo-yo starvation dieting have lost substantial muscle mass.  It's the loss of muscle mass during diets without adequate resistance training/protein intake which has the biggest impact on diminished calorie requirements at the new weight.  This is especially problematic for women who lack the testosterone to easily Gain it back.

It's now conventional wisdom among Weight loss and fitness experts that resistance training to maintain muscle mass is an essential part of effective, permanent fat loss.  Yet no where was that mentioned by any of the guests.  It's astonishing that this knowledge which is widespread in the fitness community still has yet to penetrate the main stream media.

  
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/df1ttu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/z2vg</id></website><link>http://onpoint.wbur.org/2012/01/05/keeping-off-the-fat</link><postedTime>2012-01-04T20:54:55+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-01-05T18:23:18+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/eb0a6q</id><link>http://onpoint.wbur.org/2012/01/05/keeping-off-the-fat#comment-401383243</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5kygo</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-01-04</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>