<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miczqz/post/2012-03-22T14:11:01</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi87oi</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/80i4h</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Hulk Hogan said the same thing when I was your age (9 or 10) when his "career was nearly ended" by Earthquake.  I never took The Rock to mean that he was staying forever.  Think about it for a minute.  Why would Dwayne Johnson come back to a career that keeps him on the road nearly every day of the year, keeps his body battered, and has a hectic schedule when he can make just as much money (if not more) making movies and a few cameo appearances here and there.  It's naive to think that he meant that he was coming back for good.  After his neck injury Stone Cold said something to the effect of "Monday Night Raw will never be without Stone Cold Steve Austin".  Obviously, wrestlers retire or move on to better careers - who can blame them if the money is better and the schedule is lighter (not to mention the physical wear and tear).  These guys are just like any other athlete.  Around the age of 37 or 38 they Reach the end of their prime and their skills start to regress.  They don't take the bumps they used to take, attempt the moves that used to (at least not as often), wrestle in matches for as long a period, and their mobility has declined.  Can they still put on a good match?  Absolutely.  But, watch a match 5 or 10 years earlier and you can tell a huge difference.

I'm sorry for your disappointment, but it is what it is.  Some guys get this and some guys don't.  I'd love to see Austin back in the ring, but I also know that he is probably doing just fine without the pain of being a full-time wrestler.  He retired at the end of his prime and is remembered for what he did.  Guys like Sting, Flair, and Hogan are legends, but they are past their prime and doing nothing to further their legacy.  If anything, the younger generation of fans will not see them as the great stars that we see them.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yua7o</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/e1x9</id></website><link>http://www.wrestlinginc.com/wi/news/2012/0322/550916/john-cena/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T17:04:07+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T18:11:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miczqz</id><link>http://www.wrestlinginc.com/wi/news/2012/0322/550916/john-cena/#comment-473810522</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ycbdq</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>