<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/226781/post/126195462/comment/322120983</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>*deep breath* 
 
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! 
 
Ok, I&amp;rsquo;m done. Oh&amp;hellip;no, wait, there&amp;rsquo;s more. 
 
&lt;b&gt;AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/b&gt; 
 
Guys, this episode scared me a little. Just a little bit mind you. I mean it was only a tiny bit&amp;mdash; 
 
&lt;b&gt;AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/b&gt; 
 
Sorry about that, I just have this tendency to randomly &lt;i&gt;scream in uncontrollable terror&lt;/i&gt; occasionally for no good reason. Can&amp;rsquo;t seem to do anything about it, I&amp;rsquo;m afraid. 
 
In other news, this episode gets an INSTANT Spot of my top ten list for being incredibly inventive, occasionally hilarious, perfectly  and, oh yeah, UNBELIEVABLY FUCKING TERRIFYING. I mean it, that was not only easily the scariest episode of Buffy so far, it was one of the scariest episodes of TV I&amp;rsquo;ve &lt;i&gt;ever seen&lt;/i&gt;.  the top of my head, I literally can&amp;rsquo;t think of any episode of any show that has freaked me out more (with the obvious exception of the X Files episode &amp;lsquo;Home&amp;rsquo; which I only saw once and &lt;i&gt;holy fuck once was enough&lt;/i&gt;) I&amp;rsquo;m seriously impressed, this was a brilliant episode, and I have to say some of the best eps so far have been ones which have some kind of town-wide phenomenon like this, as in &amp;lsquo;Halloween&amp;rsquo;. 
 
THE GENTLEMEN. HOLY FUCKING FUCK THE GENTLEMEN. WHO CAME UP WITH THAT???? WHOSE BRAIN COULD BE THAT GODDAMN SCREWED UP AS TO IMAGINE SOMETHING SO UNBELIEVABLY TERRIFYING???? Seriously, with the combination of the make-up, special effecs and the &lt;i&gt;music my god&lt;/i&gt;, they are the most &lt;i&gt;incredible&lt;/i&gt; creepy villains. 
 
In other news! 
 
 
-Anya and Xander were &lt;i&gt;adorable&lt;/i&gt; in this episode. It&amp;rsquo;s actually kind of a neat thing that this episode is all about losing that ability to communicate, and Xander is obviously not someone who can easily talk about his feelings. It&amp;rsquo;s a nice bit of irony that losing the ability to talk is the catalyst for him to be able to express how much he cares about Anya. Admittedly through beating up Spike, but still. Also Anya&amp;rsquo;s little &amp;lsquo;let&amp;rsquo;s go have sex&amp;rsquo; gesture and the accompanying looks of horror on the other&amp;rsquo;s faces was friggin&amp;rsquo; hilarious. 
-Giles&amp;rsquo; little slideshow with accompanying &amp;lsquo;Danse Macabre&amp;rsquo; is the most wonderful thing I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen. 
-Who is that new witch girl? She wasn&amp;rsquo;t dead at the end, so maybe we&amp;rsquo;ll see her again? I kind of want Willow to form a little coven but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if you can have a coven of two. OH WAIT maybe together they could have the power to turn back AmyRat and the three of them could chill out being witchy &lt;i&gt;please let this happen.&lt;/i&gt; 
-So Olivia showed up again. I just&amp;hellip;she&amp;rsquo;s kind of cute and I want Giles to be happy and all but I just can&amp;rsquo;t shake the part of me that really wants to see heavy objects fall on her from a great height. There&amp;rsquo;s gotta be something I can do about that, right? Because it&amp;rsquo;s a little unfair to her. Though judging by what she said, she might be freaking out over the whole &amp;lsquo;monsters and demons&amp;rsquo; thing and leaving anyway so meh. 
-Buffy and Riley seem to be heading towards some Secret revealing. I&amp;rsquo;m actually excited for this, not so much for what it will mean for their relationship (to which I am utterly indifferent either way) but because I really want to know more about &amp;lsquo;The Initiative&amp;rsquo; 
 
In conclusion: 
&lt;b&gt;AAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/b&gt; 
 </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:226781:126195462</id><idPostId>126195462</idPostId><idBlogId>226781</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:226781</id><idBlogId>226781</idBlogId><link>http://markwatches.net/reviews</link><displayName>Mark Watches</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://markwatches.net/reviews/2012/03/mark-watches-buffy-the-vampire-slayer-s04e10-hush/</link><displayName>Mark Watches 'Buffy the Vampire Slayer': S04E10 - Hush</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T18:43:20.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:226781:126195462:322120983</id><link>http://markwatches.net/reviews/2012/03/mark-watches-buffy-the-vampire-slayer-s04e10-hush/#IDComment322120983</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T18:43:20.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Mark Watches 'Buffy the Vampire Slayer': S04E10 - Hush by enigmaticagentscully</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://intensedebate.com/profiles/enigmaticagentscully</link><idEmailMd5>7a18df8bf40e7c3bd8d87072d9f480bb</idEmailMd5><displayName>enigmaticagentscully</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://intensedebate.com/profiles/enigmaticagentscully"&gt;enigmaticagentscully&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://markwatches.net/reviews/2012/03/mark-watches-buffy-the-vampire-slayer-s04e10-hush/"&gt;Mark Watches 'Buffy the Vampire Slayer': S04E10 - Hush&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>