<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/226781/post/126195462/comment/321903642</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>&amp;quot;Hush&amp;quot; 
 
&amp;bull; Oh, God, the episode menu is one of the Gentlemen looking straight at the camera with that rictus grin. 
&amp;bull; &amp;quot;A typical college girl, one assumes.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Lbh&amp;#039;er whfg n tvey...&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Gung&amp;#039;f jung V xrrc fnlvat.&amp;quot; 
&amp;bull; &amp;quot;Or n tbbq obl.&amp;quot; Bu, Tbq. 
&amp;bull; &amp;quot;If I kiss you, it&amp;#039;ll make the sun go down.&amp;quot; Dreams are WEIRD. 
&amp;bull; &amp;quot;And the last twenty minutes just laid out everything I need to know for the final. I&amp;#039;d hate to have missed that.&amp;quot; Willow, keep teasing Buffy forever. 
&amp;bull; &amp;quot;You mean an orgasm friend?&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Yes, that&amp;#039;s exactly the most appaling thing you could have said.&amp;quot; That&amp;#039;s what makes her Anya. 
&amp;bull; Tara being too afraid of being laughed at to come to Willow&amp;#039;s defense = Me sad. :( 
&amp;bull; &amp;quot;Xander, don&amp;#039;t you care about me?&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Shut up.&amp;quot; In an episode that&amp;#039;s largely silent, there&amp;#039;s still a lot of great lines. 
&amp;bull; I love this description of the Gentlemen from the shooting script: &amp;quot;He&amp;#039;s old, bone white, bald -- Nosferatu meets Hellraiser by way of the Joker. Actually, he looks kind of like Mr. Burns, except he can&amp;#039;t stop his rictus-grin, and his teeth are gleaming metal.&amp;quot; 
&amp;bull; Love the phone call, and Spike&amp;#039;s condescending look when the inevitable happens. 
&amp;bull; &amp;quot;Lethal countermeasures engaged.&amp;quot; Well, so much for Riley. And I thought he and Buffy might make a cute... oh, they&amp;#039;re fine. Never mind. 
&amp;bull; &amp;quot;In case of emergency use stairway.&amp;quot; Ha. 
&amp;bull; If they were still in high school, it would have been Wbanguna who dropped the bottle. 
&amp;bull; It&amp;#039;s &amp;quot;Revelation.&amp;quot; No S. 
&amp;bull; &amp;quot;Hi Giles&amp;quot; Aww. 
&amp;bull; &amp;quot;...recent Flu vaccinations... citywide hoax...&amp;quot; I wonder if the cover story was concocted by (or in response to reports from) the Initiative. 
&amp;bull; I don&amp;#039;t really find the Gentlemen scary, personally. (I understand why they are. And I don&amp;#039;t hold it against the episode that I&amp;#039;m able to find the scary monsters not-scary.) But if one floated by my window at night, looking in with that grin... yeah, I&amp;#039;d close the curtains and scream. Or, you know, try to scream because I couldn&amp;#039;t speak. Unless they were getting really sloppy and skipped the stealing voices part. 
&amp;bull; There&amp;#039;s the music from the episode menu on the DVDs. Should have figured it was from this episode, the DVD is all &amp;quot;Hush&amp;quot;-branded. 
&amp;bull; Oh, God. The newspaper Giles is looking at... the text is from &lt;i&gt;The Onion&lt;/i&gt;. (WHY do I check stuff like this?) 
&amp;bull; &amp;quot;Danse Macabre!&amp;quot; This scene is one of my favorites. Just... funny and infodumpy all at once. 
&amp;bull; Okay, WHY do the Gentlemen need seven hearts? What happens if they GET them? 
&amp;bull; I don&amp;#039;t know which image makes me laugh more: the one where Giles went all-out with the red marker or the one with the Gentlemen dancing to a Victrola. Or the unflattering drawing of Buffy. 
&amp;bull; For some reason, I keep typing &amp;quot;Gentlement.&amp;quot; I wish I knew why. 
&amp;bull; Tara&amp;#039;s directory of Stevenson Hall is different from the one Spike looked through in &amp;quot;The Initiative.&amp;quot; 
&amp;bull; Why isn&amp;#039;t Riley wearing his mask? 
&amp;bull; Xander, Anya, I love you both and wish you all the best. 
&amp;bull; Lrc, guvf vf oyvaqvatyl boivbhf gb gur cbvag V pna&amp;#039;g oryvrir vg gbbx fbzrbar ryfr cbfgvat n zrffntr obneq guernq nobhg &amp;quot;Jvyybj naq gur oybaqr tvey ubyqvat unaqf&amp;quot; orsber V fnj vg. 
&amp;bull; &amp;quot;I just thought you were being pretentious.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Oh, I was. I was also right.&amp;quot; Yes, the two aren&amp;#039;t mutually exclusive. 
&amp;bull; &amp;quot;I guess we have to talk.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;I guess we do.&amp;quot; I try not to just drop quotes in these without some sort of commentary. For this, I&amp;#039;m having trouble coming up with anything to say. Which, given what I&amp;#039;m commenting on, is highly appropriate. 
&amp;bull; They should have had the Mutant Enemy zombie be silent this time. 
 
Body Count: 
&amp;bull; Student, killed by the Gentlemen. 
&amp;bull; (Offscreen) Now-heartless person, killed by the Gentlemen. 
&amp;bull; (Offscreen) 15-Year-Old Girl, killed by the Gentlemen. 
&amp;bull; Footman, killed by Buffy. 
&amp;bull; (Offscreen) Student, killed by the Gentlemen. 
&amp;bull; (Offscreen) Now-heartless person, killed by the Gentlemen. 
&amp;bull; Six Gentlemen, killed by Buffy. 
&amp;bull; At least three footmen, killed by Buffy. 
 
[There may be a sixth victim of the Gentlemen; they had five hearts on the table. Tara found a Gentleman holding a heart, but there&amp;#039;s really no way of knowing if that&amp;#039;s one that made it to the table. Given that all the Gentlemen we saw were present for Buffy&amp;#039;s scream, I would assume it did.] </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:226781:126195462</id><idPostId>126195462</idPostId><idBlogId>226781</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:226781</id><idBlogId>226781</idBlogId><link>http://markwatches.net/reviews</link><displayName>Mark Watches</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://markwatches.net/reviews/2012/03/mark-watches-buffy-the-vampire-slayer-s04e10-hush/</link><displayName>Mark Watches 'Buffy the Vampire Slayer': S04E10 - Hush</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T12:10:53.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:226781:126195462:321903642</id><link>http://markwatches.net/reviews/2012/03/mark-watches-buffy-the-vampire-slayer-s04e10-hush/#IDComment321903642</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T12:10:53.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Mark Watches 'Buffy the Vampire Slayer': S04E10 - Hush by Plactus</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>b839ee1dd9aa6c9d3326790dfbf6be30</idEmailMd5><displayName>Plactus</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>Plactus commented on &lt;a href="http://markwatches.net/reviews/2012/03/mark-watches-buffy-the-vampire-slayer-s04e10-hush/"&gt;Mark Watches 'Buffy the Vampire Slayer': S04E10 - Hush&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>