<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp0t4j/post/2012-03-22T10:36:44</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>With a G.M. like Freidman why are the Rays not supposed to be a good possibility to be in the World Series. Talent is talent and thre isn't another G.M. who is better at acquiring it within a limited apyroll than Freidman. The way he has been able to sign guys like Moore, Longoria, Price, and others quickly in the beginning of their careers has done wonders for Tampa. The thing that will most likely keep them out of it is thier production at the plate. Tampa has to be better than the .244/.322/.402 that they put up in 2011 as well as hitting better than .222 W/RISP. If they can reduce their strikeouts by a good measure then that in itself will help those numbers. The Rays can't keep  on their rotation to throw over 1,000 innings as they have done 3 out of the last 4 seasons with 1,058 in 2011 which is the most by an A.L. rotation since the 2005 White Sox. All 3 being playoffs years and all 3 Tampa starters have been in the top 5 in innings pitched. That says a ton about the Tampa training staff as well as the overall makeup of the starters but reducing some of thier work can only help with their health in the long run. This is where Alex Cobb and whoever turns out to be the long man and possibly Chris Archer later in 2012 can really help getting Spot starts throughout the year. Still questions however. Who will be the long man? Neimann has a high maintanence delivery and has been better facing the order the first 2 times through as in his career he has a .704OPS first time, .667 second time, but pounded to a .825OPS third time while also struggling after 75 pitches. Davis on the other hand is at his worst the first time through(.787OPS) and gets progressively better and Davis shows no such pattern after 75 pitches. This Rays team could hit a lot of home runs this year with Pena coming back, arrival of , Longoria, Upton, Joyce, and Zobrist although they did hit 172 in 2011 which was good considering how much they struggled overall in the power categories. Question is though with Scott and Pena coming in will the strikeouts continue to be a problem? Probably. Also will injuries be a concern as they have been so far this Spring? Hopefully not as Tampa can't have that. Again this will be the toughest division by far as Boston and New York will be there to the end as well as an improved Toronto team.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ddty9</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lz6q</id></website><link>http://mlb.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120320%26content_id=27451804%26vkey=news_mlb%26c_id=mlb</link><postedTime>2012-03-20T23:09:03+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T14:36:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp0t4j</id><link>http://mlb.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120320%26content_id=27451804%26vkey=news_mlb%26c_id=mlb#comment-473627763</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cszkh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>