<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miaort/update/2012-03-22T12:39:36/722b2fe3b1b93d3dd77aa35035c2a587f72c6a3ab76700a3b0b9753228bd2398</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>First - if there was a team willing to pay Wallace that kind of money (Steelers or otherwise) - there is no harm in him asking and receiving that amount. Believe it fellow Steelers fans "most" of the past Pittsburgh players would have taken the money over the team, if given the chance. You fans would also take the cash; if you were an NFL caliber player... stop the self-righteous indignation.

Now, having said that, it is obvious that Mike Wallace is delusional! And, I must agree with the article, that it is time to look into the possibility of Wallace's trade value. Although, another team would need to give up some decent draft choices, and also need to Cough up a fairly large sum of cash. That may be too much of a price for another team to swallow. 

Lastly, I have heard several times in past news stories that MW is a decent guy and that he has a pretty good work ethic. Ben was just expressing recently how Wallace is a good team-mate. Yet, when I would watch Wallace especially on the sidelines I often have come to the thought that he's more showman, than the "fight to the last man standing" football player. You know Hines could be a show-Off at times, but he (more often than not) seemed to play at a higher level when times in the game were crucial. I think it's becoming more and more apparent that Mike doesn't have that same motivation driving him.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y4eze</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/e0bs</id></website><link>http://bleedblackandgold.com/blog/2012/03/22/mike-wallace-looking-for-larry-fitzgerald-money/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T13:18:57+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T16:39:36+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miaort</id><link>http://bleedblackandgold.com/blog/2012/03/22/mike-wallace-looking-for-larry-fitzgerald-money/#comment-473735069</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>