<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp34ed/update/2012-03-22T08:27:47/6ec02f079bd79afe5249bbfeb8ee8296e40330925b3c0405cd545f4e893bf50b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpi4r0</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cs7ky</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>These are the players that are locks (short of injury) for position players for the :
 
Miguel Cabrera
Prince Fielder
Jhonny Peralta
Ramon Santiago
Brennan Boesch
Austin Jackson
Don Kelly
Ryan Raburn
Delmon Young
 
 will most likely carry 11 position players. That means there are 2 players left to choose from this list:
 
Brandon Inge
Danny Worth
Andy Dirks
Clete Thomas
 
If Andy Dirks does not make the team, then there is something seriously wrong with the . That leaves one Spot available for the other 3 to fight out. If you look at the list, you have several people that can play several positions. Players like Kelly and Raburn play both infield and outfield. Honestly, it looks like the  have more options in the infield than they do in the outfield. Thus, Dirks should be added. This provides a little more balance. Now, out of the other 3 players, none of them are really necessary other than some late game replacement. When I think of who would be best for a late game replacement, I think of what the Tigers lack… speed. Thomas does by far have the best speed out of the group. Honestly, he hits better than Inge and seems a little more prepared than Worth. If anything, I would pick Thomas for his speed and the idea of him as a pinch runner just fits the team the best.

Let's also not forget that Inge is getting older. Even if we did carry him for his remaining contract he would be done after these next 2 years. The other 3 are starting to hit their prime and have a stronger future ahead of them. Time to look at the best for the team and move on.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y8r15</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lz6q</id></website><link>http://detroit.tigers.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120321%26content_id=27475284%26notebook_id=27475758%26vkey=notebook_det%26c_id=det</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T21:35:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T12:27:47+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp34ed</id><link>http://detroit.tigers.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120321%26content_id=27475284%26notebook_id=27475758%26vkey=notebook_det%26c_id=det#comment-473535296</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/go3u8</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>