<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp0lvr/post/2012-03-22T10:27:28</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Studies have shown that antidepressants make depression PERMANENTLY WORSE!!!  Tons of studies have shown these dangerous drugs are mostly useless except for a placebo effect and they can cause weight , suicide, violence, brain damage, sexual dyfunction, etc.  This is typical of ALL psychiatry's bogus but life destroying stigmas and brain damaging poisons passed Off as medication for social control and outrageous profits.

"Depression" is a label given to normal life crises, stressful and upsetting events like job loss, divorce, death of loved ones, illness, etc.  Now the bogus DSM committee is even planning on labeling grief over the death of a loved one a "mental illness" of depression.  Once you get a "mentally ill" stigma, you are pretty much destroyed in terms of getting insurance, jobs, entering the military and you are robbed of all democratic, civil, constitutional rights to be forcibly involuntarily committed, drugged  or electroshocked PROVEN to damage your brain not to mention the abuse and cruelty doled out by psychiatry.

Anyone seeing a psychiatrist should have his/her head examined.  Don't fall for this latest evil ploy that ECT is "safe," when the opposite is true about this brain damaging, life destroying barbaric practice, all too typical of psychiatry's history including today!!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6d0v41</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/v3kr</id></website><link>http://healthland.time.com/2012/03/21/how-electroconvulsive-therapy-works-for-depression/</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T19:18:32+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T14:27:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp0lvr</id><link>http://healthland.time.com/2012/03/21/how-electroconvulsive-therapy-works-for-depression/#comment-473621195</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/lub0u</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>