<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpou7a/update/2012-03-22T01:38:43/6833f25b27300a60562e56eb268a74ce470629dc8b62d2d8087ba1c2ac6175e7</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>While I adored the dungeon design of Skyward Sword (to the point that I would recommend the game soley based on the dungeons), I do agree that they could have increased the danger of traversing them. Even just respawning enemies would have been acceptable.

And the lore did feel weak. For example, I looked out into the vastness of Lanayru with that beautiful lonely music playing in the background, and wondered what mysteries awaited me. There was so much potential! But very little was touched upon at all. They could have expanded on these mysteries and lore without ruining the enigma qualities. As for the tribes and their lore--I was really hoping they would have much more involvement in the overall plot or history. The introduction sequence almost primes you for it, too, showing an image of the various races with Hylia defending the land together. But it hardly happens.
These are two areas I believe OoT (among others) did very well in. The races had their own bearing on the story without their roles becomming too overwhelming. I like the new tribes of SS, but they were almost pointless (the parella, anyone?). And mysterious areas like the Shadow Temple, Forest Temple, the Colossus, etc. felt like they had major plot significance but still had that feeling of the "unknown" and the "unexplored" until you arrive to explore it all. Yes, I love SS's dungeons, but in regards to their role in the game's story, many seemed to have been placed in areas by default. The Ancient Cistern, Skyview Temple, the Earth Temple...can we please have some little hints about why they're there or their significance?

Too much filler...at least this time they tried to give the padding some variety. But it's still padding. If this was all optional, that would be fine, but tacking it on to the main quest is unfortunate. As far as padding goes, your mileage may vary. Some people loved the escort missions, half-baked stealth with much more potential, and tadtone collecting. I was generally apathetic.

In general, there were two more things that bothered me in this game that haven't really been mentioned in these articles:
1. The lack of a natural day/night system was just a poor choice. Why didn't they include it? You can have both a "sleep in bed" thing and a natural progression. I would have loved to explored the surface areas at night. And here's where the potential for gameplay really kicks in--they could have made the areas more challenging after dark. Creepier, more dangerous enemies could come out. Stalfos, normall relegated to mini-bosses, could have been all over the place. They could have developed a strong Wolfos-like enemy that only appeared at night in Faron Woods, or had tons of Dark Lizalfos stand guard in Eldin. So much gameplay potential thrown away for very little reason.
2. The surface wasn't very fleshed out, at least for the most part. It was nice they gave you shortcuts here and there as you got to them for quicker travel, but even so, the paths were still incredibly linear with very little room or motivation to explore. There were few  hidden beyond some rupees, and heart pieces and goddess cubes could almost Always be Spotted while travelling on the beaten path. It would have been nice to see various optional pathways, maybe some that led to a small hidden cave (akin to TP's lantern caves) or extra mini-dungeons that needed to be completed in order to obtain some really cool stuff (maybe even that's where some goddess cubes or heart pieces are found).

I think my biggest problem with SS is that areas of it had so much potential, but that potential was rarely fully realized. Whatever, despite its flaws it's still a great game. I look forward to your "Soaring Skyward" articles!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ydy0l</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/z5xv</id></website><link>http://www.zeldainformer.com/2012/03/trouble-in-skyloft-the-miscellaneous-flaws.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T03:30:41+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T05:38:43+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpou7a</id><link>http://www.zeldainformer.com/2012/03/trouble-in-skyloft-the-miscellaneous-flaws.html#comment-473308813</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>