<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi8xxn/post/2012-03-22T13:27:25</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>10 things Im grateful for: 
1) I come from a past relationship where I ended up in a depression. Im grateful for the boyfriend I have now, who is very supportive and honest with me.2) My 2 mothers. My aunt and my mom. :D3) My Job. I was looking for a job for such a long time.4) Having food in my house. There are so many people out there who dont know what theyre going to eat tonight because they have none.5) My arms. 6) My legs.8) My little cousin. He is such a troublemaker, Always wants to be in the streets doing things that are just plain wrong and having my aunt worried at all times. He runs away from home and does horrible in school. Im thankful because he still alive and we still have time to help him.9) My house. I know where I'll sleep tonight, where I'll take a shower, where I'll go if I'm Cold.. A lot of people dont have that.10) Im thankful for bodyrock. When I found you guys I was just coming out of depression and reading what you guys posted everyday helped me SO MUCH. It is incredible how I don't physically know you guys and I still feel you so close around me. Like friends. Thank you so much for the effort you put into this everyday.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yckk6</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rcq8</id></website><link>http://www.bodyrock.tv/2012/03/21/sexy-sweat-on-me-bodyrock-mash-up-workout/</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T23:02:37+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T17:27:25+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi8xxn</id><link>http://www.bodyrock.tv/2012/03/21/sexy-sweat-on-me-bodyrock-mash-up-workout/#comment-473773016</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>unapproved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>