<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/18041/post/2125131/comment/322011260</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>:Get ready for the birth of the  second child.   Your first baby urgboht into your life the enormous amount of affection and delight, and now you are expecting second child. Albeit  you experienced pregnancy and labor before, you now have added more responsibilities and considerations to get ready for your second baby.   Firstly try to help your first child to understand what to expect, and make him aware of  the changes that are going to happen with  the birth of a younger brother or sister.   However,  bringing up two children can be a bit too much at first, your time will be restricted, and you’ll be busier.  Time for sleep and meal will lessen and usually will Depend on the age of your older child. What you really need to do is to get organized before the second baby is born.   Don’t be surprised if during your second pregnancy you may be more exhausted than during the first one,  as   tacking care for your older child when pregnant usually  takes a lot of time and energy. The first  six to eight weeks after the birth can be the most demanding, as your main job will be trying to get your  second baby on a feeding and sleeping schedule,  and at the same time actively anticipating your older child\'s needs and changing emotions.   There are as well few positive changes, with the birth and nursing of the second child you will acquire confidence in your own abilities, knowledge, and experience, moreover, stuff that seemed  so hard with your first child, like breastfeeding, changing diapers, handling illness will be much easier this time.  Nevertheless, you should clearly understand that bringing home a new baby will affect you physically and emotionally. Increased exhaustion and soft Anxiety will be your normal condition  after having the second baby.   Make sure that, if you and your partner notice that you\'re rarely spending time together go and have an occasional date once things  become calm.   Pregnancy    due date calculator </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:18041:2125131</id><idPostId>2125131</idPostId><idBlogId>18041</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:18041</id><idBlogId>18041</idBlogId><link>http://reciprocity.be</link><displayName>Reciprocity</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://reciprocity.be/anyone-want-a-piece-of-cryptographic-history/</link><displayName>Anyone want a piece of cryptographic history?</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T15:27:05.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:18041:2125131:322011260</id><link>http://reciprocity.be/anyone-want-a-piece-of-cryptographic-history/#IDComment322011260</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T15:27:05.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Anyone want a piece of cryptographic history? by Ashu</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100003405638804</link><idEmailMd5>999741383ef3595e17983b65c1da9f39</idEmailMd5><displayName>Ashu</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100003405638804"&gt;Ashu&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://reciprocity.be/anyone-want-a-piece-of-cryptographic-history/"&gt;Anyone want a piece of cryptographic history?&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>