<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp0zhw/update/2012-03-22T10:31:02/8d70e69d2367658a29e08c56e9b6b84dd7bbe35730a2a0ea223d8217e66a3206</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpknwz</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/jbxp</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Honestly, I think you are both wrong and both right to some degree.

When I said it wasn't a good comparison, I didn't mean that Superman's Krypton roots did not have an impact on who he was.   They do.  It's wrong to say otherwise.  I personally do not care for a sterile, Cold Krypton but it's still not the same thing.

It's not a good comparison because the American immigrant experience is not solely defined by being born here.  

One does not have to be born in Israel in order to experience what it means to be Jewish in American.

One does not have to be born in China to experience what it means to be Chinese in America.  So on and so on.

Jerry Siegel himself was born HERE. He was born in Cleveland.  It was his father who was the immigrant.

I am the child of immigrants.  My father was not born here.  I was.  

Ultimately, the root of Superman's story is that his parents SAVED him.   He was not abandoned.  He wasn't sent out into the universe because they didn't want him.  He wasn't dropped on the Kents doorstep like an unwanted child.  He was SAVED.  His story is rooted in compassion and mercy despite the differences in the portrayal of his homeland.   That is the key.

Superman's experience reflects the American dream for a lot of people in the United States.  He was a stranger from a strange land who escaped destruction and pain and imminent death for the promise of a better life.    He was raised by two loving humans who raised him as their son and he considered them his parents.

Superman's story is the story of many American immigrants who came to the United States hoping for a better life and trying to assimilate and find hope while still feeling like an "other" due to our cultural differences.   That's WHY so many Americans consider Superman to be one of the only myths that truly belong to US.   

That's why there are people who had a problem with an actor who wasn't an American citizen playing Superman.  I personally didn't have a problem with Henry Cavill being cast.  I like him.  But despite not agreeing with that opinion, I do UNDERSTAND where it comes from because Superman's story does have roots in a uniquely American experience about assimilation that people of all colors, cultures and religious backgrounds who have sought refuge or the chance for a life here can relate to in some way in the way that say the Batman mythos or the Spiderman mythos does not.

What has been done to the Amazons is a totally different situation that really isn't comparable because this is not just about "where Wonder Woman comes from" but also changes the entire basis of the Wonder Woman mythos and her mission with humanity.

It would be like saying that Kal-El wasn't SAVED by his parents but abandoned by them.   It would be like saying that Marthan and Jonathan Kent were killers that Clark Kent had to overcome as opposed to love and learn from. 

There is also a very disturbing gender dynamic here that is simply not comparable to what happened with Krypton.  

In much the same way that Superman has Always been an allegory for the American immigrant experience and desire to find new hope and life in a new world, Wonder Woman has been a symbol for what women can and are capable of when they are free from the chains of institutionalized sexism.  The entire point of the Amazons is that they were a world free from misogyny---free from the chains of what men have been doing to women for thousands of years---free from oppression and that without that oppression these women didn't just survive....they THRIVED.   That was the point.  Turning them into killers negates that point on every level.   And it was wrong.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y53yu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/m7rp</id></website><link>http://dcwomenkickingass.tumblr.com/post/19704793909</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T00:06:55+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T14:31:02+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp0zhw</id><link>http://dcwomenkickingass.tumblr.com/post/19704793909#comment-473623702</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yf5jz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>