<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miczxa/update/2012-03-22T14:11:04/9117965fdba722eaa36f461d7b4a2e2e8ed88093c20f28da61582495c259f3ef</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Thank you to "InRealLife". Finally someone using commen sense and doing some real homework on the candidates and their stances and solutions. I have done mine as well. While Ms Stoddard has pointed out a few of Rick Santorum's weaknesses, she has just barely scratched the surface. None of these pundits on TV and radio have done a proper vetting of this guy. He is hardly the "true conservative" - a phrase that is starting to make ME want to throw up. Proper vetting would reveal that Santorum in his own words proudly stated that he was pro choice until he made his first run for Congress. Yes, Rick Santorum, the guy who staunchly supported Arlen Specter over Pat Toomey giving Obama his deciding vote and a new Democrat in the Senate, the guy who was the consummate "team player" - wheeling and dealing and spending in the Senate, the guy who loved earmarks, the guy who voted against right to work laws, the guy who made deals with labor union bosses to try to save his Senate seat, the guy who bilked the PA education system of $70,000 to home school his kids even though his residence at the time was VA, the guy who won a Spot on the 10 most corrupt Senators list in 2005 and 2006 but lost his Senate race by 18 points, the guy who made $3 million in 18 months on K street following that defeat. And this same guy has made a fool out of his party in this primary season with is Shouting, whining, complaining and his pushing of social conservatism to the extreme. As a lifelong, conservative practicing Catholic I find him an embarrassment to my faith and my party. I will gladly support Mitt Romney. And thank God the "etch-a-sketch" can be shaken and a fresh start can be made for the general election cycle free from the nonsense of the likes of Santorum and Gingrich. Let's get down to business.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ycr4q</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/f047</id></website><link>http://thehill.com/opinion/columnists/ab-stoddard/217429-santorums-lost-message</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T22:30:03+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T18:11:04+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miczxa</id><link>http://thehill.com/opinion/columnists/ab-stoddard/217429-santorums-lost-message#comment-473810581</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/za76u</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>