<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mukunw/update/2012-03-12T10:47:58/60602ae828c7e4055235c8ac2711a449c370e0a2ddef78b3905d004289500572</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/muieok</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hk0rg</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Before you expound on  and their characteristics, I suggest a course in chemistry and not advertisements.

I would like you to cite a technical reference to your claim, all my experience with  have shown that  lose power with decreased temperature. Unless you have altered the law of physics, the following applies:

"All  deliver their power via a chemical reaction inside the
  that releases electrons. When the temperature drops, the 
chemical reactions happen more slowly and the  cannot produce the
 same current that it can at room temperature. A change of ten degrees 
can sap 50 percent of a 's output. In some situations, the 
chemical reactions will happen so slowly and give so little power that 
the  will appear to be dead when, in fact, if it is warmed up, it
 will go right back to normal output."Your reference to the 5hp generator is meant to signify what? It is irrelevant to the subject of  life and  efficiency in Cold weather. As for "deep cycling" a , you had better not do that to a starting type . It only applies to specific  types and is possible because the  plates have been designed with larger cross sections so they don't warp from the heat generated during charging. That is the reason they "cool"  during the charging process.As for "throwing" your digital camera  into a freezer, just take it out of the camera, put it down and it will recover somewhat anyway. Most Batteries exhibit load removal recovery.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yx7h2m</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7y82</id></website><link>http://www.earthtechling.com/2012/02/tesla-motors-model-x-smokes-40-million-in-a-day/</link><postedTime>2012-02-17T21:09:11+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-12T14:47:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mukunw</id><link>http://www.earthtechling.com/2012/02/tesla-motors-model-x-smokes-40-million-in-a-day/#comment-463371298</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/r5xv</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-17</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>