<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/316906/post/127022926/comment/321902705</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Hahaha debate is the pass time of kings - oh no wait, i thought  was? To the disgruntled South Coasters, I have spent time with Roosta there over the years and have only had good vibes and good times, including my encounters with many of you, so not sure where the hate is coming from? He has a job to do and that job is . Otherwise he would be just another coasty with no bucks! You guys live in paradise and lets be honest, for most of the time you do have it all to yourselves. Try living in the city, boys and girls and then we can talk. I welcome you to come  Llandudno anytime - i promise to be polite and accommodating - unfortunately I cant speak for the other frothing 60 guys, who  every day of the week! I can confirm Cold beers on the patch after wards! Its almost as good as a car park, maybe a better view though! I guess the bottom line is that surfers from the coastline outside of the major metropolitan areas will  feel hard done by when the town crews pull in -its hard when you are used to 3 guys out to deal with 10 guys out - I feel your pain, but not really. Less talented surfers will Always feel cheated by the truly talented surfers, its the way of things, they are better stronger and catch more ways, normally deeper than the locals themselves. Live with it! As mentioned above, try living on the Gold Coast with a 1000 surfers in the water every day! The ocean's for everyone - even those irritating pro ho's! ;)
Roo - you sure ous are not just scared of Tass? haha</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:316906:127022926</id><idPostId>127022926</idPostId><idBlogId>316906</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:316906</id><idBlogId>316906</idBlogId><link>http://swg.co.za/zagcms</link><displayName>Zigzag Magazine</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://swg.co.za/zagcms/carparks/</link><displayName>Carparks...</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2010-10-15T11:40:00.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:316906:127022926:321902705</id><link>http://swg.co.za/zagcms/carparks/#IDComment321902705</link><postedTime>2010-10-15T11:40:00.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Carparks... by Captain</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link/><idEmailMd5>4f08e1475e9899466691873c5cb44264</idEmailMd5><displayName>Captain</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>Captain commented on &lt;a href="http://swg.co.za/zagcms/carparks/"&gt;Carparks...&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2010-10-15</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>