<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mj5ccy/update/2012-03-19T02:33:10/5efd45eadd8c43221e327f93a4d37884d77d9d0f4b9cd89b274d8409aec80cab</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mj8o6r</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/3nea</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Actually it wasn't meant as snark.  It was a statement that I thought spoke for itself; whether it was offensive is up to you.  But since you insist, I'll spell it out.  My experience with Christian Scientists is that they talk the talk better than they walk the walk, when the chips are down.  And everyone knows about the Amish farmer who wants to borrow his neighbor's telephone or cop a ride into town in the neighbor's car when there's an emergency.  I'm sure a lot of those people are very sincere in their beliefs, but at the end of the day, modern medicine and modern communications and travel trump fairy tales and old-fashioned thinking.  LIKEWISE (are you still with me?) I find that the people I hear talking about "government distortions" are the ones who think the roads built themselves and the fact that they sleep safely in their beds at night is just God working his mysteries.  

Sorry.  I think government is like every other tool Man has invented -- it has the capacity to do great good and great harm, Depending on who is in charge.  That's why democracy is so precious. But getting rid of government because it makes mistakes is like turning in your car for a donkey because you're mad at the oil Spots on your garage floor: you have no idea what you're letting yourself in for.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6cdk38</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/eyjq</id></website><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2012/04/the-villain/8901/</link><postedTime>2012-03-14T00:34:50+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-19T06:33:10+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mj5ccy</id><link>http://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2012/04/the-villain/8901/#comment-468803493</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cg5lm</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-14</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>