<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/micr3w/post/2012-03-22T14:07:24</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I have no problems with this.  However.  
One issue comes into play when you have rogue individuals do it.  What happens when some person from England takes down a DoD satellite....do we go to war with the UK when it was an individual not a government involved?  You would have to be DAMN certain that it not an individual.  And lets be blunt:  the US's ability to not jump to conclusions *Coughs*IRAQWMD's*Coughs*  is less then stellar.

And what happens when attacks come from multiple people around the world.  Example:  Anonymous.  Or what happens when a group of hackers do a damn good job at covering their tracks and makes it look as if the attacking country may have been Turkey when it really came from China or North Korea, etc.

I don't believe our monitoring and computer forensic capabilities is anywhere near good enough to be able to go to war over something such as a cyber attack yet.  

Its  come down to this  war vs. a proportional response.   A Cyber attack should be countered with our own cyber attack.  But if we don't have the tools to do that what is our response going to be?  Fall back to old methods of course and bomb them.
This is why we really need to ramp up our cyber ops capabilities in this country.  Instead we have dipshits making fun of geeks in the house and senate. Examples being during the SOPA hearings.  The US is going to continue to do what its Always been great at doing:  ignoring an issue until it bites us in the ass.
Rules of engagement is great.    It lets our enemies know we are going to do this if you do that to us. But it doesn't change the fact that our cyber warfare defenses and capabilities is somewhere between jack and shit, and jack left town. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ydbhm</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/y2ru</id></website><link>http://www.engadget.com/2012/03/21/u-s-department-of-defense-preps-cyber-rules-of-engagement-shar/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T03:47:26+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T18:07:24+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/micr3w</id><link>http://www.engadget.com/2012/03/21/u-s-department-of-defense-preps-cyber-rules-of-engagement-shar/#comment-473807158</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8o5u</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>