<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miay4a/update/2012-03-22T12:08:57/36f4d6624e53c91245f0bee4c4e1f346c875806d2a0268ec76615542aa9545e4</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Basically, nearly all the puzzles should go. Zelda should be centered around Secrets instead that you uncover by exploring.

Combat and exploration are the two most important things in Zelda. Forget story, forget puzzles - these things are why Skyward Sword sells so badly. And yes, Skyward Sword had motion controlled combat which is not a bad thing - the enemies, however, were boring to fight. Now, I couldn't get my controller to do what I wanted it to do, but I think it may be broken so I won't complain about that. What I will complain about is slow and boring enemies that reveal their weak Spots for several seconds and do nothing to harm you. In truth, they feel more like puzzles as they present no real exciting action. Some of the enemies were hard, but that was only because it was difficult to figure out what to against them (like the electric snails). The real problem is that once you figure out how to defeat them, they suffer from the same problems as the other enemies.

More enemies (LOTS of enemies) that attack you head-on like the ones from most 2D-Zeldas (and that are actually fun to fight) and a good, responsive action-oriented combat system are some of the most important elements in any Zelda-game.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yxt63</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/z5xv</id></website><link>http://www.zeldainformer.com/2012/03/zelda-question-of-the-day-which-do-you-prefer-puzzles-or-combat.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T15:49:58+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T16:08:57+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miay4a</id><link>http://www.zeldainformer.com/2012/03/zelda-question-of-the-day-which-do-you-prefer-puzzles-or-combat.html#comment-473710681</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>