<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/micdnq/update/2012-03-22T14:02:20/be2d9d51b24e881adafa7acbaac95efdaed5d77b0e74d590ded4e1848cef4421</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>OK, everyone. Let's think about this:
1) Is this really news or is it a political smear by the corrupt PCs?
2) How did this "parking lot dispute" find its way to the Journal's front page? Why did the Sheriff or the PC's Solicitor General leak it to the Journal (the 'left-wing media')?
3) Why did the Sheriff call Mr Anderson by his first name (to his face and in her incident report)? Is the Sheriff also on a friendly, first-name basis with the Premier and her supervisor and her Chief?
4) The emotional tone of the Sheriff's description's of events suggests that she was letting her emotions get the better of her. Was this really the first time she was faced with someone who didn't just passively comply with her demands? Was she upset that her authority was questioned?
5) Why didn't the Sheriff exercise some discretion and try to Resolve the issue rather than flexing her authority? Rather than demanding Mr Anderson's ID, why didn't she just let him move his car, and check on his ID later? Didn't she stop to think that, if he didn't belong in the Leg, her equally capable colleagues would have stopped him from getting in?4) Why was the Premier not parked in her own Spot during the session? Why was she absent from debate regarding her budget??
6) westernpg: Stealing???? Really??? What about all the PC MLAs who are keeping all the money from sitting on the committee that didn't work for 39 months? What about the Premier receiving her salary for not showing up for important debates? What do you call that?</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ye7fp</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7maa</id></website><link>http://www.edmontonsun.com/2012/03/21/he-took-the-preems-place</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T01:44:34+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T18:02:20+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/micdnq</id><link>http://www.edmontonsun.com/2012/03/21/he-took-the-preems-place#comment-473802787</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zd7tl</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>