<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpkpmz/update/2012-03-22T05:29:05/b7dec042a1a12c1e224f4c4eeceed8e0843b113a54de2c63b996bccd58a68fd9</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>As Colin said, "The starting rotation after Kershaw is more of a concern" . . . .pretty much like it was in 2011.  The 2012 rotation could be one ascending star followed by four fizzles.  Hopefully, when the bell rings, there's some spark to be found in the others, but let's face it, none of the supporting crew is near the apex of his respective career.  As it stands now, we have "can't pay the Bills," a "wilting Lilly," another just trying to "Harang on,", and a potential "Cupa-guano" behind Kershaw.  
 
I know some of you don't much like to forecast possible results, but based on where these guys are in their careers, I don't think it's unreasonable to estimate the combined innings pitched among them could be less than 720, with perhaps not more than 45 wins collectively.  Toss in 18-20 by Kid-K and the bullpen will be pressed to win the requisite 18-20 more needed to help this team get a shot at the post-season.  
 
If the starters do not shape up quickly, the team will greatly  on the continuation of big run production by Kemp, as well as anticipated career-years from Ethier and Loney, plus Gordon's emergence as an all-round contributor to compensate for yet another year of generally inconsistent starting pitchers.  And, unless Ellis, Fed-ex and Uribe chime in with something positive, their Spots in the line-up could be a wasted effort, hurting the team ten or more times a game.    
 
It's too early to tell how much of this early prognostication might be accurate, but one thing I'll predict that will make a difference is the change in ownership.  Regardless of what Donnie and the players say publicly, the current regime has not enhanced either the tangible or intrinsic aspects of the Dodgers day-to-day play.  A breath of fresh air is Always welcome when you've played under the limitations of an SOB (take it easy, MLB monitor, the acronym means "shortness of breath").</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yecr0</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lz6q</id></website><link>http://losangeles.dodgers.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120321%26content_id=27493912%26vkey=news_la%26c_id=la</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T01:23:04+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T09:29:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpkpmz</id><link>http://losangeles.dodgers.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120321%26content_id=27493912%26vkey=news_la%26c_id=la#comment-473456282</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/58foz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>