<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mon6xh/update/2012-03-21T00:16:38/ab0a948529f86610e0dae87ea7d04f98bf38689abdb068fadbf5e1b172889164</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Okay, Victor, show us an example of how an atheist applies the OTF... give us an idea of the inner dialogue or the questions an atheist might ask and how they'd Resolve them.

Show us how an ex-Scientologist... who used the OTF to become an ex-Scientologist... should apply the OTF to their new-found skepticism. 

I don't think it makes sense to apply the OTF to the supernatural beliefs you no longer have-- but it makes a lot of sense to apply it to one's supernatural beliefs (those that require FAITH-- as there is no scientific evidence that anything supernatural actually exists.) 

If you don't give us an example, it just sounds like you are making a fake argument in order to avoid the implications the OTF has for your faith.  

Catholics are supposed to believe in a literal hell according to the "infallible" pope. Of course, there's a lot of fuzziness about who goes there... but I think those who are baptized Catholic are supposed to be safe which must be a great relief for Hitler fans. Unless maybe you are gay or had an abortion. But I'm not sure most Catholics know or care what the church teaches. I had no idea we were supposed to believe in transubstantiation until I left the church. I doubt many Catholics believe that the communion literally turns into Jesus. But in the past, if you Vomited up the host, that was a mortal sin... and you had to eat the Vomited host. Catholics take their blessed bread very seriously.  

I think a theist needs to come to grip with the fact that there are people with opposing supernatural beliefs that believe these opposing beliefs just as strongly as you believe your FAITH-based beliefs-- and there is no way to tell a real supernatural belief from a false one... each believer seems to be using confirmation bias to confirm their own beliefs. (I remember what I used to convince myself that Catholicism was true... and then later my New Age type beliefs.) 

Certainly, if a loved one was in a cult, you'd want them to understand about confirmation bias-- and to be willing to look at their faith honestly... but how could you do that, if you can't look at your own honestly? How could you expect the Muslim or Scientologist or Mormon to consider their faith from an outsider's perspective (such as yours) if you cannot do it with your own? Wouldn't they just make the same excuses as you make?

If all theists are as stubborn as you then we have a world full of people with conflicting magical beliefs who are all sure that they are right and none of them are really capable of rational dialogue when it comes to the stuff they imagine themselves saved for "believing in". They are all subject to the voices in their head they imagine are coming from their gods... and the rest of us have to live with the results as they make fake arguments about how the OTF is flawed because atheists don't apply it to their atheism.  

It's akin to the woo anthem "I'm skeptical of the skeptics." It doesn't mean anything but it makes each "woo" feel proud of their credulity in a given area.

Rest assured, I read what you said. You hedge at the hell question. Do you believe in hell? Do you believe that belief in Jesus can save a person from hell? Do you believe there are consequences to non-belief? You're a C.S. Lewis fanboy, so I would think that hell is a motivator. Do you believe that your salvation hinges upon faith?  Can you at least admit there is a possibility that you just stop existing when you die (like other animals)?  Certainly you understand that is a rational position, right?-- and any conjecture about life after death is something one takes on "faith" (the "F" in OTF). 

I think it's you who aren't listening. Or rather, you aren't listening any better than those of conflicting faiths would. You are asking for something that doesn't make sense instead of ceding that John BECAME an atheist because of the OTF which is a rational position; even if something does happen after death (such as reincarnation or Mormon tiered heaven), there is no way to know WHICH things happen nor what one needs to do or believe in order to influence any potential afterlife-- your theology is as good as a Muslims or anyone else's to an outsider. Science cannot even establish that any part of ones thoughts or personality live on after death which you'd have thought they'd managed by now if such things were real. 

You haven't shown a sensible or coherent way that John apply the OTF to his skepticism while imagining that it's a fatal flaw in the OTF. But it takes no faith not to believe in afterlives nor magic nor supernatural things. You do it all the time. You just make a rare exception in the area where you imagine there is a benefit for doing so.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6gmcjc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ry26</id></website><link>http://debunkingchristianity.blogspot.com/2012/03/on-taking-outsider-test-for-faith-otf.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-16T16:22:35+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-21T04:16:38+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mon6xh</id><link>http://debunkingchristianity.blogspot.com/2012/03/on-taking-outsider-test-for-faith-otf.html#comment-471239329</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cepgf</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-16</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>