<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi52ke/post/2012-03-22T14:49:15</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Let's just recap a minute. A bunch of German banks muscled their way into Ireland's pretty stagnant property market. Their aim was not to show "EU Solidarity" with Ireland - it was solely to make a profit - a big one.

In the other PIIGS nations - French and German bankers with the full support of their Governments and the encouragement of the EU Commission (Commission is their name - Commission is their game). 

These predators were after the coveted "National Projects". This was a "Sweetheart Deal" set up by the French and the Germans during the time of Chirac - but happily continued by little Sarkozy. 

In Ireland, as their plunder of the PIIGS was losing impetus - and worse - that the EU Commission had not managed to secure the urgently needed "Direct Taxation" required to fully underwrite France and Germany's robbery of the PIIGS' economies - it really started to unravel. 

A weak Taoiseach in Cowen - who surrendered his country's future in exchange for money and promises of non-disclosure and then Kenny - who came in on a  of almost pure anti-EU vitriol - which is now less powerful than pond scum. Kenny surrendered the little which Cowen hadn't given away.

The major culprits in the rape of Ireland  - well - they got their money back - the taxpayers of the EU Coughed up to set the Banks right.

Did the Irish benefit from their German enforced "Austerity". Not a penny. By now Irish MEPs were so well versed in how to counter the truth - that they all say almost the same thing. Of course they have been on the EU Defence course - how to hurt Ireland again - to stop the people of Ireland telling the EU to go to hell. 

As Mitchell MEP was saying, "sure and it's been a wonderful thing for Ireland the euro. We're much better Off than being under Westminster's aegis."

As independent a thought as Achmed the dead terrorist. 

Alas poor Ireland. Come the Referendum - kick them hard in the balls - or whatever they have there.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yuwyw</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://preview.telegraph.co.uk/finance/financialcrisis/9161155/Eurozone-poster-child-Ireland-slumps-back-into-recession.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T17:49:57+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T18:49:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi52ke</id><link>http://preview.telegraph.co.uk/finance/financialcrisis/9161155/Eurozone-poster-child-Ireland-slumps-back-into-recession.html#comment-473839458</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/c2ncg</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>