<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/moa3zt/update/2012-03-20T13:13:58/123b543a38b21634d4b0f04cf969972d85fbfd5e4d93382f82e263b23baa31a3</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>www.tenminutemag.co.uk

To whom it may concern,                                             March 20th 2012It has been many years since an otter has been moved to write.Third down on the left, looking serious: that is meAs spokesperson of the Council of Otters: spanning from the great romp of Neotropical River Otters to the south, spanning all the way up to every dog, bitch and kit of the Hairy-Nosed otter tribe to the east.Read these words carefully: I do not look like Benedict Timothy Carlton Cumberbatch.Hunted for our fur, driven to the edge of extinction by pollution and dwindling fish stocks now we are to suffer this indignity? We do not take this injustice lying down.My romp and I set Off down from our Nottingham home to have a look at this fool in the flesh. He has no style:A.      Sherlock is a pastiche of blunt cliches, unerotic sexuality and yawnful violence. The only mystery of any intrigue is how deep the stolen looks, the brushing of skin, the saucy tones that are exchanged with Watson have actually burrowed. Indeed I find myself wondering if the whole premise of their time together on screen is not in the name of solving most unlikely crimes, but to spend time freely together in a society that would otherwise have deemed it unsuitable.B. His name is ridiculous.We are not some lowly beaver, to be ridiculed for looking like that ridiculous Timothy Spall and a woman’s special area.Nay we are a proud race. We swim, fish, snarl and kill.We may like to lazily float on our backs, bobbing around and gazing to the heavans, but that is because we are thinkers – and our bellies are stuffed with clams.Undeniably a beaverYet how can I frolic in woodland springs knowing that my antics will further the man that helped War Horse come to be?Norse mythology tells of how the dwarf Otr, son of king Hreidmar would regularly transform himself into an otter – admittedly so that he may feast on Cold fish without being disturbed.However the point is clear: we are beasts descended from kings.It has been too long since we have been treated as such, sir. ‘Cumber-gate’s’ only positives are in its highlighting of a long history of persecution.  Sincerely yours,Frederick XXXIIIChief of the Northern Eurasian ottersSpokesperson for the Otter Council</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6mdgsm</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/mf6v</id></website><link>http://blogs.independent.co.uk/2012/03/19/otters-who-look-like-benedict-cumberbatch-and-other-trends-on-twitter/</link><postedTime>2012-03-19T17:22:15+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-20T17:13:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/moa3zt</id><link>http://blogs.independent.co.uk/2012/03/19/otters-who-look-like-benedict-cumberbatch-and-other-trends-on-twitter/#comment-470382425</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h9nb0</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-19</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>