<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m94kjg/update/2012-03-17T12:05:07/80472e2d791a0f8168b9b49896b73da9ce118ecd0ee48b4ecb157fa58d36994e</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9ag11</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ug62</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> Farming your own property without a license or for commercial sales or distribution is illegal in every State in America. Ownership of more than one farm classified animal on a residential property is illegal. Giving away fruits, nuts or vegetables is legal but selling or trading them to other people is illegal -federally,  by the USDA and FDA  and subject to up to $10,000.00 a day fines. It is illegal to drop a water well without city permit and State approval. It is illegal in  States to use open air tanks to collect rain water. It is illegal to collect sun rays for use in generating electric power without city permit, it illegal to sell said electricity for any reason without State licensing as a power company. It is illegal to generate more than 15% of your home's electricity needs if you do you must pay for and have installed a generator and transformer that collects the excess and sends it to the local utility company (for free) who is the "legal" owner  all local electric supplies under State laws. If you own a farm anywhere in the U.S. it is illegal to sell your products directly to the consumer, it is illegal for you to process food or slaughter animals on your own farm. It is illegal to run food co-ops than cross State lines. It is illegal to kill for food, animals not approved by State and Federal agencies. It is illegal to allow pollen and germination of patented crops to occur on your property even if you are not aware of it and it happened naturally. It is illegal to cut down trees, burn shrubbery, plant fruit or nut trees within any City limits without permit. It is illegal to ship any plants or food products across State lines without federal permission. It is illegal to sell, process for food, kill, raise, trade any animal without FDA approval. 

You must not live in the U.S. because everything here is illegal and military-style police goons are Itching to take down farmers in my country. They call these  "commercial terrorism" since all activities must generate monetary Gain but only for people with more money than you who are presently involved in the same industry or financing it.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6g5r8a</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/cusm</id></website><link>http://www.rawstory.com/rs/2012/03/16/greece-develops-euro-free-currency-in-tight-economy/</link><postedTime>2012-03-16T14:12:09+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-17T16:05:07+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m94kjg</id><link>http://www.rawstory.com/rs/2012/03/16/greece-develops-euro-free-currency-in-tight-economy/#comment-467814209</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/d3b3w</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-16</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>