<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miaaeq/post/2012-03-22T11:58:01</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Very long post, I am sorry, but I wanted everyone to get a good idea of who I am and my journeys through relationships.  I hope it flows o.k., sometimes I have so much to say in writing that my thoughts are quicker than my writing.


Hi, I been reading your blog and really enjoying all the advice you are giving everyone.Bear with me this is going to be a long post : ) I was in my first true relationship after a break-up with my 1st love. 

My relationship with my 1st love lasted about 6 years, but we still  like a couple, until I moved away. My 1st love seemed to have dangled a carrot in front of my face for years after we broke up. He used to say all the time that he was single when it felt like we were together. It took me moving to another city a year after I graduated from college to realize that hey I am single.I did not realize it as soon as I moved either, it was about 8 -12 months later that I finally had a lightbulb go  while I was driving that said I am single woman again. Me and my ex are still good friends to this day, he helped me through a lot of rough times, and I will  love him for that. When me and my ex started dating I was 135 lbs, by the time we broke up I was about 200 lbs, but he  told me I was pretty. I also went through some major depression during my college years, probably about 2-3 years of my time in undergrad I was depressed and felt horrible about myself, he stood with me throught that time. He didn't quite understand why I was going through so much horrible pain, but he was their for me anytime or anyday, did not matter what he was doing, he was  their for me, and he still is. My ex was my first love, I met him when I was in the sixth grade and he was in the eigthth grade, I think back to that time, and I was a lot more bold, confident and resisliant : ). We became friends and talked on the phone all the time. Eventually, I ended up moving and going to a different school. We still remained friends, but then he got a girlfriend that was in high school, when I was still in middle school. He called me up one day and told me that he could not talk to me anymore because he had a girlfriend now, and his girlfriend did not like us being friends because she knew that I liked him and he liked me too, but I could not date at the time so, he started going out with another girl. I was in my bed I think doing my homework when I recieved the phone call, but I don't remember being mad or really sad, I went on with my life, like nothing happen. I am sure I was probably a little disappointed, he was my first crush, and the first guy I had ever thought was the greatest looking guy ever lol : ). But no tears or outburst or feeling my life was over, none of that. So, after that we did not talk until my senior year of high school when he had broke up with the girl he stop talking to me for. He ended up seeing my friend at a festival in town and he asked her for my phone number, and she gave it to him. Well, when we finally talked, we were both so excited to here from each other, and from that point on we were inseperable. I was 17 years old then. So, I know everyone is wondering why we broke up, well he broke up with me because he felt like I had more loyalties toward my friend he did not like. During the course of our relationship he probably broke up with me about 3 times, the third time being the last time. The first breakup we had almost killed me, but as he kept on threatening the breakups, the pain got less and less, but I would be the first to say I felt like he was half of me, like we both made me whole, without him I would die. I never brokeup with him though, I  thought that people are human, people make mistakes, and everyone deserves second chances and to be forgiven. We all come with flaws, so I never threaten to break up with him, I truly loved him, the good, bad and the ugly. I loved that man and I thought that was who I would spend the rest of my life with. Anyways, but someone continuing to breakup with you after so many years gets old. So, finally accepted the break up probably about 6 months -1 year later after we had broken up, and like I said I was living in another city then. But we were still friends. Anyways, I tried dating and talking to a few other guys when I lived away from home, but none had that spark I was looking for, and when I would go out on dates they would bore me, many times I did not even want to be their. The guy I really came to like when I was there, liked someone else which was a entire different story within itself, that was a challenging situation, because I am the type of person that will sweat blood and tears to get what i want in life including the guy, I have found out that that works in your career,but doesnt work with people, so it was a lot of let down. 

Well, eventually, I moved back to my hometown single. Me and my ex were still friends, but know the tables were flipped because he was trying to still  like a couple, and i have no desire to be in a relationship with him anymore, this has been a 10 year journey for my ex and I know. So, 10 years later, after moving away from home and moving back home, I do not have any desire to be with him romantically. I can not picture marrying him, having children with him, nothing like that. I like being his friend though and I care about our friendship, I do not want to hurt him in anyway at all. 

Okay, now lets talk about my most recent relationship, I had to give you the back story, so you all could try to understand me as best as possible. I am not at all a relationship hopper, but I probably do have attachment issues. 

Well, about 6 months after I moved back home, happily embracing my single life. A guy at chruch gave me his phone number. He was an older man (18 yrs) older than me and a different culture ( I am black he is white). He seemed very sweet in the beginning, but he moved very fast. I am sorta a slow paced girl, so at the time it felt like he was running and I was trying to keep up. Anyways, he told me he wanted to marry me, he gave me a key to his house, he told me anything I wanted I could have because I had got him out of a deep dark hole in his life. He told me that he had been praying for someone like me, he told me he cried over his Bible because he was so happy that God had sent me to him. I thought that was all very sweet, and I really liked him too, even before he had said all of that stuff, but once he said it, I was in love with him. So, we told each other we loved each other very much. Okay, but this guy also came with some major character flaws, had did some crazy crazy things in his past, so it was a challenge. I did not judge him though. He could be very mean at times, put me down, make me feel basically worthless, but other times he could make me feel like I was the luckiest girl alive. Also, we both had been in similar long term relationships, and we were both trying to move on from them. So, he hated is ex, and I did not hate mine. but I would encourage him to let go of that hate because they did build so much together, she helped him raise his son. Anyways, he would  reassure me that everything was okay, and to overlook his grumpiness because he was just old. Well, like I said the relationship moved pretty fast, and it seemed like I was  trying to play catch up, so when i finally really started becoming comfortable with him, he basically started dating someone  else. I did not find this out with him coming to me saying I don't think it is going to work out. I went to his house on Father's day to take him a cake and his gift and found another car there and found some other woman clothes there. ( my neck and shoulders are tensing up as I am writing this). Anyways, it start going  downhill from that moment. I spent from June 2011 -Feb 2012 crying, depressed, and wishing I was dead, cursing God, and asking what did I do to deserve such treatment. I have been in counseling since september, I have spoken to my priest 3 times about it. I actually went to confession the other day. I feel like a new woman, a different woman after this experience. I still talk to him though from time to time. To keep myself from thinking to harsh of thoughts about him, I say to myself he is trying to find happiness just like me. I have learned a lot, but I stil have hateful thoughts about him sometimes, and I sometimes wish something bad will come to him where he needs me. I know that isn't right to think those things about him. i don't feel that I got the correct closure to this situation. Everytime I have suggested that we meet up and talk, he says he is busy or he will have to see. I say to myself, such great treatment to the one who got who out of a dark place in your life. I thought about writing him a letter and sending him his ipod back that he gave me and his business  card with his name and address on it that he gave me to call him. I think that will be the final closure I need to let go and move on. I don't want to make him feel bad or anything, I just need to let him know how I felt and what I went through, and where I am at right now. I still care about him and love him and i am thankful for the fun experience. but, i think that will give me peace. i am a very expressive person when it comes to my feelings and sharing them. I have developed muscle knots in my neck and shoulders because of this situation. My counselor said it was like a PTSD I went through with getting over him. I just stop having nightmares about the situation in Feb. It hurt me very deeply, but I am healing. I ask my priest about ways of forgiving, and he told me to pray to look at him and see him as God sees him. I have finished reading a book by the Dahli Lama, which was talking about love in general, how we shoulod love everybody including our enemies as we love our best friends or our mothers. So his words have given me , I am know reading a book called the seat of the soul by gary zukav. I am working on my Master's in Psychology, because i want to become a therapist (family and marriage therapist) I learn more and more about myself through all of the research I do . So, it has also helped my healing process.  Anyways, So please let me know what you all think of me writing the letter. I just want to be able to completely forgive him and let go. I know God has great things in store for me, but I know I haven't fully forgiving this guy and usually I am the queen of forgiveness. So, this has been the toughest challenge, and he has apologized many times, but I don't think they are sincere. I do not even consider us friends because friends care about each other, and he does not care about me because if he did he would not have let me go through the suffering i went through, and he knows I suffered. but he might was not capable of being the friend i needed him to be at that time. I also feel as though he needs me in his like more than i need him in mind. he is a perfectionist on the outside, everything has to be in order on his outside environment, everything nice and neat in its place, but internally he is a freaking chaotic mess, more chaotic than my purse. He seems to be going through life aimlessly, just wondering, no rhyme or reason. He also seems to be holding on to his youth. The new girl in his life is younger than me and I am 28, i think she is 23 or 24, i don't know. but she has done somethings to him that could have gotten him put in jail. I worry that if he doesnt change his ways someone is really going to take advantage of him, and it is going to cost him too much money. He has 1 son that is as sweet as can be, and with every decision that he makes in life, he needs to think of his son as well, because with him getting involved with the wrong type of people and being manipulated, some horrible things can happen to him that would affect his son. So, as you can see that I truly care for this individual, even if we are never together again. I don't want him to drive  a cliff, it is like he is blind, he can not recognize good, or he enjoys suffering.  in relationships. As you can see there is a lot going on with this gentleman. This is when i feel compassion for him. Anyways, this would be entailed into the letter, but I would also stop talking to him after I send letter. I would let him know that if he ever needed me I am there for him, but it is no reason that we should talk daily or even weekly or even monthly, just for idle chat, because that upsets me, because I am not completely healed. One good thing that did come from this is he is receiving counseling now, I told him back in january that i was in counseling. He recognized he needs it. So, now all I can do is pray for him after letter is sent. 

As you can see from this letter I go through so many emotions concerning him. I don't want my health to deterioate anymore from this situation, but I don't want him to continue to go through life suffering either. I feel as the letter will plant a seed, and maybe one day he will reflect on it, or maybe not, i don't know, but what I do know by sending the letter and expressing to him what I see going on with him and my journey through meeting him, is that I have done everything in my power, and to continue to pray for him to receive light into his life, but the universe will unfold the rest for it. Hopefully my prayers receive him, because he has had one heck of a life, he could right a best seller, but you should grow from those experiences not continue repeating them. So, I guess sending the letter will give me closure and the peace i desire, i am also sending the ipod back, because i do not need anything to remind me of him. I am also going to send him back his business card I held to so tightly, i carry it in my purse with me. I feel that by doing this it will be letting go in a positive way of all hope I had for our relationship. I have to relinquish control, and let God do the driving, if we are supposed to be togehter we will or if me and my  1st love should be together we will, or maybe their is someone new I supposed to be with, i don't know or maybe I will be devoted to my career and my friends and my dogs. All I know whatever it  is I will be happy because I know one thing for sure my soul and God will  be with me, and as long as I recognize that and keep that at the fore front of my mind I will Always be happy. I am tired of guiding, I am going to let the universe be my guiding force.

Other info for people into astrology:

I am a Leo, moon sign is a sagitarrius, and my rising sign is cancer
The Ex that shattered me is a Cancer ( can you believe that) but I think I might have hurt his feelings and did not realize it and this is how he retaliated. They are very sensitive. I know because it is my rising sign, but I don't go after peoples jugulars, even if I wanted too. They can also be very codependent
My first love is A Taurus: stubborn, control freaks, but very loyal. : )
 
Psychologically:
 I am a ENFP personality type. People who would like to find out their personality type just google Carl Jung personality test. I would advice you to go to similiar minds or the personality page take test and read descriptions.

My personaltity type is very happy go lucky, non judging, accept people for who they are. Like to experience the many depths of human emotions. They say we don't usually complete tasks that we start, but I do, I think that has to do with how i was raised, because i was never allowed to quit anything. Also, this personality type can hold on to bad relationships, and we are also sort of perfectionist in a different way. We blame ourselves if a relationship could not work or was not able to be fixed. Very free spirited people. : ) Very emotional, and are able to feel other people emotions which make us prone to Muscle spasms and body aches.

Google blog things to learn more about your personality as well.

Also, my friend has these crystal tarot cards and I pulled 3 of the cards concentrating on my most recent ex's name and the first card I pulled basically said that there was a light in me that God wanted it to shine. The second card said my life was going through seasons, and the 3rd card said forgiveness, so I am trying to work on the third one, it said release it and let it go. This was back in January. So, I am hoping this letter put me to ease. I was also thinking about putting a release letter of all the pain and hurt and resentment into a balloon and letting it float away. : )

Sorry my blog was so long, please let me know what you all think.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/awcrh1</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/c0o0</id></website><link>http://tinybuddha.com/blog/how-to-let-go-of-a-past-relationship-10-steps-to-peacefully-move-on/</link><postedTime>2010-07-14T06:57:30+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T15:58:01+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miaaeq</id><link>http://tinybuddha.com/blog/how-to-let-go-of-a-past-relationship-10-steps-to-peacefully-move-on/#comment-473699899</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zdeku</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2010-07-14</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>