<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi2nfe/post/2012-03-22T11:35:28</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Typical Prog pig tactic, same tactic terrorist groups use..when they find themselves on the losing end of an issue they call for a truce. For what?  So they can regroup and continue with their assault.
Barry called for toning down the rhetoric, seemingly only for the right, while he &amp; his pundits ramped up their vicious assaults on conservatives.  Barry &amp; Co.'s blatant hypocrisy is being noticed by more people everyday in spite of the media trying to cover for him, which is a good thing. No wonder the Prog pigs want a truce they have no intention of honoring for they have no honor.  I say NO. The left has a track record of a vulgar display of their contempt for everything that made this country great and continue to tear our country down in an attempt to make their insidious agenda humorous or palatable. Enough is enough!  Time to take advantage of the change in Tide/public opinion of these turd brains. Now is not the time to retreat, but to charge ahead with a full assault on Pig Maher, Letterman, Chris Tingles, Barry Soetero and the rest of the hate America crowd.  They brought this on with their assault on Rush, let them feel the wrath of what they do.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y4czo</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/6bwl</id></website><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/bill-maher/2012/03/22/pig-maher-calls-truce</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T13:14:54+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T15:35:28+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi2nfe</id><link>http://nation.foxnews.com/bill-maher/2012/03/22/pig-maher-calls-truce#comment-473678538</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/878uj</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>