<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpkuz4/update/2012-03-22T05:03:20/f7ae7676a5c0b940a293600cccb76005d261296a52a723a0f72bcd92b507810d</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mjayn1</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/z59lm</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>&lt;i&gt;Oh, and I love Lightning. Finally a strong female protagonist in a FF 
game, I have been waiting a long time for that. She's just bad ass and 
just as annoyed by Hope as you will probably be.&lt;/i&gt;

Lightning is an insufferable ice queen with an airport security guard's sense of humor, and the only reason I can imagine anyone tolerating her is because all the other party members except Sazh and Fang are completely unlikeable, and watching someone be a complete asshole to them is almost catharthic.

A character being Cold and mean doesn't have to be a deal breaker for me, if you read the &lt;i&gt;Song of Ice and Fire&lt;/i&gt; books, there will be a number of times when you'll find Arya Stark to be a deeply mentally disturbed girl capable of some truly wretched , but you actually see the fucked up shit that it takes for someone to become a hardened badass like Arya, and you admire her cleverness and want to see her fuck Joffrey to death with a dagger-strap-on even as you question her behavior. 

Lightning gets none of that because you never actually see her backstory, or see her Act charming or like an actual human being. 

A character who just broods never works, you need moments in the story where you become terrified of them, sympathetic for them, see them laugh, see them cry, see them connect with someone who's actually with them, find out what they like, or are made to question whether they can be trusted, or are even good at all. Light fuffills some of that by having to rescue her sister, but seeing as she's the main character of a 50 hour game, that's way too little. 

Going back to &lt;i&gt;Song of Ice and Fire&lt;/i&gt;, Sandor Clegane murders an innocent young boy on the lies of an evil prince without ever expressing sorrow over it, and he's infinitely more sympathetic than Lightning because every time you see him, you find out more about what he likes, what he hates, his phobias, what he finds darkly hilarious, how all this ties into what you know about his past, and you watch as his relationship with Sansa Stark grows. Not to mention that he's a side character rather than a protagonist, and he's not supposed to be regarded as heroic by the audience, as opposed to Lightning.

Lightning is a shit character in a game stuffed with them.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/yn6y3q</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gd1l</id></website><link>http://spoonyexperiment.com/2012/02/16/final-fantasy-x-2-review-part-3/</link><postedTime>2012-02-16T12:13:59+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T09:03:20+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpkuz4</id><link>http://spoonyexperiment.com/2012/02/16/final-fantasy-x-2-review-part-3/#comment-473448762</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/89j77</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-02-16</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>