<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi8xmd/update/2012-03-22T13:26:54/f98ba8376981d3ec2dedfb490cf3ddcf5e9c98a660f9c71ae128a0319662a73b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miar96</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rfm7g</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>@ign-da974da0b33086d40e4b7d24d8209c14:disqus  &amp; @ign-43f3e597355ed77433f53c7c1c4c75fb:disqus .... I know this is only a comments section on a website but I'm kindof offended here. I have an Xbox 360 because I had an Xbox and that was the natural upgrade. I play games of virtually every genre regardless of their review score, single player, multiplayer, age, kinect enabled or anything. My gaming marathons regularly consist of a good few hours on BF3 Conquest, followed by Rock Band/Guitar Hero, some sim-shooting in Operation Flashpoint, sim-racing in Forza and F1, then messing around with kinect games and bargain bin games I Spot in shops. I don't give a crap if you feel the need to offend people to keep your ego in the clouds, but don't think that gives you the god-given right to stereotype and unfairly judge people you don't know. Also why you feel that on PS3 you get a "true" (whatever the hell that means) single player experience, and that this somehow will be any different to any other platform is beyond me. I have an Xbox because I choose to, end of, and it makes no difference other than personal preference gameplay wise, which at the end of the day is the whole reason for gaming!

So grow up, stop stereotyping, and think before you speak. Also I hope I never have the misfortune of ever meeting you or even reading another of your comments ever again.

PS: Maybe I should also point out that if you dislike the Xbox so much, GTFO Off the Xbox section of IGN.
</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yxfzp</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/7d9s</id></website><link>http://xbox360.ign.com/articles/122/1221372p1.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T16:00:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T17:26:54+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi8xmd</id><link>http://xbox360.ign.com/articles/122/1221372p1.html#comment-473772500</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zdza8</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>flagged</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>