<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpwqf5/update/2012-03-22T09:40:49/7dc813cf94e77dba321df4770c83e23a8fcefb271d92365799d242c3c9bf657b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>The "religion of peace" strikes again. I am waiting for the Muslim community to condemn this attack, without their usual bunch of excuses for the perpetrator (and mentioning Gaza or Afghanistan) that make their condemnation sound like a praise. I just want to hear their leaders say: "We abhor this crime, this 'person' is not a true Muslim, and all true Muslims are revolted that someone calling himself a Muslim could do such a thing". And stop there, without beginning their usual litany on how Muslims are "humiliated" and "massacred".
 But this is in vain. It will never happen. Because the armed jihad is a part of their teaching; it is just that some are afraid of admitting it or feel that if they do, people in the countries where they are - yet - minorities will just throw them out for good.

There is another thing I am waiting for - the reaction from the Left. The same Left that was appalled by the murders committed by Breivik (as any reasonable person should be) and could not find strong enough words to condemn his crimes - and all right-wing intellectuals who they held responsible for his Acts. Their silence in this case is deafening. Apparently, they think that it is normal. Wait and you will see: soon they will attack the police for "murdering the terrorist in Cold blood".</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y7ikc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/8cxx</id></website><link>http://www.jpost.com/International/Article.aspx?id=262965</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T11:07:21+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T13:40:49+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpwqf5</id><link>http://www.jpost.com/International/Article.aspx?id=262965#comment-473583928</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6403p</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>