<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/cehpum/update/2011-04-26T12:31:59/b017f6bf4266fe75815d52098a2244af3376a67040fe79f4c8065325d356887f</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Documented, peer reviewed, published and replicated (gold standard) scientific studies provide information on the real and demonstrated non-thermal biological effects of radio frequency electromagnetic radiation at very low intensities, as is the case with the exposure to Wi-fi base station beacon signal used in schools. There is much misinformation regarding the workings of wireless access points, however, it needs to be understood that the Wi-Fi base station beacon signal emits a continuous pulse modulated microwave signal at full strength in a radius of approximately 300 to 500 feet  on the system. This beacon signal is comparable to exposure 20 to 500 feet from a cell tower base station  on proximity, both to the access point and also to the wireless device, such as laptop or ipad. The Wi-Fi beacon signal is not to be confused with the data stream, which is an intermittent exposure coinciding with downloading digital information. This download, however, can exceed safety guidelines for thermal protection Depending on proximity to the computer receiving information (see report by Tony Muc - Thermografix has it posted on website). Exposure to intermittent data stream has been compared to cell phone use by some, although there is really no scientific basis for this comparison - more a seat of the pants subjective judgement.

A typical exposure to Wi-Fi base station beacon signal in schools is approximately 6 hours per day, 5 days per week, over a period of many years. As yet, there are no studies on humans or children that analyze this long term chronic low level exposure. This is understood by regulatory agencies who specifically state that only by watching exposed populations over a period of 20 years or more will the "truth" be known about this exposure. There is general acknowledgement that we are all participating involuntarily in a biological experiment without informed consent.

With regard to animal studies, the non-thermal biological effects scientifically documented and replicated are evidenced by well over two thousand published articles.These documented shorter term exposures at very low intensities in the radiofrequency radiation ranges similar to those used by the Wi-Fi base station beacon signal include:

Changes in immune (0.001 mW/cm2) and decrease in reproductive functions ( at 0.000168-0.0010532 mW/cm2) - irreversible infertility

Increases in calcium efllux from human neuroblastoma cells (at 0.005  W/kg) altering normal cellular functions

Increases in permeability of blood brain barrier (at 0.0004-0.008 W/kg)

Increase in DNA damage in brain cells (at 0.0008 W/kg)

Changes in DNA repair mechanisms (at 0.0037 W/kg)

Effects on skin

Tinnitus and ear damage and effects on eyes (Uveal Melanoma)

Behavioural changes

Sleep disorders and Melatonin reduction

Neurodegenerative diseases

Increases in cancer risks.

See a) Report on Cell Tower Radiation, Professor Girish Kumar b) Lai/Levitt - 2010 - Biological effects from exposure to electromagnetic radiation emitted by cell tower base stations and other antenna arrays" - published National Research Council November 2010, c) Khurana, Hardell et al - 2010 "Epidemiological Evidence for a Health Risk from Mobile Phone Base Stations" - published International Journal of Occupational &amp; Environmental Health 2010 d) International Journal of Occupational Health - Epidemiological Evidence for a Health Risk from Mobile Phone Base Stations, Khurana, Hardell et al - 2010, e) Specific Health Symptoms and Cell PHone Radiation - Evidence of a Dose-Response Relationship - Eger/Jahn 2010.

Specific studies evidencing biological effects of pulse modulated radio frequency radiation at 2.45 GhZ (2450 MHz), a frequency used in Wi-Fi base stations are as follows:


Kerari et al (2010) (in vivo) (rat whole body ) - DNA double strand breaks in brain cells causing significant brain damage and indication of tumour promotion ( exposure 2 hours per day for 35 days). 

Navakatikian and Tomashevskaya (1994) (in vivo) (rat whole body) - Behavioural and endocrine changes and decrease in blood concentrations of testosterone and insulin

Pologeau-Moraru et al (2002) (in vitro) - change in membrane cells in retina

Somosy et al (1991) (in vitro) - molecular and structural changes in cells of mouse embryo

Chou et al (1992) (in vivo) (rat whole body) - alterations in immune system and four fold incrase in primary malignancies and incrase in secondary cancers - 22 months exposure

Havas et al (2010) - pulse modulated 2.45 GhZ radio frequency radiation affects autonomic nervous system at 0.5% of federal guidelines

Avanendo

</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/5ju7xc</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ybx5</id></website><link>http://mindshift.kqed.org/2011/04/cell-phones-wifi-and-the-issue-of-crying-wolf/</link><postedTime>2011-04-25T21:49:01+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2011-04-26T16:31:59+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/cehpum</id><link>http://mindshift.kqed.org/2011/04/cell-phones-wifi-and-the-issue-of-crying-wolf/#comment-192121171</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2011-04-25</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>