<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpwosh/update/2012-03-22T09:54:37/e5161839c193be069334be08cd8463f484d6369378b04243bd3566105ceaeae9</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp1g21</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Although I totally Agree with your opinion about Reed deserving the Spot instead of Heejun-This is just a friendly reminder-Remember the rules of americanidolnet.com  which states ANY POST Left In ALL CAPS will be deleted no matter the content-You seem to have great ideas so next time post in Some CAPS and some lower case --- keep posting --- Now my 2 cents worth....PHILLIP PHILLIPS can Phillip It up (as Steven Tyler said) any song by any artist-His version of Thriller by the LATE GREAT Micheal Jackson was the BOMB ..Maybe he will get to sing it live so all that missed it can see him in his Comfort zone, Not that he needs to be in it to sing the hell out of A song, HE IS COMFORTABLE just Singing and strumming his BABY Mama(aka his Guitar-posted on his facebook by Phillip himself-BTW love this reference) Steven said it best when he said "Phillip YOU JUST ARE ! ! !plain and simple" JLo said it next best- when she said the first time she SAW him sing she could see the Electricity of the music running through his body and she was feeling it too just by watching him sing" When he moves his feet and does the twist with his legs... I am from a small country town in the Great State of Georgia, A Ga. Peach born and raised, BUT If I wasn't from Ga. I would want to move here. We have home grown MANY great artist here and Phillip is one of our best. A Simple GOOD OLE COUNTY Boy, Georgia Born, Georgia Raised and now READY To share his gift to the World..He Will  STAY Simple and true and soon he will Be THE BEST Artist Discovered on American Idol by Far.... The other 9 will fall one by one till its done-What ever the order may be of each one going home is in the end irrelevant THERE CAN ONLY BE ONE to WIN AI2012 and THAT WILL BE .....PHILLIP PHILLIPS.....</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ymhq2</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/mmtc</id></website><link>http://americanidolnet.com/american-idol-2012-top-10-performances-recap/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T02:42:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T13:54:37+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpwosh</id><link>http://americanidolnet.com/american-idol-2012-top-10-performances-recap/#comment-473595853</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>