<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.intensedebate.com:2012:blog/240793/post/72702815/comment/321855243</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Yesterday,lying in Xiangtan Central Hospital in cardiothoracic surgery 36 beds ,was the 3 stab wounds Chen Sheng pale ,and placed at the bedside of flowers contrast .In January 2nd, as Xiangtan MMA union members Chen Sheng alone Yong astrology thief ,being with a knife stabbed ,abercrombie france,3 coats were stained with blood .The time of the incident ,coach outlet store online,the onlookers are mostly silent ,lunette de soleil pas cher,and after the accident ,theft ,flinch ,quietly faded from the scene .Of these ,let the anti-theft member how many disappointed ,they hope more civic-minded people can stand up for .The day before yesterday evening ,louboutin,standing committee of Xiangtan municipal Party committee ,the committee secretary Liao Guofeng hospital visit condolences to Chen Sheng ,he even says three .Alone against the thief in 3 knives on January 2nd afternoon 6 when ,it is the peak flow time .In the District of Xiangtan city infrastructure business crossing the southwest corner ,two men ,franklin marshall,a woman and a child at a back satchel young men .Two men and a woman walked side by side in front of the young man ,an excuse to block the normal young men marching ;behind, with the male youth child blades satchel .In a child from within a mobile phone bag stolen moments ,track after Chen Sheng a  forward, seized him .The child of two male accomplices waded ,chaussures louboutin,with Chen Sheng struggling together, worked as a scout Chen Sheng will soon two down to the ground ,a child was stolen young men under control .When Chen Sheng  for his mobile phone alarm call ,a thief out a folding knife ,from behind the attack on Chen Sheng ,on its back ,mercurial vapor,shoulder even holds 3 knives .Chen Sheng Renzhaojutong continued and the thief ,and finally one uniform ,two men to help me by their !Chen Sheng told onlookers people call ,I hope everyone can help ,abercrombie and fitch,but no one stepped forward to help the onlookers .Chen Sheng four the search for the stolen male youth ,the other has disappeared .Stand a few minutes later, a passing masses to call 110 .Road police station rushed to the scene, the thief over to police ,Chen Sheng was sent to hospital for treatment ,at which point his 3 have all been blood soaked clothes .More than two years previously injured Fanpa obligations Fanpa Chen Sheng in more than two years,cheap herve leger dresses, has captured more than 70 thieves ,was so hurt,christian louboutin, this is the most serious one .Although at the time the crowd showed some Cold ,but later I will still continue to catch thief ,said Chen Sheng .Chen Sheng, Xiangtan is a private voluntary organization anti-thief organization ,founded in 2005 ,they have been in the online call, or launch a close relatives to the MMA ,he was one of the organizers .As the oldest member, member P3 Fanpa disclosed,lunettes pas cher, the annual holiday ,vacation ,union will organize activities .General 2-4 person as a group ,in Xiangtan city is bustling commercial street near the camp ,chaussure de foot,patrol .Encounter thieves ,herve leger dress on sale,is also the first track ,and then in the other to steal the the process of its capture, mainly emphasizes wanting to catch him .The injuries to Chen Sheng allies heart is not easy, everybody thinks later in MMA in the activity to have to pay more attention to outmaneuver .And Chen Sheng are veterans of the anti-theft member sun said ,theft prevention activities continue ,but the public apathy and the owner to make downhearted ,hope more civic-minded people can stand up for .The perpetrators have been detained by public security before 7 ,Chen Shengzheng and a few friends in the ward, chat ,chaussures de foot,standing committee of Xiangtan municipal Party committee ,the committee secretary Liao Guofeng came in ,Chen Sheng even said three to say ,lunette ray Ban,in recognition of his justice .Said Chen Sheng ,MMA League spontaneous behavior faced legal and safe double block ,he put forward the perfection of the organization can be more professional ,more formal .Liao Guofeng said :we want to volunteer organization, launched thousands on thousands of volunteers to participate in ,so you had better ,we should sit down and explore a legitimate security model . news hero rescue fund the fifth batch of relief object identified in Changsha News yesterday ,Provincial Charity Federation decided hero rescue fund the fifth batch of relief objects ,the 8 rescue object will receive at least a month 100 yuan ,up 300 yuan of long-term assistance .Charity ,adidas f50,relief amount is based on the hero family ,franklin marshall pas cher,structure ,physical state and local economic level and other factors to consider the decision after . Hero rescue fund by the Changsha a public love donation which was formed in September last year ,the total amount of 5000000 yuan ,abercrombie pas cher,rescue object due to do boldly what is righteous sacrifices or because of disability resulting in difficult family hero .The fifth batch of relief in the list of the youngest is only 18 years old, Wen Lexing ,on July 17, 2008 afternoon 3 when ,Wen Lexing to save the drowning child Xiao Pinzheng,herve leger on sale, others saved their heroic sacrifice .&amp;#30456;&amp;#20851;&amp;#30340;&amp;#20027;&amp;#39064;&amp;#25991;&amp;#31456;&amp;#65306; &amp;#12288;&amp;#12288;&amp;#27425;&amp;#26085; The captain driving vehicles confiscated hit man rolling leg with eighteen years &amp;#20154;&amp;#29983;&amp;#33509;&amp;#21482;&amp;#22914;&amp;#21021;&amp;#35265;&amp;#65292;&amp;#20309;&amp;#20107;&amp;#31179;&amp;#39118;&amp;#24754;&amp;#30011;&amp;#25159;&amp;#12290;&amp;#31561;&amp;#38386;&amp;#21464;&amp;#21364;&amp;#25925;&amp;#20154;&amp;#24515;&amp;#65292;&amp;#21364;&amp;#36947;&amp;#25925;&amp;#20154;&amp;#24515;&amp;#26131;&amp;#21464;&amp;#12290; </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>article:intensedebate.com:240793:72702815</id><idPostId>72702815</idPostId><idBlogId>240793</idBlogId><idBlog><id>blog:intensedebate.com:240793</id><idBlogId>240793</idBlogId><link>http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com</link><displayName>Are You Healthy?  Are You Happy?</displayName><objectType>blog</objectType></idBlog><link>http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com/2011/01/26/do-you-have-the-post-holiday-blues-happiness-how-to-get-it/</link><displayName>Do you have the Post Holiday Blues?  Happiness:  How to get it.</displayName><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T10:37:02.000Z</postedTime><provider><link>http://im.wordpress.com:8008/comments.json</link><displayName>IntenseDebate</displayName><objectType>service</objectType></provider><object><id>comment:intensedebate.com:240793:72702815:321855243</id><link>http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com/2011/01/26/do-you-have-the-post-holiday-blues-happiness-how-to-get-it/#IDComment321855243</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T10:37:02.000Z</postedTime><displayName>Comment on Do you have the Post Holiday Blues?  Happiness:  How to get it. by 0jyixuan</displayName><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><link>http://louboutinenlignedfr.com</link><idEmailMd5>c0b40f49777a6466ecb51d95bfb241d2</idEmailMd5><displayName>0jyixuan</displayName><objectType>person</objectType></actor><displayName>&lt;a href="http://louboutinenlignedfr.com"&gt;0jyixuan&lt;/a&gt; commented on &lt;a href="http://www.areyouhealthyareyouhappy.com/2011/01/26/do-you-have-the-post-holiday-blues-happiness-how-to-get-it/"&gt;Do you have the Post Holiday Blues?  Happiness:  How to get it.&lt;/a&gt;</displayName><platform>intense-debate</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>