<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp3ssn/update/2012-03-22T08:59:26/a84d09e44530571f7b15b4f0076176a0b1082e2faaa23d0baf0ee621a2a8251a</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Good to see Matt Joyce hopefully continue to develop the power that Freidman and Tampa traded Edwin Jackson for but he still has a ways to go when facing LHP. His major drop in average at the end of 2011 has to be somewhat of a concern after it looked like he was finally figuring things out at the plate. Now the question this season will be if that was just a slump that all hitters go through or his good average for most of 2011 was just a fluke. Joyce might be a guy that needs to be slotted in a certain Spot in the order so he gets comfortable, like the 6th or 5th Spot behind a guy like Zobrist. The Luke  experiment is starting to worry. 6 strikeouts in 19 at-bats. Tampa can't have another Pat Burrell. As a veteran that has had good success in this division in the past he does deserve some time to show that he can help. Another problem that the Rays can't get right was something that killed them in 2011, hitting W/RISP. .220 W/RISP was next to last in the A.L. and adding more strikeouts in Pena and  could hurt more. They just can't keep putting so much pressure on this pitching staff. Another good outing from Howell is a good sign that his injuries are healing well and he is getting back to the pitcher he was before 2010. He's a needed piece to this bullpen as we have seen when he's been out. Former Rays minor leaguer Cesar Cabral keeps throwing well in Yankees camp to an ERA around 2. Looks like Tampa kept the wrong Cesar. Just another former Ray doing good things for another club. New Yorks lineup has gotten even scarier with the addition of Russell Branyan who if he gets the at-bats should hit a lot of home runs in Yankee Stadium. Just another reason why Tampa has to get better W/RISP. He's a good option at D.H. vs LHP when the Yankees are at home. Hitting 31 home runs when playing in Seattle was impressive since noone has done it in that park.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6d01fo</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/lz6q</id></website><link>http://tampabay.rays.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120321%26content_id=27477034%26vkey=news_tb%26c_id=tb</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T19:29:13+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T12:59:26+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp3ssn</id><link>http://tampabay.rays.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20120321%26content_id=27477034%26vkey=news_tb%26c_id=tb#comment-473554388</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cszkh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>