<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpkecg/post/2012-03-22T03:47:12</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpi9wr</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/muqtz</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I'll need to respond to this post tomorrow, as I am getting tired (its 2 am here)...but judging from this post...it appears that you are well read and studied on enivornmental news.  That being said, you either ,unknowingly or blantantly, left out key factors that may have helped you further understand the AP article you are quoting. 

 First of all, not once did you mention Wet Flue Gas Desulphirization WFGD as a counter to MACT and CAIR EPA rulings.   on the size and number of Units it needs to service, a WFGD can cost anywhere from 500M-2B and take anywhere from 1-3 years to build.  So if First Energy's plants are on the high end build (which I am sure they did an engineering economic analysis to figure out, perhaps even engineered a specification document) then I can definately applaud First Energy for jumping ahead of the game.  

To your comments about Coal being less than 40% of the countries total output of power...the USEIA says 46%.  We've got teams that watch that stuff...daily.

Quoting you...

"Today’s historically low natural gas prices, which are not expected to increase much any time soon, mean it is more expensive to produce power using coal-fired plants than natural gas plants."

-You go ahead and start building Natural Gas plants all over the United States.  Terrorist target anyone?  Natural Gas, as I am sure you know...is very volitile.  Yes, I am well aware that coal plants pose a threat too, but Coal explosions and NG explosions are two completely different animals.

-Coal is still an inexpensive way to produce electricity, and if they remove it too quickly, its going to do more harm than good.  Our coal plants employ more than 400 employees as well as many many more contractors. 

Regarding solar energy, They have trying to perfect it for quite sometime...and if you have a track record of Physics, then you know of the theoretical efficiency limits on Solar Cells. See Shockley-Quisser limit documentation posted everywhere online.  By comparsion of the theoretical efficency limits of carnot engines and steam turbines far outweigh them.  And Nuclear DWARFs Wind and Solar efficiency limits.  Wind and solar will forever be supplemental, and not primary.  

-2010 Winter was devestatingly Cold in our area...i dont know about yours.

-2011 Winter was mild, but summer 2012 is expected to be really rough.

Im nodding Off here so I have to go.  
Look forward to your response.  


  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yapoa</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ai6</id></website><link>http://politicalwire.com/archives/2012/03/21/romney_embraces_bush_economic_policy.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T21:11:37+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T07:47:12+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpkecg</id><link>http://politicalwire.com/archives/2012/03/21/romney_embraces_bush_economic_policy.html#comment-473426321</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hjjht</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>