<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mj4w61/update/2012-03-19T19:36:09/c40e9198abd9585880d7488000e617371c451bf56974fb27ba08989c37d61f62</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>So Craig Dearden-Phillips thinks that changes to employment law proposed by Think Tanks Aligned with the current government will be welcomed up and down the country. Not by thousands of paid workers in our sector who are undervalued, lack job security and are being asked to do more work for less pay.

Employment Tribunals may not be perfect but they currently offer basic protection for hundreds of thousands of employees in the UK. However most employees can still be easily dismissed within their first year of employment, and unless they argue a discrimination case these workers do not have the option of going to an Employment Tribunal. If an employee is not capable of doing their job this should be Spotted within the first year when it is cheap to dismiss them.

Dearden-Phillips’s suggestion that employees should stump up a £500 deposit would be a massive barrier to most potential users of an Employment Tribunal no matter how good their case is.  This would undoubtedly reduce the number of claims going to Tribunals, but it is hardly fair on a potential claimant who may have lost their job through blatant discrimination on the part of the Employer.

Employees whose claims are found to be vexatious are already liable for the full costs of an Employment Tribunal – a fact that employment advice agencies and Trades Unions are at pains to highlight to their clients and members.

As other contributors have commented, the real issue here is the ability and willingness of managers at all levels to effectively support, supervise and develop their employees.  This should be the focus of Third Sector leaders - not jumping onto an ideological party political bandwagon.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/68o857</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/uvcp</id></website><link>http://www.thirdsector.co.uk/news/1121594/Craig-Dearden-Phillips-Changes-employment-law-will-welcomed-down-country/?DCMP=ILC-SEARCH</link><postedTime>2012-03-13T10:54:36+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-19T23:36:09+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mj4w61</id><link>http://www.thirdsector.co.uk/news/1121594/Craig-Dearden-Phillips-Changes-employment-law-will-welcomed-down-country/?DCMP=ILC-SEARCH#comment-469497120</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/r4rto</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-13</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>