<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpiiwl/update/2012-03-22T02:53:46/071a26dc23a28b6d902a65e83d9934d1ceceeb0205d5105e6550e2fbe856e411</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>. So what you're saying is that Cambodia is one of the most environmentally degraded, corrupt, miserable and hopeless places on earth. Stick your finger out will ya....It is precisely the opinion of people like yourself that's the reason why Cambodia is so far behind where it should be in its development, and why people have such a badly misinformed opinion about the country.

Why did you not also mention these (also easily accessible) facts:

(1) That Cambodia has reduced its rate of new HIV infections from its peak of 15,500 per year in the early 1990s to 2,100 last year. This is despite Cambodia's population increasing from 9.5 million people in 1993 to over 14.8 million in 2010. In other words, new HIV infections have decreased by over 85% in the same period while the population has increased by 60%. 

(2) That in 1993 100% of the country's budget was composed of foreign aid. GDP per capita was less than $100 per year, almost zero. In 2011 GDP per capita (nominal) is nearing $1000 ($2500 PPP) while real GDP growth rates have averaged 8% between 2001-2010. This is the second highest recorded growth in Asia after China. The Cambodian economy in 1993 was entirely reliant on donors, while in 2011 nominal GDP has  $10 billion, and exports (garments, rice, seafood, rubber) have grown to more than $6.5 billion. Thats right, Cambodia is now exporting food to the world.

(3) When Mr Chan Sonn Ek became
director-general of the Phnom Penh Water Supply Authority (PPWSA) nearly 20 years ago,
the city had a dismal water supply, with nearly 83% lost to leakages and
unauthorised connections.&#x2028; Fifteen years after he took over, annual water
production had increased by more than 400%, the water distribution network had
grown by more than 450%, and the customer base had increased by more than
650%.&#x2028;Today, PPWSA says that there are
no unauthorised connections in Phnom Penh, while losses from the water system
are just over 5%, similar to what one would find in Singapore or Tokyo, two of
the best water-supply systems in the world, and better than London. Later this
year PPWSA will become the first company to list on the Cambodia Securities
Exchange (CSX).








(4) The Cardamom Mountains in the southwest of the country form Southeast Asia's last remaining tracts of virgin rainforest, and house rare and endangered species including the Siamese crococodile (extinct everywhere else in Asia). The Mekong River near Kratie is the only place left in the wild where you can Spot the endangered Irrawaddy river dolphin. Same goes for the sarus crane (the world tallest flying bird) and the red-headed vulture - Cambodia is the only place left in the world where you can Spot these critically endangered species, and in Cambodia numbers are actually rising. I can go on and on... 

(5) In 1993 no tourists visited Cambodia. By 2001, about 100,000 were visiting, then by 2005, over a million foreign tourist were visiting. Cambodia Reached the 2 million mark by 2008, and this year the country is on track to receive about 3.2 million tourists. The tourists include backpackers, families, business travellers, and yes, the luxury market too.

So, citizenviewer, it is very easy to selectively copy and paste facts to conform to a biased narrative like your depressing one. It is also irresponsible and ignorant.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6g2eg0</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/gcrd</id></website><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/asia/cambodia/9147837/Cambodia-Beyond-the-killing-fields.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-16T10:25:43+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T06:53:46+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpiiwl</id><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/asia/cambodia/9147837/Cambodia-Beyond-the-killing-fields.html#comment-473411892</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/h3ndz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-16</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>