<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miciot/update/2012-03-22T14:38:58/f27c7b911cd085e4887e2ae855bdab0e0bcc79d9e6e2e1f350638ffaa2a05c61</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Sorry folks but the iphones size is not going to change. First thing is it's the perfect phone size. Why would apple want it to get any bigger when it's already the perfect size? You can control the phone with one thumb. You can read everything on it clear as day because of the retina display. It fits perfectly in the pocket. There is no need for more screen space on the iphone. All of it's apps in the app store are made for the 3.5 inch retina display. Do you think apple would really do this? Developers would have to change their apps and they would loose display quality going up in size to a display that isn't a retina display. Trust me folks apples iphone size is staying that size a long long time. The sweet Spot for regular folk and tech folks alike is this size. Iphone users enjoy the fact that it is the size is it. They like to be able to navigate through the phone with one hand and one thumb. This is the size a mobile phone should be. If you are a power geek than Android phones hit all your Spots with their various display sizes. You can pick an Android phone up anytime! Iphones will  have a 3.5inch display. Every iphone user i've talked to never says MAN i wish this screen was bigger. They could care less about screen size. Why? Because screen size matter nothing with apples display technology. A smart phone is meant to function as a pocket computer. To check email, make calls, send texts, and Surf the web. All of these things can be done with ease on the iphone with it's current display. The great thing about this is it helps android be android with it's large displays. Android's place in the market is for the folks who want the larger displays. Many do want a larger screen but also many do not want the larger screen. I'm one of the people who love the size of the iphone. It fits for my hands. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yyy62</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rf3e</id></website><link>http://www.technobuffalo.com/companies/apple/iphone/apples-iphone-5-may-sport-larger-4-6-inch-display/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T04:17:45+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T18:38:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miciot</id><link>http://www.technobuffalo.com/companies/apple/iphone/apples-iphone-5-may-sport-larger-4-6-inch-display/#comment-473831585</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/5uijf</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>