<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mj8y0v/update/2012-03-18T23:06:50/4fc9465a372e1d98d353bec5bf266112b69f706d0944c726af36bc3d03d263c9</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m93v17</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>We don’t know what causes fibromyalgia, and even the risk factors are not entirely clear.  More women than men get fibromyalgia, and it usually develops in adulthood or middle age.  A family history of fibromyalgia and a personal history of rheumatoid disease (such as arthritis or lupus) increase your risk.  Some people believe that poor sleeping habits, mental or physical trauma, and repetitive activities (such as difficult physical labor or intense sports) increase the risk.  Some research suggests a connection between Lyme disease and fibromyalgia, two conditions that are often confused because they have similar symptoms.
Treatment is aimed at controlling fibromyalgia’s symptoms, since there is no cure for the condition.  The treatments you should have Depend on your symptoms.  Usually, muscle aches and stiffness are treated with heat, massage, stretching, and exercise.  If those non-drug treatments don’t do the job, pain medications or steroid injections can be used.  Relaxation and stress relief techniques can help reduce aches and pains and also lessen Sleep problems, depression, and Anxiety.  Acupuncture gives some people relief from stiffness and pain.  .......   American pain Association

Since having lupus increases your risk maybe you should prepare yourself........wouldn't that be ironic.  Then you could walk in their shoes and finally understand.  Fibro is treated by medical doctors, not shrinks.  Rheumatologists, neurologists, infectious doctors, general practioners, physical therapists, acupuncturist....  It is real......I pray you never have to find out first hand what it is like although, that might be what you need.  Show some compassion for your fellow humans......whether they suffer from physical or mental illnesses makes no difference.  We are all here to support each other.  Your ignorance is offending to many.  I pray you have not caused further duress to those individuals.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/ysktac</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/oys5</id></website><link>http://www.butyoudontlooksick.com/articles/written-by-christine/the-spoon-theory-written-by-christine-miserandino/</link><postedTime>2012-03-05T14:22:33+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-19T03:06:50+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mj8y0v</id><link>http://www.butyoudontlooksick.com/articles/written-by-christine/the-spoon-theory-written-by-christine-miserandino/#comment-468719116</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-05</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>