<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi5rv8/update/2012-03-22T15:07:44/aeb74c4da70139d0290cb0a338e43690f354e7bfe937a1d52197f5f05188610b</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>A police report made public on Wednesday said Martin's death was originally investigated as a homicide, specifically an "unnecessary killing to prevent an unlawful ."
The report, made by the first two officers to arrive at the scene of the shooting, cited a state law that says someone who unnecessarily kills another person while trying to prevent that person from committing an unlawful , "shall be deemed guilty of manslaughter."
The report said that when the first officer arrived, Martin was lying "face-down on the ground" with his hands beneath him and that Zimmerman told the officer "that he had shot the subject and he (Zimmerman) was still armed."
The officer said he handcuffed Zimmerman and removed the gun and holster from inside Zimmerman's waistband, and saw that his back was "wet and covered in grass" and that he was "Bleeding from the nose and back of his head."
Zimmerman was put in the backseat of a police cruiser, given first aid by paramedics and taken to the police station to be interviewed by investigators. 
The first officer at the scene, Timothy Smith, wrote in the report that he did not question Zimmerman at the scene. 
In his answers, Lee explained that when police arrived at the scene, Zimmerman "provided a statement claiming he  in self-defense, which at the time was supported by physical evidence and testimony."
Lee quoted Zimmerman as saying that "he had lost sight of Trayvon and was returning to his truck .... when he says he was attacked by Trayvon."
Lee said that under Florida law police were prohibited from arresting Zimmerman because he said he Acted in self-defense.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yrsqd</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5gat</id></website><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/22/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T06:52:55+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T19:07:44+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi5rv8</id><link>http://www.cnn.com/2012/03/22/justice/florida-teen-shooting/index.html#comment-473853170</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/czd4z</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>