<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpoa54/update/2012-03-22T01:16:45/5167c14666d5f2a806b5a22254c015f12852583cdf3cb86373f5bbe1f1007960</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>William Moulton Marston was one of the first pop-media feminists of the 20th century. To say that he wanted to "subjugate women" shows a total misunderstanding of BDSM culture and polyamorous relationships.

 BDSM relationships are often entered into with a contract between partners (a sub and dom) thus CONSENT is the number one value. It is often repeated, BDSM must be "safe, sane, and consensual, and if you can't have the first two, you must have the third", therefore rules are set down from the beginning whereas in many relationships people push boundaries until they anger and hurt one another and then are uncomfortable talking about those boundaries. I feel much more in control of my body and emotional well-being when this contract is discussed and set forth to begin with. A great example of this is the safe word. No matter what, if you say your safe word, a dom (or female domme) must stop in their tracks, no questions asked. They may only begin again with your permission. Thus in many ways, a submissive has more power and control than their dominant. There is also a spiritual aspect to being restrained, this is called "sub-space" wherein the body disconnects from the physical and the sub allows their safety to fall completely into a hands of the dom. For someone like myself, with Anxiety disorder this is amazingly freeing and one of the few times when I am able to forget about my condition.As for polyamory, not all BDSM relationships are so. Many are monogamous. Some are single agreed upon encounters, not relationships. Moulton Marston however, was a polygamist as he lived with two women who  as his wives and raised their children as one family. After his death these women continued living together and were reportedly very close though one can never know if they had bi-sexual attractions. When people think of polygamy they are often clouded by images of fundamentalist-mormons and their big-haired frumpily dressed wives on compounds. Not all polygamy (even among mormons) is this abusive travesty we have come to know. When people are open about their multiple attractions and again CONSENT to said activities between partners, this is a perfectly healthy, happy lifestyle.

I just wanted to say that bondage themes in Wonder Woman and the home-life of her creator are not in any way demeaning. Marston understood that consensual bondage games could teach women dominance and give them a sense of power. Being a polygamist also doesn't disqualify him from being a feminist as it was a consensual relationship among adult equals who were aware of one another and carried out with respect. Sadly, the media really doesn't take the time to compassionately display either of these lifestyles and that causes a lot of confusion and perversion of what they are about. 
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------

On another note; I understand some being uncomfortable about the Amazons mating with and then murdering men and then casting Off their sons; but for me this story is about Diana. She is in many ways growing up in this story, learning who she really is. Who you are is not who your parents are. My mother was raised by abusive alcoholics, thus she spent her life dedicated to being sober, a good parent, and having a successful marriage. I see Diana in this same way. She is horrified at what she comes from. Her utopia has cracks, they all do. But she is better than that. She is Wonder Woman not just because she is an Amazon, but because she is the BEST Amazon. She is evolved and in this way is a saviour for her race.  Just my thoughts.</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y53yu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/m7rp</id></website><link>http://dcwomenkickingass.tumblr.com/post/19704793909</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T00:06:55+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T05:16:45+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpoa54</id><link>http://dcwomenkickingass.tumblr.com/post/19704793909#comment-473279922</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zm0kh</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>