<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp0p2g/update/2012-03-22T10:56:15/437e8b99d3bbe55451f621999a45e7aaa42e3276e3aa8db40d537d600c4cfa00</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Jessica continues to impress me, so I'll say she's on top right now.  She's the one to beat.

Let me just say that Billy Joel's a bad fit for Idol.  Joel's a talented guy, but his music is from another Era.  Unlike many 
of the other classics they've covered, Joel's music is dated, which 
might explain his lack of a comeback and the way he's coasted on fame 
from the late 70s early 80s for the 20+ years since "we didn't start the
 fire." (his last hit that I can remember)   Too many slow ballads, too much cocaine in the songwriting, too Long Islandey.  

Heejun is having fun, and that's worth something.   He's not going to win and he knows it.  He's got a loyal fan base, and a Spot on the tour.  This is all just build up for his potential career.  I don't expect to see Heejun's albums on sale any time soon, but do expect to see him in ads and possible cameos in sketch comedy shows/sitcoms. 

Many of the Idols ignored Tommy Hilfinger's advice, mostly out of ego.  The man knows what he's talking about.  Phil Phillips got a little too high on himself, and his schtick has run thin. And dude, that outfit looked awful on him.  Adding Hilfinger is like saying "we're trying to see here who can be a complete package and who's going to fit into the industry."  yeah yeah yeah, rebel this and that is fine, but it doesn't sell units.  The advisors have all made millions making music, so it's worth listening to people who know what they speak of.  

Colton Dixon's a bit of an enigma.  Great performance, cool punk rocky look, but wait...John 3:16 on the sign his peeps were hoisting?  Comments about how god spoke through him?  Too many religious references will hurt his street cred...and votes.  

Deandre, aka Milli Vanilli Jr, is a throwback to the late 80s/early 90s.  He's talented and hungry, but not quite what the people are seeking.  He'll do well on his own I suspect, but the rest of Idol's going to get rougher on this young man.  He'll disappear for a few years and make a stunning comeback with a new sound. 

Anyone else feel like Molly was prepping for her opening in Las Vegas for Wayne Newton?  Elise was good, but she won't last...another one who ignored Tommy Hilfinger at her own peril.  Those curtains she wore last night could mean curtains for her singing career.  Skylar hasn't impressed me yet.  Erika's new look is an improvement, but it's not enough to make her look like a rock star.  </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ymz60</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/vh3p</id></website><link>http://popwatch.ew.com/2012/03/21/american-idol-heejun-han-steven-tyler-billy-joel/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T02:43:30+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T14:56:15+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp0p2g</id><link>http://popwatch.ew.com/2012/03/21/american-idol-heejun-han-steven-tyler-billy-joel/#comment-473642645</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>