<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/z6cb5/update/2009-11-24T16:52:19/51c0e94b8dd2a28952bbd6c09ea9fa5d5c17f1aa5741f68ac6390476c30b59b7</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>It's absolutely important to have a distinct style and essential to provide clients work that reflects it. A client is hiring you based on your portfolio and can only expect you'll give them an illustration that reflects what they see. With very limited exceptions (perhaps only with the most conceptual work [niemann fits in here] for the exceptions), a client is hiring you for the combination of your style and your interpretation/ideation skills. If you remove your style from the equation to try something new on the client's dime (without discussing it with them first) you can put the client in a bad Spot. They may have to kill the job and hire someone else, or with little time left they could be forced to run the work even though it has not met the expectations of the editorial or creative team. As a last resort they might have to resort to an immediate band aid such as an all-nighter typographic solution or gasp, stock photography. Illustrators and photographers may not realize that when art comes in -target it generally involves a number of emergency tactics and meetings to Resolve, adding to the burden of the creative team's rushed schedule at deadline time. Memories like that can last a career, and rarely will an art director take another chance with an illustrator they feel has let them down.

Art director's have bosses too, bosses that hold them to the overall success of the magazine in their eyes (not yours). A failure on the art director's side in meeting the expectations of an assignment is going to have cumulative consequences, so they are going to avoid situations where they don't know what they will get. 

That said I don't think illustrator's styles should remain completely rigid over time or they will 'date' faster. I suggest doing personal work for self expression and exploration whether it will 'qualify' to be part of your portfolio or not. Use that exploration to inform your illustration work and encourage it's growth subtly over time. 

Nate's comment about Modern Dog is right on. As a design firm they can decide what illustration style best suits a project and either hire an illustrator or create the illustration themselves. So for people with strong design skills and desire to avoid one style of illustration, having a small design firm may be a better shingle to hang than that of 'illustrator'. </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/orcud</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/5l6y</id></website><link>http://www.n8w.com/wp/2043</link><postedTime>2009-11-23T23:10:16+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2009-11-24T21:52:19+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/z6cb5</id><link>http://www.n8w.com/wp/2043#comment-23985868</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2009-11-23</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>