<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi2pdz/post/2012-03-22T11:48:00</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpwkhk</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/d7sbb</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>"He carried the gun for protection and to use to intimidate."
Where did you read that? The Florida Concealed Carry Law strictly forbids the brandishing of a weapon to  the upper hand. If true he broke the law in the past and should have been arrested. Just this year the law was amended to allow "accidental' exposure of a concealed weapon... i.e. Reaching for an item in a store and your weapon is exposed from under your shirt.
Your last point, "unarmed" is also erroneous. Most 'stand your ground statutes' don't require the aggressor to be 'armed' only for the person using 'deadly force' to be 'in fear for thier life' or the life of another being assaulted by the aggressor. In other words, a 80 pound little old lady can shoot a 6'6" 300 pound unarmed man stone Cold dead 'if she is in fear of her life.'
All said... I agree that the tapes support vigilantism and Zimmerman was looking for trouble... to be the hero. We'll never know all the facts in this case but the law is not at fault.
P.S. Not knowing all the facts, a judge in South Florida ruled justifiable homicide when a man chased down a burglar and stabbed the alleged burglar to death... if true, even judges misinterpret the law.
</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yevkq</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zmzu</id></website><link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2012/mar/21/was-florida-shooter-vigilante-or-diligent-neighbor/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T01:46:31+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T15:48:00+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi2pdz</id><link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2012/mar/21/was-florida-shooter-vigilante-or-diligent-neighbor/#comment-473689598</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/y9p3i</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>