<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpu4im/update/2012-03-21T22:44:17/b000e776e74897a1a1dbcd97d05f61a53dc813a59c0fc4641af9affcd9d87650</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpxoyk</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/cmian</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>The Flight Attendants don't do a valuable service???  Obviously non of your family were on flights on 9/11. Obviously you have never experienced a medical emergency inflight.  It's clear you have never been injured by severe turbulence or had an obnoxious or unruly passenger sit next to you for 6 hours. You've been lucky enough to  never experience any kind of emergency situation and needed to be briefed for an evacuation.  I guess the mere fact that flight attendants are trained to evaluate specific passenger behaviors and look for potential terrorists and even possible child trafficking on board EVERY flight... and to intercept "problem passengers"... so that people like you can have a calm and uneventful trip is not valuable???...  Of course we do these things silently day in and day out when the need arises.... but mostly... I'd like to talk to you after a 10 hour flight... Where you were given no food, no drink, no one turned on the inflight movie or told the cockpit when you were too Cold or too hot so the cabin temperature could be adjusted.  Then when it suddenly went from a smooth flight to a very bumpy one... no one was there to help you when you fell...  no one to warn you to fasten your seat belt so you could be safe prior to the turbulence... No one there to  your child who is traveling ALONE a sad causality of divorced parents and is crying in the seat by his or her self after  leaving one parent ....and as a mom  (or dad) the flight attendant is the person who sits and visits with your child to  him/her up give them something to do and walks them Off the plane to meet the other parent and verifies their identification in a new city... (or country) .... Finally, when some annoying  passenger is sitting behind you and kicking the back of your seat.. who ya gonna call to intercede so you are not having a confrontation with a stranger?... Frankly Petem... people like you are what is wrong with this industry... You apparently value nothing when it comes to air travel (other than the pilot and mechanic)  I can't wait until vending machines are in the back of the plane to suffice as "service" for folks like you....  Good luck and have a nice flight!</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ycq32</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/71fv</id></website><link>http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2012-03-21/amr-said-to-ready-bankruptcy-court-bid-to-dump-contracts.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T22:43:22+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T02:44:17+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpu4im</id><link>http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2012-03-21/amr-said-to-ready-bankruptcy-court-bid-to-dump-contracts.html#comment-473069599</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zm36z</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>