<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/micbsa/update/2012-03-22T14:25:23/cca1cf6ad3461d5e6693c891c130cbb6357af6cc4fd1a71aac50354cf3aed393</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>(self-indulgence alert)

Yesterday I made the bellow comment long after the thread had gone Cold, but I want it out there. TT inferred that I was negative on our soldiers and that I attack them. I am very down on US military policy and I realize that this can lead to assumptions about the soldiers. Therefore, I want to be clear about how I feel about the men and women serving:

----

You're way Off about the soldiers, TT. As I've often said, what I feel most passionate about is how our soldiers were made victims by their superiors. They were shown the ultimate disrespect- &lt;i&gt;they were asked to sacrifice under false pretenses&lt;/i&gt;. I feel compelled to support them by speaking out, as loudly as I can, against the system that has treated them like pawns - as if they were disposable and not real people with families - and by demanding that their torment end. I have great admiration for our soldiers and the near impossible task they've voluntarily accepted- I loath their betrayal.

In the case of this particular atrocity (the murder of 16 civilians), I don't blame our service men and women in general nor even the one or many perpetrators. It's a matter of poor planning and unrealistic expectations. Their mission is unclear and often baffling- because it's based on a ruse. And we cannot expect a person to endure multiple and extended tours of duty under hellish conditions in a place where they can't tell ally from foe and emerge unscathed. The mental and physical toll on our soldiers is well documented- this (tragedy) is a consequence of mismanagement and dishonest policy.

Read more: http://swampland.time.com/2012/03/21/morning-must-reads-coalescing/#disqus_thread#ixzz1przSef4N</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ytmtp</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/vhd6</id></website><link>http://swampland.time.com/2012/03/22/morning-must-reads-painful/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T12:29:32+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T18:25:23+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/micbsa</id><link>http://swampland.time.com/2012/03/22/morning-must-reads-painful/#comment-473821345</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/hf3by</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>