<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi26cg/post/2012-03-22T11:17:58</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpeagt</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6t3vp</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body> 


 IAF101 and grenadiers

Whose version of the truth? The police's? When 10 years later it is proved to
be a lie?

ibnlive: fake-encounters-does-police-have-a-license-to-kill


You might have a short memory and some agenda of your own to believe the state
machinery-police, politicians. I don't.

1997: 'CONNAUGHT PLACE ENCOUNTER'; I won't forget PRADEEP GOEL murdered in a fake encounter at Delhi by Additional Commissioner of Police (ACP) SS RATHI of DELHI POLICE. 2011: The supreme court upheld the conviction of ACP SS RATHI and his NINE teammates. 

2000:'CHATTISINGHPORA SIKH MASSACRE AND THE ANANTNAG YOUTHS KILLED IN FAKE ENCOUNTER FOR IT'; I can't forget how first 35 sikhs were killed in Cold blood in CHATTISINGHPORA in Kashmir, at the time of BIlli Clinton's visit to India todraw his attention to Pakistan's interference in India occupied Kasmir. 5 days later 5 alleged militants involved in the SIkh massacre were killed in an encounter
by the army and state police and later they were proved to be innocent KASHMIRI CIVILIAN YOUTHS by the enquiry conducted by CBI and the SUPREME COURT. Justice Pandian found that the alleged militants who were killed by the local police and the security forces following the Chattisinghpora massacre were in
fact innocent civilians.

2000:'ANSAL PLAZA FAKE ENCOUNTER'; I won't forget the two unarmed and crippled KASHMIRI YOUNGSTERS shot at point blank range after having been mercilessly beaten first by the team of delhi police officers led by ACP RAJBIR SINGH. BTW, MOHAN CHAND SHARMA, the officer who got shot in the stomach at BATLA HOUSE and died was part of ACP RAJBIR SINGH's team. The witness to this FAKE ENCOUNTER, Dr. HARI KRISHNA  I salute him for standing up to the witch hunting of the
INDIAN ESTABLISHMENT and standing by his witness account and not turning 'hostile' as scores of witnesses in other cases which go against the establishment, have had to because of massive intimidation and harassment by the police and politicians. 

2004: 'MANIPUR RAPE AND FAKE ENCOUNTER'; I can't forget THANGJAM MANORAMA (34YRS) who was picked up by ASSAM RIFLES on the suspicion of being a militant and whose bullet riddles body was found later. She was FIRST RAPED AND THEN MURDERED. Stripped of all human dignity, I mourn her and the hardships the people of MANIPUR and KASHMIR and the NAXALITE AREAS have had to endure in the efforts of the INDIAN state winning their 'hearts and minds'.

2004: I am not going to forget ISHRAT JAHAN, JAVED SHAIKH and the two other nameless victims of Deputy Inspector  General (DIG) DG VANZERA AND Joint Commisioner of POLICE of GUJRAT PC PANDE'S DIABOLICALLY IMAGINATIVE AND TRIGGER HAPPY team. Ishrat's family has told that she was shot in her private parts as well, suggesting that there was RAPE AND COVERUP. tHE POST MORTEM REPORT CONFIRMS THE INJURIES. This same team in collaboration with MUMBAI ENCOUNTER SPECIALIST DAYA NAYAK was responsible for the murders of SAMIR PATHAN, SADIQ
JAMAL, SOHRABUDDIN SHAIKH, HIS WIFE KAUSAR BI AND THEIR ASSOCIATE TULSIDAS PRAJAPATI.

These and many others are the documented cases of encounters which were recently proven to be fake and actually murders in Cold blood of innocent civilians at the whim of GOONS IN UNIFORM. But given the timeline, people who are not aware of the speed of the Indian Judicial system can see, how
excruciatingly painful it must for the families and the fair minded people of this country to wait to find out. These were the very few that could run the whole judicial course.

There are many, many more which can not be followed up in a court of law because of improper and incomplete First Information Reports (FIRs) by corrupt junior police officers. The magnitude of communal violence in the 2002 Gujrat riots and the discouragingly low number of cases in the courts are a case in
point. Of them, the cases which have Reached a verdict or even the high court can be counted on a single hand. The 'BEST BAKERY CASE' where Zahira Shaikh, the prime witness suffered more for perjury than did the convicted rapists and murderers who are still out. The' BILKIS BANO CASE',  where I believe
justice was served but by the last ounce of utmost effort of the involved NGOs and TEESTA SEETALVAD. And finally, the ongoing 'GULBARGA SOCIETY MASSACRE', where an old widow, ZAKIA JAFFERY is showing the courage we all need to show, in fighting for justice.
 
But there is an endless list of highly disturbing incidents that need an explanation if the sanctity of the INDIAN DEMOCRATIC SYSTEM is to be preserved:

2008: 'AARUSHI AND HEMRAJ MURDERS': Where instead of honestly attempting to solve the cases, NOIDA police, DELHI police and the CBI have just been covering up after each other and there are no answers to even the most elementary questions expected of our sleuths. Instead a whole character assassination campaign was carried out against AARUSHI, HEMRAJ, THE TALWARS, THEIR FAMILY
FRIENDS. It defies logic and just shows how incapable our police is at actual investigations, you know, where they can't pin the crime on the poor domestic help or a person from the minority community doing it at the behest of a foreign power.

2008: 'BATLA HOUSE ENCOUNTER' of 22 yr old ATIF and 16 yr old SAJID the boys police claims as
masterminds of INDIAN MUJAHIDEEN which has carried out nearly all blasts since 2007-2012.  Scores of ATIF's and SAJID's friends, all students in their 20s, nearly all either bleonging to JAMIA MILIA UNIVERSITY or their home town AZAMGARH are behind bars since 2008, not yet CHARGESHEETED though, FOR 40-50 SUCH BLAST RELATED CASES IN DELHI, UP, RAJASTHAN, ANDHRA PRADESH, GUJRAT..

How long will the judicial procedure take if it takes 10 yrs on average per case? In the case of these nearly 20 incarcerated boys, it hasn't even started. WILL IT FINISH IN THEIR LIFETIME? JUSTICE DELAYED IS ACTUALLY JUSTICE VERY MUCH DENIED. And now youth from minority populated areas in BIHAR are being similarly unlawfully picked by the police. 

Why on earth can't the govt. order a judicial enquiry in the incident that started it all the BATLA HOUSE ENCOUNTER AND WHERE MOHAN CHAND SHARMA, THE INSPECTOR WHO DIED DUE TO GUNSHOT WOUND HAS ALREADY BEEN PROVEN TO BE PART OF THE TEAM OF ROGUE POLICE
OFFICERS INDULGING IN FAKE ENCOUNTER?

 THERE ARE TOO MANY LOOPHOLES IN THE POLICE'S VERSION. SIMPLY TOO MANY:

Why were the postmortem reports of Inspector Sharma and Atif and Sajid not declared publicly?There is
only one exit and entry point in the house that with a grill door where the poor students were staying,and which was covered by the police ,Then how was it possible, as per claimed by the police, that two alleged
terrorists  escaped the premises during the police operation? *Why was the police firing in the air and why did it indulge in destruction of property around L-18 after the encounter? Why the police were throwing the flower pots from first floor to the ground even after the encounter was finished,  Why did doctors who did the post mortem of Police officer Sharma mentioned that all evidences were removed at the hospital
where he was first taken after injury * HOw many out there know what is the history record of officer Sharma? * The police claimed that the ‘terrorists' were armed with two AK-47s in Batla House. This has not been verified. What types of bullets were fired on Inspector Mohanchand Sharma? What were the arms
that killed  Sajid and Atif?

2009: 'SHOPIAN RAPE AND MURDER OF NILOFAR JAN (22 YRS) AND ASIYA JAN (17); Going by the details of the case, the aftermath, the postmortem reports, the flip-flops of the doctors who conducted it and given the sad and well documented record of human right abuses by the armed forces in Kashmir where 1990-2005:15,000 people were murdered, 5000 people mostly young boys have disappeared and 4000 women have been raped according to 'The Hindu' in 2005; I and many of my countrymen and women would like a transparent enquiry too, so that, if hopefully a free and fair enquiry is indeed conducted, no matter what the outcome, at least we will be able to trust our army that it is no longer short changing the people of strife torn areas and hoodwinking the rest of the country. 











</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6d5ujk</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/h8a5</id></website><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2012/03/2012319195345582204.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-20T19:55:32+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T15:17:58+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi26cg</id><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2012/03/2012319195345582204.html#comment-473664785</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/ewggc</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>