<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpx1in/update/2012-03-21T20:51:55/4f56515425ef578337df53908440da75eea089a594fb12c1aca41ca2c851b550</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I follow you closely daily on the material fact that I am foreign-based working far away from home. Naturally blogging and facebooking are one of the reliable and accurate sources not from the gravevine. 

I must commend on your hardwork to make things happened. Realising the policies for the benefit of the people of Malaysia. Not on the principle of NATO (no action talk only). 

I  a lot more respect on you and love Malaysia more each day when I discovered the fallacy of  "Hujang emas di tempat orang, hujan batu tempat sendiri"  

Malaysians are the  one, demanding everything for the sky expecting the Government to deliver. I think it is time that we should let Malaysians to work hard for their money instead of waiting for the windfall from the Government.

I am talking from my experience where I work now in Canada where the Government would not have any preference for any groups except the poor and the old. 

The government here does not provide any response to complaints but the long queue. Medical facilities here are at worse. If one is illed, he wishes a serious ill in a emergency case than a common Cold with months long wait for medical appointment. Yet they are covered with medical insurance for in case of emergency.

Nobody careless of complaints wether in public or private sectors. Unless you are instituting a legal proceeding. People here are lazy, work to rule and never willing to walk extra mile to help anyone in need. 

I admire the administration of Government of Malaysia looking after the welfare of everyone. Medical and hospital facilities are one of the best in the world. Can not Imagine with RM1 you may get consultation and pharmacy provided.

Any complaints at any moment, there are Government agencies would ever ready to provide assistance to Resolve issues. People are friendly and hardworking to achieve the benefit for the organizations and the Government.

What now are we expecting further from the Government that is responsibile and caring?

Listening to and misleading by the irresponsible people are causing Malaysians to be divided.

YAB Dato' Seri, last but not least, pursue the work objectively and preserance without fears and favours is the event of the day.

Please keep it up. From far at distance but close at heart. 


LIM YH
      </body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dbu6r</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/rjjm</id></website><link>http://1malaysia.com.my/blog/i-have-a-proposal/</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T09:29:06+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T00:51:55+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpx1in</id><link>http://1malaysia.com.my/blog/i-have-a-proposal/#comment-472984076</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>