<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/micyiu/post/2012-03-22T14:04:35</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Often the first argument you hear among low-carb advocates is that “we tried the low fat approach in the 70’s and80’s and it was a bust.” The supposedly logical conclusion you are supposed to draw from this remark is that “if low fat is not then answer, then low carbs must be.” This is of course what we call in science as “tautological thinking.” This is not a logical conclusion. But there is more to it than that. A meta-analysis of eating trends over that period of time showed clearly that people ate substantially more fat per person during these years and not less. (classic example of what we now know as “portion distortion”.) Furthermore, saying if “low fat” doesn’t work, then “low carbs” must work is a reflection of the exact same weakness of thinking and paradigm blindness. The truth is that thinking of any macronutrient as being some “thing” to be fearful of or eliminate is just not a rational means to undertake any diet-strategy given what we know about human evolution. (see my book Beyond Metabolism for more on that)
The truth is “low carbs” is as much a “bust” as low fat ever was. And metabolically-speaking low carbs dieting is far more dangerous for the long-term burnout or damage of metabolism. It’s too bad that all these diet experts are so “short-sited” about Weight-loss in the immediate and so totally blind to long-term implications of a Weight-loss approach and its potential consequences to metabolism. There are far too many wannabe scientists out there spouting low-carbs nonsense without any due consideration to long-term health or metabolic repercussions of such an approach. But when it comes to marketing all you have to do is appeal to “want and desperation” and you can create a quick fan-following.

You see, the obvious thing is that in the very, very short-term - low carbs work. Not that you are burning substantial amounts of fat mind you – but you will lose a combination of mostly a lot of water, lean tissue and fat. And as long as the scale moves most people are happy and do not want to hear anymore beyond that. But “how” the body loses weight is important for understanding long-term rebounds and longer-term weight Gain with higher established set points – and these unwanted consequences are a direct result of ill-advised diets like “low carbs” approaches – regardless of what label you give them. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yxodn</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/1a7c</id></website><link>http://www.kjendis.no/2012/03/22/kjendis/fotballfrue/caroline_berg_eriksen/blogg/kokebok/20799049/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T16:04:10+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T18:04:35+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/micyiu</id><link>http://www.kjendis.no/2012/03/22/kjendis/fotballfrue/caroline_berg_eriksen/blogg/kokebok/20799049/#comment-473804447</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rbd2x</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>