<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpi0s5/post/2012-03-22T03:17:34</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpz12m</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/87r3z</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>Ah but David, my point is that you have pontificating as if Hansen WILL be back as a dominant player. That may, or may not, transpire. From latest recorded form, he IS back at the 60sec flat territory which is probably borderline finals mark. 

However he will be probably be needing to drop at least 0.8 - full second to be contending for the big money and, to my mind, THAT will be a very big ask. Not impossible but not something I'd care to wager ye olde family homestead on. Something in the 59mids .... more realistic.

Please do not get the idea that I disrespect Hansen ... far from it. I also enjoy what you write. I'm just feeling that some of yr recent prognosis are tinged with what you hope to transpire rather than dispassionate analysis. If you want "Cold-blooded", you should read my analysis of AUS prospects whicfh may differ vastly from many !!

BTW, My view on the men's 4/MED is that the US should be prohibitive favourites (barring Acts of self-immolation via breaks/horror legs leading to panic). Similarly, my instinct tells me the US 4X200 should most likely go in favourite. The 4x100 is the one men's relay where I feel they are merely strong contenders rather than favourites.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6dac67</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/yny5</id></website><link>http://www.swimmingworldmagazine.com/lane9/news/World/30046.asp</link><postedTime>2012-03-20T17:23:41+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T07:17:34+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpi0s5</id><link>http://www.swimmingworldmagazine.com/lane9/news/World/30046.asp#comment-473418292</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/dosir</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>