<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi8ho3/post/2012-03-22T13:15:05</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/miasmh</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/jbxp</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I hate the birthing matrix so I'm not defending that at all.

A lot of the "Cold" Krypton also came from the Richard Donner movies.  Yet, I still think they made it clear in those films that Jor-El and Lara loved their child and were good people.

I personally thought Birthright was a beautiful origin story for the same reasons Maya shared above.

I personally prefer a nice mix of the modern Era with a few Silver Age elements thrown in.   So Birthright hit all the right notes for me.  It focused on Clark's humanity while still showing him feeling interest and revernance for his home world and the parents who gave him up.

It's a story of immigration and assimilation in that Superman (like many immigrants) respects and has reverance for his homeland while consider his "new" home the place that he belongs and calls home.  It's why the story means a great deal to a lot of Americans who came here from other countries and why Superman, more than any other, represents our "melting pot" mentality.

I do, however, disagree that the change to the Amazons affects Wonder Woman in the same way.

DC has now created a situation where Wonder Woman literally has to overcome her family heritage going forward as opposed to be inspired by it.  

They've created a situation where Wonder Woman almost owes a debt to the world of man for the sins of her people.  And I really, really hate that.

They've also killed the entire concept that there could be a peaceful society of women that truly THRIVED without the company of men by falling back on ageless sexless stories that painted women as being distrustful.

I find it very upsetting.</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y53yu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/m7rp</id></website><link>http://dcwomenkickingass.tumblr.com/post/19704793909</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T00:06:55+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T17:15:05+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mi8ho3</id><link>http://dcwomenkickingass.tumblr.com/post/19704793909#comment-473762913</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/yf5jz</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>