<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp0tbj/post/2012-03-22T10:36:56</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><inReplyTo><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpyif1</id><author><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/zmz25</id></author><objectType>comment</objectType></inReplyTo><body>I actually liked the post, which is not from your own blog but someone elses?  It reminds me a lot of Buddhist beliefs concerning interdependence, causality and connectedness. There is a belief that that every breath you take, you breathe in the Buddha, and in light of recent studies in physics, that is entirely accurate. You share the same breath and the same atomic universe as every other human being who has ever lived. When at the moment of death people left behind can feel isolated, alone and cast adrift, bringing their attention to the shared experiences of humanity at the most basic level can be a  realisation.  The realisation of mutual interconnectedness is supposed to bring the individual to cultivate universal love for one another in all times and places.  There is nothing Cold or inhumane about that.   Feeling the breath move in and out of my lungs and sharing breath with someone who is no longer breathing?  That is a spiritual connection, unbreakable, we will breathe that same air until our last one leaves us, an earthly, tangible connection.  With every breath, I am reminded of all those who went before me, and also all those yet to be born.  
 I find that there is nothing less mysterious or spiritual about death being an atheist, we are just as ignorant as everyone else about what happens at that moment, so at least by admitting it we Gain a sense of wonder and curiousity and reverence for life.  If this life is all we know and can know and death is indeed an impenetrable barrier, all the more reason to find meaning and value in what people have accomplished and the memories they leave behind for others.   Atheists should regard death as the last great adventure of discovery. </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6mf226</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ant8</id></website><link>http://www.alternet.org/belief/154570/when_it%27s_not_god%27s_plan%3A_8_things_to_say_to_grieving_nonbelievers/comments/</link><postedTime>2012-03-20T08:06:17+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T14:36:56+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mp0tbj</id><link>http://www.alternet.org/belief/154570/when_it%27s_not_god%27s_plan%3A_8_things_to_say_to_grieving_nonbelievers/comments/#comment-473627907</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/rqc1c</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-20</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>