<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9wab1/update/2012-03-18T16:08:21/6973365164d0d437aa7e864acd1cbf316c9411ad06cec3b613c2b3080127fd49</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>I am sure that as you sit in your middle class home, in your all white neighborhood it seems that most of "us" support this legislation.  The law affects almost exclusively the poor and people of color.  The cost of the ID will be about $20.00, not too much for you but for some will amount to an unaffordable poll tax.  Your analogy of the need for the law to the lack of local gambling arrests is short-sighted and naive.  The fact is that over the last 5 years in the entire Commonwealth,(not just Clearfied County), there have been no prosecutions for voter fraud.  Not one.  Zero.  This legislation is an example of a power grab by a bigotted GOP.  The people affected will be overwhelming in their support of the Demovratic party.  It is an attempt to stel more elections.  The only bright Spot to this is that I believe the law will be challenged by the greatest, non-military defender of the Constitution in this country.  No, not the tea oparty but the American Civil Libirties Union, of which i am a proud member.  The real reason conservatives hate the ACLU is because when they take a case, they almost Always win.  If the law is overturned ican can pass along some advise from our despicable governor, "just close your eyes".</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6eemjb</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/mwup</id></website><link>http://www.thecourierexpress.com/tricountysundaytriouropinion/953891-349/new-voter-id-law-supported-by-most.html</link><postedTime>2012-03-18T04:57:38+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-18T20:08:21+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/m9wab1</id><link>http://www.thecourierexpress.com/tricountysundaytriouropinion/953891-349/new-voter-id-law-supported-by-most.html#comment-468521664</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/-1</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-18</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>