<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpwzko/update/2012-03-22T09:33:24/2f387ae4121084cfcb9ab4d69689e3e38b944a8fb8f7521abe971921a3fa88e7</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Overall I thought it was a kind of anemic night, didn't really have the fire I wanted from enough of the people who are capable. 

That being said &lt;strong&gt;Elise&lt;/strong&gt; totally brought it and she was last night's best by a mile. Even though her song was unfamiliar even to me, I feel like this is one of those performances where it won't matter because it had one of the best grooves out of the songs sung last night. I love her phrasing. She did go too hard on some of the notes because she was trying to make an impression but 95% of her interpretation was Spot on, she told the story, she moved well, and she sounded great. That run right before the end WAS crazy difficult and she nailed it. I don't know if it was the best idea to sing those last three notes low - she didn't hit one of them 100% clean and her voice lacked a little clarity down there but overall, absolutely loved this performance. She definitely got overpimped but I'm not even mad. I'm actually happy to see the judges and show Acting like they want her to stay. I think she bought herself another week.
2nd place tonight for me was &lt;strong&gt;Jessica&lt;/strong&gt; - she nailed the song vocally and I do think it was probably the best she could do in the Billy Joel songbook. I actually like about her that she wants this so bad and she's so professional about it. I just didn't really care for the song too much. Not the world's most interesting performance but she did what she does really well, and what she can do she does better than almost everybody else in this year's group.

&lt;strong&gt;Erika&lt;/strong&gt; - I love her voice, I love her vocal style, I keep waiting for her to successfully build an arc within a 90 second performance and for some reason it hasn't happened yet. She did a good job here, it was just somewhat lacking the excitement factor for me. I would listen to her sing just about anything - her tone kills me. As far as the make over, I don't know, I was kind of liking the soft blond hair framing her face. I fear she is in danger this week of being bottom 3. But, she was 3rd best last night in my book.

After another big gap, &lt;strong&gt;P2&lt;/strong&gt; is next as far as having a successful performance I guess. He does the same thing every week. I felt like the whole mentoring session was a set up for him being such a rebel. The thing is that though the suggestions weren't helpful to Philip, the critiques that were at the root of the suggestions were right on. I'm bored and feel he only stands out in contrast to other people on this show. I give his credit for being in tune and it is fun to watch him groove. But, a whole concert of P2 doing this is not my thing.

&lt;strong&gt;Colton's&lt;/strong&gt; performance was wildly overrated IMO. I actually wanted JLo to start talking about nasal singing again because there were long portions of that song where he was totally singing through his nose. He sounded pinched, unlike Skylar who even at her most nasal has a beautiful, more open sound. It's good Colton was able to inject his own phrasing somewhat into the song. But, it just didn't do it for me. It was competent but not great or that believable. 

&lt;strong&gt;Deandre&lt;/strong&gt; also did a competent job but the difference between his confidence level on Master Blaster and Only The Good Die Young is all too obvious. He actually sang very well on this but I agree with Brian Mansfield's comment that a more modern pop arrangement would've helped Deandre. I hate how cowed Deandre is by this show right now and I don't feel like the mentoring is getting through to him. He's in danger of being bottom 3 unfortunately.

Staying with the competence theme, &lt;strong&gt;Joshua&lt;/strong&gt; was like Deandre in that this was a performance that felt like a pale version of his highlight performance of the season. In Joshua's case, we saw him tear it up with When A Man Loves A Woman, and this felt hollow emotionally in comparison. He sang well but he didn't seem committed. I actually think he too could be in danger this week except hopefully last week's excellence helped him.

After another gap, &lt;strong&gt;Hollie&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Skylar&lt;/strong&gt; both disappointed. Hollie did sound a little shrieky at times. She did fill the stage better this week and I do still love her voice. I just need to get more storytelling out of her. Skylar took on a song too big for her and though she attacked it, it didn't work this week. I still love her voice and her phrasing but she struggled with the low parts of the song and oversang the chorus. She just couldn't work this one out. 

And then there's &lt;strong&gt;Heejun&lt;/strong&gt;. I was torn between laughter and frustration. It's a little disappointing to see him go full Sanjaya. I can still hear the raw potential in his voice, even in that performance. But, here's another situation where the coaching and mentoring isn't working so I guess he sort of checked out of the whole thing now that he's made tour. 

Predicted bottom 3: Erika, Heejun, Deandre
Leaving: Deandre :(</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y5q50</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/q17i</id></website><link>http://www.mjsbigblog.com/american-idol-11-top-10-recap-videos-and-photos.htm</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T23:41:21+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T13:33:24+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpwzko</id><link>http://www.mjsbigblog.com/american-idol-11-top-10-recap-videos-and-photos.htm#comment-473577688</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6idlm</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>