<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpkvz9/post/2012-03-22T04:33:49</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>hefact is that this man, (Zimmerman) is a Cold-blooded murderer!
I cannot call for the police chief to be Ousted, becasue I am not aware of his being intentionally disrespectful to the law in this case, even though I think he has botched it to a degree.
Mr. martin is not responsible to answer for his presence anywhere where he is not posing a direct threat.
Mr. beck, if someone were to view you as a threat to them, either real or imagined, I should think that you would hope that your life would not be taken as a result of their misundertandings.
Mr. marti was murdered, much like a fool with a sub-machine gun, who hunts for quail, murders not protects himself form his "dangerous" quarry!
This was a case of Zimmerman going out on a "hunt". He found his prey, adn decided to over his tracks with a phone call to the police, a call that I might add, is reasonalbe enough eveidence to any reasonably thinking person to suggest, that his was far from a case of self-defense!
I am devaastated to see that Mr. Beck could actually co-sign a post of this sort, if he in fact is aware of those that are going out over his site before they are so broadcast. 
In any case, he is the fidurehead, and just as he blames Obama for the situations that were produced by earlier presidents, he as well, can have this storm placed upon his brow!
Peae to the family of young Mr. martin, and hopefully, justivce will find a place in all of this so unnecessary situation!
This is not specifically about color, as much as it is about the price of the life of any human being, who may be seen as a threat in the eyes of an obviously "compromised" person such as Zimmerman. He sees himself as a heroic figure, when in fact, he is a predator who scored a kill that leads to nothing more than bragging rights for himself!
Our nation needs to see this a a wake-up-call, to weed out this sort of injustice. Just rememebr that this could be anyone's child, even yours Mr. Beck, should some idiot decide that a bag of candy and a soft drink are weapons of an imediate danger!</body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6yyhdu</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ewhe</id></website><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/trayvon-martin/glenn-beck-site-the-blaze-suggests-trayvon-martin-was-a-dangerous-threat.php</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T04:23:14+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T08:33:49+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mpkvz9</id><link>http://www.thegrio.com/specials/trayvon-martin/glenn-beck-site-the-blaze-suggests-trayvon-martin-was-a-dangerous-threat.php#comment-473439698</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/8rqps</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>