<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mickj1/update/2012-03-22T14:40:34/b6a098a37979be0e0e63deaf1d78575819ae92c5381f364e8a4858566799d465</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>Mr. Tyrell was correct in stating that the financial crisis of the United States was designed by a previous mindset.  But he identified the wrong  outmoded, expensive,a nd disastrous policies.  Social Security and Medicare did not create this disaster.

The sixty plus years old Cold War created most of the expense, debt, and threats to our society which now exist, from the policy of sending our jobs and industries out of the United States  to third world countries to "promote capitalism and free enterprise" in a  "long twilignt struggle" to contain communism to our self appoined role as "policeman of the planet", to the huge federal government we have screated  to administer these  grandoise plans to sweep the planet's beaches free of sand,  We have broke ourselves and almost destroyed the Country and Constitution.

Begin by dismantling every institution of the Cold War.  Start by ending every program of support fo sending american businesses and jobs to other countries and assisting them economically.  That will save the trreasury and taxpayers a lot of  money and bring millions of jobs back home to the US.  If it creates economic woes for  Chinase, that's wonderful.  

End the multidude of funding schemes whereby upwards of a trillion dollars are annually sent from Washington to Local and State Governments for programs which exist only because the feds fund them.  Left to themselves, the states and local governments would not spend a penny of local taxpayer funds on any number of programs the feds fund locally.

Then take  to Cold War Government agencies like the US Department of Education, which was created as the "Office Of Education" in 1957 because the Russians got to space first and we could let them get ahead of us in Science and Math. And that's just the beginning of what should be done.  Instead, Paul Ryan wants to cut social security and medicare--and insure the re-election of our first Marxist President and a bigger Government with bigger debt.  Ron Paul's criticism of Ryan's Plan was right on target.  In many ways, it's Washington as Usual.

Why anyone would Cheer Ryan except Democrats, I do not know..</body><verb>update</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6y5hz5</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/zmzu</id></website><link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2012/mar/21/overextended-america/</link><postedTime>2012-03-21T23:31:12+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T18:40:34+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/mickj1</id><link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2012/mar/21/overextended-america/#comment-473832852</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/6xbfj</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev>approved</disqusTypePrev><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-21</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>