<marklogic><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/micrio/post/2012-03-22T14:07:17</id><type>P</type><type>P</type><body>


 JAMES
BAMFORD: “ . . .They missed the first World Trade Center bombing. They missed the attack on
the USS Cole. They missed the attack on the U.S. embassies in East Africa. And finally, they missed the 9/11
attacks. . .”


 


Stopped
reading at this point. Statements like this is how you determine whether or not
you’re reading a piece of propaganda to justify an Orwellian center to spy on
humanity to ultimately fit them into slots, or send them to the Halliburton
pens. 


 


NSA didn’t
miss anything. And everything that has been fed/is being fed the public since
9/11, including the explanation of who/why 9/11 happened, has been a lie.
(Google David Ray Griffin) The first World Trade Center bombing?  The spooks had a mole inside the blind Mullah’s
group.  And Google questions about the Murrah Building bombing in Oklahoma City while you’re at it.    If you’re still interested and not ill, background
search the so-called “terrorist attacks” on America or American facilities and
you’ll find BAMFORD-type information inclusive in The Big Lie brought to you by
those wonderful folk behind the curtain what tried to bring the world a swine
Flu pandemic that wasn’t, “mandatory” vaccines,  the demonization of Dr. Andrew Wakefield and
his research partner  whose findings
suggested links between childhood vaccinations, the gut, and autism (Wakefield’s
assistant has since been exonerated and Wakefield has filed a lawsuit against
his accusers), a worldwide recession-about-to-be-depression,  global warming, genetically modified food
that sterilizes and harms organs in lab animals tested (it has been fed the American
public and the world since, oh, about the mid-1990’s; now Banned in Europe), peak
oil.  The list grows.


 


Have a nice
day.


 


                                                                                                                                                                  


                                                                                                                                                                  </body><verb>post</verb><target><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:thread/6ylck3</id><website><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:forum/ant8</id></website><link>http://www.alternet.org/story/154641/exposed%3A_massive_new_spy_center_built_to_track_your_emails_and_phone_calls/comments/</link><postedTime>2012-03-22T07:07:28+00:00</postedTime><objectType>article</objectType></target><postedTime>2012-03-22T18:07:17+00:00</postedTime><object><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:comment/micrio</id><link>http://www.alternet.org/story/154641/exposed%3A_massive_new_spy_center_built_to_track_your_emails_and_phone_calls/comments/#comment-473807044</link><objectType>comment</objectType></object><actor><id>tag:gnip.disqus.com:2012:account/xzrq</id><objectType>person</objectType></actor><disqusTypePrev/><disqusType>approved</disqusType><platform>disqus</platform><posted_date>2012-03-22</posted_date><followers>0</followers><statuses>0</statuses><region>N.A.</region></marklogic>